Oh.
There it is.
Yes.
Welcome back, Master!
Hello, hello, hello!
One second.
One second, I forgot.
I forgot to...
One second.
Thank you for the 10 gifted!
Welcome back.
Me?
Where did I go?
Help you a lot soon?
Thank you!
I think I'm like... I think I sound so much better.
Right?
I still just have...
Little cough.
Lapu!
Thanks for the gifted!
Happy Membu baby.
Ducky, thanks for the 5 gifted!
I hope your voice is feeling better.
I think so.
No, I'm not gonna say...
I'm not gonna say...
Jaguar.
Ducky, thanks for the 5...
There we go.
I forgot to put it on repeat.
I forgot to download all my... I'm on my new computer, right?
I forgot to download all my programs.
I don't have the VLC.
I don't have Fubar.
I feel so...
I feel so naked.
I'm using all the Windows thingies.
Abichongus, welcome to Membu ship!
Thank you for the 20 gifted!
Thank you so much!
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
Teacup and NyanNyan, thanks for the 5 gifted!
Shady, welcome to Membu ship.
Thank you so much for the 5 gifted.
Thanks for the super chat.
TikTok was gone and it came back.
Seiya and Rio, Playable and VA.
What a crazy 24 hours.
I know!
I was in mid-saving my TikToks...
That I wanted to save for today's stream.
Because I have maybe like 2000 favorites.
And it's like a mix.
It's not like I could just download all of them and be like...
Okay guys, we're just gonna watch everything.
No, it's like...
I say 2000, I honestly don't know how much it is at all.
How many there are.
But it's like a mix, so it'll be like...
Some are recipes, some are travel things.
Some are funny videos.
So I can't just be like...
I couldn't just be like, okay, I'm gonna download all of them.
And then we just watch them all.
No, I wanted to download the funnies.
I wanted to download the funnies.
So I downloaded...
There's a few that are like...
That are like...
I thought they were interesting.
So I wanted to share them.
Hope you're feeling better.
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you.
April Roman, thanks for the 10 gifted!
Best foodbar user.
Hi Mint, hope you're doing better.
It was my birthday yesterday!
Shia, happy birthday!
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday dear Shia.
Nicholas, thanks for the super chat.
I hope you feel better.
About the influenza.
Sometimes I get the influenza.
It's not great.
Um...
It's my birthday!
Churro, happy birthday!
I think TikTok is back though, is it not?
I just... I didn't download anything else.
I just saved what I have.
And I was like, you know what?
Today...
It's enough, I think.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday dear Churro.
Happy birthday to...
Who are you?
I went to the zoo yesterday, but no jaguars.
Jaguar.
What's weird about the way I say that?
I swear.
You guys are going to be my...
Well, I was going to say my 13th reason, but...
I'm already dead!
13th reason to...
What would a ghost do?
Extradead.
Yeah, X, ascend.
I don't know, go into the light.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Smashboo, thanks for the 5 gifted.
Oh my gosh, your profile picture is so cute.
Pedro, welcome back.
It's been a month since you yelled at me to quit smoking, and I haven't touched a cigarette since.
Thank you for the inspiration, keep being great.
Oh my gosh, maple flower.
Am I an influencer?
Am I like...
Am I like an influencer?
Wake up, vlog.
Thank you so much for the 10 gifted!
Because I am still like...
Wanting my voice to get a bit better.
I was like, well, I still want to do karaoke today, but...
I also really wanted to watch my videos.
I don't plan on becoming a react channel, but...
Sometimes it is just fun to show off videos that you like, you know?
I could...
It's not the same as like posting a thread on Twitter or anything, you know?
A thread of all of them.
Sometimes I just want to...
Be like, guys, look at this funny video.
And we do watch them sometimes on the stream.
Thank you so much for the gifted.
Yeah, we can react on the occasion.
Sorry for...
What is a react Andy?
No, I'm Mint.
What is react Andy?
Wait, that's not my name.
React Minty.
That's better.
It's a funny way to say streamer who reacts a lot.
Don't we?
Aren't we all reacting?
It's a Jerma joke.
His name is Andy.
I thought I was Jerma.
Aren't we all just reacting though?
When I play a game, am I not reacting?
Am I not reacting to everything that happens in the afterlife?
Isn't just life and afterlife just reacting to the things that happen around us?
Perhaps we are all react Andys and we just are not fully aware...
Of our status.
At our core, we are all Andys.
Darkwraith, welcome to the membership.
Hello Mint, Mintominky.
First off, I hope you feel better.
Although it is already over halfway through January, I was hoping to get some words of encouragement for 2025.
Something to help me and others lock in this year.
I wish I could get those too.
I feel like I need to lock in more.
You know...
Hmm...
I feel that...
I feel that sometimes maybe words of encouragement can maybe put a pressure on.
So I would say that, you know...
If you are able to go forward a little bit and do things a little bit...
Even at your own pace, that is...
You know?
That is all that you need to do.
So...
I think you can...
Not have...
So much...
Fret.
And...
You got this!
Why?
Don't worry about it.
I'm not good at...
I'm not good at the motivationals, okay?
Encouragement, we all need it.
My favorite elf died on my birthday week last year, so...
Could I maybe get a mature minto happy birthday?
With extra helping of parasocial Delulu, please.
I'm sorry for your...
For your dead elf.
Elf on the shelf?
What did you touch the elf on the shelf?
And then you...
Don't have it anymore?
Something like that.
Darkray, thanks for the 5 gifted!
Appreciate the words of wisdom.
Welcome to membership.
I suppose I can try...
Mature minto happy birthday.
I suppose.
I need to drink water.
My voice just got done from being so...
My voice just got done with being so...
So...
You know?
Let the gremlin out.
My voice was already... It was so...
Gross.
Wait a second!
Try?
Were you not the one that I told you to delete that photo and then you didn't?
And you want a special happy birthday when I told you to delete that photo?
That I deleted and then you didn't delete it?
And I said delete it and then you did it?
And then you pinned it to your profile picture.
You pinned it to your profile.
But you want an extra special happy birthday?
I see.
Caught in 4K.
Sometimes I don't think that Minto sees, but I see.
My eyes are big enough.
No comment.
BRB gotta delete something unrelated.
Kanen!
Welcome to membership.
Thank you!
Sing for me, Minto?
Oh my gosh.
Okay.
We do need to sing though.
We have videos and we have karaoke.
I will sing you a happy birthday.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday dear Choi.
Happy birthday!
Nerdy Laundry, thank you for the 5 gifted!
I'm not sick enough.
I'm not cruel enough to deprive someone of their birthday song.
No matter how burned I feel.
Can we get chocolate rain in the karaoke?
You know what I discovered with Kerafun?
I discovered this.
I think on my old computer, Kerafun was not updated.
And I redownloaded it on this computer.
And it has a QR code.
It has a QR code that if you guys were to scan it, you could add things to my queue.
So I think not today.
Not today obviously because it's not going to be a full karaoke.
But maybe sometime in the future.
It could be fun.
And then maybe I will get songs that I don't usually get.
Do you trust us like that?
No.
But if I don't know a song, I can always skip it.
Remix!
Welcome to membership.
Thank you.
Maybe do like a...
What's the word?
Other members or something.
4000 snake eaters.
Is there a snake eater around here?
Snake eater.
No way!
I'm not used to the new Kerafun layout.
It all is different to me.
Is this real?
Karaoke night with Minky.
Oh no, but that will be so much fun.
Let me see.
Hold on, I'm going to test it.
What's this one?
Oh my god!
It's a real Kerafun version!
And I'm melting to you What a fear in my heart But you're so supreme I give my life for you And my time There'll be no one else Crime is the way I fly to you I'm still in a dream, snake in a hand Someday you'll go through the rain Someday you'll feed on a tree frog This ordeal,
the trial to survive On a day we see new life I give my life Not for honor, but for you
My time, there'll be no one else Crime is the way I fly to you I'm still in a dream, snake in a...
I'm still in a dream, snake in a...
What?
They didn't put the ending snake either.
They didn't put the ending sneater No!
Wow!
I'm so impressed Kerafine.
I'm so impressed!
Wait, if I put in Metal Gear... Metal Gear... What else comes up?
Metal... Metal... I don't know what the hell that is
There's more No way!
I can't tell if these are... These look like...
Hold on.
I'm not going to sing this But I kind of want to hear what it sounds like.
Oh wait!
Vote for Rules of Nature and we'll notify you if we add it to the catalog Everybody!
Get... Everybody!
Get Kerafine right now!
And vote for Rules of Nature Oh my god!
You have to vote for it!
Niels, thank you for the very big akatsupa Dearest Minfantome, would you make me the happiest wisp and be the one and only ghost to haunt me for the rest of my life and afterlife?
I have to take off my eye patch for that I... I mean... I would love to be the only one that haunts you Because, you know, ghosts are quite territorial actually I don't want to be sharing with another ghost So, I mean, like, if I can absorb life force while you're alive and,
like, you provide sufficient... not sacrifice, sorry Offerings, like, you know, I don't get it, I mean...
Snake Eater by Minta was a perfect start to today's gym session!
Thank you for being with me on Spooky Spotify Well, I was just about to show a video, though, I hope that's okay What a brave guy Why are you guys 07?
Why?
This is... It's like a... Well, not parasocial relationship Parasitic?
It's a bit of a parasite relationship Probably Paranormal?
No, not paranormal There's nothing normal about this No, no symbiotic, no Only parasitic, paranormal, parasocial
Paramedic?
Nah Para para We need some Eurobeat Is it okay if I show you guys some videos?
I actually... Actually, no, before that, I do have another song I wanna sing And let me... This is a song I learned from TikTok So everybody who's just like, nothing good comes from TikTok, you're wrong Kind of, kind of wrong Wait a second, let me... Oh,
my thing is all messed up
Wait, where's my font?
I downloaded it Okay, I'm just gonna have to switch to a different font Okay
Not a karaoke... It is a karaoke stream!
What are you talking about?
It says karaoke and funny videos Okay, this song, I don't know it super duper well So if I mess up, I'll sing it again another stream Let me test the volume
Ah, I can't stop the loneliness.
Why can't I stop this sadness?
I can't stop the loneliness.
But the kiss smells like a lie.
I realized it when you hugged me.
It's not enough.
Like a storm.
Friends and lovers.
I can't stop the loneliness.
I can't stop this sadness.
Sorry,
the video is kind of funny.
I can't stop.
I can't stop
this sadness.
I can't stop the loneliness.
Why can't I stop this sadness?
I can't stop this sadness.
Oh, not 23.
Gosh, Murphy, why did you have to send such a big don't know mid-song?
Thank you!
What is Pedro?
Pedro?
Who is Pedro?
AI summary before the song.
Viewers are excited about the upcoming karaoke stream.
The streamer Pedro is known for their singing ability and viewers are expressing their appreciation for Pedro's talent.
I'm now Pedro.
Pedro.
What's up, Pedro?
Pedro!
Hold on.
Pedro.
Wait.
I kind of did it.
Kind of.
And thank you for three months!
I don't actually know how this song goes.
You guys want to watch some funny videos?
Okay, hold on.
Let me pull it up.
Let me... hold on.
We're gonna... we're gonna...
Oh no, that's so loud.
Hold on for me.
Oh no.
Wait, where are all the videos at?
Oh, here we go.
This is the first one.
When I wanted to show.
We're just gonna warm up a little bit.
Okay, so...
Oh my gosh, what sucks is that my For You page, even though TikTok is back, is completely ruined.
I have to, like, read... find... which takes forever.
It takes forever to, like, reset your For You page, so...
Oh gosh, I have to, like, probably take a day to just do it.
But I don't feel like it, so I haven't touched TikTok since...
But that's okay.
I have all my funny videos right here.
Let me get rid of the set list, because it's like...
Hold on, I'm gonna move over.
Let's move over.
And...
My Oshie Pedro.
Pedro, Pedro, Pedro.
If you watch your favorites, it will fix it.
Really?
Actually?
Okay, this one is a very simple video.
Okay, guys, this one...
Actually, I don't even think we need sound, but...
Hold on, let me make sure the window capture is the correct thing.
I can't tell.
Maybe.
Hold on.
I'm scared.
It doesn't even show up.
No!
Why isn't it showing up?
One second.
Why won't it show up?
Hold on.
What the heck is wrong with the OBS?
Oh, I think it does that on purpose?
Wait, I don't know.
Everything is weird.
My whole computer is weird.
Why are the videos not showing up now?
What's going on?
What's happening?
Why?
Maybe if I game capture?
I don't know.
Media player.
Does that work?
No, it's not showing up.
Guys, hold on.
I'm sorry.
I set this all up pre-stream and now it's not showing up.
Because it hates me.
Why?
Oh, I know why.
I had to open it in the... what's it called?
Media player instead.
Not...
I remember.
I got it to work.
It hates her.
It does.
It does hate me.
Okay.
Alright.
Wondering Taco, thank you for the 20 gifted!
And I think I saw people saying happy birthday.
MoriPlays, happy birthday!
Thanks so much for all the big energy you put into your streams.
You inspired me to reach all my goals.
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday dear MoriPlays.
Happy birthday!
Alright guys, you're gonna know immediately why...
Why I have chosen this video.
Do you see him?
Okay, hold on.
I don't think we need the sound.
It's just a lady talking.
But look at that little guy.
Oh my god!
He's so cute!
Lunch and a... Oh hold on.
Actually, I kind of like the lady's commentary.
He's so cute!
Oh my gosh!
He's like, I hit the jackpot baby!
Lunch and a show.
I feel like that's gonna hurt him.
No?
The pineapple?
The pineapple is gonna eat his brain.
You know how it eats your... Supposedly has like the things that eat your tongue or whatever?
I feel like he's gonna have...
I feel like it's... He's so small, it's all gonna eat his brain.
It's cooked so it's not as bad.
I love cooked pineapple.
Oh my gosh!
I don't... I've only been to a...
What's it called?
Like the Brazilian steakhouse?
I've only been one time.
I didn't pay for it because it was like a business thing.
But good golly!
When they bring out that pineapple, I'm like...
Well, it only happened once.
You know what I mean?
I'm just like...
So good!
Bring me the cooked pineapple.
I wanna go back.
What's a good... Is there like a good Brazilian steakhouse franchise?
Maybe one that like everybody knows...
So that I can also try maybe and go...
Sometime.
Today is my brother's birthday.
Can you sing a happy birthday to him?
Not sure what to gift him.
Does he even... Does he even like me?
The Fogo de Ch達o!
Yes, I've heard of that one.
Fogo de Ch達o.
Ch達o!
Fogo de... Is it actually good?
Fogo de Ch達o.
Come to Brazil.
Well, speaking of a brother...
Hold on.
Hold on, you guys.
This is... This is not the first time I saw the brother.
But I saw it... I first saw clips of it on TikTok.
So, I learned... I started getting obsessed with it because of TikTok.
Hold on.
I have to like go through my videos.
I have to find it.
I can't stop...
Brazil...
Everything is so small in this folder.
Everything is so small.
Is this it?
No, this is the baby elephant.
This baby elephant went viral on TikTok because...
You just have to look at it and you'll know why.
And a baby elephant is spreading holiday cheer at the Houston Zoo.
Oh, Kirby!
Like, apparently this is how just elephants look when they're born.
But Kirby has seen the other side.
Like, my God.
Kirby does not look okay.
It's so...
He's truly just like, I was not... I did not choose to be born into this world.
Yeah, he remembers everything on the inside.
It's like elephants, right?
They remember.
And he's just like, I know.
I've witnessed.
I have witnessed.
Yes.
Okay, whenever I show you, I'm going to delete so that I don't repeat things, you know?
Especially now that I have access, reaccess to my favorites.
And I also requested my favorite, like my data and everything so that I can just have it all downloaded.
Downloaded, yeah.
I love this.
People were like, people were like making videos.
Like, there was a filter I guess you could put on your face that made your eyes like all messed up and watery and gross.
Put me back, I'm not done.
And they would like, they would be like that one elephant at the zoo.
I can't find, oh my gosh, I don't, I'm trying to see.
I'm like looking at tiny little, what's it called?
Let me make the icons extra big.
I love, I love TikToks about pets.
You know, that's just everybody, right?
But I also have some other just kind of, I don't know.
So at one point, hold on, I think this one might be loud.
At one point, I liked a couple bird videos and I would just start getting videos like this.
I'm not quite sure why.
I don't know why, but I'm just like, look at them go.
Yeah, they're kind of, kind of awesome though.
It's like such a...
That guy, he has free will.
He doesn't follow the rest.
How can I get this to happen to me?
How can I get a bunch of birds to follow me like this?
But look at their legs, they're crazy.
Volunteer, what's volunteer?
I heard sacrifice earlier.
Calima, Calima.
Food, true.
Do we need a wisp sacrifice for Mint's voice?
No, scary looking dinosaurs.
Oh my gosh, I didn't save one.
But it was truly like a dinosaur.
There's this bird though.
Which everybody knows that I love this bird.
Shoeboos!
Look!
So cute, he's happy.
Look at them.
They're so beautiful.
I think Futaba is the one that does the bow though.
I don't know which one, which Shoebill this is.
Yeah, Shoebills are like my favorite bird too probably.
They're so...
Oh, it doesn't show what the account was, that's weird.
This is a Shoebill Stork...
28 maybe?
Is that the A10 Warthog noise?
Maybe that's why I love the A10.
It's just like a Shoebill.
I wish when I went and saw the Shoebill at the zoo, that it did this too.
But they were just very...
I wish also...
Look at that!
Oh my gosh!
What a face.
So beautiful.
So Minto likes her bills really big.
Locked in.
I know.
They really do, they just lock in.
Okay, hold on, I have to delete some of these videos.
What did I show?
Can't remember.
Okay, let's do some karaoke!
What should I sing next?
Basically I'm gonna do...
Karaoke, show a couple videos.
Espresso.
Okay, actually I can do that one because I have a...
I have... Okay, you know what?
That's perfect.
Because I have two TikToks that goes with that.
I think I remember how this song goes.
I'm pretty sure.
Now here's...
Think about me every night, oh That's sweet, I guess, oh Sure you can't sleep, baby, I know That's not me, espresso Move it up, down, left, right, oh Switch it up like Nintendo Sure you can't sleep, baby, I know That's not me, espresso I can't relate To desperation My give up bugs Are on vacation And I got this one boy And he won't stop calling When they act this way I know I got him Too bad your ex don't do it for you Walked in a dream,
came through it for you Soft skin and I perfumed it for you I know I mountain dew it for you That morning coffee brewed it for you One touch and I brand new it for you Now here's...
Think about me every night, oh That's sweet, I guess, oh Sure you can't sleep, baby, I know That's not me, espresso Move it up, down, left, right, oh Switch it up like Nintendo Sure you can't sleep, baby, I know That's not me, espresso That's not sweet,
I guess, oh I'm working late Cause I'm a streamer Oh, you look so cute Wrapped around my finger My twisted humor Make him laugh so often My honeybee Come and get this fallen Too bad your ex don't do it for you Walked in a dream, came through it for you Soft skin and I perfumed it for you I know I mountain dew it for you That morning coffee brewed it for you One touch and I brand new it for you Now here's...
Think about me every night, oh That's sweet, I guess, oh Sure you can't sleep, baby, I know That's not me, espresso Move it up, down, left, right, oh Switch it up like Nintendo Sure you can't sleep, baby, I know That's not me, espresso Think about me every night,
oh That's sweet, I guess, oh Sure you can't sleep, baby, I know That's not me, espresso Move it up, down, left, right, oh Switch it up like Nintendo Sure you can't sleep, baby, I know That's not me, espresso That's not sweet, I guess, oh That's not me,
espresso
Sorry, my voice was starting to like give out from being so low
But actually, that's also not even the song that I was thinking of Oops Okay, I don't actually know how this next song goes It's also Sabrina Carpenter I promise, I have to...
It's because they're related, I promise Also, hot dog Since you're crazy enough to do karaoke, would you be crazy enough to sing Miku?
All I know is the...
That's all I know, though Any word about when the selected concert songs might go up?
I... I... I don't have... I'm sorry, I have no idea I think we're waiting on... I think they're doing some extra editing to it So, it might be a little bit longer Also, do you have any merch available?
I do!
There's a link in the description of the stream!
Thank you, thank you I'm thinking Miku, Miku, ui u I'm thinking Miku, Miku, ui u Okay, next song, hold on Sorry, again, it's Sabrina Carpenter But this is because I was thinking of this song and not Espresso But it's still okay It's still okay I'm gonna try... I don't think I really know this song very well,
but...
I don't know if I've ever sung this one before, actually Now that I think about it Have I?
I don't know I guess we'll see Hahaha
Don't Hahaha
Whatever devil's inside you, don't let him out tonight.
I tell them it's just your culture, and everyone rolls their eyes.
Yeah, I know...
All I'm asking, baby...
Please, please, please, don't prove I'm right.
And please, please, please, don't bring me to tears when I just did my makeup so nice.
Heartbreak is one thing, my ego's another.
I beg you, don't embarrass me, motherfucker.
Please, please, please...
Well, I have a fun idea, baby.
Maybe just stay inside.
I know you're craving some fresh air, but the ceiling fan is so nice.
We could probably move happily if no one knows that you're with me.
I'm just kidding, but really, really, really...
Please, please, please, don't prove I'm right.
And please, please, please, don't bring me to tears when I just did my makeup so nice.
Heartbreak is one thing, my ego's another.
I beg you, don't embarrass me, motherfucker.
Please, please, please...
What's this stupid tool doing in front of me?
I don't know this part at all.
If you don't wanna cry to my music, don't make me hate you prolifically.
Please, please, please...
Please...
It's just straight up desperate.
I thought in the last song she was like, I don't relate to desperation.
But this song comes off the entirely opposite way.
She's literally begging.
Come on, which is it, Sabrina Carpenter?
The begging Riz.
Please, please, please...
Act normal today.
And please, please, please...
Don't say anything about my armpits.
What's normal?
I don't know.
You screaming please like that reminded me of Orca.
What do I not know about your relationship?
Shattered Remnants, welcome to membership.
Thank you!
Minto karaoke is my espresso.
Thanks, Akira!
Please, Minto, my Miku fever is boiling.
What do I sing, Miku?
What do I, what do Miku?
Anything?
The world is mine.
I don't think I could.
Sorry.
Brain rot?
I'm still standing.
I tried saying that before, not so long ago.
Wait, hold on.
What's my songs to learn?
What was the song?
Burning Desire?
Okay,
I have some videos though.
Hold on, before we get into Miku, Miku, thinking Miku, Miku...
Hold on, I have some more TikTok.
Okay, so these are two Sabrina Carpenter.
I'm not even that big of a Sabrina Carpenter fan.
I do like her music, but...
These are related to Sabrina Carpenter.
This is how I learned the song, I think.
Whenever I listen to this I feel like I'm about to...
I feel like I'm about to start raising from the floor.
I would love
to hear you sing Magical Cure Love Shot one day.
Especially with all the calls in the background.
Does the composer release a version of the song with including the calls?
I wonder.
Okay, so that's one Sabrina Carpenter song or TikTok that I have saved.
But also this one.
This girl's puns are like off the charts.
It's me, Sabrina Carpentermite, telling you to please, please, please call Linda Johnson Extermination for all of your pest control needs.
Do you have a termite infestation or other bug infestation at your house?
Sabrina Carpentermite.
Well, Linda Johnson's working late so the bugs don't linger.
Please, please and other bugs.
Please, please, please to get rid of bugs just take your phone and call up Linda.
Linda Johnson Extermination.
She'll help you take care of your bug infestation.
Please, please, please.
It's the constant looking to the side of the...
I feel like it should have ended there.
Everybody call up Linda Johnson so she doesn't have to work at Pizza Hut anymore.
This is a Carly Leopard.
I don't know why it's not...
Sometimes when you download a TikTok it shows the credits at the end and it's not showing the...
Hold on, let me shrink the video just a little bit.
Oh no, you guys are still in the way.
Okay, hold on.
You guys need to move down a little bit.
Move down.
Big head over here on the left.
You have too big of a head.
Shrink, shrink, shrink.
There we go.
Sorry.
You can see the TikTok handle.
I don't want to not credit people if I'm showing things.
Especially if TikTok is back now.
So, please.
She does other ones too.
They're so funny.
Because the puns are just too...
The puns are too on point.
That's me.
Sabrina Carpentermite is too good.
I love that.
I think I've seen a Chaperone one before too.
Hold on, let me delete the videos that I've been showing.
I can get rid of Shubill.
Goodbye Shubill.
I have to show you guys this one too.
This one just...
So this one...
Okay, so...
It's one of those random lockers where you like...
It has a prize in it, but she gets the one...
It says on it, Heaven or Hell.
So it's like a mystery.
She gets the mystery one and it says Heaven or Hell.
So, what do you think is going to be in it?
Do you think it's going to be Heavenly?
Or Hellish?
Mimi, welcome to membership!
Okay, I'll start from the beginning so you can...
7!
Her nails are so cute.
It's one of my favorite videos ever.
I can't get over it.
Look
at the quagsire.
He's so cute.
It's such a good video.
Heaven, Heaven, Heaven.
Okay, I have to show this one too.
Wait, I posted this one on Twitter.
You guys, this video literally brings me to tears.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I'm going to sound like an actual crazy person to this video.
I know it's...
What?
I need to watch it again.
I think I've watched this like 50 times.
I really love when ornaments just start dying, you know?
And they start sounding terrible.
Like the Elsas from 10 years ago.
They were like, let it go, let it go.
It sounds so...it's literally...
Sorry, I had to stand up.
Liz, hi!
Hi chat, Qtees, hope you're all doing well.
Liz, I'm showing a video of some TikToks that I like.
This one.
You
can't even see the Mickey on it.
All that effort for nothing.
All that torture for nothing.
You don't even see Mickey's face.
So cursed.
It's so cursed.
Okay, back to singing.
Back to singing, back to singing.
I'm normal, I'm normal, I'm normal.
Austin, welcome to membership.
Thank you!
Okay, what should I sing?
Oh jeez.
What should I sing?
Let me bring you guys back too.
Except I don't know that song.
I'm sorry.
Okay, that's the only part I know.
I can't only just sing that part.
My ghost mitt is broken.
I'm sorry.
Let me just search Vocaloid karaoke.
I wonder what we'll get.
Actually, I wonder if like I...
In Kara-Fun if there's anything.
Oh they actually have World is Mine.
You know what?
Fine, I'll try it.
I'll try it.
Hold on.
My voice is all messed up.
After this I'll take a cough drop.
Okay.
Was the sound okay?
I'm the number one princess in the world.
That's how you treat me.
Right?
I'm
sorry.
I'm sorry.
I don't have my right hand down.
I'm not saying I'm selfish.
I just want you to think of me from the bottom of your heart.
Kamaite sekai de ichiban no hime-sama Kizazuite ne ne
na shiyou Dare da to
hometai Ima sugu ni yo!
Check 1, 2
No hanashi chanto kikiteru Chotto wa Sore to ne Sorry, it's been a long time since I've heard this song.
Ukaemi kite Wakattara Shizuite Otote Oh, hime-sama ke Betsu ni Wagamama nante Ikitenain dakara Demo ne Sukoshi kurai Shikatte Kuretatte Ii no yo Sekai de Watashi dake no Ojiisama Shizuite Hora Hora
Otezakashite Mirai
nakamashimasu Wagamama na koto da to omowanai de Watashi ni datte yareba dekiru no Ato de Koukai suru wa yo Tozen desu Datte Watashi wa Sekai de
It's been like 10 years since I've listened to the full version of that song.
Oopsie.
The world is mine.
I remember my favorite part being the...
I don't think I should have sang that at all.
Kind of killed my voice.
I'm not the Ohime-sama.
I'm the maid.
Please don't spam song requests.
Thank you.
I'm getting a cough drop now.
Do I have a...
Hold on.
I'm going through the karaoke classics part of...
Of...
You know.
Kara-fun.
Let's see.
I should have really just came up with a...
I had like a couple songs in my head that I was like, I want to sing these.
But then I was like, I should have come up with a full set list so I don't...
So I like know what songs I'm singing.
So I know what songs I can sing and not to not strain my voice too much.
Abba song.
Oh my gosh.
Speaking, well since...
Since Erb was here earlier, I was watching her karaoke yesterday and she was singing a bunch of Abba.
And...
Like she did the Does Your Mother Know.
There was another one that she sang and I was just like, oh!
Oh, I want to sing this one too.
It seems fun.
Is it Gimme Gimme Gimme?
Which one did she sing?
Hold on, let me listen to this one.
Do I know this one?
Hold on.
What
do I do with my cough drop?
Wait, hold on.
Maybe I don't know this song.
I don't think I know this song well enough.
Yeah, I recognize the beginning of this one.
I don't know it well enough, guys.
There was a different one that I was thinking of.
What is it?
Is it this one?
Hold on.
Go away, gimme gimme.
Sorry, I'll learn it though.
Let me write it down.
Gimme, gimme, gimme.
So many songs that I...
Like tangentially know, you know?
Uh oh.
Carefun, don't freeze.
Don't freeze on me.
Please.
Stupid.
Play the next song.
Maybe it's this one.
Doggo, wasting your emotion Lay all your love on me
It was just like shooting a sitting duck A little small talk, a smile And baby, I was struck I still don't know what you've done with me A grown-up woman should never fall so easily I feel a kind of fear When I don't have you near Unsatisfied, I pick up my pride I beg you,
dear
Don't go wasting your emotion Lay all your love on me Don't go sharing your devotion Lay all your love on me Did you not have another oshi or anything?
Right?
I mean, like, that would be so crazy.
I've had a few little love affairs.
They didn't last very long and they've been pretty scarce.
I used to think that was sensible.
It makes the truth even more incomprehensible.
Woah, what
can I do?
Don't go wasting your emotion.
Lay all your love on me.
And don't go sharing your devotion.
And me, and me!
Don't go wasting your emotion.
Lay all your love on me.
Don't go sharing your devotion.
Don't go wasting your emotion.
Lay all your love on me.
And me!
Yay!
That was...
I'm going to need a break.
I'm going to watch more videos.
That was...
Lay all your love on me.
And did I finish my cough drop?
I put it in my cup.
Yay!
Let's watch some videos.
Why did I eat my...
Do I have any frogs in there?
I had some saved, like favorited, but I don't think I saved them.
I'm just going to go through a couple that I think are kind of funny.
I parasocially hate you.
What do you mean by that?
Thanks for eight months though.
Let's see.
I've quoted this clip before.
I love quoting this.
It's so funny.
Well, I think I'm looking forward to cracking up.
I hope I can totally crack up.
I haven't totally cracked up in a long time.
I'm looking forward to cracking up.
I love that one.
This one is pretty good too.
What's great about these is that they are so short.
So I can just be like, okay, next video.
Okay, so we are at the market.
Oh, Call of Duty book!
A coloring book.
Call of Duty book.
I love the Yaoi Call of Duty coloring book.
How do I get it?
How do I get the Yaoi coloring book?
I love the guy's reaction too.
Just, woah.
Woah.
Woah, woah, woah, woah.
Totally looking forward to cracking up.
This one, when I got this in my feed.
It felt like it targeted every aspect of my soul.
Which is all that I am.
Me opening up a Minto stream.
I'm looking forward to cracking up.
It's been a while since I've cracked up.
The most part about cracking up TikTok is the Osmosis Jones post.
He's wanting to crack up.
You're gonna crack up at Osmosis Jones.
But this next video, when I got it.
It was like, oh my gosh, this is so for me.
Because it targets Indiana Jones.
It targets my love for animatronics at theme parks.
I was like, this is just for me.
And it targets my favorite ride.
Which is the Indiana Jones ride at Tokyo Disney Sea.
Apparently.
I've ridden that ride so many times that I remember how it sounds like the song.
But this is, I guess the one at California is not very well maintained.
And so the Tokyo Disney one is actually like...
He's like huffing and puffing and he's like...
Man, that was tough.
But this one, he's like...
This guy is so good at imitating animatronics.
They should hire him for the FNAF movie.
And then you're just stuck there.
Because you're...
And you're stuck there waiting for the...
For the car in front of you to go.
He's so good at it.
I'm gonna watch it again.
I just realized, I think his whip is like a USB cord, right?
It's funny.
I love the Indiana Jones ride.
Why is he...
He looks like he could be in the ride.
It's insane.
It reminds me...
Whenever I think of human animatronics though, I think of the Pirates of the Caribbean ride.
More than anything.
That's so good.
Ok, this next video is another video that...
Makes me cry from laughing.
So it's a voicemail that this person got.
I think they have it written on the screen actually what the explanation is.
But it's a voicemail that this person got.
And it's like an AI voice.
But the AI voice is...
Oh my god, it sounds like a gun is being held to their head.
It's so funny.
And then suddenly it turns to a different voice.
It's like it's the fake breathing.
Now she's fine.
I know she's not fine.
Someone help her.
Help her.
AI voice with anxiety.
It's true.
That sounds awesome.
She's fine now.
Why is she so like...
It's the fake...
It's the fake like...
She actually sounds so distressed.
It's kind of freaky.
It's like...
Why does she sound so scared?
Who programmed you like that?
Who hurt you?
Who hurt your code?
The beginning is so funny though.
Could you please call me back?
625531.
This is a very urgent and time sensitive message from Relief Advisory Agency about funding your hardship account.
You have been pre-qualified for a $31,000 hardship benefit to pay your bill.
You have been pre-qualified for a $31,000...
What I learned in voting school is...
Someone help her.
I love that video.
It's so funny.
You can see the day I saved it.
It was in September 2023.
Well, it's kind of hidden, but...
And I think about this video still all the time.
Why was I programmed to feel pain?
Wait...
What did you say ghost meant?
I see people responding to you.
Sorry, I missed it.
I much needed karaoke after that singles mixer I attended yesterday.
This one girl I saw...
Wait, this one girl saw the mint keychain I bought at Otaku-san.
Her look of disappointment told me all I needed to know.
No!
Seriously?
I think if you're wanting someone who's into the same things as you though...
Going to like a...
I think you need to go to like...
You know how some cities have like bars, but they're like nerd bars?
Surely those kinds of places have to have like a speed dating thing.
Or like a singles mixer kind of night.
Right!
Like...
I feel like...
Go to one of those instead.
Dodged a bullet.
For real!
You dodged a bullet.
100%.
She sucks.
She's gonna get with someone and they're gonna be sad.
Because she doesn't have fun hobbies.
Maybe, I don't know.
I don't know her at all.
But she should not be, you know...
She should not be judgmental.
She should not be so judgmental.
Please call me back before my code is deleted.
Okay, this next video I love...
When it's Christmas time because...
They do...
What's it called?
The Grinch!
They do The Grinch at the Universal Parks.
And this one just sends me because he's so funny.
That means stinky.
That means strong.
Merry Christmas!
Bye bye!
Sayonara!
I quote that all the time.
I go...
My name is The Grinch.
Nice to
meet you.
My name is The Grinch.
Nice to meet you.
That means stinky.
Very strong.
That means strong.
Merry Christmas!
Bye bye!
Sayonara!
The Grinch.
He's actually so good at the Grinch voice.
I know, right?
They always get the best people.
I have another Grinch one actually because the guys are just so funny.
Hold on, let me get my other Grinch TikTok.
Sorry, I'm almost done with my...
Cough drop.
I'm almost done with my cough drop.
Where's my other Grinch video?
I have another Grinch video.
I saved it.
I'm worried some of my videos didn't save.
I'm not seeing them in there.
No, it has to be.
Where's my other Grinch video?
Where are you?
Where?
And I'm so sorry.
Did I accidentally save it in my offline folder?
No, okay.
I don't know.
Nevermind, maybe I can't find it.
We'll go through these so we'll get to it eventually maybe.
I don't know.
The Grinch.
This.
My name is The Grinch.
My name is Minky.
Okay, for everybody who's just like...
This is so much like brain rot girl, please.
Okay, I'm going to show you a good video.
This is related to everybody's interest, okay?
Everybody can appreciate this.
If you've never seen this video, it's so good.
It's so cute!
So cute, right?
Everybody can appreciate Godzilla and Kaiju.
I love the ears, how the ears go forward.
What?
I love that.
See?
Very powerful.
Everybody can be powerful.
Everybody.
I love my Yoshi.
What is this one called again?
What is the Kaiju named again?
I don't remember.
Baragon?
Baragon.
So cute.
Okay, I finished my cough drop.
So...
One more video.
I'll do a short one.
Some of these are a little bit longer and some of them are shorter.
I have a mix.
I mean, today is my birthday today.
She is the first female suit actor by the way.
Yes, it says it right there.
Rie Ota was the first woman to play a Kaiju in the Godzilla franchise.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, happy chungus.
Oh, I found my other...
Okay, wait.
I have two more videos.
This one is related to Godzilla.
Look, I kind of have like a pattern going on.
Isn't this great?
This one is related to Godzilla.
And then the last one, I found the Grinch video.
Look at this.
We need to buy a humidifier for the plants.
Look how perfect this is.
Look at him.
He is charging up.
It's perfect.
Maybe it's not perfect.
It's hitting that one plant really good.
It's hitting that one guy really well.
He will be nice and atomic.
Radioactive.
Yeah, the plants are getting nuked.
We love that for them.
They appreciate it.
They are going to grow like really crazy.
Okay, here is the last.
Here is the Grinch one that I was going to play earlier.
Can I get you to say something for my boyfriend Noah?
He is sick right now.
He is sick?
Yeah.
What's his name?
Noah.
Hey Noah.
May I just take this please?
I am stealing her phone.
Great.
She will never catch me.
I want to play the Grinch at the park.
Oh, fine.
I will come back.
Alright Noah.
What's your name?
I don't care what his name is.
Right.
Pretending to be sick is a fine way to avoid being seen in public with her.
They are so good.
The makeup is so good.
The acting is so good.
I want to play the Grinch.
Do you think that they would allow me?
Do you think that they would be like...
Minto is totally Grinch material.
Do you think that I could get hired to play the Grinch?
Perhaps.
Too short.
Grinky.
No.
I want to go around.
It's like when I was...
It was a long time ago.
When I was in grade school.
I got to skip school one day because I was hired...
Well, not hired.
Sorry.
I was asked by my friend.
He...
His mom worked as a teacher at a college.
And...
She was a theater teacher.
And so she got to do a bunch of silly things.
And I got to skip school because I got to dress up as Curious George.
And run around the library.
And cause mass chaos.
And I got to do whatever I wanted because I was a literal monkey.
I got to climb on tables.
I got to skip school for this.
Green hates Christmas.
True.
He's kind of scaring me.
Go away Grinch.
Curious Minky.
Yeah.
It was so great.
I know how to make people uncomfortable.
Probably.
It was such a great time.
And then I banged my knee on a table really bad.
And I remember it knocked the wind out of me.
And I was like keeled over.
And I was like...
And they were like, come on Curious George.
Come cause mischief.
And I'm like...
I'm like family guy Peter Griffin on the floor.
It was my karma for being too good of a monkey.
Probably.
Anyway, let's sing more songs.
Let's sing some more songs today.
Let's sing them.
The Grinch?
No.
We can't sing The Grinch.
It's not Christmas anymore.
We can't.
We'll do this song.
I'm sorry.
I was going through a...
Folder is called the best of.
Not folder.
Playlist?
It's on Caravan.
Eyes on you by Faye Wong.
For some time later.
Or another stream.
I think I can do that one.
This one.
Of which I'm certain.
I've lived a life that's full.
I've traveled each and every highway.
And more, much more than this.
I did it my way.
Regrets.
I've had a few.
But then again.
Too few to mention.
I did what I had to do.
And saw it through.
Without exemption.
I planned.
Each charted course.
Each careful step.
Along the byway.
Much more than this.
I did it my way.
Yes, there were times.
I am sure you knew.
When I bit off.
More than I could chew.
But through it all.
When there was doubt.
I ate it up.
And spit it out.
I faced it all.
And I stood tall.
And did it my way.
I've loved.
I've laughed and cried.
I've had my fill.
My share of losing.
And now.
As tears subside.
I find it all.
So amusing.
To think.
I did all that.
And may I say.
Not in a shy way.
Oh no.
Oh no, not me.
I did it my way.
For what is a ghost?
What has he got?
If not himself.
Then he has not.
To say the things.
He truly feels.
And not the words.
Of one who kneels.
The record shows.
I took the blows.
And did it my way.
Yes.
It was my way.
Thank you, thank you.
That was my way.
From Frank Sinatra.
I was worried my voice wasn't going to be able to hit those notes for a second.
She's not even at full power.
I was worried I wasn't going to hit some of those.
My voice is healing.
That was awesome.
Thank you for the five year third.
Got me all teared up with that one.
I feel very connected to the lyrics.
With that one.
What else can we sing?
I still have a lot more videos I want to share, but I also have a lot more that I want to sing too.
Thank you for the gift.
Die with a smile.
I guess I could try.
I feel like, didn't I sing it last time?
Trying to find more new songs.
That's why I added a couple new ones to the set list as you can see.
Let me do eyes on you.
Hold on, let me double check this is good.
Actually this one should be good.
This one should be good.
Hold on.
There we go.
Okay.
White Houses, oh I like that song.
Yeah, I'll do that one.
I'm going to need to go get more water in a minute.
On the stage, on my own Whenever said my words Wishing they would be heard I saw you smiling at me Was it real or just my fantasy You'd always be there in the corner Of this tiny little world My last night here for you Same old songs, just once more My last night here with you Maybe yes,
maybe no I kind of liked it your way How you shyly placed your eyes on me Did you ever know That I had mine on you Darling, so there you are With that look on your face As if you're never hurt As if you're never down Shall I be the one for you Who pinches you softly but sure If round is shown then I will know that you are no dreamer
Close as I want to be Close enough for me To feel your heart beating fast And stay there as I whisper How I loved your peaceful eyes on me Did you ever know I know that I had mine on me.
Darling, so share with me your love if you have enough, your tears if you're holding back, your pain if that's what it is.
Out
in the dress and the voice, just reach me out then, you will know that you are not dreaming.
Darling, so there you are, with that look on your face, as if you're never hurt, as if you're never down.
Shall I be the one for you, who pinches you softly by shore?
If promise shown then, I will know that you are no dreamer.
Maybe I'll...
I don't want to push it so much, so...
Maybe a couple more songs.
We'll do a lot of videos, if that's okay.
And then we'll do, like, it was a break, and then...
Maybe a couple more songs.
But let me do White Houses.
Crouched on the floor when I moved in, this little bungalow with some strange new friends.
Said, I'm too late, and I'm too thin.
We promised each other it's till the end, now we're spending empty bottles, it's the five of us.
With pretty-eyed boys, girls die to trust.
I can't resist the day.
No, I can't resist the day.
When Jenny screams out and it's no pose, cause when she dances, she goes and goes.
A beer through the nose on an inside joke, and I'm so excited, I haven't spoken.
And she's so pretty, and she's so sure, maybe I'm more clever than a girl like her.
The summer's all in bloom, the summer is ending soon.
It's alright, and it's nice not to be so alone, but I hold on to secrets in white houses.
Maybe I'm a little bit over my head, I come undone of the things he said.
And he is so funny in his bright red shirt, we were all in love, and we all got hurt.
I sneak into his car's cracked leather seat, the smell of gasoline in the summer heat.
Boy, we're going way too fast, it's all too sweet to last.
It's alright, and I put myself in his hands, but I hold on to secrets in white houses.
Love, or something ignites in my veins, and I pray it never fades in white houses.
My first time, hard to explain.
Brush of blood, oh, and a little bit of pain.
On a cloudy day, it's more common than you think.
He's my mistake.
We're
all faster than me, we gave each other up so easily.
These silly little wounds will never mend.
I feel so far from where I've been, so I'll go.
And I will not be back here again.
I'm gone as the day is fading.
On white houses I lie, put my injuries all in the dust.
And my heart is the five of us in white houses.
And you, maybe you'll remember me.
What I gave is yours to keep in white houses.
In white houses.
Thank you.
You can probably hear it, especially with that song I'm getting.
Kind of raspy, getting a little raspy.
Okay, I'm just gonna like, speed run.
Maybe some songs, or not songs, some videos.
Oh my god, hold on.
This next one, I saved, it's like a compilation, but I only saved it for one video, so I have to get to it.
Okay, here.
This one.
Okay, oh, I found it.
Ah, ah, ah, no, no.
Okay, okay, okay.
Alright, let's watch some funny videos.
So this one, you guys know how much I love voice changing stuff, you know, I think it's all so silly.
So, do you have any cat ones?
I think I have a few.
Actually, I have so many evil kitty ones, but I don't think I saved any of them.
This one?
Is that this one?
You know it?
Oh my gosh, I love this one.
Okay, any questions before I go on from here?
Great.
I really understood that well.
I'm guessing this is like when classes were online during the pandemic.
Great.
I have another video though that's also voice changer involved.
This is the, I like don't know anything about dress to impress, so I don't know how people do this.
But...
Hold on.
Oh, here it is.
That was really pretty.
I could've salvaged it, truthfully.
What the fuck is that?
Get the fuck off my screen.
She's so scared.
I think she hit the wrong button.
Why is she so, the fact that she's freaking out and it's like...
It's like, what's his name?
Never gonna give you up, but...
Who is that?
Rick Astley, yeah, yeah.
Sorry, I couldn't remember his name.
It's Drake?
Degrassi, yes, I knew that.
I knew that.
It's the absolute panic.
It's the absolute panic with the stupid voice.
Get the fuck off my screen.
You can hear her saying it.
It's like Rick Astley and she's like, get off my screen.
Let's see, I have some more game stuff.
This one is like this grandma who plays games.
And it's just so...
What's it called?
Wait, did it share who the name of...
Oh, this is from Treasured Curls.
Here, I'm gonna get rid of you guys again so you can see the...
This is where the user name...
Down here.
Hold on.
How do I get out of that?
Oh, I got it.
There we go.
Grandma playing... This is her playing Dead by Daylight.
And it's just so weird.
Hold on, I'm gonna move over.
The music is so funny.
She helps him.
And look!
Look what he does.
And then even the killer was just...
Go get him.
I don't think this is a real grandma.
I can't tell.
Go get him.
You see that?
She helps him.
You should leave.
What even is that?
This is so messed up.
Did you see that?
Go get him.
But the voice sounds so much like a grandma for real.
Total Granny TV.
Total Granny.
It's so funny.
The guy is just like...
Nah, I'm just gonna go.
That was messed up.
I have some more video game ones.
This one is not funny, but...
Oh my gosh, it spooks me to no end.
Look at this.
Look at this mechanic.
The voice, everything about it makes me...
Oh my gosh.
It makes me crawl.
This is the scariest part.
Oh my gosh.
The fact that it went the other direction.
I could never.
If there is a game that is made like this I would never play it.
I think I would...
Oh my gosh, it's so scary.
The step sounds take me out of it.
It's clear.
Yeah, I think it's too much.
But look at that.
She's so fast too.
She's so fast.
It's like Weeping Angel almost.
I hate that.
Wait, hold on.
I'm deleting some videos.
Here is another video game one that I die every time.
You got fired so you drowned your sorrows in booze.
She had to get a part-time job working at a grocery store cash register.
The only reason she could earn a wage at all was the manager liked how she looked in a skirt.
You remember, right?
Exactly 10 months back.
You got fired so you drowned your sorrows in booze.
Why is it so true?
Too real, man.
I have another PT one.
I used to get a lot of PT.
A lot of PT TikToks.
Hold on.
I'm gonna play this one.
I'm sure you guys have seen this, but I love compilations like this.
Wait, where did it go?
Oh, wait.
This one you guys have probably seen.
I feel like this one was popular enough it probably got posted on like Twitter or something.
Putting Waluigi's skeleton inside of all the guys.
Oh god, it just turned into a horror game.
This one is jorts.
I love how Yoshi and Birdo refuse to comply.
They're so... They're so scary.
Oh my god.
Donkey Kong looks relatively normal.
Bowser is okay too.
Goomba is so... Oh my god.
It's so bad.
Long Toad is... Look at Boo, he looks almost normal.
He's so cute.
I didn't see the DK Skelly one.
Goomba kills me though.
Where is Goomba?
Where is he?
Why does he look like that?
He's feeling something though.
Oh wait, I was watching it and I forgot to search for the other video that I was gonna look for.
No.
Someone asked for cats earlier?
Here's a cat.
Here's some cats.
I love cats that look like Adam Driver.
What?
Oh my god.
Everybody's honking.
What?
They harmonize at the beginning.
I love that.
Hold on.
I'm trying to find the videos that I've played so that I can delete them.
But I'm bouncing all over the place so I'm getting confused.
Oh this one's funny.
I have a couple Sims ones too that I would get.
I love the Sims.
Turbo Baby!
Why didn't he leave though?
The baby has no survival skills.
Why?
My cats have been summoned.
They think it's dinner.
Oh no!
What did I just play?
Oh there's the honkings.
The honks.
Honk, honk, honk.
Let's do this one.
Oh my gosh.
This one is really satisfying to me because watch the way he slaps the pig.
It's so satisfying.
It like scratches such an itch.
It like is so...
It's so...
It's so satisfying to watch.
It's like violent ASMR.
I love it.
I'm kind of obsessed with it.
Wait, did I save the ASMR one?
Hold on.
Oh I did!
Oh my gosh.
You guys, if I ever do ASMR it's going to be like this.
Sorry, trigger for like... Wait, if you hate... Hold on, hold on.
If you hate sounds of people eating.
Here, I'm going to turn it down because I do too.
I don't know why I even watch this because like she started doing it and I was like, oh, that sounds horrible.
I hate it.
Did you smell it?
It's a mixture of all my other boyfriends.
Here, eat some.
Here, I'll take a bite for you.
It's so crisp in my ear.
I think I'm going to throw up.
I turned it down.
Sorry, I couldn't deal with it.
It's your turn.
Okay, I know when she chews because I watched these last night.
Okay, here we go.
It's over.
You just bit my finger.
You did not.
Did you just bite my finger?
It's the cowboy.
And I thought, I thought you were the one.
You just bit my finger.
I thought you were the one.
Oh, I was showing a video game compilation earlier.
Or I mentioned it.
I found it.
This one.
I'm sure you've seen all of these, but they're so funny.
I love dogs.
Let's see if we can't find those mountain lions.
This makes me want to play Oblivion.
I'll not have anything to do with you.
Be gone.
This one though.
Snow.
We need more snow.
Can't have enough snow.
Indeed.
Snow.
We need more snow.
Can't have enough snow.
Indeed.
I can't tell if they're glitched into that or if that's just how you find them.
You know?
So good.
Indeed.
Such a classic.
So funny.
I don't like this one.
Okay, well.
I saved it because I felt like it was kind of like a...
Oh, girls are bad at video games kind of TikTok.
So I wasn't super a fan of it.
But I come into it with the mindset of like, this is you guys watching YouTubers.
Don't just think about playing Oblivion, please.
I'll consider it.
But this one, I think it's funny.
If you come at it with the mindset of it is a VTuber, like you're watching the VTuber play.
Okay, you're gonna love this game.
It's really cute.
It eases you in.
See, this is the tutorial level and it teaches you all the controls.
Nice.
Here we go.
I'm sure she'll figure this out.
She's not figuring this out.
She's still doing the same thing.
This is how I feel when I'm playing.
Change tactics, VTuber.
Who's the legendary journalist?
Who is that?
Do you guys know this guy?
Why would I read the background decoration?
This is actually VTuber simulator.
That's not doing anything.
Nope, that's not it.
That was dumb.
Not even close.
Oh, why didn't we say so?
Wow, that game was awesome.
I was like this is too relatable.
I think.
We must yell at screen person.
It just feels too relatable.
I was like this isn't working, you guys.
You have to do this.
You have to do this, Minto, please.
Minto, please.
This one was great because I got Donna Burke naturally on my timeline.
I was like Donna Burke, there she is.
This is a non-Metal Gear.
It's all the people.
The train on track 5 is bound for Shinagawa and Shibuya.
I know it's him, but he just sounds like...
Please stand behind...
It's like so consistent.
JY-17
They're professionals, I know.
It's crazy, it's a voice made for announcements.
Hers,
I hear the least.
When she does it in person.
She didn't seem like she was very in the mood.
I think like...
I think like she's got to get in the mood, you know what I mean?
Like the groove of it, you know, I think.
Okay, this one, I don't know anything about sororities.
But this is actually a horror movie.
I'm turning down the volume way crazy.
I don't know anything about sororities, but they're crazy.
Howdy.
Don't dead, open inside.
Oh, you guys have seen this one?
Oh
my God, I can't do it anymore.
It's this though.
What the hell?
Why would they think this is welcoming?
I don't understand.
The original is even worse?
What do you mean the original?
Is this not the original?
I'm pretty sure this is the original.
Okay, I don't know what this one is.
We're just going to open it and see what happens.
Oh yeah.
I
like the two giant lights on it.
And the teeny tiny Santa hat.
I think the tee is really...
So this next one requires context.
Apparently, whatever this hockey stadium is...
When they sing the American National Anthem...
All of the audience...
You know there's a part in the song where it goes...
The red lights, the red part, everybody goes red.
But they did not tell these little children that are singing the national anthem...
That they do that.
Red!
What did we do wrong?
We were stunned.
I'm scared of the silence.
I would be so terrified.
It sounds so violent.
Oh,
it's good.
This one is cute too.
This one is so funny.
Oh my god, it's so loud.
Sorry.
Kawaii desu ka?
Poor dog.
Can't keep up.
This is how I feel like you guys act with each other.
No, it's not scripted at all.
I feel like you guys would do this.
I feel like you guys would agree to create something like this.
I feel like you would.
Oh my god, okay.
You guys, I have to show you this one.
I almost did a watch along of this movie because of the TikTok.
I almost did a watch along.
I can't... I can't remember what it's called.
Is this a dream?
Yes,
this dog's got pies.
It's the dead eyes.
Oh yeah!
And there's...
Apparently, this is like... so...
If I remember correctly, the Air Bud movies, right?
The Air Bud movies all went to these movies.
These like puppy dog superstar talent show movies.
This is like a whole thing now.
The Air Bud has moved on from sports.
This is now the Pupstar Universe.
Like...
The dead eye singing like...
You're gonna CGI its face and like its mouth, but the eyes just nothing is going on.
It's so horrible.
Pupstar.
Yeah, Pupstar Cinematic Universe.
Oh my god, it's so painful to watch.
Is this a dream?
You believe your dream came true?
Damn, she's got pipes though.
It's just the static standing.
You got like the dog judges.
I can't.
It's the eyebrows.
It's so funny.
I can't stand it.
Speaking of music, I would like to show everybody the inspiration...
Between the brain rot bash.
Well, I say inspiration, where I got the idea from.
The banana really sold it for me, you guys.
Here is the ball, the gas.
This is where I got the idea from.
This very exact video.
You're welcome.
Sorry this is cringe.
It's supposed to be cringe.
What are you talking about?
Cringe is free.
Speaking of cringe, here is some Roblox content, but it's actually good.
It's so good.
And then it's these guys, they're like all trying to do the...
It's me.
It's how all the people in Oz felt when she was singing that song and flying through the sky.
They only hear the little itsy-bitsy pieces of her.
And she's just soaring through the sky.
It's so funny.
Oh my gosh.
Gosh, I love this one too.
I kind of quote this one, but I don't think I've quoted this one on stream before.
I feel like I have another hope core one.
What did I save?
Oh, I was trying to find this one earlier.
This is so... Oh, because of PT, that's right.
It goes so well.
Really throwing stones from her glass house.
What do you mean?
I need someone to sample that now.
For like a song.
Oh, I found it.
I found the other hope core one.
I need someone to sample that though.
For real.
It sounds so good.
How did she even think of this?
I don't know.
People's brains just work in other ways.
In ways that I cannot fathom.
Okay, here we go.
He got it perfectly.
It's so true.
You know, he could speak multiple languages though.
So, he's doing better than me.
I've probably said something just as bad in Japanese.
I really like this duck.
Where'd it go?
Wait, there it is.
I really like this duck.
I love that.
Do the duck walk, Curly Beth.
I don't even know what this is from.
It's from an account called Halloween Commercials, but I don't know.
Do the duck walk, Curly Beth.
I love that.
Oh, it's goosebumps.
Do the duck walk, Curly Beth.
I love that.
Oh, man.
What is this one?
Oh, I love this one.
This is another one with ducks.
Why
does the statue exist?
Clearly.
No clapping, only quacking.
No clapping.
Only the way that everybody starts quacking.
Yeah, it's better without context maybe.
No, it's a statue of Long Boy.
Whoever Long Boy.
Yeah, memorial for Long Boy.
Everybody is so like...
Quack, quack, quack, quack.
I hope that Long Boy is okay.
Well, I mean, that Long Boy lived a good life.
That's what I mean.
Oh my gosh, thank you for the hot guys.
Thank you.
Here's some more... Oh wait, here's another duck.
Like I mentioned earlier, I like some goose and bird videos and then I would get stuff like this.
Do dee do dee do dee do dee do dee do dee...
So many good ones.
So many good ones!
This one is another animal.
I love animal videos.
Who doesn't?
He remained calm.
So many duck bits, what are you obsessed with?
Go away!
It's the lady in the background going, Oh.
My.
God.
I pre-ordered my plat space for your arm crease you sold on Twitter and just wanted to send this bribe to grease the pits of... hey.
Indy, chill out, okay?
Doody, doody, doody, doody, brrra brrra brrra brrra brrra brrra The ini benini guy was the president of my country!
No!
Don't be embarrassed It made for...
Oh...
Yeah...
Beginning's a hard word.
That's fine.
Um, can you guys guess which Harry Potter movie this is from?
I'm about to play you a scene from a Harry Potter movie, but I'm not going to tell you which one.
I already know.
Yes, leave your answer in the comments.
The Goblet of Fire.
Five?
Which one's five?
Which one's four?
Four is Goblet of Fire.
The Goblet of Fire.
This one makes me laugh because...
I kind of want to start singing my happy birthdays like this.
Happy birthday to you.
Joy, thanks for the beat!
Happy birthday, dear Bowman, Bowman, Bowman.
Oh, so context?
Apparently this user really likes this lady, and all of their friends bought them cameo of this lady, and so they stitched them together.
Bowman, happy birthday to you.
Happy 27th birthday, Bowman, from Alice Elm with Elegant Interior Decorating.
Alice Elm with Elegant Interior Decorating.
I hope that you have an amazing, amazing, amazing, amazing birthday.
And just a few of my decorating tips.
Well, first of all, I like neutral colors, but you choose whatever colors that you like.
But also add a beautiful area room in just about every room in your home, because it really enhances just about every room in a home.
And when choosing lighting, add a beautiful lighting that creates an ambience.
And nice decorative pillows.
Look, she's giving so much advice.
You're getting your money's worth.
And just a couple of fashion tips, Bowman.
Always dress for the occasion and wear well-fitting clothing.
I love you.
I love you, Bowman.
I love you, Bowman, I wish you nothing but the best.
Love always from Alice Elm with Elegant Interior Decorating.
You guys, my birthday is October 1st.
I love you, Minto.
I love...
You can hear it now.
Oh,
man, so good.
These types of videos, actually, Matara would send them to me all the time.
There's so many of these.
They're so good.
I only saved one, but I had so many of them saved.
This might be my favorite one.
I want to try this with my cats, but I have to get a video of them, like...
I'm doing anything.
What's this one?
Oh, I love this one!
Oh, Chico Bandito.
I love you so much.
You're just a cat.
Yeah.
You're so handsome.
I love you so much.
You're just a cat.
Yeah.
Oh, Chico Bandito.
Sorry, okay.
I can't stop listening to him.
He's just so cute.
Do I have any more cats?
Oh, I have lots more cats.
What's this one?
What is this cat video?
Oh, yeah.
The music choice is so...
Why does he do that?
Why?
Why is he like that?
And then this is another one.
Here's another cat video.
Sounds good.
Rocky.
Thank you.
Hi, I'm Fallen.
I'm glad you like my TikToks.
My feed wasn't so cursed.
My feed is funny.
My feed...
This is kind of cursed though.
Here, I'll show you guys this.
Oh god, I hate the bears.
Music is so funny.
Who is this?
Who is this dragon?
Who is that?
I've never seen that guy before in my afterlife.
Never seen him.
I'll lie through the eyes of a toddler.
This one's good in focus though.
It's pretty nice.
This one is really...
I don't think it's the photo.
I think it's just the way he looks.
I think it's just him.
I don't think it's the figment.
Pete's dragon.
Looks like Spyro.
Spyro if he gained like 50 pounds.
Pimpy.
Figment is an OG.
I don't know him at all.
I don't know.
I'm a fake Disney fan, I guess.
Here, this one's also with dragons.
This is us before Dizzy Dragon.
Their screaming is so...
Their screaming is so dramatic until you see that it's warranted.
Dude on the right though is not happy.
Hi.
He's going through it.
His expression matches the shirt.
If you ever ride a spinny ride with me though, this is exactly what you're expecting.
This is what you will get with me if you...
If you ride a spinny ride like this with me.
Man's traumatized.
Wait, what's this one?
Oh, Fish of the Week!
I know what it is, but what do you think it's gonna be?
Hackfish.
Yeah, giant sea bass!
Yes!
It isn't actually a sea bass and is part of the wreckfish family.
But it certainly earns the giant part of its name as it gets up to 2.5 meters and 360 kilograms.
They live in the...
I didn't read that.
This giant sea bass can live over 75 years.
They live in kelp forests and are the apex predators there.
Unfortunately, they are critically endangered and locally extinct in Southern California.
Fish of the Year is only three weeks away!
Oh, I don't know what guy is Fish of the Year.
It's crazy because like in Animal Crossing, you get the sea bass like crazy.
But to know that it's critically endangered is so crazy.
Right?
But in Animal Crossing, it makes it seem like it's the most common fish you'll ever experience.
The sea bass.
This is the giant sea bass.
Oh.
Oh yeah, you're right.
In Animal Crossing, it's just a sea bass.
Oh.
You're so right!
Here's a dog.
It's a bouncing ball that bounces on its own.
Hi, I'm Larry.
The shivery, cheerful bird.
I'm cold.
I need a sweater.
She's gripping it, yeah.
What kind of dog is that?
She's so pretty.
It also isn't really bouncing on its own.
It's just wobbling everywhere.
It doesn't really bounce.
Faulty product, I think.
I like this one.
This one has nothing to do with animals or anything.
I just think it's funny.
The bus can't even go.
Oh my god, call the police.
Oh my god, he is the police.
Oh my god, oh my god, call the police.
Oh my god, call the police.
Oh my god, he is the police.
The comedic timing.
We love that.
Oh, I just realized.
I think I got shut out of TikTok before.
I could download...
Oh, I wanted to download the one of the dinosaur ride.
But I have this one.
This ride instead.
Okay, hold on.
At the end of ET, he says your name.
And the group of young guys in front of us all gave their name as Chuck.
Oh,
TikTok is bad.
No, I downloaded them all last night.
I don't... I didn't care to touch it this morning, honestly.
Chuck, Chuck, Chuck, Chuck.
Fine, thanks for the five gifted.
Thank you.
Okay, this one also kills me.
Because grandma's on Facebook, just...
Oh, grandma's on Facebook.
Take me to the king.
I don't have much to bring.
My heart's all in pieces.
It's my offering.
Take me to the king.
It's like that damn pop star.
Stupid
pop star video.
Oh, gosh.
Does Mint know about Tyranno dance guys?
I don't think so.
Maybe I know of them.
I don't know their name.
And for me and TikTok, I don't...
I only followed like one creator.
Everything else, I just enjoyed the surprise of it all.
Because I would just get the most random things.
Oh, I want to play this one about the wasp.
But it's kind of gross.
What the heck is that one?
I don't remember.
I downloaded these last night and I don't remember what some of them are.
I really like this one though.
I like this one.
Oh, he's so cute.
Yeah, dig it.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, he's so cute.
Yeah, he's so cute.
Gosh, look how precious he is.
Oh, what a snake.
Oh, he's so cute.
Okay, I need to back away.
Here, this one's cursed.
Oh, wait.
This one's also so cute.
I told you I like to get bird videos.
I wish a pigeon would text me.
Several pigeons are typing.
Look at that.
What if he sends a bad word though?
Oh my god, she fell asleep on the key.
Oh, big yawn.
How is the pigeons cosplaying a creeper?
Sixteen.
Oh, daddy.
F6.
So cute.
Such a good idea.
What a joy to just periodically receive texts from your pigeons.
Such a great idea.
That would be such a joy through my day.
If I'm at work and suddenly I get a text from my pigeon, I would...
And it's a nice keyboard.
I love the yawn.
I would not want to clean those keyboards.
You know what?
So true.
I can't believe it looks like such a nice keyboard too.
Like, it's got the RGB and everything.
Wasp video.
Okay.
Oh my gosh.
Okay, so it's a wasp with a parasite.
And he has to get the par...
Stuff like this is so fascinating, right?
He has to get the parasite out.
Wait.
Why isn't it playing?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I opened it with the wrong thing.
This one.
Look.
Oh my god.
Look at him trying to sting him.
It's crazy.
Look how many there are.
Ew, not this.
You asked for this.
What are you talking about?
Play the wasp video.
I said the wasp video was gross.
Okay, here it is.
I don't think that.
Nasty.
I wonder if it hurts though.
He's a fat boy.
Gooey.
I don't think we should save the wasp though.
That guy sucks.
Look, he weaves.
Bye bye.
This one, he has like...
Look at that though.
Like, that's...
This is an extreme amount.
Like, that's an extreme amount.
It looks so uncomfortable.
He was a friendly wasp.
I mean, he tried to sting.
But like, he's friendly too.
Yeah, a little bit.
He's just, he's just, you know, he's like...
You're also trying to go inside my body.
You're too big.
I'll die.
No, he wasn't.
He was gonna extract the things in your body.
More please will go to Kelvin Wiley's TikTok and you can get more, you know?
Also, I don't...
This one, it just came across my feed.
You're watching videos of wasps while I'm giving a stop.
Immediately went on to sting a family of four.
No!
This one is so crazy because...
I didn't...
I was waiting for the picture of the rat.
And then when I got the picture of the rat, I was not prepared for the picture of the rat.
Oh my god.
I'm about to get on r slash rat.
This is the first one that was being posted constantly and Perky was massive.
Like a massive rat.
Like absolutely, just like morbidly obese, huge rat.
Huge rat!
This wouldn't be promoted or allowed on a lot of like pet subreddits because the size was indicative of abuse.
But, Perky's owner was like, no, Perky's a rescue.
This is like leftover medical issues from a past owner.
Okay, that's totally understandable.
You know, you saved Perky.
You're helping him get better.
So they started doing like, Perky pose.
Perky was super famous on the subreddit.
You guys are not ready to see Perky.
Then, people started noticing that, for one, Perky's owner was not really telling anybody what the medical issues were and why they couldn't be fixed.
And also noticing that the other rats that this person had were also pretty large.
Except for one rat that the owner posted very recently and was like, See?
This rat eats the same as Perky and this rat's not fat.
But also, someone pointed out that apparently that rat had died five months prior.
So then the moms were like, we're not gonna promote Perky anymore because we think that Perky maybe is being abused.
And this started a huge civil war of people being super pro-Perky and being like, Fuck you, we're leaving.
We're gonna make our own pro-Perky rat subreddit.
And then other people posting and just tearing apart Perky's owner and being like, This person should have their rats taken.
But listen, guys, when I'm telling you this rat is massive, let me show you a photo.
Look at this fucking rat, dude.
That's grotesque.
That is insane.
Like, whatever is going on here is not kosher, okay?
This rat needs help.
And this has been going on for days.
You can't even see his face is being engulfed by his body.
This poor rat!
Perky!
Oh my god, he's ginormous.
Oh my god, Perky.
Someone save Perky!
I have never heard anything else about Perky the rat after this.
I don't know if Lana the Goblin ever did an update, but...
Good golly, that rat!
He's huge!
Oh my god!
That rat's huge!
I know!
Cheeseburger, happy birthday!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday dear Cheeseburger!
I feel like Milkhouse 6000 YouTube videos are up your alley.
Milkhouse?
Like Milhouse?
I'm happy to find a fellow NGS fanatic.
Thank you for the superchat!
I'll definitely look up the account.
I love ones about awkward dogs.
Another awkward night with my dog of 70.
Why do dogs look at you like this?
Like you're intruding.
He's just like...
The music really sells it.
I'm going to do this video, and then we can go back to singing.
I still have so many more videos.
I'm going to have to do the best of the best.
Oh wait!
I have two more videos.
This one I actually brought up on stream.
And so now I can show you.
Because I brought it up on stream before.
And I talked about the...
The jep...
The malore?
Thanks for the spooky!
Thanks for all the good vibes today.
Both the karaoke and the silly videos.
Yeah!
The malore, the one alcohol.
But I first, if you know Red Letter Media...
I first watched this video because the guy looks like my oshi, Mike Staclasa.
And then I watched the content and I was just like...
Jepson's malore!
Yes, thank you.
And then I watched the video and I was like...
Okay, this is kind of funny.
Alright, ready?
What is it?
Doesn't he look so much like Mike?
Jepson's malore.
And then you take it.
And you say...
I'll have another.
Wait, I say that after?
Yeah.
Alright, ready?
Who's Jepson?
Jepson's malore.
Here it goes.
I'll have another.
Here we go.
Jepson's malore.
I'll have another.
Alright, ready?
What is it?
I don't know what this...
People said it tastes like something humans should not consume.
But I'm a ghost, so if I tried it, would I be okay?
Jepson's malore.
Oh gosh.
That I... One last video.
This one is of some giraffes.
Sorry, I have so many videos.
I love them all.
Look at this.
This is majestic.
Sorry for giraffe balls.
The wide stance.
It's the wide stance.
He like wraps it around.
Step.
Shut up, Indy.
I actually almost shared one of my videos that reminded me of Haley Joel Osment.
But I think I would have gotten so upset.
I wouldn't have wanted to continue.
But I have videos saved of people that look like Haley Joel Osment that make me mad.
I could probably find it now and save it, but I don't want to...
Do you guys know Offlane?
I had to make an individual folder for Offlane.
Because I love his videos.
The peener snipper guy.
Offlane is awesome.
That's the only account I follow on TikTok, honestly.
No, that's a lie.
I follow idols and that's the only real account.
I'm going to go get some water.
I'm going to put something on for you guys to watch while I'm gone.
What should I put on?
Oh, I'm going to put on this one.
Okay, there's a backstory to this one.
When the hook to a girl first came out with her podcast, I didn't know what it was about.
And then I saw this video and I was like, whoa.
Wow, she's actually using her platform.
I didn't know she was like so cool.
And so I saw this video and I actually thought this is what the first episode...
I don't even know what she talks about on her podcast.
But I thought this was...
When I saw this, I thought it was real.
The talk to a podcast's first discussion, 16th century naval warfare, proved to be an incredibly enlightening and insightful dive into an underrated and poorly understood topic.
The conversation began correcting a major misconception.
Although sailing ships were in use by the Syrians, war-powered galleys still dominated the Mediterranean.
The reason for this is because speed and maneuverability in shallow waters was key.
Naval warfare still imitated one of the works of Poseidon.
While ships were equipped with cannons, these early models lacked the range for the fire and raw power to reliably take out enemy ships before they were inborn.
Sailing ships, which relied on favorable winds, were especially at risk when compared to galleys, which did not need wind to maneuver well.
Then the podcast moved on to the actual nature of galley warfare itself.
They explained that like land warfare, the majority of naval conflicts in this period were not large pitched battles, but raids, skirmishes, and sieges.
However, when two fleets did engage, the result was often far more destructive than on land.
When Haley questioned Whitney on why this was, she responded that the utter chaos and unpredictability made retreating in proper order next to impossible once the fighting began.
As ships fired volleys of missiles at point-blank range and men fought their way across decks, there was nowhere to run or hide.
Men who otherwise may have fled the field and survived on land had no choice but to fight or perish.
And of course, enemy weapons weren't the only danger.
We can finish watching.
It's so interesting, right?
I used to get a lot of videos like this and a lot of videos about like executions and like royalty and stuff.
This is why I like TikTok, you guys!
I would never look this up myself!
Spain, Venice, and the Ottoman Empire were the preeminent naval powers of this period, and controlling the waters of the Mediterranean were imperative to their wider strategic goals.
As galleys had little room for food and water, frequent resupplies at ports were needed, and thus the primary focus of these powers was control of the port cities.
Eventually, cannon and ship technology would render galleys obsolete, and European strategic focus would shift more towards the New World as their colonial empires grew.
Leading to the True Age of Sail we all know and love, but to the ladies of the TalkTua podcast, galley warfare is an incredibly fascinating chapter in naval history that should be appreciated more.
The TalkTua podcast...
Cool!
Happy Birthday!
Happy Birthday to you!
Happy Birthday dear Matt Kramer!
Yeah, that's why I wanted to share that one because I just thought it was so funny that I actually thought that's what they talked about in the first episode.
And then, I have never heard anything, a single thing about that podcast.
Have you guys ever heard one thing that they've talked about?
Ever?
If we get around to doing JP songs again, can I request Sose no Aquarium?
Yeah, I can sing that.
Thanks for the super chat.
Let's sing Aquarium.
Here we go.
Aquarium.
Sorry.
I love Aquarium.
I've been in love with you for a thousand years.
I've been missing you more since I was eight thousand years old.
I've been in love with you for a hundred million years.
Ever since I met you, music has been playing in my hell.
You've become an adult over and over again.
You've gone far away over and over again.
I watch over you.
I can't sleep.
Even if I'm all wrinkled up.
I sing your name.
I've been in love with you for a thousand years.
I've been missing you more since I was eight thousand years old.
I've been in love with you for a hundred million years.
Ever since I met you.
I've been missing you more since I was eight thousand years old.
I've been in love with you for a hundred million years.
Ever since I met you, music has been playing in my hell.
Aquarium.
Nice!
Nice, nice.
I watch over you.
I can't sleep.
Even if I'm all wrinkled up.
Let's see.
Eva opening.
I feel like people are so sick of that song, are they not?
I mean, not that I am.
I guess it's kind of...
It'd be silly if I'm just like, I don't know if people are sick of that song, but I'm not even sick of that song.
Kind of, maybe.
Let's go, let me see what's in the caravan.
I am trying to sing.
What's in their 80s hits?
Oh, no, no, no, no, quiz.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm not studying.
No, no, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Oh, join the quiz using QR code.
Oh, no, I don't want to do that.
Let's see.
Rock love songs.
No.
Disney.
Ikanaide.
I haven't sung that song in a long time.
Let me see.
Ikanaide.
I don't know if I'll be able to sing it very well.
I can try.
Right now, I mean.
I don't know.
I've never sung this version.
It sounds so crunchy.
So crunchy.
I don't know.
Jikan dake ga sugite iku boku wo tsurete tte Kaerimichi kurai keredo hitori de daijoubu kana Gaido ni terasarete kage ga dekite iru hitoribocchi sa Tooku e to kiete iku boku wo oite tte
絎障篁綺 紊羯蚊с 羈ｃ＜ 羈ｃ＜ с綵荐 茵 羈ｃ＜ 羈ｃ＜ с綵荐
茵 I don't know if I've ever sung this before, so it's kind of kind of new for me.
Actually, YouTube is is suggesting something and I'm like, should I sing this?
I didn't get to sing it during the stream, so I'm like, maybe now is the time.
And I have permission to sing these whenever I feel they said I can.
Where is it?
I don't know if this one will get the stream taken down though.
Maybe not.
Hmm, that was lovely.
My heart hurts.
Actually, I will sing this one because this one will make my heart hurt.
Once again.
Okay.
Let's see.
Maybe I'll do this one since we just did a slow one and then I'll go to faster songs.
I managed to pull myself together.
I managed to pull myself together mostly.
Oh my gosh.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
That was a Kuchizuke Kibun, which is maybe my favorite song from from my idol group that recently disbanded.
Named Tappokumi Inc.
So, yeah.
So sad.
So that's why the song was going to make me cry because it's just, oh, it's one of those songs that just gets you like it ran to the heart.
Did they sing it at the last live?
They did.
I got to hear it both days, so I was very happy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But that made me, that made it worse because I was just crying, sobbing both days because of it.
I mean, obviously I was sobbing in general and not just me, everybody around too.
So it's okay, maybe.
Oh, I have another song I want to sing.
This is another Utada Hikaru song.
I've never sung before actually, so I'm a little nervous.
If I sing sorry, but I didn't practice and also, but I listened to the song like a lot.
So, hold on.
Let me look up the lyrics just in case this video doesn't have it.
Okay, I try singing.
In it with you, in love with you.
In it with you, in it with you.
I've been in love with you.
In love with you.
In it with you, in it with you But I can't believe in myself I don't believe in anything I don't exist, I'm just a green plant The only thing I can be sure of is the truth
No one can take away the contents of our hearts I can't protect it that much
In it with you.
In love with you.
This backing track sucks.
Wow, it sucked.
Go listen to the original!
It's so good.
It's called...
篏蚊с Wait, why is it so far away?
There we go.
Whenever I like walk around in Japan, I have that song on.
It's like my walking song.
I don't know why.
And also, sorry my voice is so shaky.
My voice is still a little...
It's still a little...
You know?
But then I was also gonna do...
What was I gonna do?
Bizarre Quest, Uptown Girl by Billy Joel.
Like, uptown girl.
I've been living in an uptown world.
I don't know that.
I only know that part.
Wait, where did I save that?
Wait, maybe here?
Yes.
But, where are the lyrics?
Where did I save the lyrics?
I don't remember.
But I don't trust myself.
Maybe under...
Here.
Did I get deleted?
I don't know.
I wonder if I got deleted on my old computer.
Jonathan, welcome to my bishop.
Thank you!
Did you guys see that tweet about how scary that was?
I saw that.
Robbie Williams.
Who is that guy?
He's the monkey, right?
Oh, I do have the lyrics.
Okay, I'm perfect.
Awesome.
Okey dokey.
Nice, nice, nice.
Jump scare.
Does
it have my backing vocals in it?
It's gonna sound a little empty sometimes.
Haha.
I can't see it, I can't touch it, I can't feel it.
The thorns of my heart are being snatched away.
There's no way I can meet you.
I want to see you, but why does it hurt?
I keep picking up the words I've lost.
In the long journey to the end.
I'm lost, but the miracle is shaking.
Ah!
Thank you!
Brother.
I'm sure I'll love the pain in your chest, Phantom Face.
Wow, like a phantom.
I sang a cover of this song for Touhou Last Word.
So now I'm singing it on stream.
I got lost in the moonlight.
I hug the heavy wind.
I hold your hand.
If I trace it with my dark fingers, The pain that pierces through to the past.
This is too bad.
Pity.
Oh, sweet dreams.
We keep screaming with tears in our eyes.
Encore.
I want to disappear.
Forget it.
I can't remember.
I was made to dance.
The shadow of my heart.
There's no way it exists.
I know.
If that's the case, why does it hurt?
I take a step forward.
I'll find my way to the end of the journey.
No matter how much pain there is, I'm sure.
I kept on dancing.
Wait, I lost my phone.
Phantom Face.
I lost a part in the lyrics.
Who saw it?
I can't see it.
I can't touch it.
I can't feel it.
It's taken away.
The thorns of my heart.
There's no way it exists.
I know.
If that's the case, why does it hurt?
I keep picking up the words I've lost.
I'll find my way to the end of the journey.
While I'm lost in the city.
If I can believe in a miracle.
I'm sure I can love the pain in my heart.
Phantom Face.
Like a Phantom Face.
Won't cry in the rain.
Oh my gosh.
The song is still so...
There's parts where it's like...
Where is it?
I can't see it.
I can't touch it.
I can't feel it.
I can't see it.
I can't touch it.
I can't feel it.
It's like a tongue twister.
It's taken away.
The thorns of my heart.
Thorns.
There's no way it exists.
I know.
If that's the case, why does it hurt?
That part.
I can't see it.
I can't touch it.
I can't feel it.
I had to do that part like maybe like...
20 times.
Thank you for the five gifted.
Oh my gosh, there were so many five.
There were so many gifted.
Thank you guys.
Thank you for the gifted.
I'm scrolling.
Thanks for the gifted.
Thank you guys.
Thank you.
It's only showing me up to there, but...
It was so much.
And then...
Well, that was a part of that song.
No, that one was good.
It's the...
I would just have to sit there and go...
I have phantom pain.
So does my home screen theme.
Good luck for everybody entering the giveaways.
Yay, thank you.
Spank thanks for the 20 gifted.
Thank you so much.
If you could talk to David Hayter, what would you want to say?
I've talked to David Hayter before.
Oh my gosh.
I just realized how long I've been streaming for.
Holy moly.
What?
Seriously?
That's crazy.
I have so many more TikToks I was going to show.
But I think I'm actually going to end it with...
This last song.
I don't know.
It's been almost four hours.
Wow.
I talked to David Hayter and I basically thanked him.
I was just like, wow.
You don't know this.
But you changed the entire trajectory of my career path.
Not path, but...
I told him, I was just like...
You don't understand.
How much things changed after Metal Gear.
It's still so much fun to have people come in and be like...
People will comment and be like...
It's really cool to see someone...
A Vtuber so into Metal Gear.
Things like that.
So...
Those kinds of moments are really precious to me.
I feel like I got known as a Vtuber that loves Metal Gear so much.
And so...
Maybe made a different...
What's the word?
A different name for me, maybe.
I don't know.
It's hard to explain.
I couldn't really explain it so well to him.
So I was like...
And he was like, that's cool.
Hold on a second.
Let me...
One second, one second.
This last song...
One second, I have to get it up actually.
Where did I save the lyrics to?
Sorry, I didn't get through all my TikToks.
But they're stupid anyway, so it's fine.
My voice is starting...
Not to hurt, but it's starting to feel like it's reaching its limit.
So I'm just like, okay, I will...
I'll call it after this one last song.
I wanted to do at least like 15 songs.
So I hit my...
I was able to watch lots of funny things.
And that was so much fun.
And I was also able to sing some songs.
So that's good too.
Where is this person?
Oh my god.
Okie dokie.
Open, save image.
There we go.
I did not save the lyrics, I just realized.
Okay.
So this last song is a cover.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you so much.
Cover song.
Wait, hold on.
Before I explain it, let me pull up the song.
One second.
There we go, maybe.
Okay, perfect.
Okay, so this is a cover of a song.
I'm sorry if I don't sing it very well.
But a group I like...
Their name is Mosaic Wave.
They recently...
They recently put out a cover album.
And this was one of the songs on it.
I thought it was really cute, so I was going to sing it.
And...
And so...
Yeah.
I'm going to sing it.
And this will be the last song.
You've heard of them?
Yeah, I love Mosaic Wave.
Okay, here I go.
Kimi no yume ga mitsukaranai Sagashini ikou yo Densetsu no machi e Are you tired of working hard?
Maybe it's time for a brand new start Come with me to a legendary place It's name is Akiba's Kanashii kao shinaide Kimi no egao ga tsuki da yo Mattete my lovely friends Himitsu no mahou Egao no mahou
Ageru Let's go!
You'll find the magic Tokimeki no ichi Yume miru machi no fantasy Tsuki no sabaku mo taiyou ni Taiyo sore ga chokora kagayaiteru You can see fairy Doki doki party Sore ga sekai no hajimari Sei no de tobikomu yo Don't be scared, take my hand The thrills they never end Samishigari na chatty bird Michibitte ne wonderland Kimi ni mo mieru Tenshi no yokose The electric fairy Of Akiba Don
'ni nani tereteru no?
Kimi wo motto shiritai na Kimi dake no energy source Motto oshiete yo I'm from the virtual forest I'm not a fairy Believe me, believe me Let's go together Akiba is always waiting here for you Nijiiro no platform Oritateba utsu wa hirogaru Nijigen to sanjigen no kaisetsu Nukete Akibarization Kanyo We are in the world Believe in magic Powerful energy Dare ni demo I do Pepper it Ashita no kodo wo kanjite Kimi no namida Ima kagayakuseru So pure and more awake Kyun-kyun,
screaming!
Sawagashii, we know my story Mori no naka kara kimi e Coming out of your screen With a mysterious fun!
Arita no yo, early bird Tsurete ite, wonderland Kiseki wo yobu Denshi no yousei The Electric Fairy of Akiba If you're feeling lost, you can find yourself here!
There's anime, games, doujinshi, maids, and many, many yabai stories!
What weird lyrics.
Yugure no sekai wo se ni Kyou no kimi ni sayounara Kimi no egao ga Ashita no enerji Is it universe?
Or metaverse?
No!
This world is Akiba!
You find the magic of Kimi no Enerji Yume miru machi no fantasy Keki no sawaku mo Taiyou ni kaechau kudai Ima kagayaiteru You can see fairy Doki doki party Sore ga sekai no hajimari Sei no de tobikomu yo Don't be scared, take my hand Thrills ain't never end
Kimi ni wo mieru Denshi no yousei The Electric Fairy of Akiba I'm an electric fairy of Akiba