Monkey time.
Monkey, monkey, monkey, monkey, monkey, monkey, monkey, monkey, monkey, monkey, monkey, monkey, monkey, monkey, monkey time.
This is the weirdest bunny girl cafe I've ever seen.
You guys, I'm sorry.
Today on my schedule was... bunny garden.
Woah!
Why is Discord sending me stuff even though I have OBS open?
Huh?
Oh, I disabled streamer mode.
Matara!
She said this song appeared on my Spotify.
And it's from Metal Gear Rising.
Yeah!
The game is quiet.
It is quiet.
Because, look at this.
I can't stand listening to the music in this game.
Yeah, the game itself will be louder though.
I was thinking actually maybe just putting on my own music.
Put it at max!
Yeah, I might do my own BGM.
We'll see how, you know, we get.
As we... as we listen to monkey.
If you guys don't know this game, I actually just like started replaying it a couple days ago.
So, oh wait, this might be loud.
Okay, hold on.
I'm gonna turn it down.
That was loud!
I turned it down.
Insta-monkey!
Yippee!
I only started replaying a couple days ago.
And I was like...
I don't know.
I was just feeling it.
Nothing caused it.
I was just like, wow.
Love.
I was like looking through my games and I was like, Oh, Bloons!
I'm just gonna...
I'm just gonna play it again.
Monkey!
Picked it up on the Steam sale.
No, no, I already own this.
I already owned it.
Yeah, so...
It was...
Easy... or not easy.
It was in my library.
I guess easy to play.
Because it was just there.
Yeah.
Happy maid day to my favorite mint maid maid mint!
I'm lucky that my super chat is mint colored.
Thank you, Steel!
Yes, it's...
I thought... I was like, oh my gosh, it's maid day.
Should I have changed to something more maid-like?
But...
But maybe it's okay because...
Maybe it's okay because...
I should be able to play anything that I want today.
How do I turn...
Hold on, I don't want Discord to message me again.
How do I turn the streamer mode back on?
Streamer mode...
I don't know how to do it.
Just gonna exit out.
Just gonna leave.
Quit Discord.
Okay.
We're disconnecting for real.
Settings, app settings, streamer...
Thank you.
W Hammer.
Honk.
Did you guys notice we're on a different side of the screen?
Actually, I actually... actually...
I flipped my monitors.
So now...
You guys are on the right side.
She be moving around.
I know, isn't it so exciting to...
to...
go to a different spot?
Why are you guys a clown emoji?
Why are you guys a clown emoji, huh?
Andricos, thanks for the 10 gifted.
Thank you.
Keep us on our toes.
Absolutely.
What was it?
W Hammer, can you post it again?
I lost it.
Wait, um...
Oh!
It's enabled already.
Never mind.
It's because I reopened or...
I got it.
We're good.
I think it's because I quit.
Settings, app settings, streamer.
Thank you.
Even Bazongas cannot overcome the urge to return to Monkey.
Happy May Day to my favorite maid.
Thank you.
Yeah, I was like...
Maybe I should, uh...
Maybe I should, like...
play whatever I want.
Because it is maid day.
It's my day!
Actually, did you guys know that there's a Minto day?
Um...
Unfortunately, we missed it.
It's, uh...
March 10th.
But it's me.
Like, three in Japanese is three.
And then, in Japanese, ten can be read as tol.
So, Minto.
Mario Day?
That guy's stealing my gig!
No, it's Minto Day.
It's not Mario Day.
Forget about Mario!
Don't listen to him.
Forget about Mario.
You can see I've played a little bit.
Not so much, though.
Oh, should we do the balloon?
But I've already done this one.
Happy Elatement Day.
Thanks!
My Toes Day?
What do you mean by that, Hugo?
I can see the Aurora Borealis from my bedroom.
Wait, actually?
At this time of day...
I mean, at this time...
Wait.
All localized within...
the out...
out...
of your...
bedroom.
Sorry.
My brain is not working very well today.
I think my brain is...
No, I saw some people talking about the Aurora Borealis today, though.
Yeah, you got it.
It's the spirit.
Right?
I can never forget about Mario.
I can't believe Minto is broke after her time in the balloon's war.
Which one should we do?
Which one should we do, you guys?
We can do any of them.
Oh, this one's kind of spooky.
I love spooky.
It has a bonus reward.
Let's do this one.
I just really want to get off this menu.
I'm going to put everything to the same.
Yes?
Why isn't it working?
Why isn't it...
Yes?
Hello?
You have to hold on to...
Yes?
Welcome to membership.
Thank you.
Yes?
Sir.
What?
That is so weird that you like hold on to it.
Yes?
I'm probably gonna play this a little poorly.
I think there's also this monkey.
I have yet to unlock that monkey.
I actually don't even know what this monkey is.
I think when I was playing before, this monkey did not exist.
And March 9th is Miku.
March 9th, thank you!
Fairy baby!
Welcome to membership, thank you!
Thank you, thank you!
I thought you were a god gamer.
I am a...
Why no perfect gameplay?
Actually, Matara and I were recording the Patreon side of the podcast today.
Like almost... not just before this, but...
And I was like, man, I really just want to play Bloons.
We got actually like really into talking about Bloons, even before we were recording.
But I was just like, you know...
One thing that...
When I play...
People will be like...
Oh my gosh.
Sorry, Matara.
I'm leaking...
I'm leaking Patreon content.
When... I was like...
When I play...
And like...
You know...
I don't put my monkeys in the exact way that like...
Bloonslover777 put them in on YouTube for the optimal Bloons gameplay.
People are just like...
No!
Why would you put that monkey there?
It's so funny.
The meta monkey.
But Matara said that she really likes Ninja Monkey.
And...
Boomerang Monkey.
So those are going to be my focuses today.
Because...
I have not played with them at all.
And...
I usually play with Dart Monkey.
Bomb Monkey.
Tack Monkey.
Sniper Monkey.
Sticky Monkey.
Bucket Monkey.
Heli Monkey.
Magic Monkey.
Oh!
No.
Alchemist Monkey.
Sniper Monkey is cool.
Sniper Monkey is so good.
Actually, can you stand on top of this?
Oh, come on.
Come on.
That's a perfect spot.
$500!
Anyway.
Mint Monkey.
Can't wait for him to go...
Seriously?
So basically, everything except for those who...
It's not everything.
There's still a good bit in here.
Oh!
I started using the Gatling Monkey recently.
And the House Monkey.
Monkey Village.
Well, I'm gonna put a Boomerang Monkey.
Can I afford him actually?
Boomerang Monkey is gonna go...
Okay, where should I put Boomerang Monkey?
If you want to unlock that locked monkey, click on the monkey next to the fountain in the main area and click monkey.
There should be a quest floor.
Where is the Maid Monkey?
Right here!
Do you guys want some coffee ASMR?
I got a can of coffee here.
I'm gonna open it.
Hold on.
Here, I'll even turn off my noise gate.
Alright.
This is some...
ASMR...
Can coffee.
My
sleeves are in the way.
Sorry.
Coffee ASMR.
Yummy.
Okay.
Can monkeys hang out on the bridge?
No.
I just don't know how to use a Boomerang Monkey.
I'm gonna put him...
I'm gonna put him right here.
He's not gonna know what to do either.
Actually, he's kind of pricey.
What does he do though?
Why is a Boomerang Monkey so good?
Maybe I put it here.
I love this bit so much.
What are you talking about?
It's not a bit.
High Pierce.
Boomerang is honestly cracked.
Is he?
Rangs aren't cheap.
Okay.
I'm gonna give him...
I'm gonna...
I'm nervous.
People are gonna be like, your monkey placement's so bad.
Oh my gosh.
Whenever I play...
Whenever I play by myself, I'm like, put a monkey anywhere.
Hold on.
Just ignore them?
Okay.
I'm gonna ignore them.
Just like Miss Cat said.
What do they do?
A Pops A Balloons.
Moab Press.
Is that related to the mating press?
Moab Press is goated.
Don't say it.
The Primate Press.
Heavy Kylie Boomerang hits Moab-class Bloons multiple times per throw and sometimes knocks them back a short way along the path.
Okay.
I'm gonna put him right here.
And we're gonna put a little dart monkey right here because I want him to be there.
Moab means mother of all bombs.
It does?
I'm just happy to see you play monkey game again.
Thanks.
I don't think I've ever streamed it here.
Minter monkey placement is so bad.
Yeah.
Cry about it.
Cry about my monkey placement.
Okay.
Yeah.
You might be wondering why did you place him all the way over there?
He's too good.
This monkey was nervous.
This monkey said I won't work if he's too close to me.
He's like this guy is like too cool.
He's nervous about it.
Oh my gosh.
Don't let them through.
I'm gonna upgrade him.
I have the crossbow master.
Oh, I can do the super fan.
Is this one any good?
The super fan?
This monkey business is getting out of business.
Can the monkey business go out of business?
I wonder.
It's not meta, but it sure is funny.
Got it.
Go juggernaut.
Juggernaut.
I was like trying to...
It's slow though, isn't it?
Because this one says it's a slower attacking spike-apult.
So I was like, I love the spikes.
Depends on the amount of dart monkeys.
Ah.
It says converts up to 10 years.
But...
Oh, they gotta be dart monkeys.
Oh.
What if I have a whole field of only dart monkeys?
But I do have crossbow master.
So we'll go for that one.
You guys, I think we're in trouble.
What?
You fool.
Oh, we should give enough money for this guy.
Uh-oh.
Okay.
Come on, boomerang monkey.
Everybody believes in you.
Nice.
Wait, I have an upgrade.
So moab press.
Let's go for that one.
I also want the red hot rangs.
Nice.
The spicy rangs.
You rang.
We're saving up for forest monkey.
Nice.
Oh.
Where should I put him, though?
This path is kind of difficult.
Because it's like...
It feels like it just...
Anywhere I put it...
Anywhere I put a monkey, it doesn't cover enough ground.
You know what I mean?
Hey, mean toe.
I forgot that I had the room on my phone.
Got a big surprise while driving a client to his work.
Oopsie.
Your monkey placement is just fine.
It's just as random and awesome as you are.
Thanks, Zach.
Thank you.
The near the first U-turn.
Right here?
Here.
The spirits of the forest awaken.
Oh, my God.
It's so loud.
It spooked me.
Yes.
Yes?
Yeah.
Attack them.
Yes?
Ha ha.
What's the monkey that says yes?
I think I'll switch to him next time.
Quincy.
Satan.
No.
He's not that bad, right?
It's my first time seeing this game.
Why do they all have Ikemen voice?
This only...
This guy is a wise monkey.
See?
I always read his name wrong though.
O-B-Y-N.
Green foot.
Oh.
That's a lot of blue.
Handle it.
You guys stop...
Wait.
I thought...
Oh.
Target.
Target?
No.
It's Oben.
You guys are typing his name wrong.
My fave is Pat Fusty.
How do you misread it usually?
Oh, yeah.
I said I was also going to use him.
Okay.
I'm going to try some other monkeys.
This guy is...
I also need to level up.
As you see, I have no...
Nothing for him.
My goal is to get to level 100.
I think balloons would win IRL.
That's where you're wrong.
That's where you're so wrong.
I read the game title as Balloon Titty 6.
So, imagine my surprise when I open the stream.
Jonesypoo, you just have...
You...
Um...
You are...
You...
You have a friend.
Rightyaxcoidianslip.
Thanks for the raid.
Hello.
Hello, everybody.
Hihihi.
I was on Lea's stream yesterday, if you haven't watched it.
Oh, oh, hold on.
Let me also unpin this.
Thank you.
Thank you, YouTube.
Raymac, thanks for gifting.
Oh, the sex things for gifting.
Barbie, thanks for gifting.
That's her因為 We got shamed.
Yippee!
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
Definitely go watch the collab on Lia's channel.
So fun.
I'm playing with monkeys right now.
Oh my gosh.
Thank you for... I'm gifted, you guys!
Wait, wait, wait.
AKS, TF2, thank you!
Kenja, thank you!
Rock4Robot, thank you!
Fun Comics, thank you!
And Draco, thank you!
Yep, collab was great.
She judged my fashion.
But in a good way.
Alright.
Monkey, monkey.
I don't know what I'm saving up for.
Let's upgrade this monkey.
Okay, what's the best...
way of the ninja?
What is the best path of the ninja?
E-moment?
Tonight will be the night that I will fall for you!
Over again!
What anime characters are you gonna base your fashion on now?
I don't think I've ever based my fashion on an anime character because...
I don't even know.
Like, I feel like...
so many anime characters...
Oh, no!
Well, okay.
In the past, I always wanted to, like, look like Paradise Kiss.
But...
My son got me into you recently.
This is his favorite game.
Just wanted to thank my son, Pat Fusty.
Why do you hate your son, Rachel?
Ashen, thanks for the gift.
I know a lot of YouTubers have big heads, but I think you have had...
But I think if you had no hair, you could fit three faces on yours.
Why are you so mean to me?
What the hell is this?
I'm asking for help and...
Pat Fusty is a name of honor?
I think Mint's monkey placement sucks!
Yeah?
I'm gonna make you cringe tonight.
Do you play Cookie Clicker?
I do.
You guys, what's the best way of the ninja?
Stop getting off topic.
Who cares if my head is big?
And my neck is extendable.
And my hair is jelly, apparently.
It's not a comment someone made.
It was like a clip of me or something, I think.
And they were like, Wow, Mint's hair is just made of jello.
Or whatever.
I was like...
Yow!
Backseaters, where you at?
IDK, I'm not a ninja.
Five, five, five, go to...
Wait.
Wait, I don't...
Two...
Wait, I don't remember what that means.
Wait, two, two, five?
So, seeking shuriken?
Ten should be first?
Top path.
Oh, that...
Green Ninja said top path.
And Green Ninja is a ninja.
So...
Five, zero, two.
Okay.
Top path is good early.
Unlock!
Wait, so...
Someone said five, zero, two.
So I'll do this one too.
Nice.
What are you doing?
Do your job!
Oh, whoa.
Whoa!
Wowee!
Look at him go!
I'm glad we can...
Four, two, zero.
What did you say?
I said you're a ninja.
It's in your name.
I think I've told this to someone before, but you can change the size of the cursor, etc.
By clicking hotkeys.
Extra large cursor.
Thank you.
You guys wanna see my big finger?
Tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle!
Tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle!
Has the Dr. Stone hair?
No, Dr. Stone has my hair.
Watch
where you're tickling.
Sorry, I didn't know that we were...
You know.
Okay.
Let's just...
Let's do...
Hmm...
Quick shots instead.
Very quick shots.
I feel like in this game, quick is most important, right?
We'll just keep collecting money.
This guy down here...
This is Dart Monkey 7.
He is our backup support.
Gotta go fast.
I finally made a monkey.
You've made a monkey out of me.
You must be swift as the coursing river.
With all the strength of a great typhoon.
With all the speed of a ninja monkey.
Mysterious eyes, the dark side of the moon.
Be monkey.
I was thinking maybe I would do English karaoke next week.
I keep saying I'm not going to do karaoke with my voice stressed.
But also, so fun.
I haven't done English karaoke.
Is your voice okay?
I think so.
I think the hardest part is like when I have to record the podcast and also like talk for a long time like on stream and everything that was also part of today I was like, I don't think I really want to talk so much in like reading a visual novel.
So, please sing Bee Monkey version of the song.
Any chance of karaoke of the man who sold the world?
I'd have to learn it, but I can do it.
I graduated college today.
Thanks for helping me get through finals.
Congrats Red Cross!
Congrats!
Oh my gosh!
You did it!
The man who sold the world.
The good G word.
Yeah.
Yes!
Well with this I can just sit and back and kind of let the monkeys do the work.
Yeah.
Send out, send out your stuff.
Oh wow, they're getting really fast.
Oh, we have so much money.
Okay.
This might be a little, you know, like premature, but I think we got to start getting a farm.
Wait, where can I even put a farm in this map?
Oh my gosh.
A green day karaoke.
A Metal Gear Rising karaoke.
I am so nervous about that though because like, I feel, I feel, oh yes, this one's good.
Nice.
I don't, I just don't feel like I'll sing them good, but I guess it's, you know, I don't have to sing it well.
I can just sing it for fun, right?
I thought this is a bunny garden stream.
I'm so sorry.
I just, I only had monkey on the brain.
I'm really, really sorry.
I'm really sorry that I'm only thinking about monkey.
Oh no!
Uh oh, uh oh.
I thought we were doomed.
Get a boat, you buffoon.
You're so right!
You're so right, actually.
Boat monkey!
Ahoy!
What's the, oh, um, it is, uh, this monkey that can turn them into gold.
This monkey will turn our lead balloons into gold.
I kind of want him to do that.
Let's put him here.
Oh no, I have to upgrade it.
Okay, we'll get him.
I'll get enough money.
I only have monkey on the brain, so nothing changed.
The more things change, sometimes the more they stay the same.
Right?
Happy May Day.
Happy May Day!
I really want...
Look at this, we have lead and spikes.
Double shot.
Wow, balloon jutsu!
Do you guys ever wonder why we are on the right side of the screen now?
Oh wait, I told you.
Never mind.
Sorry.
Actually there is another reason.
Okay, I'm just really excited.
Okay?
More people joined, you can say again.
There's another reason that you guys are on the right side of the screen now instead of the left side of the screen.
I asked earlier... because usually I have my chat settings on the right side.
And... and... not chat settings.
I don't know why I said settings.
My chat on the right side... or left side and me on the left side too.
But I moved my monitors.
So I moved all of us over to the right side.
Can I just show you guys?
Can I show you?
Actually, it's May Day.
So I'm gonna show you guys, okay?
It's May Day.
It's May Day!
May Day!
Oh!
I'm drowning!
May Day!
The
maid cafe may have gotten an upgrade!
Isn't it so cute?
I say upgrade even though there's like some cobwebs and some dead plants in here.
It's okay.
I'm working on it.
Isn't it so cute?
Yeah!
And then we have some patrons in the cafe.
Yes.
Excuse me!
You up there!
Please get back to your seat.
You're causing a disturbance.
Hold on.
I'll show you guys.
With my monkey music in the background.
Okay.
Hold on.
Sorry.
I'm gonna get rid of the chat real quick.
Oh, wait.
Okay.
Hold on.
I'll zoom in.
You didn't see anything.
There we go.
Okay.
Hold on.
I'm a little scuffed right now.
Okay.
There we go.
See, you got some ghosts here.
Look at them.
They're just...
I think they're...
I think this guy is...
He's having like a first date or something.
He looks really nervous.
You got this guy singing back there.
He's so cute.
Yeah.
He's like...
La-la-la.
La-la-la-la-la.
And the busting sign, of course, is still there.
Of course.
It must always be there.
My play button!
Because I'm a real YouTuber.
I'm a real YouTuber.
So I have my play button in the background.
These guys are enjoying a hot cup of joe.
Yeah.
This guy is my favorite over here.
Just like chilling back there.
He's like...
And a little counter here.
Oh, and the stage.
Yeah.
That's it.
That's it!
Where did I go?
Oh, I'm down here.
Isn't it so cute?
So, welcome to the new maid cafe!
Why are we on the menu?
Because you're a snack.
Snack!
Get off the stage!
I could be... I could be over there.
Welcome
back!
Miss!
Why is the chat going so fast?
What's happening?
Oh.
Today is maid day!
So I'm going to play monkey!
Oh, wait!
My favorite song!
Monkey!
Ooh!
It's time for monkey!
Monkey time!
Break it down!
Why am I so tiny?
Thank you!
I want this as my ringtone.
Okay, let's get back to the monkey business now.
Sorry, monkeys.
Oh, there goes the chat.
It's zooming.
Do I
know any Funky Monkey Babies next?
I do!
I do know Funky Monkey Babies.
Oh, this one.
I usually do this one.
Incredible performance?
It mesmerized me.
New Rainforest Cafe, looking good.
Yeah, I hope you guys like it.
I hope you guys like it.
Oh, wait.
So this one, and then maybe Faster Throw.
MOAB, Blue Blimps stand for... Oh!
Thanks to Chonky!
ZOMG stands for Zeppelin of Mighty...
Gargantuaness.
DDT!
I've never seen the B.A.D.
though.
Big Airship of Doom.
I don't think so, at least.
Definitely seen the DDTs.
It's always like, what?
Stage 93 that gets me?
When do the B.A.D.s come in?
B.A.D.s at round 100.
Oh!
What do you mean a permit for those curtains?
Bionic Boomerang.
I'll do the faster one.
Let's just start getting some... some cannons.
Don't let the health inspection see that cafe.
It's like, literally...
It's like, don't worry about it.
You don't even need to worry about it at all.
Cause... cause... it's like abandoned.
There's cobwebs, you guys.
The curtains are so close to the candles.
No,
they're not!
What the...
No, they're not!
There's only one candle!
And it's... it's... it's this one!
But the curtains aren't even any close to it!
This one right here that I'm pointing to.
It's the only candle.
Back off my cafe.
Okay.
Back!
You know what?
You don't deserve to be served here.
You come into my cafe first day in.
And you... complain?
Oh, my curtains!
My curtains are too close to the candle!
Oh, my food!
Oh no!
My food is made of... it has ectoplasm!
Oh, the curtain is on fire!
Oh, no!
The cafe is on fire!
I'm dead!
Complaints!
You know what?
Go take it up... with... the manager.
The
manager.
It's me.
DJ!
Welcome to the membership.
Thank you!
I'm the manager here.
Can I have a... alarm?
Okay.
Back to Monkey.
Oh!
Uh-oh.
I became too small.
There we go.
Okay.
Mint reaction corner.
Is that what you want?
Okay, guys.
Hey, guys.
Today we're playing Monkey.
Welcome back to Monkey.
Let's play Monkey game.
Live Mint reaction.
It's like one of those Japanese TV shows.
You can't like see so much of the... right down here though.
Are you really okay with that?
Oh!
Handle it!
Sweet.
We handled it.
Oh yeah.
I keep forgetting to upgrade this guy too.
I was trying to make him rich.
I'll give him this one too.
Greetings, Minto.
Long time donator and first time viewer patron of the maid cafe.
I was burned by the molten chocolate dripping from this curtain.
Can I get a discount on my meal as compensation?
I'm really sorry but you signed the waiver when you came in.
That says...
I don't mind.
Keep being burnt by the curtains.
The molten chocolate is part of the cafe experience.
Drunk.
See us.
Lest...
Lest to my ose.
Go!
Don't drink and super chat.
Yeah, there's a waiver.
There's a waiver.
Monkey!
Monkey, monkey, monkey, monk.
This is the health inspector.
Oh my gosh.
You're binary ghost.
So you're actually the health inspector.
There have been reports of ectoplasm in the kitchen.
That's a violation.
Everybody scatter!
Scatter!
You guys, I'm lost.
I don't know where I am.
I'm lost.
It's really dark here.
Where am I?
You guys, I'm trying to...
Wait, wait.
I'm lost.
Hold on.
Let me see if there's like a...
Like a reset.
Hold on.
I'm lost.
This isn't...
This isn't supposed to be funny.
This isn't a bit.
I'm lost for real.
I can't come back.
I can't come...
I'm clicking and dragging but I don't know where I am.
I'm lost.
I'm...
Oh, my God.
I don't know.
I thought I came in.
No.
I'm...
I'm lost in VTube Studio.
I don't know where I am.
Okay, guys.
There's only one thing that I can do here.
Oh, my God.
Hold on.
Oh, I think...
Okay, hold on.
I have to recreate myself.
I think using props...
Okay, hold on.
Oh no!
Wait, I actually don't know where I am!
Okay, I'm gonna be Hoshino today.
Wait, how do I get it above?
Wait.
Oh no, wait!
No, I can't move Hoshino now!
Oh my god, hold on.
No!
Okay, hold on.
Start over, redo, redo.
Where am I?
You guys, this is...
Okay, I'm gonna...
I don't...
Use bit 1.0?
I don't have bit 1.0!
Actually, okay, I do have this.
But I'm not sure how it will be.
So I'm kinda nervous.
Okay, hold on.
Oh no!
No!
Um...
You guys, it's...
It's Goofy's smile.
It's...
It's the one with...
The big-ass smile.
I'm so glad we played balloons today.
Look
at myself!
I can't...
I can't even...
Okay, anyway.
Let's balloon.
Wow, they just keep coming.
She's really into it.
I'm having a good time.
Oh, hold on.
Actually, let me try something.
F**k!
It worked!
Yippee!
Your other flew out the window.
Oh my goodness gracious.
That was a silly bit of a...
A little bit.
I'm gonna start bringing in SniperMonkey.
He's my favorite guy right here.
SniperMonkey is my favorite guy right here.
What's the best place to put him though?
Hmm...
Maybe here covers...
No...
Up here.
Over here.
No...
Up here.
Sniper's a good job mate.
Welcome back.
It's been like 10,000 years.
I can't believe I got lost.
Bottom right might be better.
Oh, he's gone.
Wait, hold on.
Bottom right.
No...
It's because of the house.
I'm on top of the house though.
Hmm...
Shouldn't have gone towards the light.
Where's the dart monkey?
This one?
Yeah, I think you're right.
I think you're right.
We missed behind the car, but I think it'll be okay.
We'll put some other guys over here eventually.
I'm also gonna add...
Okay, hold on.
How do I want to do this?
Because I do want to put a village.
Oh my goodness.
The village takes up so much space.
3D balloons game would be crazy.
Didn't you...
Didn't know you enjoyed these monkeys that much.
Just look at that smile.
I'm a monkey fiend!
I love balloons!
Gosh, this one's really hard to fit in though.
And click on the car and remove it.
Actually, you know what?
We have enough money to get rid of it.
You just ran my monkey over!
Oh my god.
Oh my gosh.
Stonks, stonks, stonks, stonks!
And uh, wait.
That's not who I wanted to click on.
You.
No, we're waiting for the balloon jutsu.
Stonks, stonks, stonks!
More money!
Um...
Okay, I'm gonna put him...
here.
I think maybe I will put a little town there.
Let's go for the Moab...
Assassin.
Okay.
Oh!
You hear that money?
Baby!
Awesome!
Your super silly smile or model reminds me of honey and clover.
Man, you're so rich.
I also like...
I'm bad about like...
I'm like, what if I want to save up, you know?
I want him to get to 21.
I gotta save up.
Well, right now, we don't need to do any more spending.
I think we're doing okay.
Extra
money!
Is it really making that much money?
I can't tell.
Truly, I can't tell.
Oh, and let's upgrade you.
Um...
We'll go...
We'll go with the Moab meme.
Nice gift!
Binary goals!
Thanks for the 10 gifts!
For Fox's sake!
Thanks for the 5 gifts!
Thank you!
Hey!
Oh my god.
Get him!
So
fast, so easily!
Sniper monkey!
You know what?
I'm gonna put another sniper monkey and I'm gonna make him shoot faster.
Fast sniper monkey.
Yeah...
Oh!
There we go.
Upgrade the bow.
I don't have any more...
I don't have any more that I can upgrade.
I'm gonna put another boat though.
We'll put another boat.
Here.
Wait, can I put another boat right here?
No.
I think I might... I can put one there.
Three boats!
Machine gun sniper monkey.
He's cracked!
That's why I like the sniper monkey so much.
Um...
What was I...
Oh!
I realized I don't hear...
Um...
Streamlabs for some reason.
I'm so sorry you guys.
I might have to turn them up.
Um...
I'm the lone wisp at the corner vibing.
Don't worry.
Ghost fire from ghost candles doesn't burn.
Just like how ghosts can't hurt you.
Bunny garden got a weird update.
This is THE update.
This is optimal bunnies!
See?
You see booba so much, you return to monkey.
Yippee!
Knowledge point.
Return to monkey.
Monkey, monkey, monkey.
Oh!
Nice.
Probably should do some more boomerang monkeys.
Oh wait!
Um...
I've been...
Okay, what's the best monkey... what's the best route for the... for the boats because monkey is just a superior bunny.
Exactly, Road!
You get it!
Top route.
Top path.
Oh no!
Wait!
I wanted to get that one too!
It's okay.
We can at least start upgrading some of these guys.
I'm feeling insulted by that.
Sorry.
Actually there's quite a few rabbits in there I think.
Where's the monkey girl cafe?
Whoa!
Why was it stuck?
Haha!
I'm waiting.
Ooh!
He's waiting.
Oh!
Wait!
Whoa!
Am I gonna be okay?
Get it!
Why was it taking you so long?
Buccaneer is one of the best towers I am on.
But each path has its uses.
This is the buccaneer?
Oh wait.
Oh!
Like...
I forgot.
I called just a boat.
I think we might be okay.
The camel can only shoot sniper with goggles.
Yeah!
I know.
But he had the goggles.
He just wasn't doing anything.
But it's okay.
We are good to go.
Ah!
It attacks super duper fast!
Um!
But I really want the extra money!
But it's only one guy.
Okay, I'll get the destroyer.
It's only one guy that will be generating the money.
For now.
I don't know what I have that is stopping the moabs.
But it's kind of awesome.
Is it you?
Um!
Is anyone going to attack it?
Oh!
The sniper!
He...
Okay.
So funny.
Alright.
What do I do?
Long range...
Oh!
Camo balloons!
Hmm... Middle path on the destroyer.
Well, I was going to do one middle and one bottom.
So...
Whoa!
Nice!
Oh!
Yeah!
I forgot that I need to do this one too.
Um!
The frag bombs.
Should...
Should I do a frag or should I do bigger bombs?
Two layers.
Pop more balloons.
Maybe the bottom.
That monkey placement just works.
Can't let any balloon go through if all the monkeys at the front start them.
Haha!
Oh!
Stop though.
Yeah.
Frag.
Nice!
There it is.
It's coming, you guys.
Don't worry.
It's going to get you.
Oh!
It'll... It'll show up eventually.
Maybe.
Yippee!
Alright.
Let's try and get to level 100.
100.
I've seen somewhere like the whole...
The whole thing is just DDTs.
And I'm like, how much...
How much crazier can they get?
I think we'll be okay on the next one even.
But if not...
Look at that.
Oh my god.
Thank you!
Thank you for the rifting gifts!
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
Let's see...
I always feel bad when people gifts...
Like, you know...
I kind of mentioned it when I first started memberships that I kind of priced it lower because my focus is on the podcast.
And I know the podcast is not forever.
And once the podcast ends...
I'll be able to do more membership stuff.
But...
And I won't change the price.
Oh, we're okay.
Oh, round 63 is kind of crazy.
Oh!
Spike turrets can be good on those curves.
I was just...
I was just thinking about putting this one.
I do not have...
Like, you're talking about this thing, right?
Melted Ice Cures!
Welcome to the Memphis show!
Trees...
I know, I do need to plant some.
But I'm trying to find a good place to plant it.
Right there!
It's perfect, actually.
Um...
Let's do...
Let's just...
Nice!
Alright, 21...
Uh...
Yeah...
32... 14...
Okay, we can probably get the Elite Defender.
Oh, my dart monkey is down here!
It's completely...
Completely nothing!
We'll just get him too.
Oh!
Nice!
He's helping.
He was!
He was helping.
He was.
Stupid shark!
Thank you for the 20!
Yeah, at least...
There's the emote.
If I'm working on anything, I'll try and post little preview stuff.
But...
Um...
Right now, I have like...
Nothing that is...
That I can...
Show.
Handle it!
Okay, now that we're here...
Oh my god, it can only cover these four?
If only... Why can't he go right there?
Oh...
Why?
Why are you so big?
Village thing.
Oh, range upgrade!
You are so right.
So bigger...
Actually, what I do is...
I do this path.
But...
Yeah...
You know what?
I will do this.
Do I want to do the bureau?
Intelligence bureau?
Or do I want to...
Chat is always right.
I don't know about that.
But I already have these one...
No, never mind.
I have this one as the bottom.
Oh, I should have...
I forgot that I was gonna put the thing here.
I should have done this one as the middle also.
Oh well, it's okay.
Chat is kinda mostly sorta right.
Middle path for DDT.
This one!
Let's add another boat, baby.
We'll put you right here.
We'll just stack them all up.
Actually, can I even...
I can't.
But that's okay.
Oh wait.
Maybe the faster shooting up top.
You and your boatsmen.
Getting a little crowded in there.
Not that!
The monkey village.
Oh my god, Samson, stop yelling at me!
Oh, this one for DDT.
Oops.
No, you're okay.
I'm kidding.
Don't worry.
Everyone yell at her.
No, stop yelling at me!
I'm sensitive today, you guys.
I'm sensitive.
This is like a classic example of miscommunication.
Here I was like, Okay, another boat!
I was just like, Okay!
Oh, sorry.
I clicked out of the video.
The game.
DDT is 90+.
Are you sure?
I'm pretty sure there's at least one before, right?
Did I miss bunny garden?
I'm confused.
I'm sorry, Blake.
I switched bunny garden today to balloons because I didn't...
I wasn't...
I was only thinking of balloons.
Oh.
But this one allows more range and pierce and projectile speed.
It just seems like the whammy.
But what I can do is I can put another one here.
I can put another one here.
We'll go with this one.
We'll go with the bureau.
Big brain.
I know.
And then it can affect any monkeys down here.
Bigger radius.
Okay.
Handle it!
Oh my god, handle it!
Are balloons the weapon to surpass Metal Gear?
Nah, I ain't afraid of no balloons.
I ain't afraid of no balloons.
Oh wait, I was meant to do this one.
Bust.
If you want a really good DDT, unlock preemptive strike on the sub.
Have it see camo with a village and you're good to go.
Ah!
Thanks, Ben.
I'm gonna try.
I actually, I don't think I've unlocked anything on the sub, so...
Oh no, that's untrue.
That's untrue.
I've unlocked some stuff.
Wait, so pre... what was it?
Oh, preemptive strike.
Oof.
We're pretty far from that.
But...
Plant it near the village.
Here.
I'm gonna do two of them.
Okay.
I can't upgrade it just yet, but...
Middle path is crazy strong.
Is it?
Okay.
This is why I have you guys here!
Thanks, guys!
I don't really need that there, but whatever.
Um...
Okay.
600.
Ooh.
It might be tough.
I'm not gonna lie.
It might be tough to get this before...
Is it loud?
Let me...
Be honest with me.
Is it loud?
Top path for a bow is really good.
We're working on it!
We're working on it.
It's fine?
Okay.
Thank you, guys.
You guys are so cute.
Sweet.
Okay.
Make it louder.
Hopefully, we get... Let's see.
We're only at 3000.
But that's okay.
We're working on it.
Even if we don't have it for this...
For this one, we can have it for future stuff, right?
Louder!
Nice.
I'm gonna try and get, um...
This monkey to the crossbow master.
Gonna try and get him to crossbow...
Oh, wait!
I forgot I...
I added this guy.
Wait.
Where did he go?
Where's the monkey that just...
Oh!
My bananas were gonna go rotten!
Or... Oh, wait.
I think actually I should go for...
The elite defender.
I think.
Probably.
Go!
Feel nature's wrath.
Okay, 75.
Bananas have gone bad.
No, they're still good.
They're just a little brown.
Nothing wrong with that.
Whoa!
That was so close, right?
Woof!
Easy peasy.
She's gonna die.
What'd you say, gamer random?
Huh?
What'd you say?
I was gonna die?
Huh?
What'd you say?
I was gonna die?
Huh?
What'd you say?
I was gonna die?
Huh?
I think...
No, I know that I always...
Usually die at 93.
No, unbeliever.
I wish though I could upgrade these guys.
Twin gun.
Actually...
Long range targeting...
Wait, which one of...
Oh no, yeah, I'm going for the middle.
Hmm...
What's the bottom path?
Oh, double attack speed.
Enhances attack speed of other weapons.
Intel for subs is huge?
Okay, well I have that unlocked, so...
I figure it's probably better to...
Oh wait, I didn't get this one.
Oh my gosh, my bad.
Oops, too many boats and stuff here.
I have too many boats.
Can't see everything.
Can't see anything.
Well guys, this might be it.
This might be it.
If it is...
I guess we'll see.
Add another dart monkey.
Dart monkey!
Yeah!
Maybe I can spike bolt him.
Spike...
Spike bolt my monkey.
We'll make him faster.
Because he's slow.
Go monkey, go!
We'll just do a couple of those.
We're still alive, baby!
It helps that we have a bunch of guys that are able to...
see camo balloons.
Triumphant!
If you set the target of the spike path to the last, you will throw all the way down the path.
That is a great idea.
That is actually a really good idea.
Yes, yes, yes!
Yes,
yes, yes!
But you're already dead.
You're so right!
I'm such a...
I'm such a hypocrite saying that we're alive, aren't I?
I mean, you guys are alive.
I'm the dead one.
You know, just ghost things.
Ghost things.
I think I can make the next one.
I might regret saying that, but...
Holy cow!
Holy moly!
Rise!
Oh my god!
Yow!
Look at the fetish of the IQ!
Rise!
Wow!
Couldn't even get to the trees!
Easy peasy.
Just like that.
I am going to add a helicopter monkey in here though.
And I'm going to...
I want to buy a village.
Oops!
Where did he go?
But I don't think I can...
Hmm...
Village for the snipers.
That is true too.
Down here.
I'm going to put it here.
Okay, so here's the plan.
Put one here, so when I fill out this area...
It reaches with the range.
And then we can have one down here.
That will help any monkeys over here.
So we'll just kind of put this one...
Right on the edge!
Right there.
And...
Should we do it?
Well, we have this one.
Oh wait!
Oh my gosh!
I have this one.
That's the...
Oh, this one!
Yeah!
I was going to do that earlier!
I completely forgot!
Oh my gosh!
Keith!
Thanks for the five gifted!
Money, money!
Middle path village for camo and...
Yeah, you're right.
You're right.
And we can do the bigger radius.
Oops, no jungle.
There we go.
Oh, the Z-O-M-G!
Z-O-M-G!
Sorry, I'm American.
Oh my gosh, so easy.
Oh my
gosh, so easy.
Snipers already see camo.
I think...
This one does not.
This one...
This guy doesn't.
Now he does because of here.
This guy did, so it was kind of like whatever.
But this guy who's super fast did not, so it's okay.
Umm...
I think this guy also already did.
Oh yeah, he did.
But that's okay!
It's okay, we're going to have monkeys down here that aren't able to see camo.
So it's okay.
Do you think we'll ever do a few games with the wisps?
We can even make a team clan and have weekly challenges.
Like...
Like this game?
Like bloons game?
Can you make teams in bloons?
Is there multi...
This game has a clan system.
Really?
Oh then hell yeah!
Let's do it!
Co-op bloons!
Can you imagine if like two people are trying to play bloons at the same time and I like put something down and like whoever I'm playing with immediately sells it and is just like STOP IT!
They sell it and like put another thing in its place trying to optimize the map and I'm just like la la la Oh!
I shouldn't have...
I didn't realize it was still there.
Go monkeys go!
Crazy!
Have you done a boss battle yet?
In bloons?
I have not.
I am going to put this one here.
I actually have not used the spike factory at all.
And so I do want to trade it a little bit if I can.
Um, magic monkey.
I also want to...
I barely used him.
Um, I want to get the necromancer.
The necromancer route.
So we are going to put him like right here.
He is just kind of like a random monkey but he can start summoning or should I put him down here?
For like extra defense down here.
Fire wizard is cracked.
I usually pick fire wizard but it was Matara who was just like I love necromancer monkey so I kind of wanted to use it.
Spike 100 killer with middle path.
Okay.
We will focus on the middle path.
What is this one anyway?
Oh, the spike storm.
Oh, it's crazy.
It is.
Necro is more cracked.
I only remember playing balloons during school.
What's the current lore on why these monkeys hate balloons?
I don't... Is there a lore?
I have no idea.
Back end defense.
Yeah.
That's what I was thinking.
And we get the help of the...
of the... I do want him to be able to like fight more so that he can get more experience but it's okay.
Oh, he's fighting!
He's fighting!
Look at him go!
Go monkey!
Go!
Little monkey!
Thanks to the Super Chatrix!
Thank you!
Ow!
It's okay.
Nature prevails.
I'm wondering if I should have a glue monkey.
Sticky monkey.
Hmm...
Just slow down anybody.
Bottom path for sticky monkey.
Balloon solver is crazy.
Balloon's a problem?
Here's the solution.
I can't unlock it yet though.
I'm close to the super glue.
Bottom path is good late game.
Hmm...
Let's get a glue monkey.
We'll get him...
We'll put him kind of close to the front so we can start slowing people down.
I'm just gonna put him right on top of there.
And we're gonna give him...
We're gonna do the bottom path for you.
I usually do bottom path and then two up top.
0-2-5 glue is good especially since you have camo.
Like this one.
Okay.
0-2-5.
Start slowing those bloons down.
I feel like that already made a ton of difference.
Holy cow.
Oh wait.
Maybe I should've... You know what?
Whatever.
Are you doing anything?
Are you working?
It's 22.
Yeah!
Surprise!
Can you like do something though?
Upgrade some towers.
I think for the most part I've upgraded anything that I can.
Unless I'm...
No, we're doing middle path here.
Why is the sub taking so long to unlock anything?
Like the sub is taking so long to get any experience.
But they're killing a...
Look at the... Oh wait that's the boat.
What's the name of the monkey on the bottom right?
Is that a new monkey?
I haven't played bloons in a while.
Less XP passed post stage 60.
Oh...
I didn't realize... Oh I think actually I was told that before and I just completely forgot.
I'm gonna place a helicopter down here.
Um...
This might be not the best placement right here.
But it's also kind of hard to place on this map and I want him cause...
Oh wait but he'll also get to attack any type of bloon.
So...
Can you destroy the house?
You can't.
Oh!
Tickle tickle.
Oh he's good can move it wherever.
Yeah so usually what I do with the helicopter is I do...
Um... I do 2, 5.
But...
No I'm sorry.
The 2 up here.
Wait...
I do 2, 0, 5.
Well 4.
In my case.
But...
2, 0, 5 is fine.
Even if I...
So... But if I put it here I'll be able to...
To... Um... Actually I might be able to put it right here.
Oh come on.
There is space there.
Maybe down here then.
Over here.
On the rock.
Maybe right here then.
Ah...
Put it next to the snipers.
Okay yeah.
I think... I think it'd be best to have the power up from the...
2...
5.
Okay.
Yeah!
Handle it!
Batara!
What the heck!
So easy!
Handle it!
Go monkeys!
Go!
We don't have the DDTs yet.
So...
Oh my gosh!
I'm watching from bed.
You better be doing the stuff that...
You were supposed to be doing missy.
You better be doing that stuff.
She's developing a new meta.
You'd be homeless if you had...
Wait.
If this had an MGS collab transaction.
Why are you gonna say it like that?
I wouldn't... I didn't...
I didn't become homeless when Fortnite had Metal Gear, huh?
So...
I think I'm pretty good.
I think I'm okay.
I think I can handle myself.
As... as...
OBGYN would say.
Handle it!
Holy cow!
Oh
my god!
Our monkeys!
Oh no.
I was like...
Oh good!
We have enough!
No.
I need the top.
Oh my gosh!
I need so much more for the top!
Oh!
It's like... really tempting to purchase the other upgrades when you see that they're green and all.
I mean...
Like this one.
Oh!
Heat tips...
Okay.
We're gonna upload...
Upload?
We're gonna upgrade the MOAB Eliminator next.
What would the adjective for a monkey be?
Like Psycho Mantis or Sniper Wolf?
Monkey Monkey.
Wizard?
Where's my wizard?
It's so hard to see where anybody is.
He's also pretty...
Oh wait.
No.
Wizard.
Oh!
Him!
No.
He's like got nothing.
My wizard's got nothing.
He's so small.
Manic Monkey.
Actually that sounds...
That actually sounds like it could be real.
Manic Monkey.
Who's that monkey?
Monkey Monkey.
Oh wait.
Or maybe...
Maybe I should do the Sniper Monkey.
Maybe I should make my Sniper Monkey instead of you.
MOABs are immobilized for longer and take extra damage from all the other attacks.
You can name your monkeys with them.
A.K.A.
Sniper Wolf.
I can?
No I can't.
No I
can't.
Change Sniper to Strong.
I usually do.
Thank you.
Handle it!
Oh they're fast.
Oh they're fast and they're furious.
They're fast and they're furious.
Nature prevails everybody.
You need to buy the ability to name them from the shop.
Really?
That's crazy.
I'm coming up on the faded round soon.
We're getting close to DDTs.
I know.
I'm scared.
First DDT check.
Oh gosh.
That's why I'm thinking I should...
Massive damage to MOABs and assassinate ability deals 6x damage with a short cooldown.
Take extra damage from all the other attacks.
I think I'm going to save up for the Sniper Monkey.
Okay.
Handle it!
No way!
Thank you.
I always forget.
I do usually change these but I think I'm going to I think I'm just silly because I...
Because, you know.
Just silly things.
I must resist!
That was...
That was not so great.
That was a little rough.
I think.
No!
Don't leave!
But...
Big Sniper Monkey.
He's slow though.
I wonder if it's okay.
But he's so slow.
Handle it!
ZOMG!
Rise!
It's the next round that I'm really worried about, you guys.
Uh oh.
Wait.
Oh no.
We're about to lose.
Okay.
It's the next round that I'm worried about.
Hmm...
I don't think I have so much money that I can like...
Also, I should just start unlocking these because I have nothing else to unlock here.
The Dreaded 93.
Okay.
Both snipers target strong, so we're okay.
Pursuit...
Spike Factory is just down here doing his thing.
Oh...
Gosh...
You got this unironically?
You think so?
Okay.
I just always die at 93, so...
We'll see.
DDT!
EFT!
Oh!
Handle it!
Okay.
Oh my god!
Let's go!
Wow!
Easy.
Easy peasy.
I love balloons!
Oh my gosh.
Is there anything else we should add in?
I was thinking...
No!
We're close.
Um...
Um... No!
We'll save up.
Um...
Hmm... I'm trying to...
That was a good place for Gatlin Monkey.
Hmm...
Add a glue monkey?
Okay.
If you guys think I need another glue...
Where is he?
Oh, glue monkey.
Like right here.
Right next to other glue monkey.
Um...
Should I just do the same?
Well, this one...
Maybe I do the corrosive on this one, right?
Or should I just do the same route?
You can make that one aggressive.
With the balloon liquefier.
Alchemist's buff...
Alchemist's buff snipers?
Glue does not stack with other glues.
It doesn't?
But maybe then we do the corrosive.
So if he gets... If he slows them down...
He starts...
So we'll do the corrosive.
Um...
Then we'll do more.
He gets more of them.
Alchemists are really good.
Oh, shoot.
Okay.
I'm gonna...
Alchemist monkey down here.
This is the alchemist, right?
Am I on... Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
Right there, baby.
How does he buff them?
Powerful monster.
Top path.
Louse...
Oh, throws a helpful potion that nearby monkeys...
Pop lead balloons and do extra damage to ceramic...
Oh!
Throws special brew to nearby monkeys...
Giving them extra damage range...
Well, range, whatever.
Because it's, you know, snipers, but...
Hmm...
Okay.
Let's try it.
And then maybe the pool.
For, like, extra damage down here.
Top alch is mega OP.
Really?
Oh...
We can try another round.
Yeah!
Pool is useless?
Really?
Okay.
I'm trusting you guys.
I'm, like, trying not to rely on you guys too much, but also take your advice.
I don't want to seem like I'm just, uh...
Ah!
Oh my god.
Holy cow!
It's okay.
Maybe.
Oh, maybe it's not okay.
Oh, no!
No, it's okay!
Yeah, I don't think the MOAB glue is working!
Uh-oh.
I think...
That was close.
The glue liquefied is overriding the MOAB glue.
Yeah.
Uh-oh.
I think I just wasted a bunch of money.
Wait, what's going on here?
Why is it bubbly?
Why is it bubbling like that?
Oh, because he gave me a potion!
That's so cute!
Sell useless stuff?
Oh, no one's useless to me.
I wish I could move them instead of just selling them, you know?
Okay, goodbye.
Goodbye, balloon liquefier.
Sorry, I shouldn't have put you there.
I shouldn't have put you there!
Oh,
that scratch is a good itch.
Oh, this one I can unlock!
Should I...
Wait, I might just be able to put that on him.
Wait, what does this do, actually?
Glue so strong it temporarily immobilizes all affected blooms.
Oh, let's go!
You know what?
Let's just get it.
How much is it?
24 ,000!
We can do it.
Live!
Oh,
my God!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my bananas!
My
God!
You said not even close, but to me, that was pretty close!
That felt pretty close to me.
I love... I love...
Heli... Heli monkey is so good.
Heli monkey is awesome.
What is this one?
Upgraded weapons also automatically cause three more monkeys.
Permanently!
98 is scary?
Okay.
97...
Everything above 90 is a pain, apparently.
Here's the second VTuber I've seen excitedly shout, I love bloons!
Thanks, Rico!
Don't know to test...
Don't know to test to say minto estinco on Fridays.
I don't know why I can't hear...
I mean, the game is kind of loud, but...
Butt was not clenched.
My butt was kind of clenched.
I don't know why I can't... why I'm not hearing the streamlabs.
But I am reading them, so...
Lampy!
Welcome to Mambusha Bank!
Thank you so much!
One tier 5 to survive round 100.
I have two!
Well, tier 5 what?
There's no notice.
At all?
None at all.
That's weird.
That's very strange.
How long is the wait for a party at one of your cafes?
Um, don't worry about it.
Orange sniper.
This guy?
On first?
I think he might actually need to be first because he's so fast.
And if people are down here you need to like go for them, you know?
Oh!
This one we can now pay for, right?
We went for the... we're going for this one, right?
Yeah.
This is a test of the emergency super chat system.
It's not super chats with the issue.
Hmm.
What kind of a game is this?
It's a tower defense game.
Drums!
Oh my gosh, thank you!
Holy cow!
I think this one is all...
Yeah, it's good for now.
Oh my gosh, thank you!
I can't believe I forgot to do that.
Super glue.
I'm trying to think if I should add something else.
Maybe another ship.
Maybe another boat because they have so much range.
Or a sub down here.
Like right here.
More helicopters?
Nah.
Okay.
Boat on lower.
Okay, so we'll do the boat instead.
Down here.
And place them.
There we go.
Nice and cozy.
What did I do for these guys?
No, not you.
So it's 5-2, right?
5-2?
And then more glue is what people are requesting.
I can do more glue.
Especially because we got our other guy before.
Maybe we put him like...
Wait.
We can get the buffs here.
Maybe like here.
Or over here.
Actually over here might be better.
Oh my gosh, please stop spamming.
I'm definitely not going to add an ice monkey if you continue to spam.
Thank you.
Oh my gosh.
Holy cow.
How?
Sorry, I'm trying to figure out where to place this guy.
Maybe actually here would be better.
Because it's...
Because it'll hit them for down here.
Okay.
And we're going to glue soak.
And we're going to glob.
Actually...
Yeah.
We're going to glob it up.
Okay.
Attempt.
Handle it.
Oh my gosh.
Please.
Handle it.
Rise.
Okay.
I guess I could have been worse.
Why does Mindy hate balloons so much?
Balloons?
It's balloons.
Not bad.
It could be worse.
They still got what down here about.
So...
What's in?
Welcome to membership.
Thank you.
And GK, Siren, welcome to membership.
Monkey.
Ducky, welcome to membership.
Thank you guys.
Thank you so much.
Can I slow them down more?
For what?
Ice?
Oh my gosh.
Please, pancake.
Please.
I don't even have my guys upgraded.
I don't think they'll do much.
Okay.
I think before I mentioned adding another helicopter.
I wish I could put them right in there.
But...
Unfortunately, he might have to be...
He might have to be...
Villageless.
You can still help the Spike Factory.
You know what?
I think you're right actually.
Because...
We're not getting anything from him.
So yeah, we'll sell him.
What?
Fireball!
I really want the Necromancer.
07 Spike Factory.
I was going to say, can he even fit?
I think I can make him fit to where I can add some other monkeys into.
Let me see.
Can I put like...
No.
Oh!
A little bit.
Spike Factory has served its purpose.
A zero zero zero ice monkey is insecure.
Let's see.
Okay, we're going to do... I like to do the pursuit.
We have Moab Shove.
Do I want another one though?
Shove is amplified by bigger jets and our little guys when they're needed.
I'm wondering if I should just do four two on this one.
I can only go up to three though.
I don't have the Apache Dart ship.
I don't have Apache monkey.
How do you say this?
Comanchi?
204 spam!
You'll get to four soon enough.
I don't think in this though.
Because I'm not... I'm higher.
So the XP is way lower.
If you like tower defense, check out Domekeeper.
Oh, I do.
Trip trap!
Welcome to membership.
Comanchi.
Another 204.
I think I feel safer like that.
Because then I can do the high level one, you know?
Okay.
Here we go!
Handle it!
ZOMG!
Nice!
Handle it!
It's barely moving because both of them are shoving.
Let's go!
Yeah, the sniper and the two planes are just making him like stuck there.
Nice.
You know what?
I'm even gonna go for round the next round.
This might be a mistake but...
Nature prevails, baby!
Nature prevails!
Don't bust it!
No!
Uh-oh!
Oh my god!
No!
I'm gonna die!
I'm
gonna die!
I just wanted to get to level one!
I just...
The last round was such a tease!
It made me feel so confident.
We were two levels away.
98 is one of the hardest rounds.
Gosh!
Okay, Icarus...
Hey!
What would have happened if you had the 0-0-0 Ice Monkey?
Not sure how monkeys got their hands on...
Comanche's...
When the Comanche program was cancelled 20 years ago before it even entered production.
Look, monkey technology is not for you to judge, okay?
Ugh!
You Vegeta-ed it.
Stop!
Only you listen to Ice Monkey.
Oh my god.
It's mint over.
Dang you!
Wait!
It's free!
If I want to continue!
Need more high-end D.
Free continue!
For free?
Do not!
Why not?
We can get to level 100!
Right?
Only the first continues free.
Just level the monkeys?
You're probably right.
It would be better to get more experience.
Look, that monkey is just like me.
Monkey is just like me.
Yeah.
Game over.
No,
stop.
You're taking my spotlight, monkey.
Oh, whoa, whoa.
My bad.
Game over!
Okay.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Why are you like this?
What are you talking about?
Collection event?
I'm collecting a monkey!
Insta-monkey!
Neat!
Wait, what are these?
Featured insta-monkeys.
I want that.
Wait, someone said buy the fountain, right?
This guy...
There's a...
Is it a challenge to get the monkey?
No.
Tutorial to get the monkey?
You can get whatever the hell these are.
Experiments on the monkey?
Five rounds.
Fifty MOAB class bloons on each round?
How much money did they give you at first?
The raids.
Oh, is that what it is?
Wait.
How do you see the raids?
Hold on.
Monkey boost.
Events?
How do you need to be level 40?
Whoa.
Shucks.
Play social.
I want to change my mind.
Oh.
Good, good, good.
Let's change to general mon...
Oh, no.
Sniper monkey.
My favorite.
My favorite sniper monkey.
Any new heroes?
I think I have to pay for all of them.
There he is.
The Pat Fusty.
Benjamin.
Eliza.
Adoro.
I don't have so much money though.
I can't even afford a single monkey.
Hmm.
Giraldo.
The goat.
I like Corvus.
Is this guy new?
A guide to the book of spirits.
Help Corvus harvest the bloons on dark path.
What does he do though?
Oh, here.
Haunted bloons.
Are weakened and explode when popped.
Adding mana to the mana pool.
The spirit.
The spirit attacks bloons wherever on the map of Corvus's command.
Interesting.
Hard...
It's amazing but hard to use optimally.
Hmm.
Corvus is too complicated.
Whoa.
My...
He's awesome.
I like how...
I like...
I like this guy.
That's me.
Oh, yes.
I like when they have different outfits.
I know they're just cosmetic.
But they look so cool.
Wait.
Does he have one?
No.
Whoa.
Ocean Guardian.
Corvus can solo?
That's insane.
Sada is good for being a nurse.
I love this one.
This Yangshi is so cute.
What is...
I've never played a Sada.
Slashes.
Oh.
Can pop camo.
She's so cute.
She's awesome.
She's really good on most maps.
Someone said Giral...
Oh, here's Giraldo.
Oh.
It's cute.
Gadgeteer.
Paragon belt.
I'll be honest.
Like, I don't really read what they do.
It's probably bad.
There's just so many effects.
There's so many.
I like it.
I like Striker Jones too.
Oh my god.
Octo Jones.
He's so cute.
Biker bones.
Giraldo sells stuff he can use.
Oh, really?
I like Ben because he just gives you more money.
Nothing complicated or crazy.
Love that.
I love that.
Hi Mentos, one time.
Random question but I need to satisfy my curiosity.
Are you interested in playing Touhou fan games?
Thanks for speaking.
Yeah, I would be interested.
I can play whatever I want now.
There was actually some Touhou...
I guess you would call them fan games.
Not official.
Some other Touhou games on Steam that I'd wanted to play before but never could.
So now I will have the opportunity to, I think.
Not I think.
I know.
I saw...
I saw Fuwawa playing Mountain of Faith the other day.
I was watching her and I was like, this is making me want to play Touhou.
Uh oh.
I also want to play Mountain of Faith.
Maybe not Mountain of Faith.
I don't know which one I would want to play.
Hmm.
But I love the music in Mountain of Faith so much.
SA.
I was never good at Subterranean Anime.
I'm never good at it.
I was thinking UFO but I don't know.
I'll try practicing more off stream so that when I play I can actually like get somewhere.
Because it's...
First of all, I need to be good enough to overcome my performance anxiety.
Do not play Mystia's Izakaya or you'll lose 60 plus hours of your life to it.
That's one of the ones I wanted to play though.
Oh my gosh.
Mystia's Izakaya.
What kind of game is it?
I think I...
Wait.
Did I buy it?
I do.
I own it.
I bought it.
Highly recommend Mystia's Izakaya on Hero of Iceberry.
Super tough.
At first though, Clown Piece kicked my ass three times.
Let's just restaurant sim.
Oh god.
That sounds so fun.
And there's lots of...
Holy moly.
There's so much DLC.
Does this count as a DLC?
It's a fan game.
I mean...
It has so much content, but I guess it's a fan game though, right?
Is it a fan game?
I do own it though.
After...
I was thinking because I'm like trying to figure out like a schedule-ish type of what I'm doing for like longer form games.
Like right now, I would say Ghost Trick is like the longer game.
Longer game I'm playing right now.
I think after Ghost Trick, I'll play...
Oh my god.
Stop.
I just looked this up the other night.
And I couldn't remember the name of it the other night.
I was like...
I was like, no way.
Hold on.
Oh my god.
My brain.
She plays Xenoblade.
I actually do.
Kamaniki told me to play it and I said I would.
So...
I think I have to play it.
But...
I'm...
Hesitant to start such a huge...
Such a huge thing...
Right now.
But...
Xenoblade will be eventually...
Most likely.
They just finished translating the last DLC for the...
2.
The Izakaya team are super cracked for being so small.
That's so awesome.
Mike!
Thanks for the...
Pink!
This is the Purgatory Maid Cafe.
We would like to inform you that in recognition of your 10,000th visit...
You are now a Platinum tier member.
However, we humbly request that on your next visit...
You cease to Wotage with the breadsticks.
You can't tell me what to do!
As your Platinum member, I should have permission to Wotage with whatever I please.
Even if it's...
Like...
Even if I grab someone's feet...
And swing the person around...
Like...
Pen lights.
Baking a cheesecake for my mom for Mother's Day.
Never made one before but it smells good in the oven.
Wish me luck!
Good luck!
I've made cheesecake before.
It's not so difficult.
It's pretty good.
It's...
It's pretty...
It's not so bad.
Oh yeah.
Um...
Yeah...
I'm not going to buy anything right now.
I'm going to switch the...
Riding Quincy.
What have I bought?
Oh!
I wouldn't want to level up to 20 though.
Wolf Pack Quincy.
I'm going to switch to Quincy though, so we can hear...
So we can hear... Are you kidding me?
Are you kidding me?
Just look this up.
The highest round someone got was...
3,275!
Now my round 250 seems small.
Thanks for stream.
I'm not done yet!
Sunday is my birthday.
Can I get a song?
What would it be?
Like...
Otagei move?
Or Otagei like...
Hold on.
I'm going to pick a thing real quick.
So I can stop listening to this song.
Oh!
The loop has a golden balloon.
So let's do that one.
Do you mean like...
Otagei as in like...
A move?
Or do you mean like...
Thunder snake?
I don't know.
I feel like thunder snake might be kind of hard for people.
You can start with the simple stuff.
Like...
O.A.D.
And...
P.P.P.H.
And then...
But once you learn thunder snake...
I'll admit you feel pretty cool doing it.
All in with namaste snake.
That too.
Time to do it.
Otagei teaching stream.
The day I get 3D.
I have to do that and I have to do a dance cover of...
Umamushime.
I finally can do that.
If I get 3D.
I'll actually have 3D.
So I can use it.
Okay.
Quincy my man.
My man Quincy.
And then this map...
We can put sniper wolf anywhere.
So it's fine.
Um...
What is Quincy...
Oh Quincy's range is pretty good actually.
I'm gonna put you right here in the middle.
Alright good job Quincy.
Just give me a target.
Yes?
Nice.
Okay.
Sha!
Easy peasy.
On the chocolate river map.
You can find monkeys hidden in the map.
And you click them in the right order.
I think I have done that before.
Okay.
Guys before we get any further.
What are some monkeys, not ice monkeys.
That we are trying to level up.
Like...
Tack monkey.
And uh...
Wizard monkey!
Okay.
Buy wizard monkey.
Buy the wizard monkey.
Ice monkey.
Oh yeah.
I'm not listening to anything.
Anything.
That says ice monkey.
Especially if nanoplasm says ice monkey.
I don't even know if that person is still here.
I might have really made them mad.
Sorry.
I don't even know.
Ninja monkey.
Oh um...
Because I want the balloon jutsu.
Balloon jutsu.
Have I been saying balloon jutsu this whole time?
Wow he looks so awesome.
In this outfit though.
He looks cool there too though.
But this one is so cool.
Wow!
Oh wait.
This is the...
This guy is scratching his head.
Like why am I here?
Okay do something wizard monkey.
Uh oh.
Wow wizard monkey.
Wow.
We'll do the spikes here.
Oh my gosh wizard monkey.
You really let the ball down there.
Okay we'll put...
I usually put this one in here.
But we'll wait for spikes monkey.
We'll wait for spikes monkey.
He can already evolve.
Intense magic.
Oh he turned into a monkey.
He turned into a nerd.
Wizard monkey is a 000 tower.
He's doing his best.
He became blind.
What is this astronaut monkey anyway?
I can't tell.
It looks like he's wearing a space suit.
Okay.
Attack monkey will be in the middle.
Here.
We're going to get our submarines too.
Right?
Because we're trying to get...
Wait no.
We're trying to get a preemptive strike.
Right?
So I'm going to put one guy in there too.
Wow Quincy.
I've got a fever and the only cure is ice monkey.
Are you actually sick?
Oh I forgot to spend money on my intense magic.
Alchemist monkey?
What were we trying to level up for him?
We still have to do the top one though right?
I don't know where I want to put him.
I don't know where I want to put him yet though.
Yeah, we trying to do the top one.
I do want to get this guy down too though.
Oh wait I know now.
My guide says 0-0-0 my ice monkey is best in the corner where I can't hit anything is the best slot.
Everyone has a 0-0-0 ice monkey on their map, obviously.
4-2 Alcazope.
That's what we're trying to get here.
But I don't know where to put him.
I guess I can put him here with everybody, right?
I can have him like kind of like that.
Or maybe...
Where will he cover most monkey ground?
He broke monkey ground!
Ice monkey in bio.
Near Quincy?
So it's like right there.
Good.
Okay.
Sneak up on him.
Like right...
Actually, I want enough space here.
So we'll put him right...
Here.
I love when they're all really good friends.
Oh.
Can't even tell if he's doing anything.
Some monkey is just...
Look how cute he is in the little boat.
He's like...
La la la.
He's like rocking side to side.
He's so cute.
Little...
He's just a little guy.
Oh, he's so funny.
Monkey sense.
Monkey dollars and monkey cents.
Sub will shoot if you get the top two.
Yeah, we're gonna...
That one will be...
Oh, wait.
Yes.
Wait.
No, we're going for the middle one.
Sorry.
We're going for middle barbed darts.
Why is the chat crazy about Ice Monkey?
Because there was someone in here earlier who was spamming that they really wanted Ice Monkey.
So...
You can do the top two then go for middle.
Oh.
I guess that's true.
You're right.
You're so right.
Go.
Shoot.
I'm sure Ice Monkey is a really nice guy, okay?
Oh, the hearts.
The hearts...
I'm confused.
Do they grow more hearts or do they just regrow their layers?
Which monkey is your monkey-sona?
Oh, they regrow.
So they regrow layers.
Okay.
Ohh, yeah.
Alright!
Yeah!
Joshua!
Thank you for the akasuba!
It could have used a little more ice monkey.
I gotta have more ice monkey, baby!
Why did you send an akasuba for the ice monkey?
Why would you do that?
Why?
Joshua!
Balls in your court, missy.
Oh no.
Can I even afford... I can't even afford the ice monkey!
I can't even afford him!
How's your Friday going, you guys?
Do you have any plans for the weekend?
Welcome to membership.
Thank you so much!
He sent you a hundred dollars.
You gotta...
I just bought something else.
Oh, I can't afford him now.
Okay, fine.
This is for you, Joshua.
He freezes one balloon at a time.
Ice monkey funds.
Not really.
I plan to dye my hair.
Wait, by yourself?
Or are you going somewhere?
It's already weekend in my country.
What are your plans?
What does he do?
I started that, but I don't even know.
Come on!
Ice monkey!
Okay, so what's the best route for ice monkey now?
Let's see...
Frozen bloons grow sharp icicles that can pop bloons that touch them.
Freezes all regular bloons on screen.
0, 0, 0, of course.
I hate you guys so much.
Fine, I'm gonna keep him there.
I'm gonna keep him there.
And he is going to be 0, 0, 0 the whole time.
WestTrip, happy birthday!
Look at your profile picture.
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday, me, mom.
Happy birthday, WestTrip, me, mom.
Me, me, mom, mom.
Happy birthday!
Ice monkey sucks.
Please sell it.
Sorry.
If you want me to sell it...
No, I'm just kidding.
Please don't do that, actually.
Please don't do that.
The ice monkey is not worth it.
It's not worth a bit.
Please.
Also, I love that ice monkey 0, 0, 0 donated in Streamlabs.
One of the ice monkey's freeze blast sound effects is similar to the one...
The friend.
Fruit quench sounds...
Did I say French?
When slicing fruit in Fruit Ninja.
I have never played Fruit Ninja.
LilyBweeze, you're gonna have to keep that name until YouTube allows you to change it back.
Just letting you know.
It's okay.
Where are we at?
I want to have this guy out, so...
Long reach, maybe?
But I want the bigger stacks, maybe.
Not there!
Oh my god... Mike!
Ice... Ice Monkey...
Worth...
Please sell the Ice Monkey, then buy another one at...
He's at zero zero zero!
I didn't upgrade him!
He's zero zero... He has no upgrades!
He's zero already!
Stop!
That's a bad one.
Yo, it's not worth it, you guys!
Go to the next one and buy a membership!
Sell the Ice Monkey!
Look, he's juggling with the ice, you guys!
How am I supposed to sell this?
Okay...
Oh
my god!
Keep him in!
Look at his greatness!
Buy another zero zero!
What after you sell it?
Please!
I said I was gonna keep him zero zero zero!
No!
I'd like to cancel Ice Monkey!
You guys, please!
I'm serious!
This is the dumbest bit ever!
It's not worth...
It's not worth sending this!
Okay...
I'm going to continue on moving forward.
Okay, everybody.
We're moving forward with our afterlives.
Oh, I'm moving forward with my afterlives!
I can't tell who's winning the bid war at this point!
Me either!
Okay...
If I sell this Ice Monkey and put him in the middle of the field...
Where he will be absolutely useless...
Will you guys feel better?
So then I technically sold him.
And I bought another one.
Buy, buy, buy.
Ice, ice, ice.
Do it.
No, don't sell.
Zero, zero, zero in the middle.
He'll be the mascot.
But I can't hurt anybody.
Ice, ice.
Baby.
Sweet.
I feel like I lost in the end.
I feel like...
I feel like I just got bullied.
Into this.
Oh my gosh.
Ballistic missile.
Holy cow.
Membership lapsed midstream, so I was jarringly not green.
Here's extra.
I don't need extra, but thank you.
I got two monkey bucks.
Yippee!
Gonna join the 30s gang on Tuesday.
Could you sing me a happy birthday song in a granny voice with love, Bozo?
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday.
Young man.
Dear Bozo.
Happy birthday.
To you.
Let's get the berserker brew after this.
I am Quincy.
Son of Quincy.
I didn't know he said son of Quincy like that.
I am Quincy.
Oh no.
He has an upgrade.
Ice Monkey wins by doing nothing.
This is crazy.
I am Quincy.
Son of Quincy.
Ice Monkey has an upgrade.
I
don't even remember what this does.
Oh yeah, that's right.
He's just juggling in the middle.
I am Quincy.
Son of Quincy.
Okay.
I can post this here.
If I put it right in the middle...
Can I still put monkeys on the side?
Like a ninja monkey around?
Oh my gosh.
Can I put this in the middle and decorate it with ninja monkeys?
No.
Not the last loop.
This loop instead.
Okay.
So, I am Quincy.
This is Samson.
Samson is really adamant about it.
It won't fit.
Are you sure?
Wait.
Hold on.
I can't afford anything anymore.
But we need these guys to level up too.
We need these guys to get more experience also.
Ha!
What was...
So it was...
Magic shots last longer and seek out the bloons even behind cover.
Pop through two layers.
Oh no.
I want the wall of fire.
I think.
We'll do the wall of fire.
Fireball.
I'm sorry.
I'm just enthusiastic.
It's okay.
Just try not to spam too much.
But I'm asking for help from you guys so...
I don't mind...
the backseating a little bit.
But...
I'm gonna do actually the stronger acid.
Because I remember someone saying the acid pool is not as good.
So we'll do that.
But...
You want some?
Ice Monkey standing center.
He's like...
And then when we win he juggles.
It's so awesome.
Hahaha.
My favorite intern.
Yay!
Juggle monkey juggle.
Hahaha.
David thanks for the five gifted.
I'm barely taking this one seriously.
I can barely concentrate.
Hahaha.
He's so cute.
He's really cute.
He's pretty cute.
Why is it so hard to place this?
Like... what the hell?
Hi ice monkey got me distracted too.
Monkey farms?
You're right.
Oh this has an upgrade.
We're gonna go for the faster production.
Okay, I have no money, so...
Look at the way he juggles so fast!
Juggle, juggle monkey!
Juggle ice monkey!
Darksider, welcome to Bamboo Ship!
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
Holy cow!
I think I was going for banana...
You want banana?
We have banana!
Banana crates?
We're 300 each!
Nice!
Wall of fire!
This one is $10.
Wow, he looks so cool!
Okay, I need more money.
Oh, pop it, pop it, pop it!
Pop the golden cup!
Pop it, pop it, pop it!
Yippee!
Okay, nice.
It's also the banana bank.
Which one is that?
The Wall Street one?
Pub of Monkey Trades earns colossal income, generates lives each round.
What?!
Two more dollars!
Hey, two dollars is two dollars that I did not spend with my real money.
Even faster!
Bank is the middle.
Monkey-nomics?
All money generated in this farm is now stored in the bank and earns 15%... Oh!
I see, I see, I see.
Okay, I'll do another one.
And we'll go for the middle path.
Gold balloon for you.
Oh, thank you!
Mr. Wow, welcome to membership.
Thank you so much!
This map is making me wish it was fall.
Okay, uh-oh.
I just realized, we have a lot of balloons getting through.
Watch out for the MOAB.
We have a lot of balloons getting through.
I think we're in trouble.
I think we're a bit in trouble.
We'll do the wall of fire at least, and even the faster production.
Ding ding ding ding!
What's this one?
Collect the radius of bananas is larger.
Uncollect the bananas, auto-collect.
Nah, I'd rather have more.
Nah, you'd win?
Really?
Did you play this on stream with Mata?
Actually, I would love to if she wants to, but I think we might be like, put this monkey here.
No, put this monkey here!
Is engineer monkey good?
Maybe we should get him too.
I haven't used him once.
And I haven't really used the druid monkey.
Oh, I have a little bit.
I lied.
I lied, I lied.
Yeah, he's good.
Engineer gaming?
Okay.
If I put him like here.
Kind of as like a defense at the end of the, you know, the end of the...
The end of the line.
Top path engineer goaded.
With the sentry.
That's the one I was looking at, cause it kinda seems fun.
Removes camo and regrow and pops left.
Wow.
Engineer puts more gun.
I love gun!
But how far do they reach, you know?
Bottom's good for money.
I think we're good for money right now.
Hmm.
A decent range?
So I don't have to put him right here then.
I could put him like here.
And he's kinda like, building his little sentries and they're like
average range.
Put them where Quincy is.
Oh, okay.
Like here.
So here actually then.
Yeah, basically.
Not that much of a range.
Okay.
He'll build in his range, but the sentries can shoot wherever, right?
Or the sentries can only shoot in the little circle that he's in, is what I'm asking.
Oh, he gets the buff here, so.
Sentries have their own range.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Can become huge with the middle one.
Longer range.
I wish sometimes you could like, I wish sometimes it wasn't just a circle.
Like I wish I could make a rectangle.
You know.
Circles in this game are so hard.
How you doing Ice Monkey?
Are you working hard or are you hardly working?
You know what?
I don't have any snipers, so let's add a sniper right here.
Right here.
Actually, okay, hold on.
How do I want to do this?
Because I also want to add a village.
We can put the village in the middle.
Like right here and sniper monkeys and then some guys down here probably.
Incoming!
Oh, we're fine.
I think.
Yeah.
Alright.
Yeah, we're fine.
We're fine.
I need more money.
Alright.
It's like the dune.
It's like the dune popcorn.
Right?
Just me?
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm going to do bigger because I don't think I need to reach longer.
I think we're okay.
Let's do bigger stacks.
Actually, no, I'm going to hold out.
Why are you saying ha?
What are you saying ha for?
It looks just like it, I think.
Holy moly!
We have so much money!
I wish I could upgrade you.
Close though.
We're close.
Let's see.
What else?
Um, stronger stimulant.
Whoa!
Shimmer.
Yeah, I know.
I am Quincy.
Son of Quincy.
Let's go for the MOAB here.
And I'm going to actually do faster firing because we have the intent of building a village right there.
So...
Don't necessarily need
currently.
Spend it all on ice monkey.
We're rich baby!
Woohoo!
I just need them to generate a little.
Oh wait!
Oh!
I can still do the same thing even though we're taking different paths with each one of them.
I just realized.
Oh yeah!
That's what I'm talking about.
I think your spikes are stale.
What?
Why do you think that?
They're actually really great!
Monkey bank!
Middle path druid is very broken.
This guy?
Really?
I always go for the top one.
Dang!
He generates a life and cash?
But see this one like the druid this one it only he only gets one balloon at a time.
Risotto!
Welcome to membership.
Thank you!
Middle is OP.
Okay.
We'll add him.
Let's try him out.
Rise!
We'll put you right.
Look at him waving.
He's strong trust.
Next to the bank?
Like here?
Wait.
What is the upgrade?
I'm confused now.
Generates cash each use plus extra cash per banana farm!
Oh my god!
Wait does this count as near?
Let's go!
Oh the open buffs the druid.
I do remember that actually.
Give us money.
Wow!
He got rid of all of those.
That was really crazy.
Oh yeah!
Good job Quincy.
Son of Quincy.
I'm doing deadly.
I'm doing the precision with this one.
Oh I should have I should have bought the monkey bank.
But that's okay.
What are you doing anyway?
Welcome to membership.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Okay we need jungles bounty.
Oh we're so close though.
Awesome.
Go get it!
Get it!
Get the crown!
Yeah!
Two real bucks.
We want the real bucks.
Monkey!
Thanks for the 20.
Thank you so much.
Monkey!
This location I feel like kind of sucks.
He's just really random.
He's just randomly there.
But that's okay too.
Hahaha!
Wow he was really strangling that guy right there.
Hayden!
Thank you so much for the five gifted.
Thank you.
Oh my gosh!
I just noticed how much money we have!
Bank!
Wait should I do bank on both?
Now I'm conflicted.
No!
I wanted the plantation.
I wanted the whole field.
We are making bank now baby!
The monkeyconomy.
Monkeyconomy!
Potato!
Thank you for the 10 gifted!
He's still hitting balloons?
Oh my gosh!
You're right!
How is he hitting them?
Oh!
From over here!
That's crazy.
Is there anything else I can buy?
Yeah?
Everything I'm waiting on upgrades.
Oh!
Except you.
Okay maybe the spikes aren't so bad.
Headshot!
Hahaha!
Quincy is so obnoxious.
Oh Quincy.
Quincy!
I don't like this one though.
I don't like the next one.
It's a $9000 loan.
I don't want to be owing anybody.
I think that's why I didn't go for the middle one.
But I really like this one.
Wizard monkey.
No we're still waiting on the necromancer monkey.
Why is there a monkey in the middle not able to do anything?
He's our mascot monkey.
He's mascot monkey.
He doesn't do anything.
Is that all you got?
Oh!
200 monkey money!
Holy cow!
That's a lot of monkey money.
Yeah he's just there to be cute.
He doesn't have to do anything.
What is something else that I need to level up?
I haven't really used super monkey all that much.
Oh we were going to do engineer monkey.
In fact we were going to do sentry engineer.
We're just going to put him right up there.
Alright go monkey!
Moab!
Handle it!
Reach...
10% attack speed for...
Maybe I'll just do this one.
Close though.
Close.
Oh my gosh!
We have money in here!
Alright!
Alright indeed!
Quincy's dead father is available as a redeemable item in this shop.
That's so messed up!
Wait what?
Alright!
Don't forget to collect your bank money.
But if it's stuff in the bank doesn't it like...
Earns 15% interest.
We should wait until we get it up to 9000 right?
It's Quincy senior.
What is this game?
Nice!
We got the shredder.
Yeah shredder.
What next?
Actually I'm going to add another sniper monkey.
Oh actually no no.
No no no.
Sorry.
Put you here.
And then another sniper monkey.
Right next to you.
So you... okay.
Will become...
The monkey business.
And bigger radius.
And then we can also put monkeys down here.
That will be able to...
And so these guys can become like...
This guy can be our fast monkey.
The fastest monkey in the west.
Get it!
Two monkey bucks.
How's our little engineer guy doing?
I don't even know what he's doing.
He's killed 141.
You want some?
This guy is...
The druid is cracked.
Incoming!
What's this do?
You can all have some.
Headshot.
You want some?
You can all have some.
I can't.
The engineer is a pain in the butt to level.
Well that's why he's here.
Oh my god.
She's killing nothing.
You can lower Quincy's voice.
No I turned it up on purpose.
Because I think it's kind of funny.
Something sounds wet and I don't know what it is.
What's that wet sound?
I don't know.
Also...
Oh let's get the boat in here too.
Oh my gosh wait!
I only have two rounds left.
I think I meant to put the boat in sooner.
I completely forgot.
My bad.
Oh well.
Oh is the alchemist doing it?
Probably.
There he comes.
I can hear him.
Oh my gosh.
It broke?
They destroyed it off stream.
Or off the screen.
Free play!
Oh man.
Buccaneer I forgot to put you in.
And now it's going to take forever to get you leveled up.
Let's see.
Yeah.
Let's just keep going.
Is that all you got?
Oh yeah.
I like the way he's like squeezing them.
With the vines.
That makes me almost want to restart.
Because I want the nature's bounty.
I want the bounty man.
Check the bank too.
We still have a good amount in here.
You know what?
I'll collect it at this point.
14,000.
Heck yeah.
Wish I could buy experience.
I mean you can with real money.
But I wish I could with my monkey bucks.
For 5,000 monkey xp it's one dollar.
One dollar USD.
7k might be max in an unboosted bank.
Just play the game.
There's no rush.
Right?
I guess if you're really impatient.
Mr. Alphaisy.
Thanks for the 10 gifted.
Thank you so much.
If it was zero dollars.
I'd buy.
Mint do you want a dollar?
No.
Our monkey village.
Radius gets tier 1 upgrades for free.
For free.
Increased range and reduced ability cooldowns.
What if you sold Ice Monkey for a dollar?
Ice Monkey is priceless.
What do you mean?
I'm going to buy a monkey.
I think we can use him.
I don't know what else to add.
I think I'm invincible.
I do like Gatlin Monkey.
Actually Gatlin Monkey would be kind of great here in the middle.
Gatlin Monkey and...
Actually I like putting Gatlin Monkey facing right there.
Oh my gosh.
Thank you guys for the super chats.
Woohoo.
Add a plane.
Yeah.
I think I will.
No I don't have them upgraded at all.
I have used them.
But not very much.
Hmmm.
Hit camels and do more damage.
Yeah.
Dark Storm is OP.
Not everything can be OP you guys.
This is goaded.
Pineapple.
Wait.
I'm so sorry Kiara.
My Gatlin I have...
Oh that's not a Gatlin Monkey.
I have a...
I was working on the top one.
Because...
I don't like having to swivel my own guy.
I don't like that.
So I just fixed him there.
And I was setting on these two.
You
know what?
I'm gonna set him up.
I'm gonna put him right next to Ice Monkey.
He is protecting Ice Monkey.
I think.
Locked and loaded.
Windle.
Sweet.
Ice...
No.
Ice Monkey protect him.
So true.
Wow.
That was scary.
Oh it's level 63.
I just realized.
Oh.
You can all have some.
I hate him so much.
Oh wait.
Or is this round 63?
Oh.
I think we're in trouble.
Okay.
I need to actually come up with a plan.
I'll take my $800.
And um...
Let's see.
What do I wanna add?
Oh!
Oh you need to be better.
There we go.
Let's see.
Actually.
No.
You're first.
You're strongest.
You're locked and loaded.
What next?
Engineer Monkey is doing his best.
Wizard Monkey.
Yeah.
Five walls of fire in the first loop.
Guys!
Five Wizard Monkeys going ham.
This is a Wizard Monkey.
Yeah.
Wizard Monkey.
One.
Two.
Three.
Let's go.
Four.
Five.
Yeah!
Look at them.
Oh no!
I can't afford it!
Uh oh.
Incoming!
Well, I think we'll make it.
I think we'll be fine.
Ooh!
They're getting faster.
Headshot!
More fire!
Nothing is even making it over there.
Nothing's even making it over there.
Ugh.
That was fun.
I'll do the bureau.
I'll do the MIB.
Monkeys in black.
Monkey Intelligence Bureau.
Headshot!
They don't do it at the same time though.
This guy is out of sync.
Oh my gosh!
Engineer Monkey!
Aww.
Have you seen the latest Anikura meta from Meatfest or NikuFest in Odaiba last weekend?
Gundam Epion is out.
Mr. Mime Bariado is in.
What?
No, I haven't.
Can you link me?
Can you like, put it in my live tag or my general tag?
Lemmo Lemmo!
Thanks for the 20 gift!
Qmelia!
Welcome to Membo!
Is that a Tenshi profile picture?
I love Tenshi!
Is that all you got?
Nice!
Ouch!
I'm just gonna keep going you guys.
Incoming!
I'm just gonna keep going.
What else can we do with these guys?
Maybe we shouldn't do anything.
Hahaha!
Maybe they should just be Wall of Fire and that's it.
I kinda like the guided manner.
Spews endless flames and nearby bloons and enhance...
Enhanced Wall of Fire!
Save for Necromancer...
I got
really excited about that one.
I got really excited about that one.
You know what?
Don't even tell me how much I spent on that.
Badabra!
Dada down, dada do Badabo!
Badaba!
Very good.
How are you doing?
We can upgrade Sentry Gun!
One singular upgrade, please.
Dragons!
Holy cow!
Oh my gosh!
Oh, look how cute it is!
It's a little guy.
You can sell it for zero dollars.
This sentry is getting out of my way.
This is not going to hit anything.
Okay!
Oh, he's popped 14!
Let's go!
Brandon, welcome to membership!
Thank you so much!
Sweet!
Oh my gosh!
Incoming shot!
Come on!
Make it to the wall of fire!
I dare you!
Thank you for playing this game!
It is awesome!
I love it!
Happy Mexican Mother's Day!
Thank you!
Am I your mom?
What are you doing over there?
Oh my god!
He's looking!
You guys!
I think it's an inside job!
I think he's trying to take Ice Monkey out!
I think he was trying to take Ice Monkey out.
Oh my god!
This sucks!
It sucks so bad!
Sounds so nice!
What's the next one?
The Phoenix, right?
Powerful Phoenix wreaks bloon havoc for 20 seconds.
Do-do-do!
Ba-da-boom!
Da-da-da-dum!
Ba-da-da-dum!
Let's get the 14,000!
Yes!
We have...
Is that all you got?
I want to see... I want to see some get to the wall of fire.
BFB incoming!
BFB!
Okay, next time we'll get enough money.
Just keep going!
Oh yeah!
Okay, next time we'll get enough money.
More banks?
Maybe.
Incoming!
So close.
BFB incoming!
Headshot!
Nice!
We're on round 77 already!
Your druid is stopping them from reaching the fire zone.
Stop being so good, druid!
I really want jungle's bounty though.
Oh, we're at 9,000.
That's not bad.
Druid is the GOAT.
I'm almost like doing it a second...
You know what?
Hell yeah, we'll get a second one.
I will get a second one.
Oh, they made it!
They made it though.
How Engineer Monkey doing?
He's good!
He's killed a thousand bloons.
Look at this guy producing everything.
Oh!
They were... they were camels.
They didn't die in here.
Hmm...
If I put a village here...
Here...
If I extend the range...
How far is the range on this one?
I don't think it'll reach.
But it might be good just for everybody here.
Give the ice monkeys a village.
Above them.
Do it above them.
Oh, maybe here!
Oh!
This is actually...
But then...
I wish I could do it down here.
So I could reach like a little bit of these guys too.
Because this one...
They'll overlap.
You know?
They'll overlap in range.
But...
A village can increase other radius?
Nah...
It's worth?
Okay.
So right here, are we in consensus?
If you are in consensus of this spot, say...
Say...
Yee.
Hear yee!
Oh, say aye!
I can't tell if it reaches them.
Okay.
We need more money.
Come on, bank.
Thank you.
Handle it!
Yee!
Headshot!
I just realized I've been playing Bloons for three hours.
Oh my gosh.
You guys are like...
You don't even understand.
Because I think after stream, if I had done Bunny Girls...
I would have been like...
I just...
I'm just gonna play Bloons.
But now after this, I'll be all Blooned out.
Kind of.
So I can like...
Work on other stuff.
You know what I mean?
I can like finally be like...
Okay.
Headshot!
I did my Bloons.
I can do other things that I need to finish.
I can work on anything else that I need to work on.
Oh shoot.
Well.
Is that all you've got?
Incoming!
BFB incoming!
Destroy!
Oh look at them!
They're so cute!
Little sentries.
He's trying.
He's helping.
How's my cookie clicker?
I haven't checked it in a bit because I like to leave it alone so it will harvest sugar lumps.
You guys, we're already on round 82.
We're already on round 82 with this setup.
With this setup.
This is kind of insane.
I don't know how it's happening.
But...
First strike capability.
Ice monkey carry, ice monkey carry.
Now here, do you think I should have another boat or should I get another submarine?
What do you think?
Because I think I can just fill this up.
I mean, there's only two water units.
So...
Siege!
Thanks for the...
Thank you for the 10 gifted.
Thank you so much.
Just upgrade?
I can't!
Just upgrade they said.
When I can't even upgrade.
Waiting for 12,000.
Sub?
Submarine?
Submarines are cooler.
A gatling straight down the path.
Like this.
Then we can get one here too.
That'd be so awesome.
You're so right.
Oh my gosh.
One here, one here too.
Locked.
Locked in.
You locked in.
Getter Emperor!
Thank you for the five gifted.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Okay.
Top.
Oh.
Wow!
Actually, that's really nice looking, isn't it?
It's pretty nice looking watching all like the...
Is that all you got?
Oh my gosh.
Aren't you scared, Gatlin Monkey?
Aren't you scared?
And then they'll also get the camo.
So it'll be good.
Collecting that so we can buy this for each of them.
And yeah, let's go do another round.
Headshot.
After this, I'm gonna buy a helicopter.
Helicopter.
Awesome.
We'll do some pushing.
Some more pushing.
Can I even fit it here?
I don't think so.
Aw, it's too far away from anything.
No!
Oh.
Oh!
Yo, that placement is insane.
That placement is insane!
Holy cow!
So we'll go pursuit.
We'll do two...
Okay.
Yo!
That's like pixel perfect placement, I feel.
Incoming!
Is that all you got?
Minty.
Daughter of Minty.
Holy woomy!
Not woomy.
Thanks for mine!
Is that all you got?
Thank you so much.
BFB incoming!
Incoming!
BFB.
I'm still scared of the DDTs though, you guys.
I'm scared.
And your return stream, you mentioned you're still figuring things out.
A professor I had once told me, I'm still figuring out what I want to be when I grow up.
Sounds silly, but I hope it helps.
Aw, thank you.
I think, I mean, I think a lot of people are, you know, thinking of what they want to do.
ZOMG incoming!
And it's okay to always be thinking about stuff.
Headshot.
For sure.
But I appreciate your, your, your, your, your wanting to help.
Furry!
Welcome to membership.
Thank you!
When I upgrade this, does it add anything else or?
Call?
Oh, it just calls in the mini.
Command trees.
Oh, see!
Look at that!
We're already back at 7000!
Nice!
We can probably get the Necromancer.
At this rate.
It's always good to be open to the possibility of change, too.
Yeah!
I mean...
Is that all you got?
There's been a lot of stuff on my mind recently.
Um, but...
I think I...
Well, I'm not think.
I know I'm an over-thinker.
So...
Some decisions that come easy to some people...
Oh, yeah!
People aren't so easy for me when I'm just like...
Drowning pool!
Welcome to membership.
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
I wonder if I should put some guys right here.
Just because we can, right?
Maybe I should have like a whole team of snipers just...
Actually, we can have another Alchemist, right?
Let's do it.
Let's throw another Alchemist on these guys.
Right here.
And then he can buff...
Let's do it.
Buff, buff, buff, buff.
Round 89, baby!
Wall of Fire!
Ring of Fire!
Louie!
Welcome to membership.
Thank you so much!
Glue boy?
It might be time for some glue, right?
Well, I don't know if time is the right...
Do glues... do glue guys work?
Do they work on DDTs?
Do the glues work on the DDT?
I question.
Yes?
Okay, we'll put a guy in here.
We'll put him right here.
So, Red Lentil is a glue.
Glue, glue.
Oh, I need more money.
Thank you.
Glue!
Okay, DDT, do your worst.
DDT incoming!
Only if they can spot Camo.
What do you mean?
Oh!
Okay, okay.
So we need them to be able to see Camo then.
DDTs count as Camo?
Yeah.
Shut up, Quincy!
Shut up!
I need an actual answer to that.
DDTs are Camo and Lead.
Oh!
Said it's strongest.
Thank you for the reminder.
Maybe then we put a little village here.
It's not much, but it could help in a pinch.
Headshot!
Thank you for this every time.
I'll read it in just a second.
Sorry.
Hold on.
I'm bloosin'.
I'm bloosin'!
The one last pop.
Where'd it go?
My chat's all wonky.
There's so many carriers you can do.
And you know that you can always switch to something else in the future, but that doesn't help decide what to do first.
I don't know...
I don't know.
It's...
It's a little complicated, but you know.
It's fine.
It's all good.
I just take it one afterlife day at a time.
I'll play with you guys later.
Thank you!
Quincy's got your back apparently.
Yes?
Yes, you do.
You on my back?
I think...
We'll soak.
Yeah.
We'll be a little more offensive.
Battle you got?
Be a little bit more offensive.
Come on!
Oh my god, you sound so like...
COMG incoming!
You sound so like...
92 baby.
Colin, welcome to membership.
More choppers?
I agree.
Gray.
I agree, more choppers, more choppers.
And we can put them right here too.
Is it enough?
It's enough baby, it's enough.
It's enough for now, it's enough for now.
PSP incoming!
Come on!
You can...
have some.
Let's go!
I usually...
I do usually die at that one.
Incoming!
Headshot!
COMG incoming!
I
think I'll be able to get...
enough from this round.
Look, they don't even make it past the wall of fire!
Yo!
Silver guy, welcome to membership!
The wild spire...
Whoever's idea was the fire circle...
You...
You are...
You've cooked with that.
And they're not even like...
They're just...
They're 3-0-0...
Like 0-3-0.
It's nothing else.
I'm wondering...
Would it be worth, like, unlocking something else?
Like the...
Like, will they do other stuff as well as the wall of fire?
So...
How close are we to Necromancer?
Actually, really not that far away.
Really not that far away.
0-0-0.
Ice Monkey giving so much luck.
I mean, like...
Buying...
Oh, I only have intense magic, actually.
Should I...
Should I upgrade the intense magic?
Do you think it will...
What's the...
What's the one after that?
Oh, the Camel Bloons.
Which I don't entirely need, but...
No, I am still aiming for the Necro.
That's why I'm not gonna buy any other upgrades.
But, I mean, like, buying...
Buying the intense magic, would it be worth it?
Or does...
Is it not gonna change anything, I wonder?
Save the money?
Oh, okay.
That's...
You know what?
That's fair, too.
Because...
How much is it?
I don't know.
Oh, it's so cheap!
It's so cheap, actually.
Wait.
Is it actually that...
Why is it so cheap?
I...
Oh, a water base.
That's right.
I was gonna get the sub.
Can I get a sub end bolt?
I don't think so.
I think it's one or the other, man.
Yeah.
Only three guys can fit here.
That's okay.
What...
What'd I give you?
I don't know.
Oh, I didn't mean to do that.
Oopsie.
I didn't mean to do that.
Since I can't add another guy, anyway.
Okay.
Whew.
There we go.
Is that all you got?
Oh...
Aaaaah!!
You can all have.
Come on.
Holy cow!
Oh, I'm gonna die.
Wow!
Awesome!
I'm a knowledgeable monkey.
Sheesh!
The wall of fire is so OP!
Holy cow!
And also the druid!
I'm like, should I upgrade him too?
How close are you?
Maybe I should also do like the hard thorns?
Hmm...
What's the one after that?
Oh, the thunder!
Yeah...
Doesn't hurt to buy it, right?
Headshot!
COMG incoming!
Holy cow!
You know what you need more of?
What is it, Josh?
What could it be?
Hahaha!
Absolutely cooked, man!
Absolutely cooked!
Hahaha!
This is crazy.
We're gonna be able to get the necromancer so soon.
Hopefully, hopefully.
Oh!
Oh my gosh!
Whoopsie!
What about you?
Oh!
And maybe the plasma generator too!
Maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe.
How much is that one if I end up getting it?
11,000.
That's okay, we can afford it.
Okay.
I might even get another necromancer.
You know what?
Since we're about to get the necromancer, I will get another magic monkey.
I'll put him down here.
Perfect.
And...
We're gonna also do that.
Wall of fire!
Headshot!
Stop!
Oh!
Wait!
Yippee!
What about you?
So close!
Let's go!
Alright.
Is that all you got?
Oh my god!
They scared me!
I was like, what are these?
You can all have some!
Oh!
Oh my god!
I am the best!
Why were all the attacking balloons going up?
I guess they count for like some back end support.
You can change where he summons.
Oh!
Awesome!
Okay, let's see.
Um...
Click to set targets.
So like that, right?
And like this?
I don't know actually.
What does this do?
Oh!
Is it like targets...
Camo and doesn't target camo?
But is it camo or non-camo?
Like you can't do both of them at the same time?
Quincy, son of Quincy, is now at max...
He's max level!
Let's go!
Mmm!
Just priority!
But it will still attack the other ones, right?
So it's not so bad.
How are you doing?
Ooh!
We're pretty far from that one, but that's okay.
Okay.
What can I get?
Because they got through pretty easily.
They got around to here.
So I'm nervous.
I'm nervous.
I mean, there's so much we can add.
We have so much space.
Um...
Bigger stacks for the... Oh!
For this one?
Ooh!
And hot stacks!
There we go.
Trying to decide what I want.
We'll take our money too.
Upgrade what I... Upgrade what I have now.
I don't have anything that can like go... See, like everything is... Everything is... I'm waiting.
I can't really upgrade anything that I have right now.
Unfortunately.
I'm trying to get more of the top path for that guy.
Another helicopter.
This is good.
Maybe another ice monkey.
Oh, I wonder what is... Yo!
We're doing nothing!
Guy is absolutely cracked.
Absolutely cracked.
0, 0, 0.
There are ice monkeys in the center.
In the middle.
Glue monkey for the wall of fire.
Oh, so like have him like kind of stuck in here?
That's a good idea.
I like that.
We'll even do the same one.
And...
Oh, wait.
Would he fit here?
No.
Oh, but he could fit here.
Oh, shoot.
I don't think he's getting... Oh!
Maybe I messed up.
You know what?
I'm sticking with it.
Get bigger globs.
I did.
Run ruined.
Okay, let's get another helicopter.
Do I have a mid helicopter?
No.
I do not.
In fact, I'm gonna put this one here.
I think you can fit a monkey next to it.
What, like this one?
The downdraft one?
I guess I could unlock it.
Other glue needs bigger globs too.
No, this one... I already did this one.
It's corrosive though.
The path is support, which is not bad.
Support is good because, you know, the more we can push back, the more time we can save to blow them up, you know?
So maybe 2...
2...
5-0?
Maybe.
I can't afford the apache.
It's great versus ceramics.
I think I want to try it, you know?
Oh, I can't afford it.
And then pursuit.
Incoming!
DDT incoming!
Yeah!
Am I...
I feel like I'm stressing for no reason.
Because everything is like la la la, easy peasy.
You have a mid blue fellow in the middle Yeah, what about him?
What about him, Joshua?
You can't bully me!
He's perfect the way he is!
I have 18 bucks left.
Alright.
Well, I can't actually do anything because I only have $18, so...
YOLO!
Oh!
This is the big airship of Doom!
It's big, slow, and incredibly hard to take down!
Uh, guys?
You can all have some.
Come on!
Um...
Whoa, I just noticed what these look like.
Um, guys?
Oh.
Is that all you got?
Insta monkey!
Yippee!
Let's go!
Oh my gosh!
Round 100!
Woohoo!
Yeah!
Oh, hi for you!
Oh, we're so close here!
What about this one?
Oh!
Close!
Close, close, close.
Alright, you know what?
Just go for it.
Headshot!
That was it?
That's it?
I felt like that was nothing!
No, I can't get my gatling.
I want the plasma.
I can't get it yet.
You know what?
Just keep going.
Headshot!
I'm coming!
You can all have some!
Come on!
I'm hearing someone talking on the right.
I don't know who...
Who is talking in my ear?
Came back from a break.
Glad to see our blue boy still dead center.
Absolutely!
Look at him go!
He's like, Yippee!
We won!
Yippee!
Spiked balls!
Do extra damage to ceramic and fortified balloons.
Shoot out a thick layer of spikes over the entire track!
I want that one.
I need a lot of experience though.
Let's just keep going.
Is that all you got?
Uh oh.
I said uh oh, but I didn't mean it.
You can all have some!
We'll see though.
Uh oh.
Uh oh for real.
Uh oh for real!
Seriously?
Come on!
Yay!
Oh
man, that was intense.
The fire has breached.
That was awfully close.
It actually was pretty close, wasn't it?
That was pretty close.
But we've reached around 103 in fact, so I am quite satisfied with that.
Give me one second.
I am going to take us over to our brand new, if you guys haven't seen it yet.
If you haven't seen it yet.
Ta-da!
I'm also going to turn off the music because I want to listen to my own music.
Um...
What do I want to listen to?
This...
one.
If you haven't seen it yet...
We moved!
New maid cafe!
Yeah.
I showed it earlier on in the stream.
So if you want like a detailed tour, you can check it out then.
Gigi Ice Monkey MVP Star Creator!
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
So cute, right?
Yeah.
So...
It's all...
All revamped.
Fancy.
For main day!
Well, not entirely for main day, but it just happened to...
To kind of work out that way.
I forgot it's 310.
Happy main day!
Thank you!
What?
If you're interested in a new theme, there's an Adventure Time Bloons.
Really?
Adventure Time themed?
Boy, that sounds so awesome.
Ah!
Cute Minto.
People, people.
Welcome back for one month!
Thank you so much!
Finally, what?
I know people have been asking When is what three?
Patience.
Whenever Wet 3 happens, it happens.
And if you don't know what I'm talking about, you can check out some of the videos on my channel.
I did Wet, and then Wet 2, and then one day will be Wet 3.
Thanks for the stream, IceMonkeyMade.
Thank you guys again.
I'm so sorry for the change in the schedule.
But thank you for letting me indulge in in my monkey shenanigans.
So...
I appreciate it very much.
Thank you so much.
It was a lot of fun too.
Yeah.
Wait.
Oh my gosh, my chat is frozen.
Hold on.
Was that on Akasupa again?
Happy May Day to our favorite ghostly maid, Valentine!
Thank you!
Happy May Day!
Aw, you guys are so nice.
Thanks for wishing me a Happy May Day.
And Happy May Day to you too!
I hope your timelines have been blessed with many wonderful maid art and fan art.
So...
Lovely maids that always blesses the timeline.
On days like these, Twitter feels a little less cursed.
Right?
When it's like...
My favorite is in
November because when you do 11 as the date, it kind of it looks like I-I So that would be E.
So like in Japan, almost every day is like E, which means like good blank day.
So it'll be like E E Futamomo no hi Good thigh day.
Or something like that.
So, November is super duper blessed for that.
For all that fun stuff.
Mint, I'm crying.
I got to see the Northern Lights here in Oklahoma!
How do you see them in Oklahoma?
So effing happy right now.
So I demand more balloons in the future.
Thanks, Nibby.
I hope you're having fun.
What?
That explains a lot.
Yeah, good tummy day?
Yeah, yeah.
Good tummy day is another one.
Good day thing beloved.
It's because of the solar storm.
I saw them in New York tonight.
What?
Solar storm?
I had no idea.
I don't catch up with the news.
I don't I don't I don't keep track of anything.
Oh gosh.
Wait.
Maybe I could have seen the Northern Lights.
I don't know.
It's cloudy here.
Oh no.
I'm gonna go out when the clouds clear up and check.
Yeah!
Wait, do you guys have any pictures?
I wanna see!
I wanna see the Northern Lights!
But honestly, I was like thinking of maybe doing a trip to see the Northern Lights.
Because I I'm I want to be a little bit more world travel-y.
I've never been to Europe.
So I was like, well if I go to like I don't know.
I don't know.
But like, I would wanna I don't know.
I have no idea.
I have to think of how I can incorporate it into something, you know?
Um...
Like uh...
Like maybe if I went and saw Kiwawa and then traveled to see the Northern Lights or something.
That could work.
Or if Kiwawa wants to come with me.
I don't know.
Can you see them in Alaska?
I... Maybe in parts of Alaska.
There was actually... I um...
I saw a video recently about a national park in Alaska.
I bookmarked it.
Hold on, let me see what it's called for anyone else interested.
Because I was like this sounds so awesome.
Um...
Cause it's...
You have to...
It's a bit more difficult of a national park to get to because it's very mountainous.
Hold on, I saved it though.
Cause I was like, I really wanna go here.
Um...
But because it's hard to get to, it's like you know...
It's pretty... secluded and you don't have a lot of people going.
Wait, what are some of these videos that I saved and they were deleted?
I hope one of them wasn't that.
Oh no!
Maybe I should start saving them to my phone instead of bookmarking them.
Um...
No way!
Was one of them it?
I saved it not too long ago.
Oh!
I found it!
It's called the Gates...
Gates of the Arctic National Park.
And it's America's northernmost second largest national park.
But it's also the least visited of...
Oh yeah!
K.O.
knew it!
Yeah, it's also the least visited of the national parks.
Um... But like...
The photos are just so insane.
And I was like, any reason to go to Alaska, baby?
Good guess, K.O.
Yeah!
I've been there?
Oh!
What did you think, Clockwork?
Did you like it?
How was it?
I wanna see Glacier National Park too.
Yeah!
Gates of the Arctic.
Got it.
Thanks, man.
Yeah, of course!
Hmm...
The pics on Wiki look pretty cool.
Right!
Happy May Day!
I'm going on a European cruise this summer!
So I hope...
I hope you can travel more as well.
Oh my gosh!
Where is it going?
That's so awesome.
Cold but very pretty.
I don't mind the cold so much anymore.
I went to Antarctica.
I experienced the cold.
I experienced the... I don't know.
Sounds hard to get the coldest place on Earth.
I experienced the southernmost place on Earth.
I went to the ends of the Earth.
Italy and Greece.
Woo!
So fun.
Mike Tyson!
Thanks for the gifted!
You went there in the summer though?
Yeah, because they wouldn't let me go in the winter.
Though, if there was like a way to do a...
I mean, I would have to...
If there was a way to like...
I don't want to call it an internship but like...
Maybe it would be considered an internship with the scientists that stay.
The side that I went on was the west part of Antarctica which is...
probably maybe the better side to go to right now because that's the side that's actively melting but the east side of Antarctica is actually growing.
So we might find that Antarctica changes shape.
You know?
Like in...
I mean it's gonna take hundreds of...
hundreds of years.
If you guys become a ghost you might be able to see it.
But it's kind of interesting.
Shiraishi went to make content so...
Glacier growth?
Yippee!
Yeah!
I applied to one of those internship thingies.
I don't think I got in...
Nooooo!
That one time my Oshii went to Alaska and saw the northern lights out of my...
Thank you.
If I go...
You can bet your butt that I will film everything and then I can do a best yet to come song cover of it and I have to learn Gaelic.
And then I will sing it.
And then I will have the footage in the background just like at the end of MGS1.
Yeah.
You can bet your butt that's what would happen.
What melts freezes elsewhere.
Cool.
Yeah.
Cause you know whenever you hear about Antarctica it's always like pretty grim sounding.
But when I learned that at least some part of Antarctica was growing.
I don't know if it's growing at a rate to...
What's the word?
Like offset the melting you know but...
There is hope.
Ghosts don't belong in Alaska.
I was busy doing finals and forgot about the stream.
No.
That's so much more important.
I hope you...
got them all done and passed.
But...
Yeah.
Thank you guys again for being a little flexible with me and...
Letting me play balloons today instead.
Tomorrow though.
Endurance.
I learned it's not nasal.
I... I'm nervous.
To be honest.
I'm nervous.
But...
Um...
Mmm...
I played a little bit.
I like played a little bit last night and I was like...
Oh god.
I think I got to stage 3.
And I think there's 99 stages or something insane.
Of course it's always a good time with you.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you guys for the funny ice monkey.
And all the super chats and everything.
I always appreciate you guys so much.
Endurance stream?
Yes.
Endurance stream.
I came back from my vacation to Tokyo this month.
Oh my gosh.
Otsu.
It's gonna be rough.
It is gonna be rough.
But...
Let's all... Let's all... I'm gonna do...
I'm not... I'm not... It's not... I'm...
Hold on.
I am planning on not using save states at all.
So...
Um...
We'll see how that goes.
What kind of a game is it?
It's just...
I know you like MGS.
I wear an eyepatch and I'm told I kinda look like Big Boss.
Really?
How... I mean...
That's so cool!
Thumbnail though.
Roy!
Welcome to Mambusha!
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you!
Thank you for the laughs at the stream.
Yeah.
Maybe a little save state as a tree?
No, no.
No, no, no.
No save states.
No.
I gotta do it with all skill.
All skill.
Hopefully we make it.
Hopefully.
We will see though.
We will see.
Get ready for rage.
I'll do my best.
So with that I am gonna go to sleep then because I gotta be up.
Wait.
What time is my stream?
I think it's 2 or 3?
For my time.
Uh...
14 hours from now.
Sleep time.
Thank you.
Oh my gosh.
You guys.
Well.
Actually no.
Never mind.
I'll save this for later.
You'll have to watch the next episode to find out.
Atsuminto everybody!
Atsuminto.
Actually you know what?
Since we're here and it's our first time in the new maid cafe.
Uh...
I'll let the artist know that I used it.
She said I could.
There's actually one other thing that I commissioned from this artist.
So...
But it's not done yet.
I was like waiting.
I was like maybe I should hold out on showing the background.
But I was like It's maid day.
So I do kinda wanna show my new maid cafe on maid day.
Felt a little perfect.
Da ba ba ba.
Da da ba ba ba.
YouTube Tube Tube Tube.
Bustin' bustin' bustin'.
Bustin'.
Also Anthony!
I saw your streamlabs.
Thank you for the spooky number!
Maid channel.
Oh my gosh I missed this!
Oh my gosh.
I'm so... I don't know what's wrong with the sounds.
This is a sound test.
Minto cute.
Minto is extremely cute.
Thank you for the Akadono!
Tell you something.
If there's something weird.
Sleeping in your bed.
Ow!
Let me tell you something.
Oh.
Ba da ba da Ba da ba da ba.
Bustin' bustin' bustin' Bustin' bustin' bustin' See look!
You're sitting at your table all the way over there.
Sorry I didn't give you better seats to the stage but you know.
Um.
It's just you know.
It's a pretty crowded day you know.
And no one...
Thanks.
Sleeping in your bed.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah.
An invisible man.
Sleeping in your bed.
Ow!
Let me tell you something.
I'm so sorry about the streamlabs though.
I will see what is wrong with them so that the sounds come back.
Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Makes me feel good.
Feel good.
Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Yeah yeah yeah.
Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Makes me feel good.
Feel good.
Freaky ghost maid!
Freaky ghost man!
Freaky man, baby!
If you're all alone, let me sleep in your bed.
Let
me tell you something, sleeping makes me feel good.
Yeah!
I ain't afraid of no sleep.
I ain't afraid of no bed.
An invisible bed.
Freaky ghost bed!
Bustin' bustin' bustin' bustin' bustin' bustin' bustin'
Makes me feel good, feel good, feel good, feel good.
Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Yeah!
Yeah!
Blues!
Clueless!
Welcome to Memphis!
Thank you!
Feel good!
Atsuminto!
Have a good night!
Thank you!
Thank you everybody!
Atsuminto!
Bye bye!