OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO Nobody's here yet.
We can just literally kill it.
No, look!
It just refreshed!
We literally just started 5 seconds ago.
Look there's Orca!
Oh... it disappeared.
Stop enabling it!
You couldn't have caught out anybody.
We got the top of the list!
There's people here.
Hi.
Hello.
Mint's being lazy and I'm signing.
You're not even halfway through my file!
Oh my god, we're signing...
It's not my fault you have experience!
We're signing postcards for the Phantom Thief!
Phantom Thief!
Buy tickets, guys!
We're signing the VIP postcards.
We're signing the VIP postcards right now.
We've got time, she'll practice.
I think we're like...
The fumes from the Sharpie.
I think so too.
I think it's healthy.
I don't know.
Guys, just so you guys know, we bought VIP.
I'm sorry we got the one that I fucked up on.
There's several of you guys that...
It's not just those several.
Do you think so?
We got every other postcard!
Every other postcard, you've been like, Oops, I fucked it up.
I really have a reference of my signature next to me.
I know, you're like staring at the screen.
We were dancing earlier and practicing earlier.
We're so tired.
Weren't you gonna stream?
Yeah.
By the way, guys, maybe you restreamed later.
I still don't know.
For those who follow me and follow the Adventures of Russ Blau, literally messaged me on Discord this morning.
It was like, We're gonna parachute into the kingdom today!
I was like, Sorry, I have to dance.
I don't have to dance.
I said that there were people typing.
Wait, there's chat?
No, I don't think it's...
It's just replies.
Did you dance the Macarena?
I wanted to do Soldier Boy, but it was too late.
We finalized our setlist.
Yeah, and I was like, Oh my god, we could have added Soldier Boy.
But we finalized it like last night.
Sorry, whoever gets this one.
How did you fuck it up?
She's stabbing it.
I stabbed it accidentally.
I stabbed it.
Guys, I'm sorry.
There's like several very special ones.
My handwriting is really ugly, so I don't think anybody would know which one's a special one.
They'll all think it's special.
The marker is really thick.
It's not!
The marker's a regular Sharpie marker.
Do you want me to go back to signing?
No.
Okay, yeah, get through my pile.
Yeah, and I know you don't actually mean it.
The same pile.
It took me like 20 minutes.
We weren't talking.
We weren't having a conversation.
We were gossiping.
I was like, should I just do a Twitter space?
So that we're sitting here and we're productive and you guys can listen to us yap.
Yeah, you can hear the Sharpie ASMR.
Can you hear it?
Hold on, I'm going to put the phone.
I've just finished my...
Oh my god, okay.
Do this one.
Okay, okay, okay.
Can you guys hear this?
Whoa.
Oh, new replies, but Twitter's broken.
Yeah.
Did they hear that?
No.
Did they hear that one?
I don't know.
I don't fucking know.
I don't do Twitter spaces.
I'm so tired.
We're so tired.
We still have to practice after this too.
No.
Yes, we do.
We're going to fuck it up if we don't.
And you know it.
I know.
You know it's a very hard dance.
We have a limited time because we're only together for a limited amount of time.
The dance requires a lot of interaction between those two.
Okay.
What are you trying to imply with that?
What does that mean?
I really want to understand it.
Oh my god.
How else do I phrase it?
Please enlighten me.
How else do I phrase that?
I don't know.
That dance has a lot of us having to hold each other's hands in the...
Oh my god.
The more we have gloves on.
Yeah, we have gloves on.
We have gloves on when we hold each other's hands.
Yeah.
We hate each other.
We don't want to touch each other's fucking bacteria.
We actually wear masks like 80% of the time.
We really do.
We don't want to breathe the same air.
Disgusting.
Someone said mistakes make it authentic.
See?
Well, the thing is, I'm the only one that's making mistakes.
Mint has fucking been all the time.
No, I told you that my signature is so inconsistent.
Those postcards are really cute, though.
They're really cute.
Too bad you can't see them right now.
They're very, very cute.
They're very cute.
But, like, our signature sort of blends in with the postcard, though.
Stop, please!
And the correct light, it doesn't.
I like the gold.
I know, but, like, you can only see...
And the correct light, it doesn't.
I like the gold.
I know, but, like, you can only see it like this, you know?
You do it like that, you can't...
No, I see it.
It's the opposite for me.
Really?
I see it, like, when it's, like...
I don't see it there.
I see it now.
Okay, when it shines, you see it, right?
Yeah, yeah.
That's what I'm trying to say.
It looks shiny.
Why is your signature so pretty?
You should have hired me to make your signature.
You know what?
Make me a new signature.
You got rid of the little pee-pee at the end, and then the...
That's like a bullet.
Oh.
That's what it's supposed to be.
What did you say?
It's a dick!
It's a bullet!
I'm gonna start getting rid of it now, guys.
This is a new crash hour.
It's because of what Min said.
I'm getting rid of the bullet in my signature.
What does it look like?
It's because of my handwriting!
My handwriting is perfect!
It looks like a...
Stop!
It's bullet-shaming!
You're bullet-shaming me!
It's a micro-bullet!
Look, you forgot the bullet!
You're just bullet-shaming me, Mom!
Guys, congratulations to the lucky whisp-goon that gets the one with no bullet.
Because, like, you'll know if you get that, you'll know that was when she bullet-shamed me.
I literally made one postcard that only has no bullet.
I can't!
I can't see, like, the new reply.
You know what?
I'm gonna put sad face there so people will know.
Sad face?
Oh my god, there's a sad face!
There's a sad smiley on the bullet chain!
There's an elusive sad hand.
So you'll know this is the one.
I wonder if it's, like, the person who never listened to the Twitter space and then they received it and they're like, why is it sad?
It's like those, like, you know, the factories that receive, like, a child's letter?
It's just like, please help me.
And they're like, what's going on?
And they have no context.
They're like, oh my god, why is there a sad smiley on my postcard?
Have you seen, like, there's some, like, uh, some, like, food, like, like, uh, mac and cheese boxes or, like, some random, like, potato chip bags or whatever that will include, like, a letter that's just, like, Illuminati.
A bunch of numbers and people are like, what is this?
And it's just something that randomly has slipped into some boxes.
Just to fuck with people.
I guess.
I do that.
That's fucking hilarious.
Someone said, size doesn't matter, it's how you shoot it.
Jira, bullets still kills.
No matter what.
As long as they're dead, it's fine.
Oh my god.
Guys, I hope, I do hope the person that gives my sad, the not, the no more, the bullet shamed postcard actually understands the context.
And not some random...
Yeah, if someone, if someone sees that their friend get this, you have to have, like, explain it to them.
Give them the context.
Yeah.
Because I even gave a, I even put a frown face and I don't want them to think that I'm being abused right now.
I don't think they would have thought that.
I put a face, I was like, why did she put a face?
Why is she so sad?
Why did she put a sad face on my postcard?
Clearly she's being abused.
Like, abused mentally by me.
I don't want them to think that.
They'll be like, oh my god, am I supporting a sweatshop?
Oh, I'm so tired.
And you still have to practice, you can't be tired.
I'm so tired.
This is a sweatshop.
Maybe we are, maybe we are.
Signing postcards and now with the dancing lady.
I signed postcards for Patreon, I signed postcards for concert, my life is postcards, never ending hell.
You told me how many postcards she has left to sign.
Because of the...
There's more in that bag.
I know, there's more, but we still have this pile too.
What do you mean?
How is this 200?
I don't know.
It feels like I'm signing 500 postcards.
Maybe it's extra.
Oh my god, I'm counting these, so I signed exactly 200.
We should number them.
True!
Guys, we're going to start numbering.
Okay, we're going to give ourselves more work now.
We're going to number them.
I'm putting number 1 on the sad one.
Okay.
But she shouldn't be sad.
Okay, no, no, no, that's the last one.
That's the last one?
Oh, 200.
Okay, whoever gets 200.
We don't put 200 on it yet, we don't know.
Oh, actually, yeah.
Or should we put it in the back?
Guys, front or back?
Oh, we can't really read that properly though.
Front or back?
I can't see the new replies.
Wait, is it because you're on a fucking Android?
Yeah.
Here!
Oh my god, you're so stupid!
Okay, so basically, there's the most relevant replies, you click it, and you can sort by most recent.
You're so stupid.
Okay, okay.
You're like, oh, you finally have something against me for the bullet.
Whatever.
You're so technologically inept.
All right.
I think she's talking about you!
They're talking about you staying up mumbling!
Refresh.
Oh my god!
You have to click it every time?
This sucks!
Oh my god, they think of a better way!
Okay,
let's see.
Okay, front.
Someone says front.
Literally one person.
Oh, back, front.
Front, back, back, front.
Back, say back.
Because they're gonna display it.
Someone's gonna be like, I'm number one!
Okay, 200 on the sad one.
200 on the sad one.
Lucky 200.
Wait, we should make it silver.
No, make it consistent.
Why silver?
Because it's numbered.
But it's gotta be the same as always.
But it's like not, you can't see it.
I can see it!
Why did we sign all these in gold?
No, I meant the numbers!
Oh, no, I can see it.
I can see it.
Yeah, because the light hits it.
It'll hit it.
The light exists everywhere.
Yeah, but like, okay, if I do it like this...
You see it properly.
It says 200.
Yeah, but it's so hard because there's like red and purple on there.
Then we should have done all the signatures.
No, because we put it in gold.
Wait, number is a different color.
It makes sense.
Guys, okay, guys...
Numbers in different colors are the same color.
Yeah, numbers in different colors are the same color.
Guys, make a poll.
Don't just ask.
Someone said have odd numbers, one color, and even numbers, another color.
You're trying to kill us!
Guys, we don't...
Like, I don't want to say we don't care enough because we care about you guys, but somebody else doesn't care enough.
I do it.
Yeah, I do it.
Get off the floor.
I do it.
I'm trying to get the supermarket to drop.
It's not me.
We know it's the desk that dropped it.
We literally blamed the desk earlier together.
I didn't.
You have no proof.
I'm gonna write one that really just says, like, help me.
Help me, please.
I am trapped.
This is my sad face.
I'm gonna put that in silver.
They're gonna be so stoked.
Are you crossing it out?
Look!
It's so much better.
It looks the same.
No, it's not.
Oh, it does look better.
I told you!
I fucking know color more than you!
Maybe you should've signed it in silver.
It actually looks a lot better.
We tested it, though.
Where's the test one?
Over there?
Yeah.
What's the silver look like?
But silver doesn't match the colors as well.
Oh, true.
The silver one for when it hits that.
Yeah, it doesn't look good.
But up here in the corner, it looks fine.
Who the fuck drew this cat in the corner?
I think...
I mean, I don't know.
It was already on there.
Oh, it was already on there.
Whoever gave us the postcards.
Yeah.
Okay.
Alright.
The divorce is delayed, guys.
Because we came to an agreement on the colors.
On the colors!
Okay, well then, I'll start numbering the ones that...
Yeah, oh, it's true.
You can start numbering them.
Yeah.
Oh, the one should be the helping one.
Where is this helping one?
We haven't written it yet.
We'll get there now.
Wait, so that's going to be number one?
Yeah, it should be number one.
Okay, then I'll start with 002.
Why are you putting 00?
Because it's like 00200.
Just write two!
No, that's not fun!
Why not put an extra number?
Because it's like 001, 003.
I don't care!
I'd rather see something that writes one.
So I'll be like, I'm number one.
You won't be as number one.
It's like 007!
When you get to seven, you can write 007.
It's not funny to write 069.
It looks so ugly!
See?
You write them all.
I give up.
I'm done signing.
She wrote 001 and it looks horrible.
You guys did divorces back on it?
It looks ugly.
See?
Linda's correct.
The extra digits make it feel more official.
See?
Look!
Leading 007!
That's two!
Two for me, two for me, two for me.
Like the anime 009.
See?
Oh, one out of 200.
That's too much work, actually.
Oh, out of the 200?
Yeah, that's a lot of work.
We agree.
We agree on something.
I think...
You know what?
Okay, it'll be so sad if it's just one.
No, it's not.
It's so sad if it's just one number.
We last did this for like three years ago.
I wrote 001.
I just wrote one.
Actually, no.
It might have been 01.
But it was out of 100.
No, because it was out of 100.
No!
Not on this computer.
No, I prefer...
Okay, guys, we can't say what it is.
Remember the last time we gave you autographs?
A very long time ago.
Paige, you were number one.
Did we write 001 or did we write one?
If you had a specific wallpaper that had a message from us and a number...
Oh, Paige is here.
Paige!
Did you write 001 or one?
Paige was number one for me.
I don't remember who was number one for me.
Wow.
You both sold out.
I remember.
Where are you?
See?
I wrote 001!
Oh my god.
I'm consistent.
Thank you, Paige.
It's not fair because she's just agreeing with you.
What?
No.
It's because I'm consistent.
I know it looks better.
Because it's like three digits.
200 is three digits.
And so you go up with the digits.
I just think it looks ugly.
I think it looks ugly.
I think it just...
You don't...
Oh, you can't even fucking say words.
Okay.
When I get...
Numbles.
When I get numbered stuff, I want it to say number one because it's clean.
Clean.
I like it when it's clean.
Someone else said mint is correct.
It's because the Twitter space is on your account.
Okay, well then you start your own Twitter space and you can ask for everything.
We just have a Twitter space.
Do a double.
Double Twitter spaces.
It's just being unproductive at that point.
It's just stupid.
Can we just get through the pile and then we'll be done for tonight.
2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9.
I have nine more to do.
There's no way.
I'm pretty sure that's like a lot of extras.
I'm pretty sure.
There's no way.
It feels like...
When I order them, they come in packs of 250.
So it might be 250.
Okay, so we just don't have to do the little extra 50.
We might as well.
We'll do 20 extra.
We'll see how we feel when we get to the end.
Yeah, I know.
It might be fine.
We're already complaining.
Doki, you wrote number 039 for my autographed item.
Doki!
To be fair, we have consistent rules.
I think...
You are not able to resist!
This is a personal preference, but I'm pretty sure for those, there was a strict guideline.
More digits feel fuller.
Fine.
See?
You're not winning this.
I'm sorry.
Fine!
Just because I have paper plates doesn't mean...
Just because you have actual utensils at home doesn't mean that you're right.
Yeah, I eat off of actual dinner plates.
Yeah.
You guys...
Just because she has her life together doesn't mean she's right.
My afterlife.
I'm dead.
I'm dead and I have more of a life together than you do.
Doki is close enough to sniff for real.
Shut the hell up!
She keeps leaning on me while getting on my phone.
You have your weirdos in here.
Why does Doki sound sexier than usual?
Look at her facepalm.
Are you trying to say your fans don't say the same thing?
They're fine.
You don't think you're sexy?
They don't think I'm sexy and that's fine.
What do they think of you?
I don't know.
What do you guys think of me?
Am I kicking my feet?
What are we?
Chat, what are we?
What is she to you guys?
What are we now?
What do they say?
I don't know.
She's freaky.
Yeah, but that's not...
That's not a thing.
What, freaky?
No.
Wait, what?
Why do they watch you?
Because you're freaky?
Yeah, we're all freaky.
You're all freaky?
Yeah.
What did you do to them?
I have enabled them to unleash their inner freak.
I mean, you fucking stalked them.
I know.
I mean...
I like how at first the Dragoons were like, why doesn't she do that to us too?
Guys, I look at your tweets and replies even the ones that you don't tag.
I just don't say anything.
What?
You want the satisfaction?
You're enabling it.
When someone follows me, I go to their profile.
Every fan?
No, sometimes it'll pop up and I'll be like, who is this?
I was like, your notifications must be fucking hell.
Yeah, because it's not...
I used to have it where it was only people I follow that would show notifications.
But now it's everybody.
Oh, what?
You actually unleashed it?
Yeah, I unleashed it.
But I miss a lot because of that.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
You miss a lot of notifications.
But then I also see who follows me and then I go to their profile.
She was telling me about one wisp that was doing a marathon.
I was just being like, who's doing?
I told her, I was like, you're living my tears through this guy right now.
I was like, that's like...
You like this anime character, okay.
What did he say?
Oh my god!
You ripped your chair in time!
I'm okay, I ripped the chair in time.
Cap that before you...
No, but I own my pants!
Doki is a freak too.
The fact that she doesn't enable us is part of the fun.
So they're just like bursting at the seams.
Oh my god, do you think she read this?
Exactly!
The fun part for me is they're like paranoid because they're like, do you think she read this?
Do you think I posted this?
Do you think she ever read this?
She might be here right now.
And that's the thrill for me.
We have two different thrills, you guys.
She likes it when you know that she's stalking you.
Yeah, I'm stalking you, but also you don't know when I'm gonna show up.
And then for me, I like it when you guys don't know when or when I'm not there.
No, she's not taking off my pants!
I'm wearing pants and I don't want sharpie on them because they were expensive!
Yeah, they look like expensive.
They're like less material, though.
Well, it's just the lace.
Yeah, ooh, guys, there's lace here.
Yeah.
Guys, I'm touching the lace part.
Oh, I see.
Earlier in my life, you gave her so much.
Oh, the one time out of like 20 years I say something.
How long has it been?
How long have you been dead?
Yeah, I want apple juice.
Thank you.
Domestic life now.
I like these bottles, they're cute.
They're shaped like apples.
Drink your apple a day.
We got free apple juice.
Oh my god.
Here we go.
Yay!
Guys, I don't know if I can stream today.
We have to practice dance later.
We're very tired.
We are very tired.
How many hours did we practice dance session earlier?
It was like...
What, we got done at 7?
No, we got there at like 11.
11?
No, we got there at 12.
12 to 7.
It was a 7 hour dance session that we had.
And it wasn't even the dance we needed to practice the most.
I know.
So we're doing our actual practice later today.
But how long?
What, we do it twice?
And then we're like, okay, good night.
At least like an hour, I feel like we should.
It's like, you know, it's that dance has a lot of interaction and stuff.
I'm on my last one.
Yeah, we have barely made a dent.
You didn't even write numbers!
We agreed to the number system and you didn't.
Okay, okay.
It's like 1 in 200, that's it.
We've been talking for so long.
I couldn't have gotten to 200.
Yeah, but we could have gotten at least a 20.
Yeah, now it's my turn.
Your turn to write.
Zero...
I'm gonna be writing even more after this.
Zero, zero, four.
Zero...
Guys, I don't think that's a square.
Zero, five.
Yeah, me counting to 100.
Zero...
Guys...
I'll go to 110.
Zero, zero, seven.
Guys, Mick told me some secrets today.
Whoa, that's all I'm gonna say.
There was something I was gonna say earlier.
I don't remember what it was.
What could it be?
Are you dying?
The air's really dry here.
It's so dry.
Zero, one, zero.
It's so dry here, guys.
Apple juice.
It's good for your throat.
What are you saying now?
What?
What are you guys saying?
My friend told me something.
She was like, don't tell your fans this.
I told her something about my fans.
She was like, don't tell them that you feel this way or else they're gonna get really crazy.
Wait, what?
I can't say it on here.
Type it.
What if I accidentally say it?
I don't think you will.
Secret Neopets codes.
What does that mean?
I wanna know.
Type it.
Why not?
Because then you might say it.
True.
What if I say it?
What if I don't say it?
Yuki, please don't die.
I'll try my best, guys.
But I'm like sitting next to Min right now.
I'm stealing the life energy.
It's how I eat.
Come on, get off my back.
She told her friend that she loves him.
I saw that.
Yuki can't be trusted.
I can't be trusted.
Osni is even saying that.
That guy knows everything.
Osni said that?
He said, Dragoon over Wisp.
That's true.
I know you guys.
You guys know us.
Yeah.
Especially this freak here.
Get a humidifier.
You hear that?
Oh no, now I'm coughing too.
That's right.
I'm gonna get her sick if she can't stream.
You said you weren't sick.
I said I wasn't.
Oh my god.
Who's quote retweeting this?
You're socking quote retweets?
Now we're sick.
Documento podcast.
Absolutely.
Don't bullish me.
Our little podcast.
Just because you got tired of me slowly doing my autographs.
Well, it helped.
It worked.
I was gonna get to it eventually.
I was doing it faster without the podcast because I'm arguing with you.
What?
I was literally doing it much faster.
What would we collab?
Massage.
I'd even play massage.
You play it.
Yeah, and then you'd be here.
I'll drink too because I can't get through with that.
I don't want to be with you drunk.
You can drink too.
I don't drink.
You don't, you're right.
You're gonna be like the designated...
I'll be like fucking sober.
The designated driver.
Now you know how I feel when I have to deal with you sober.
I'm always sober.
But you act drunk.
Just because I turned autocorrect off doesn't mean I'm drunk.
Drunk orc massage.
Our channels will just get banned.
Yeah.
She actually played through the whole game.
Me?
No, I bought it though.
You said you played up to a certain point.
No, I didn't.
Did you even play it at all?
I haven't played it yet, I just bought it.
Oh, mortuary assistant?
Yeah, they updated.
They haven't updated at all.
No, I think they did update it.
Oh my god, my pants, my expensive pants.
Okay, you did that to yourself.
What?
I don't know why I did that.
You're literally picking on it right now.
No, but look at it.
I did that by itself.
No, I love these pants.
Just cut it.
Yeah, I will.
Just cut that thread and then it'll be okay.
Okay.
I'll get scissors.
Oh wait, I have scissors in my bathroom.
Okay, guys.
Let's play the quiet game with me.
Whoever is the most quiet wins this game.
It's a fun game, guys.
If you guys want to win in the video game.
Let's play the quiet game with Uncle Doki now.
We lost the quiet game.
Shut up!
We were having a fun time.
We were having a fun quiet game time and you made us lose.
Guys, I'm not going to talk so you can hear her change her pants.
But I didn't want to practice enough because I didn't want to get sweaty in my pajamas.
So, no practice.
I brought Cinnamoroll.
Oh, that's cute.
Yeah, I think I brought Cinnamoroll pajamas too.
Cinnamoroll pajamas.
Doki always busts out the quiet game when she has a visitation of the Whispersoons.
True.
It's quiet.
It's the quiet game, everybody.
The worst dad.
Time for quiet.
3, 2, 1, quiet.
Oh, you lost the quiet game.
You lost the quiet game.
I'm sleepy.
We're so tired.
Guys, we're so...
Oh, hey, look.
Oh my god, she started listening to your speech.
I should listen to it too.
I should listen.
Oh my god.
Wait, actually.
Request to be a speaker.
I'll go to the bathroom.
Okay, okay.
Okay, hold on.
Wait, hold on, guys.
Did you request?
Oh, wait, wait.
Yeah, sorry.
Okay.
Did you request?
I don't see you.
Oh.
It literally...
It literally says zero requests.
Look, look, look, look.
Look, look, look right here.
Look right here.
It says zero...
How am I supposed to refresh it?
Oh, forward.
Oh my god.
Look right here.
No.
Stop, stop it.
Stop the stream.
I'm trying.
Oh my god.
Literally, you can't refresh a...
Refresh your Twitter.
Yeah.
It showed someone else requesting.
Oh, wait, wait.
Okay, hold on.
Look, it shows this person.
Can you turn it off, please?
So I can walk over to you.
See, it shows me...
Yeah, it shows me this person, but no one else.
See, only one request.
It's a space.
It only shows one person.
Who the fuck is that?
Try coming in again.
Okay.
It didn't work.
Oh my god!
Wait, maybe if I find you...
If I find you, I can invite you.
It says you're not listening.
Yes, I am!
Idiot!
Wait, maybe if I find you...
Hold on.
If I find you, I can invite you.
I requested so many times.
Idiot!
I can adjust the settings.
Wait, now it says 11 people requested to speak.
Hold on.
Nevermind.
I give up.
Turn it off.
It's not me!
Twitter is a broken site!
Twitter...
Okay, then here we go.
You do it.
Give me your phone.
Alright.
Request.
No, don't go yet!
Request the thing first!
I don't know how to use Android!
What do you want me to do?
How do I do this?
Request to speak.
You know how to Android?
I don't know how to Android!
I literally told you I don't know how to Android.
Okay, okay.
Give me a sec.
I'm tired.
I'm so tired.
Okay.
Give me a sec.
I'm really tired right now.
Okay.
Yes.
That's right.
And I am...
Only the top 500 people can listen?
I'm not even in the top 500!
Okay, I can invite you as a co-host.
Wait, if I invite you to a co-host, does that count?
Yeah, but I search your name and it didn't show up.
Okay.
Yes, I did.
I'm not in this space.
Wait, why am I...
Why am I not in this space?
Okay, wait.
I'll restart my Twitter.
Give me my phone.
I'll restart it.
Stop throwing them around.
They're delicate.
Are you guys okay?
Yeah, but they're listening on this phone.
Yeah!
She's throwing you guys around!
Like you're a rag doll!
I dropped you guys as a baby.
I'm sorry.
This is so sad.
I love you guys more than she does.
That's why I'm the weekend dad.
That's why she's the weekend dad.
I requested it again.
Oh, you did?
It shows that I have 10 requests to speak, and then when I go to it, they don't...
No!
You literally don't even show up, and it won't...
I think I just have to end it.
No, that's fine.
I don't need to be in there.
I'm literally in the same room as you.
Why do you want me to request?
I'm literally in the same room.
I just thought it'd be funny.
Get on my bed.
Get on her bed, guys.
I'm so tired.
Let's practice the dance, we can't.
We have to practice dancing.
Can we just lay on the bed instead?
I mean, we technically can.
This is going to be an ASMR sleep stream now.
We can practice while laying down.
That's true.
Let's spoil demolish that list.
I'm dancing in my head.
And then the kicky.
The kick.
And then the...
You know, like when we do the twist to the front?
Uh-huh.
And then we do this thing.
And there's one where we have to do a heart.
And then...
I don't know if we can do the heart, though.
They'll fix it.
They can fix it.
I'll try.
They can adjust it.
We're tired, guys.
It's been a long day.
Can they even hear us?
They can.
They should be able to.
We're tired.
When we fall asleep, then you'll just hear us snore.
You'll hear Doki fart.
Oh, the real scoop.
She's gonna blow her nose.
Where the fuck is the tissue?
I don't know.
In the bathroom.
Oh, it's in the bathroom.
Guys, I'm not sick, by the way.
If I am sick, then we know who to blame.
I will throw the tissue in your room.
Why did you put your socks on the bed?
Those are unused.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Look, they're pizza socks.
Are you gonna wear them tomorrow?
I was going to, but they're kind of high.
I didn't want to get bunched up.
It says yummy.
Yummy pizza!
I'm holding her socks right now.
Oh, my God, guys.
Smelly socks.
My yummy pizza socks.
Did we put this on auction?
No, I like my socks.
I don't want to sell my socks.
I like these ones.
Not even for charity.
You hate charity.
I don't.
Not even for charity.
When did it become a charity auction, huh?
Auction out of greed?
Out of your own pocket?
We see the socks.
I wear these out, though.
So, no, you can't.
Look at all the ankles now.
Sorry, you can't see my socks.
Look at everybody's ankles.
If you're like, we gotta find...
Yeah, but I literally said yummy pizza.
Nothing, you gotta look for yummy pizza.
Fine, I guess I'll just throw these out then.
Because I'll never think I want to wear them out again.
Oh, my God.
You literally read out the text.
I just called them my pizza socks.
And you ruined it.
I can't even...
Google yummy pizza socks and see.
No, no, you're fine.
Is it like a popular...
Yeah, yeah, but I can see the color of the sock.
No, don't say the color.
Because I narrowed it down.
Yeah, exactly.
It says yummy pizza, but you don't know the color of the sock.
Stop saying what it says on there.
Oh, my God.
Look, today I'm wearing cat socks.
It's a brown sock.
Stop
with the cat looks.
I didn't say anything.
If you look up cat socks, there's gonna be so many cat socks.
I know.
Oh, my God, someone said...
Stop blowing your nose.
Someone said, I have those same exact socks.
Sure does.
Post it on Twitter.
And we won't tell you if it's the same socks.
I'm just curious.
Let's see.
Let's get all my socks.
I'm getting all my socks.
Why are you getting all your socks?
It's not like they're post-it sock pictures.
Oh, my God, I have to show you my hat.
But you can't explain this hat because it's actually one-of-a-kind hat.
You're a little boy.
You look like an elf.
You look like a fucking elf.
You don't think you have to do that, Dad.
You have to do that in one of our parts.
You have to do it in that group dance we're practicing tomorrow.
Okay.
You know that one, the short one?
Yes, you have to do the exact dance.
I don't know.
Why not?
I don't want the world.
The world's not ready for...
The world's not ready for that?
Yeah.
You look like a little fucking elf.
I did?
Not in a good way.
What do you mean not in a good way?
I love my little elf.
Not in a good way.
That, like, narrowed it down.
Yeah.
Mint hated one of my songs.
Oh, yeah.
She's a hater.
I'm a hater.
No, she hated two of my songs.
Yeah.
And one of them she has to sing in it, too.
Oh, we did decide that, didn't we?
You can't say that one word.
Oh, wow, someone's showing their socks.
Look at these little doggie socks.
Oh, that's cute.
He doxxes himself.
He doxxed yourself, Shutterdog.
He doxxed yourself.
We're gonna find you.
I'm gonna get those same doggie socks.
I think I've looked at all the ankles now.
Someone I got once a package.
Oh, was it a package?
Retweet, dude.
But it was someone made Wisp socks.
Oh, that's cute.
I'm gonna make socks.
Yeah.
When I fix all my issues.
You're socks-ing yourselves.
Yeah, socks yourself now.
Socks yourself, everybody.
Socks yourself.
Sounds like suck yourself.
Ew.
What?
Socks suck.
Socks sucking yourselves.
Socks sucking yourself.
Socks sucking sex self.
We're not okay.
We're not okay anymore.
Oh, yeah.
I'm gonna tell me what hikikomori is.
Did you post your score?
No, I didn't post it.
I just took the test.
Because everybody's been doing that hikikomori test.
I didn't know what that meant.
Yeah, Doki didn't know what hikikomori meant.
Her score was apparently really high.
No, I've seen way higher.
You have to take it and see what yours is.
My score has to be really high.
I don't go outside.
I know.
I don't go outside except for like this week.
Yeah.
Yeah, but I'm like, you go outside so much.
Only for idols.
I told you.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
She said that and I was like, you talk to him.
And she's like, that's not the same.
They're divine beings.
Exactly.
Talking to an idol is not talking to a normal person.
They are a heavenly being.
And so, therefore, I'm like talking to a deity is not talking to a normal person.
And they're like, so true because we're talking to you too.
What was my score?
My score was like 70.
78.
I didn't say 78.
You did.
You said 78.
Someone posted your shoes for some reason.
Retro doofy shoes.
Oh, yeah.
They're all socks.
Oh, my gosh.
I like the astronaut one so much.
I want those.
Thanks for... Oh, my God.
They have like eggs and bacon.
Ew.
Someone showed their feet.
Ben.
Wait, can I see?
Their feet?
No, I wanna see like what they post.
It's literally just feet.
It's their feet!
Okay, never mind.
Okay, freak.
No, I thought there would be more context.
I thought there would be more context.
And I think a bunch of people's scores are pretty high.
I think we're all just, you know, a little special.
Alright?
Let me go in my room.
No.
We have to practice!
What the fuck?
How are we supposed to practice if we don't- How are we supposed to practice if we don't- How are we supposed to practice if we don't-
Oh my god.
How long has this Twitter space been going?
I don't know.
We finished signing this thing.
I just retweeted it like 10 minutes ago.
You could've reminded me.
You could've said something.
I don't know stuff about Twitter spaces.
I don't do them.
I think I've done it once when I was getting my wisdom- when I got my wisdom teeth removed.
Oh, I like these socks too.
The cats with the little leaves.
They're like Canadian cats.
Why can't you believe that?
Of course!
Of course I care about my dragons more than- more than men cares.
Yeah, I hate wisps.
I hate you guys.
You have a problem.
I would say this- this, like, relationship you have is like- is not healthy.
What are you, my therapist?
I don't need- I hate you guys.
You can't even do it right.
Too much hot and cold.
You gotta have a balance.
Call me Katy Perry.
We're quiet because we're- Tired.
What are we even talking about?
I don't know.
Like, it wasn't even supposed to be a podcast.
It was supposed to be just us trying to get through- get through the- I'm too tired.
Please, we have to- Ouch, ouch, ouch.
You're slapping- you're slapping my knee.
Ow, she's abusing me.
We're gonna slap you.
Guys, help.
I'm being held against my will.
Guys, I slapped your ass today.
Whoa, okay.
I said that and you were like, that's not true.
Wait, you did win.
I thought I told someone and you were like, that's not true.
No, you didn't say shit.
You didn't say anything.
Okay.
Okay, you better not do it again.
Anyway, that wasn't true.
You better not do it again.
I lied.
I just wanted to know what chat's gonna say.
Okay.
Why are you so weird?
Why are you so- Why is that weird?
I was just saying, I just wanted to see chat's reaction.
I didn't slap her ass, I just- I just wanted to see your reaction.
Okay.
Why did you-
I don't even want to look at their reactions.
This is like not even- Is this even content, you guys?
Guys, I think like dumb girls doing dumb things is always content.
That's true.
Yeah.
Or dummy dumbs.
They're so dumb.
People are posting more of their socks.
I like the space ones.
Yeah, I like the space ones.
Guys, if you're gonna post your socks, we're gonna make a hashtag.
There's no Pluto on these socks!
Okay, guys.
Okay, I'm gonna check if this is a real hashtag.
Alright.
Is socks yourself a hashtag already?
Guys, if you're gonna post your socks, can you post it in the socks yourself hashtag?
Is it 1X or 2?
It's S-O-C-K-S yourself.
Socks yourself.
It sounds like a threat.
Post it in the socks yourself hashtag.
Yeah, I know.
I think it should be like S-O-X-X.
S-O-X-X?
Socks?
Like docs, but socks.
Oh, look at these!
Wait, those look like my Wisp ones.
I wonder if they're the same person.
Okay, socks yourself.
Hashtag socks yourself, everybody.
We'd like to see your socks.
Okay, S-O-X-S-O-X yourself.
That's not a claimed hashtag, by the way.
What, S-O-X?
Yeah, S-O-X yourself.
It's not claimed?
No, it's not claimed.
Oh, I thought you said clean.
No, no, no.
Okay, guys.
Alright, it's S-O-X yourself.
S-O-X yourself.
Yeah, that's our hashtag.
Make that trend, guys.
Here, I'll type it.
Okay, S-O, and then you can post a sock that you don't care about.
No, I care about all my socks.
Oh my god, just do a cheap sock.
So we can have, like, context.
None of my socks are cute because I just wear, like, sports socks.
I literally am wearing a Nike sock right now.
These ones match the pants I was wearing earlier.
Oh my god, literally all my socks that I brought were literally Adidas and Nike socks.
This one is, like, just cute.
It has, like, a little moon on it.
It looks like Nike.
And then it has, like, little frills, and then this one has frills.
Ooh, that's cute.
Yeah.
This one looks like the most generic that you can post on Twitter.
Why are they so often, though?
No one's gonna see the top part.
They're just blue socks.
That's why they're generic.
That's why you get socks yourself.
Oh my god, she's telling me to socks myself.
Socks yourself now.
I have more over there, more socks over there.
Oh my god, people are socksing!
Check the tag!
People are socksing themselves!
Oh my god!
All I'm saying is that we're enabling people right now.
Oh, these are pretty generic.
Oh my god, yeah, yeah, yeah, socks yourself there.
They're cute, they're like my wintry socks.
Yeah, take a picture of that.
Oh my god.
What other socks do we have?
Oh my god, someone has...
Oh my god, I love her.
This is so funny.
Oh my god!
These are all my dirty socks.
Look at these cats.
It's like an ultra-realistic cat on my sock.
It's a black sock.
Stop!
She's not going to wear these out!
So many black socks!
It's not like they'll actually figure it out.
They're crazy.
I don't know, it's crazy.
Oh, these are cute.
I like these.
What is that?
Oh, the dinosaur ones!
Why do they look like they're for babies?
How small is your foot?
I guess that's the size of your feet.
Oh, these are hand-dyed.
Wait, that's a glove.
It's a cinnamoroll glove.
I'm not showing anyone my feet.
Look at my gloves, though.
Someone literally just posted their white, normal socks.
It's like their grandpa socks.
Represent.
You don't need cute socks.
Oh my god, Mountain Dew Baja Blast socks.
Whoa, wait, what?
Yeah, they were right above the dino baby socks.
Wait, I didn't see that.
Dino DNA socks, those are cool.
I like that.
Santa socks.
The calico ones are so cute!
Oh, I see the Mountain Dew, yeah.
Count Chocula socks with Count Chocula Crocs?
Wow.
That guy is getting all the ladies.
Tia, what the hell, girl?
Or that girl, who's getting all the ladies.
Whatever, whatever ladies you want.
The Bluey socks.
I don't think that's their socks, they literally just googled Bluey.
That's like, not even actual...
I'm gonna buy them myself, then.
Bluey?
I like Bluey.
I heard Bluey is really good.
I heard Bluey, the reason why their colors are like that, is that even dogs can...
Yeah, so dogs can...
Can watch it, too.
Yeah, it's good for dogs.
Yeah.
Wait, this person has the exact same socks as you.
Where?
I'm joking.
Oh.
I was more curious, I was gonna be like, wow, how?
And then Tia would be like, oh my god, is that actually...
I go to sock stores in Japan and buy all my socks there.
Yeah.
Oh, that's cute, look, there's like, sushi socks.
That's actual sushi.
No, it's not.
Oh, those are socks!
I'm like, she said that and I zoomed in.
I'm like, it has to be for her.
Oh, I like the ocean socks.
Oh, you got them at the aquarium.
Why is it pizza and turtle?
Oh, it's a...
It's a Ninja Turtles.
Has been hotel socks?
There's so many socks in here.
You guys are actually doing this, thanks.
Keeps your socks to yourself.
Yeah.
See, you were like, judging my hashtag.
No, I am just...
Yes, you were.
You were judging my hashtag.
It was such a cute hashtag.
Gabbie, I like your socks.
Thanks for everybody for socksing yourself.
Oh, I like the Donkey Kong barrels.
This is our... this is what you do in our podcast.
Oh my god, look at these sloths, but they're like, dabbing sloths.
It's kind of horrible.
Oh, I like the alien ones.
What is it, three for two?
I like how they're from H&M.
I know, what is happening?
That's three for two.
My oceans really got me to post my feed.
We just want the socks, you don't have to include the feed.
You can take it off your shoe.
We didn't ask for the feed, we just wanted the socks.
You did that yourself.
Take off the socks before you show it.
I think this person put their socks on their dog.
Like, that's not their foot, right?
There's no way that's hair.
That's really hair.
What if they have a really hairy leg?
Is that on your dog, the Mintara ones?
Plant Man?
No, that's on the dog.
Is that your leg?
No, that's... there's no way.
Oh my god, the Metal Gear socks!
Mine came in while I was gone.
Stop.
These ones are so cute.
These bear ones.
Oh, they are in the...
Oh, you just passed it right there, yeah.
A little dog, Shiba Dog.
Mug Buddy.
Gio, your socks are cute.
Mochi, your socks are cute.
Zomfunk, your socks are good.
Happy G, I like your socks.
Regan, I like your cat.
Andy, at home, I like your matcha.
CJ, what are your Scooby Doo socks?
CJ, I like your Scooby Doos.
My phone is starting to get really hot.
Alright, guys, thank you for socksing yourself.
And oldest one, you'll like this.
Crazy cat, dude.
Thank you, ya boy.
Ya boy.
Ya boy for the crazy cat.
Crazy cat socks.
Wait.
Your socks are cute.
Manthy Rose, Manthy.
Manthy Rose, we like your socks.
We like your socks.
Radius, I like your socks.
It says horny for pizza.
Hey, it matches yummy pizza.
Yummy pizza.
One of us is feeling a little freaky for pizza, though.
Oh my god, it's Hello Kitty Gundam socks.
Kida, we like your socks.
Yeah, Kida, we like your socks.
We didn't get our socks look like...
Nova, I don't know if I like your socks.
Okay, I think, look at this, there's Stitch, but Stitch looks like a, look, it looks like a tentacle.
Oh, wait, wait, it's like those hand socks.
Like an octopus.
It's those hand socks where the toes are like...
The split toes.
Yeah, yeah, you know like those, okay, you know like those shoes that look like feet?
Oh, wait, okay, what?
Those shoes that look like feet.
I mean, I hope so.
No, no, because you know, okay, it's like, they're so ugly.
Because like, the whole goal is that it, this one, this one, you know these shoes?
You know, like, I don't know what they're called.
They're like...
They have like, they look very toed.
Yeah, yeah, they're like, they're like, something like this.
Like, toe shoes.
Oh, they're toe shoes.
They're apparently healthier because they simulate, like, simulate like walking barefoot on grass and stuff like that.
Because like, walking barefoot is apparently healthier.
Yeah, I've heard that.
Yeah, but I like, they're so fucking ugly.
And I remember in university, I'd see some, one guy, like, would always wear them.
And I'm like, you're such a...
There's like a Nike shoes that actually are like, they're not, they're like split toed.
Oh.
They look kinda cute though.
Let me see if I can find them.
Like, Nike.
I'm sorry if you wear toe shoes, guys, but like, not in public, please.
Where I can see them.
As long as it's not in public, where I can see them, I'm fine.
You know what, Neppers, I like your socks, because like, those are very similar to the socks I wear.
Like, do you like these?
They look like goat shoes.
Yeah, I kinda like them though.
I want people to think I'm a goat.
Yeah, like, renaissance fair shit.
I'm the goat.
I like how somebody put like...
You guys, when you get your...
Oh, that's cute though.
Yeah, see?
Guys, if you get your mint puppet, put it in a sock like this, like June did.
I have the creature with me.
Put your mint dolls in a sock.
Don't cute Grease, she's kinda fat.
Yeah, like the mint puppet is like, so...
Like, I grabbed onto the mint puppet, and it was like, rock solid.
I told them to put less stuff in.
It was like, rock solid puppet.
I was like, what the fuck is wrong with this puppet?
It's not a puppet, it's a doll.
Like, literally, I couldn't even squeeze it.
That's how hard...
I told them to put less stuff in.
I wanted to like, chuck it, because it felt like a rock.
Well, that's actually, maybe that's better then.
If it's kind of more stiff.
Better for chucking.
Better for throwing the puppet.
Not a puppet, the doll.
God damn it, you have me saying puppet now.
Alright guys, I'm tired now.
Yeah, me too.
I'm tired.
Okay.
Alright guys, we're gonna practice.
Are we?
What do we do in the morning?
Before brekkie?
Yeah, before brekkie.
So we should get up early then, and we go to bed now.
Guys, I might not be able to stream rest, guys, I'm really tired.
We shouldn't have done the Twitter space, we should have practiced.
You said, you said, I said, no we shouldn't, you're like, I'm gonna do the space.
No, you did not say that.
I was like, I'm gonna do a Twitter space, and you were like, okay.
You literally were just like, okay.
I was like, should we though, should we?
You didn't even say that.
Shut the hell up, you liar.
No, I was trying to be a responsible person.
You were signing forever, I was like, well, while we wait, I'll do the Twitter space.
I was literally faster before the Twitter space because we kept arguing.
Oh, we got a good idea.
It was a good content idea.
Yeah.
Okay.
Thanks guys for joining us.
Bye guys.
We're tired, tired, tired.
We might have the op collab tomorrow.
Tomorrow, depends on how fucked up we feel tomorrow, but.
That's the only time we can do it.
That's so true.
And it's not so true.
If we.
It'll be tomorrow night, because morning, morning.
We can't.
Yeah, tomorrow night.
Even if it's just a short one, we could just do a short something.
Yeah, we'll do something short.
But this kind of is like a Twitter stream too.
Not a lot of people use Twitter.
True.
Okay, guys.
Good night.
Bye bye.
Say bye.
Bye.
I'm tired.
Thanks you for socksing yourself.
Thanks for socksing yourselves for us.
Thank you for socksing yourself and seeing our other socks.
We really liked looking at the cute ones.
Yeah.
And thank you for not putting your feet in it too and making it weird.
Okay, we're gonna go to bed.
Good night, everybody.
Good night.
Wait, hold on.
I'm seeing if anybody's saying good night to us.
Who said good night?
Minto and Doki.
Good night.
Bye bye, Minto and Doki.
Doki and Minto.
Shut up.
I want Doki and Minto.
Someone...
Okay, fine.
Next, you said Doki and Mint.
God.
Yeah, bye bye, Doki and Mint.
Oh, thank you.
I knew you were a real one.
I knew.
I'm shutting this off.
Bye.
And...