Punga Punga Manchun, Punga Manchun...
Welcome home, master and lady.
Today...
I would like to play baseball.
Why in Japanese?
Why Japanese?
Today, I want to play...
Kumanopu-san's homerun...
TABIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIII
Japanese, why?
I don't know!
Oh gosh, my voice is...
I had to sing a bunch of stuff today.
My voice is so like...
Chibi-minto kawaii!
Arigatou!
I can't wink.
It's my birthday and I'm sick so thank you for streaming!
Kiera!
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday dear Kiera!
And feel better!
Oh my gosh.
I had to turn the music down way low so I can barely hear the donuts.
I'm so sorry.
There's no God.
Only Christopher Robin.
Christopher Robin.
This game has been living rent free in my brain for so many years.
I tried to play it in heaven too actually.
I wanted to play it the first week I got to heaven.
But Disney!
But I'm indie!
So I don't care about Disney.
Well I care a little bit about Disney.
Hope you have a great day and Kumano Pusan is not a cause of...
Why are you a hater Anton?
I'm not a hater.
Disney does not mess around.
No they don't.
But yeah, we're just gonna start.
So...
I know that there's like a power up.
Like you can power up your stuff.
There's power, meat and speed.
We gotta be meatier.
My birthday is this Saturday.
Can I have an early MGS5?
Happy birthday from Akavius.
Happy birthday.
Congratulations.
Happy birthday with salutations.
Happy birthday.
May your skies stay blue.
Happy birthday to you.
PP Paladin.
Happy birthday!
Are we ready to start everybody?
I think we should just start.
Power to make the ball fly.
Meat to make the ball hit.
The bat easier.
That's what it means.
Like meat the bat, right?
The last to stream to surpass the Yomowari final boss fight.
I want to eat Hachimizu.
Hachimizu is delicious.
Silly old maid.
If the harbinger of spring is the sound of a bat on a ball...
Then I have become the harbinger of winter.
Christopher Robin.
Oh my god.
It starts so fast.
Don't worry about it.
So basically we have...
Eight...
Hold on.
I'm trying to explain the game.
Oh my gosh.
Hold on, Eeyore.
You have seven balls.
And I have to get three home runs, you guys.
Oh my gosh.
Wait a second.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Eeyore, please.
Why am I only getting fouls?
You guys, this is a warm up.
This is a warm up.
That's an example of a home run.
It's okay.
Do you understand how to play the game now?
If you're fouling off pitches, that means hitting the ball.
You just have to adjust your timing.
Okay.
Andregos, thanks for the 10 gifted.
Oh.
Okay.
I'm too... I'm too early.
Tire Robin onto your team.
Nice!
Actually, it took me...
I... I...
Not to say that I practiced, but I...
No!
Foul!
I...
I didn't realize you have to like really kind of hold the bat, you know?
You have to click it down with firmness.
You have to like...
Firmly...
Like you can't just...
You know?
You can't just click.
You have to...
Oh my gosh.
You have to like firmly...
Really...
What?
No!
That was only a hit!
Oh golly.
Please.
It's a hit.
You have to firmly...
You want help?
No.
Why would I want help?
Firmly grasp the bat.
You guys can hear my cough drop, can't you?
Hear my cough drop, can't you?
Can you hear my cough drop?
Oh gosh.
Oh no!
You can't?
Oh, good.
Oh god!
Oh, I'm a foul!
That's a home run.
Yeah!
Cough drop ASMR.
I'll be probably guzzling these babies down.
Probably guzzling these babies.
Oh, foul.
But if we get more stuff...
Oh, whoops, my bad.
If we get more bonus points, we can add...
We can enhance our skills.
You're foul.
You're foul!
Oh, whoops, my bad.
I wasn't paying attention.
Oh, there's one more.
You aren't supposed to use upgrades.
What are you talking about?
My Kamiyoshi Pikami used upgrades?
I will use upgrades too.
Shut the hell up.
What is this guy's name?
Rumpy?
Oh my god.
Is that a fowl?
What's his name?
Eeyore's down.
I think that's just a hit.
I've literally never seen this one before.
Oh god.
Oh!
I think that counts!
Wow, 139.
Okay, let's go.
I'm killing it.
Let's go.
I've never seen this man in my life.
There's like... Oh, that's just a hit.
There's like a... They're from the movie.
Yeah, there's like a bunch of Heffalumps, I think.
They're called, right?
There's like the guys that are... Oh, shoot.
Minto playing peek.
Oh.
Yeah, there's like a Heffalumps.
I don't think I'm gonna make it.
Oh wait, maybe.
There's still five left.
Let's have faith.
Okay, if you throw it that close to me, are you trying to kill me?
This guy is trying to murder me.
This is Kingdom Hearts 4.
Yeah.
Oh, please!
Why is that a foul?
Please make it.
Oh!
I love baseball!
The clutch.
Piglet.
Pigleto.
We have to...
We have to hit eight.
Oh my god, he's fast.
What does he do?
He jumps and...
Oh, gosh.
Why does he look so smug over there?
Oh, god.
Oh my god, Piglet.
Oops.
See his kid degrees, baby.
Oh, god.
He spikes it.
Oh, it's just a hit.
Why is he so smug about it?
Please be a homerun.
Foul.
Guys, that's fine.
Oh, okay.
I don't think this is a curveball.
Oh!
Wow, that counted.
Okay, let's go.
He's so fast.
Oh, shoot.
Okay, that was too off.
Oh!
I made sponsor the Winnie the Pooh baseball team.
I'm trying to...
My team is at a disadvantage.
We have this really hungry guy, okay?
Oh, gosh.
Oh, no, I'm not going to make it.
I'm not going to make it.
Wait, am I?
Hold on.
No.
Oh, no.
I got confident.
We have a really hungry...
Oh, why did I...
Why did I do that?
Hold on.
Stop sending me super chats.
Oh, stop sending me super chats.
It's so Jover.
I said I might make it and I immediately missed every single one from there.
I couldn't donate on your anniversary, but I just want to say you made me laugh in moments.
I really needed it.
Oh, Peachy, thank you.
Pooh's Heffalump movie.
When Roo sets off on his own 100-acre woods, he discovers a friendly and helpful heffalump named Lumpy.
Oh.
Your feet have to be in contact with the mound.
Yeah, where's the ump?
Send more super chats now.
Pigletto.
Okay, we got this.
Come here, Piglet.
Oh, God.
The first one is so fast.
He's trying to kill me.
He's like, I'm sick of...
Oh, gosh.
He says, I'm sick of this Pooh Bear.
This Pooh Bear who's hungry for...
Oh, my God.
It was so close.
All he wants is honey.
Both distracting and free.
Nice.
Trying to take my head off.
That's what I'm saying.
Oh.
I wonder what my highest is.
Oh, my God.
Why is it so fast?
Piglet.
Come on.
That was not a foul.
That...
Ref.
Where's the referee?
No.
That was a foul.
Where's the referee?
Where's the umpire to call that one?
That one was in.
Let's go.
Thank you.
I think this is it.
Okay.
Nice.
Please stay in.
Yeah, baby!
Boo-hee!
I wonder what my longest distance is.
Nice.
Free Supas!
Hit it out of the park!
Thanks, Jack!
You can never be around cause busy, but I love you, desu.
Thank you, desu!
Piglet is also refereeing.
Hmm-hmm!
Good job, guys.
No Supa, but Streamlabs is okay, right?
I can barely hear it though.
Because I had to turn down this music so much.
Oh boy.
Kenga time.
Okay.
Those are just warm-up rounds, right?
Kenga and Ruru.
I used to love Ruru.
For anyone more curious...
Oh my god.
Um...
Holy moly!
I'm cracked.
142?
I think that's my longest.
Oh, okay.
Um...
Uh...
The first is how many balls they have.
The second one is how many home runs I have.
And the third is how many balls are left.
Oh, no!
Sorry.
The first one is my goal.
How many home runs I need to get.
I need 12 home runs.
Oh!
Oh my god.
That was unfair.
Okay.
It's not...
Hits don't count.
Which is such...
They should count for half of something.
They should count for half.
I swear.
Oh god.
Okay.
Four?
It's a home run derby.
Not a hit derby.
Oops.
You're right.
That was a foul.
It's all...
The hits should still be like...
Half or something.
Right?
You should get half a point.
And then if I get two hits...
I get...
Oh, dang it.
Do you have a super chat?
Thank you.
I can't read the whole thing right now.
Hold on.
Oh.
Okay.
That's a foul, isn't it?
Why...
When it's so slow...
It's hard to count.
When it's so slow, it's hard to count.
Okay.
Nine.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, my God.
Oh, this is going to be so...
Uh oh.
Ah ha ha!
You guys, I don't think I'm going to make it.
There's only three balls left.
Alright.
I got so far.
Tonight.
Nice!
Good start!
It doesn't even matter, I had to fall to lose it all.
But in the end, it doesn't even matter.
142!
What if I don't want to upgrade?
Stop spamming!
Don't backseat!
No backseating, you guys.
I'll upgrade when I feel like it.
Oh my god!
I wouldn't have homerun that one anyway.
Strike three!
You're out of the park!
Can
I passenger seat instead?
What sounds do kangaroos make?
Oh, I think that's not in.iii!
Ehem.
The sound, boxing sounds, they like... No, they have to make a sound.
Oh, dang it.
They probably like...
Oh gosh, they probably like squeak or something, right?
Oh my god, oh no no no no, here's where it happens!
Oh god.
They probably be like...
Nice.
Ten?
Alright, alright, two more, two more, two more.
Oh gosh!
Okay, one more!
We got it guys, we got it.
Maybe I'm secretly a genius at this game.
I say as I strike.
Oh, I forgot the rabbit's name.
Oh, it's just rabbit.
Rabbit!
You're overthinking it.
Huh?
How do you do that?
He controls time and...
Oh my god, my bad.
He controls time and space!
Wait!
He controls... I need to get 15 overrides, I can't even get a single hit in!
Oh my god, wait.
Oh no!
Rabbit!
It's actually... it was my fault.
Remember how I said you have to like really... you have to commit to the... to the press?
It was my fault.
I wasn't committing to the press.
I wasn't committing to the press!
Well, that's a foul.
It was my fault.
Say yes to the press.
The world!
Please, please, please.
Don't prove I'm wrong.
Please, please, please, please.
Nice.
Press, press, press, press.
Press!
A foul.
I'm spitting out of fear and it's like getting on my monitor.
I'm like...
Oh.
Just kidding.
Maybe that'll be it.
Nice.
I'm like...
All over my monitor.
Okay.
Chat, I expected better of you.
Really?
Okay.
Ten?
We got seven left.
We need five more.
Don't mess this up, Minto.
Oh, gosh, Minto.
Uh-oh.
Uh -oh.
Perfectly.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
I work better under pressure, baby.
No way.
No way, no way.
We were so close.
I was so close.
Okay, but I know his game now.
Kind of.
A little more!
Send
me your strength.
That's just a hit.
Hit!
Nice.
It was the ping!
Send me your energy!
Spirit bomb!
Okay, you didn't send that much energy because that was really close to not being a home run.
Actually, Rabbids is not so bad usually.
I say as I don't make it.
But I at least hit it, you know?
That is a hit.
Oh no.
Oh no, no, no.
I still need ten more.
Nine more.
Rabbit, it's rabbit hunting season.
Okay, maybe I shouldn't taunt the rabbit.
Hey, batter, batter, batter!
Oh no, oh no, no, no, oh no.
Wait, I'm the batter.
Oh wait, wait, wait.
I misclicked.
Oh no.
Hey, batter, batter, batter.
Hey, batter, swing!
Batter, batter, batter.
Nice.
Some of the slow ones are really stressful, I'm not gonna lie.
Hey, pitcher, pitcher.
Hey, pitcher.
Hey, pitcher, you pitcher of water.
Okay.
Hey, pitcher.
Oh no.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no.
I still need six more.
Uh-oh.
I need home runs.
Home runs, baby.
Home run derby.
Hit or miss?
I guess they never miss.
No!
Please!
Please, that wasn't a foul.
Oh, rabbit, please!
I still need five more.
No!
Oh!
Oh my gosh!
Oh gosh.
Oh-oh.
Oh, gosh.
It's only fouls.
Okay.
Nice.
Just come back.
I'm choking.
No!
Okay.
Three.
Three left.
Two left.
Nice, nice, nice, nice.
Okay.
Two left, two left, two left, two left, two left.
That was 142.7!
Thank you for the super chat.
No!
Wait, wait, wait!
Oh god, oh god, oh god.
Please, not again.
It wasn't even a home run.
You're gonna regret going through this if you haven't already.
Two, I can't believe the first thing that came to my mind seeing this is the Pooh horror movie.
I'm not regretting anything.
So close each time!
So close each... Foul!
Believe in yourself as a gamer.
Oops.
Oh, I didn't commit to the... That was my fault.
Believe in yourself as a gamer.
The fouls are gonna mess me up, man.
Nice.
Mr. Instincts.
As a gamer.
We're hitting?
Oops.
Our stats are not looking...
143!
Oh, so great right now.
It's just a hit.
But you know...
Every Shonen protagonist...
Has...
A recovery...
ARK!
Oh, dang it.
Oh, no.
I have to be really locked in now.
Guys, I don't think I'm gonna make this one either.
I think we're...
I think Rabbit's gonna...
Filter us.
Guys!
Nice.
Wow!
That one's...
That one seems pretty far.
Please, please, please, please!
Nope.
Guys, it's so over for us.
I'd have to hit every single one.
I'd have to...
I'd have to do every single one, please.
Oh!
Nope.
That's it.
How close will I get though?
Oh, that's a foul.
So the foul is timing and not like the placement of my bat?
I don't understand that.
It's both.
Oops.
Hey, bada-bada-ba.
Swing!
Bada-bada-ba.
Hey, bada-bada-ba.
That's okay.
It's okay.
We get close every time.
How many stages are there?
I don't remember.
This is a Flash game, actually.
Oh.
Eight stages.
Okay.
Does that include Christopher Robin?
Isn't he a special stage?
Okay.
Oh, no, no, no.
3 after Rabbit.
What the?
He's number 8?
Okay.
Please, please, please.
Yes!
Why is it so slow?
Oh please, please.
Nice.
Lock in, Minto.
Locked in.
No!
Please.
Nice.
Yeah.
I'm locked in.
Oh!
Yeah!
I
already know that their upgrades exist.
Oh
come on!
That was your fault, Rabbit.
That was your fault.
It was so slow.
So slow.
Oh come on.
Okay.
6 more.
5 more.
Dang it.
Okay.
Please, please, please.
6 shots.
Nice.
Sometimes I can't tell though.
Sometimes they move so slowly.
Oh no!
There's very little room for error here.
Okay, okay, okay.
I wonder even how many points I have.
What do you do?
Here?
Wait.
Actually, where do I do the...
Where do I do the upgrade?
Oh.
Oh, status.
My bad.
I thought it said stage.
Whoa!
I have a ton of points!
Stage.
Select.
Mr. Owl.
Okay, I need...
Oh!
Okay, I need 19.
Okay.
Oh my god.
Oh gosh.
Wait, do I have to have...
Do I have to have power?
Oh god.
What?
Do I have to have more power up?
Oh I'm not... I'm hitting but I'm not getting any...
Oh no, no, no.
Uh oh.
Oh!
Nice!
I beat him without upgrades?
Okay.
Show off.
Chill!
Tip of the bat equals... Yeah, yeah.
I know, I know.
I know.
I'm trying to get it in the green.
You know?
Wait, who was standing behind Pooh?
Who was standing behind Pooh Bear?
Is that me?
Oh, it's a fowl.
He was downgrades.
Wait, is it Gopher?
I think.
I think it's Gopher.
I used to love his whistliness.
I'm Gopher.
Uh oh.
There's no way this is happening.
How the hell?
Oh, nice.
Okay, we really have to get it on the tip.
We really have to get it on the tip.
Oh.
Or a strike.
Two.
Okay.
Oh, even that though was just a hit.
Oh my god.
Oh, that one was good.
That one was good.
That one was mighty.
Who the hell is Gopher?
That's not his name?
Wait, is his name not Gopher?
We're not gonna make it.
But, it's good to get some practice.
He has already figured out...
Wait, what?
What does that say?
Hold on.
Wait a second.
Oh.
Why is it so close to me?
How do you throw it like this?
How do you actually throw it like this?
What's wrong with you?
What's in this ball, you cheater?
I'm not doing so bad though actually with this.
Dang, if I hadn't messed up in the very beginning, I would have been done...
I would have been pretty good.
Oh, just kidding.
Just kidding.
This guy's a cheater.
Wait till Tigger.
I'm scared.
I don't remember how Tigger's pitching is at all.
I don't remember.
Okay, we got to 12.
Oh, 11.
Sorry.
I'm getting ahead of myself.
We got to 12.
This is not pre-recorded.
Oh my god.
Pre-recorded.
Nooooo!
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no.
You guys, give me one second.
You're gonna have to listen to this horrifying music.
I'm gonna grab food really quickly.
Actually, hold on.
I'll put on my own music.
Sorry.
I suddenly started to get so hungry.
I'm gonna... Sorry.
Oh, my god.
I should have eaten before stream.
It's my fault.
I'm an idiot.
I'm a dummy dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb stupid head.
I'm really sorry.
I should have... I should have eaten before... before... before stream.
I'm so sorry.
Okay, BRB!
BRB!
I quickly grabbed a pizza slash.
Mmm, yum yum.
Pizza!
Pineapple and green pepper?
Yeah.
Pizza.
Oh my.
There's something on that I don't like.
I'm almost done.
It's a small slice because I got a smaller size.
Could use some candy corn?
Huh?
You're judging me for...
You're judging me for putting...
Pineapple?
For putting pineapple and green pepper on mine?
But you're gonna say, oh...
Could use some...
You know...
Could use some candy corn on my pizza.
Ha ha ha.
Ignore the fact that, you know, I totally judge you for...
for...
having a...
green...
green pepper and a pineapple.
That's so crazy.
This is Captain K.
Come in, Minto.
Be careful.
There's a dangerous foe on the enemy team.
Codename Robin.
They say he's able to manipulate physics itself...
into baseballs for powerful and deadly throws.
Mmm.
Thank you, Captain.
Pineapple and cucumber pizza?
Not gonna lie?
Would.
Green pepper is great.
As is pineapple.
I know.
And together, they're awesome.
Ha ha.
Keep up the great work.
Thank you.
Cheers.
Hey, I'm no cheap.
This is a cheat engine.
I'm no cheater.
I'm no cheater?
Why does Owl look like that?
Why does he look like...
He's so...
I dunno.
Jalapeno and pineapple?
I can't have spicy, though.
He's sophisticated?
I'll give you a piece.
He looks really disappointed.
He looks so disappointed.
He's just like...
Okay.
Let's get back into the game, everybody.
Did you miss this song?
Also, Verlin, before I...
Because I'm not going to hear your donal.
But welcome back from your trip!
Knock it out of the park.
Thank you!
Thanks for the very spooky donal, too.
Okay.
Here we go.
Cool.
Where's Tigger?
I'm not there yet.
Two!
Guys, I know your games.
Owl, I know your games.
I know your games.
Oh!
People said that the Japanese one was harder.
Which is if you're curious why I'm playing it in Japanese.
They said it was harder than the English one.
Got 93% on my final.
Let's go!
Hold on.
This next one's for you!
No, run!
Oh.
Hey, hey, wait, wait!
Don't distract me!
That one's for you!
There is an English version.
It's on some Disney site.
This one I got from the Internet Archive.
Oh God.
Uh-oh.
Oh!
Please... Please!
No!
What's wrong with me?
Nice!
Oh my god!
That one was a pure skill issue.
Ten more!
But we only have room for an error for two.
So... I mean for one.
Why is
it so close to me?
You're trying to kill me!
That was a foul pitch!
I spat all over my monitor again.
This never happens.
I'm getting really into it.
Thanks for the hot dog, weenie.
You're a little weenie.
That was an owl pitch.
Now I'm hitting them.
This is messed up.
This is so messed up.
I can't even win!
Okay.
Foul.
Owl.
So after owl is...
Shoot.
Is a... Tigger?
Oh no, no, no, no.
Come on!
Okay.
I'm gonna hear this in my dreams.
Why are they calling me weenie?
Weenie's losing.
Oh, shoot.
Oh, that was so close.
Why did they call him weenie?
Weenie's losing.
It's so...
Oh, shoot.
I was too slow.
Come on!
This is not looking good for us, you guys.
Oozzy the Pooh.
Can I restart the level?
Can I restart the level already?
I'm not gonna make it.
Oh, bother.
We need to make it to Robin.
Oh, we'll make it to Robin.
A hundred percent.
Hasn't even been an hour.
Four.
We're gonna make it to Robin.
Come on!
Oh, li-li-li-li-li-li-li.
Oh, come on.
No.
Oh!
I think that's it, right?
Yeah.
I can't make it.
Oh, my God.
Gopher.
Why does he glide like this?
I can't with him.
Oh, that was a good one.
I have a system.
The system.
Wow.
That wouldn't have even...
That was...
That baited me.
I thought it was a home run.
For real.
It's cruel that it lets you keep playing even after you can't win.
Right.
But I guess if you wanna, like, just practice, you know.
Who play-tested this game and thought the difficulty level was acceptable for children.
They were like...
It's just a dumb owl.
Oh, come on.
Something to keep the kids busy.
You know?
It was a parent that played this and was just like, my kid will be playing it for hours.
My...
My kid will never get off the computer.
They'll leave me alone.
That's what they thought.
Believe in us that believes in you.
Yeah.
That was so close.
Oh, dang it.
Fard.
Hito.
Just like a Minto.
Minto.
Thanks you guys for... I actually... I think it's so funny that people started calling me Minto.
Even though my name is just Mint.
But people started saying Minto.
I think that's kind of fun.
Stop!
Please!
Thanks for indulging me in my stupidness.
That's not a foul.
Nice.
Our nickname for our maid.
It's always these ones.
That are too slow.
I can't make it anyway.
Owl.
What the hell?
Did I just out of whim?
Maybe this is the stream.
Strat.
What?
Maybe this is the Strat.
Min in Swedish means...
Mine.
So it's Mito.
Mito.
What is toe in Swedish?
Oh.
Dang.
Mito.
Is this the furthest we've gotten, you guys?
12?
19 is rough.
19 is really rough.
Johnny Bravo!
You know, maid mama.
They sometimes serve baseball peppermint at these games.
But the mint I prefer is the pretty one on my screen right now.
Johnny!
Oh...
Whoa...
EVIL...
Did they really serve mint at baseball games?
Did I escape?
Oh my god.
I can't leave this screen you guys.
I'm stuck here.
You can't leave the game once you're in the game.
You can't I'm going to leave the game.
Whoa, mama.
This is what I'm going to do to your head, owl.
Winners don't hit restart.
I hit.
I could technically still make it, which is insane.
Oh, never mind.
So
close.
Okay, never mind.
Now we're...
I have to be a god gamer.
Why was it so far away from me?
Okay, this is it.
Just can't miss.
Why you guys got to jinx me like that, huh?
It's your fault.
How far can he get?
I'm trying to see how far forward he can get.
I guess this is the furthest he can get.
It's not my fault.
It's not your fault.
Everybody, it's owl's fault.
It's owl's fault.
Please, let me out of here.
If you get all the way to the owl, you can knock him off the mount.
Actually, he's on a tree stump.
How is that a hit?
Or a home run?
How the heck?
Also, statistically, Pooh Bear is insane.
He's getting all these home runs.
Pooh Bear is kind of insane.
Which version of Little Busters is this?
Yeah, Pooh is kind of cracked.
It's all that honey.
Oh god.
Starting strong.
It's the lack of pants.
Do I need to take off my pants?
Oops.
It's so easy to underestimate...
Or to misinterpret the speed of this thing.
Like here.
I'm already...
You guys, I'm already having bad feelings.
Just like Strike Witches.
What?
That was...
That baited me so bad.
I thought that was it.
I thought...
I thought that was a home run.
Are you kidding me?
It was just a hit.
Oh my god.
That one was speedy.
I'm regressing.
Lock in my child.
Okay.
And...
We're basically done.
Let me court things with a gift.
Dude.
You are trash.
Get ready.
Poobear is coming.
Pool bears not even wearing shoes.
He has no proper hitting shoes.
Let me court things with the five-grifter.
I will need to be tested.
If we're doing a home run derby, this needs to be a fair, clean game.
Let me court things.
This needs to be a fair, clean game!
Speaking of poor stats, who's going to run sabermetrics on the entire 100 acre wood?
Alright guys, alright.
Locking in, locking in.
Take our energy, Minto.
Oh!
Three!
That one was more than just a hit.
Come on!
Thank you, Shallows.
I'll read it once I'm done.
Please!
No!
Oh my god!
Just
barely!
Just barely!
Eight.
Oh, we're halfway there!
No!
That one!
We're halfway there!
Now we're halfway there.
Oh god.
Wait.
I can't miss one.
Wait, I just missed one.
Oh... I just...
Uh...
Oh wait.
It's 19!
It's not 18!
Oh, never mind.
It's not even... Oh gosh, I even got the number wrong.
Oh, finally it's over.
Shurya!
Birds.
Okay.
Owl.
More like.
We haven't even made it to Tegu yet.
Do we need to call an exorcist?
No!
I think fowls should count.
I'm still technically getting it really far.
Just backwards.
Yeah, maybe call an exorcist for the ball, honestly.
Call an exorcist.
But not for me.
Oh, is this supposed to be fun?
I think challenging things are pretty fun.
Oh, whoops.
My bad.
That was my bad.
Even though I go a little cuckoo crazy.
Cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs.
While it's happening, you know?
Oh, come on.
That one was really far away.
Please not a fowl.
Okay, now it's Jover for real.
Now it's really over.
Oh my god.
I can't...
I get like...
What's it called?
Like I'm trying to get the tip, right?
But...
I think I'm miscalculating how...
Where...
I don't know.
I'm miscalculating.
Like see?
I feel like that should have...
I don't know.
I have no idea.
What's the goal?
We have to get 19 home runs and we're at 4.
5.
Can't make it though.
There's only 11 balls left.
We need a break.
There's some incredible memes about this game.
Versus Robin Hood is my favorite.
Oh, it's Robin Hood.
Versus Robin Hood.
Christopher Robin.
Long time VOD.
Head poking you for the first time in life.
Thank you.
Your MGS catalog is the best when I'm chilling with some games.
Have fun at the con.
Thank you so much.
Christopher Robin Hood.
This guy is stealing from my sanity.
Who invented baseball?
I hate Americans now.
Who invented...
John Baseball.
I hate you.
John Baseball is the worst guy in history.
I will invent a time machine.
I will go back in time and I will erase that guy.
We will never have baseball.
I will never have baseball.
I will never
have baseball.
Even I will never have baseball.
I think 12 was the closest we got in guys.
But they'll still release this game, you know?
They'll find a way.
They'll find a way to still release this game.
Disney will be like, look.
Look.
We came up with this ultra innovative, super cool game.
Same.
No one's ever heard of it before.
It drains your sanity.
If I beat this, I'm gonna eat a whole thing of honey!
Oh my god.
All the fowls though.
Nice!
Oh, that was like a perfect hit, wasn't it?
Straight down the middle.
Alright, alright, alright!
Nooo!
Not enough.
Okay, okay!
We're at four!
We're still at four!
That was too close to me.
Literally hit an invisible wall.
I'm gonna...
Owl, I'm going bockards.
Owl, it hit an invisible wall.
They were cheating!
The Hundred Acre Boys is against me!
OOOH!
Oops, that was me.
NO!
Seven.
It's the hits.
Eyy!
Please not be a fat...
Mr.
Owl, how many times does it take to beat your level in winning the Pooh's Home Run Derby?
Let's see...
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Five...
Six...
Seven...
Eight...
Nine...
Ten...
Eleven...
Twelve...
Thirteen...
Fourteen...
Fifteen...
Sixteen...
Seventeen...
Eighteen...
Nineteen...
Twenty...
Twenty-one...
Twenty-two...
Twenty-three...
Twenty-four...
Twenty-five...
Twenty-six...
Twenty-seven...
Twenty-eight...
Twenty-nine...
Twenty...
Twenty-one...
31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50!
I beat my old... No, I didn't beat... I reached my old record!
I reached my old record.
12!
You wanna do upgrades now?
Nope.
My record is not beat.
You doing okay there, Minto?
Yeah.
I'm dandy-grandy.
Take me out to the ball game.
Take me out to the crowd.
Buy me some pizza and cracker jacks.
I don't care if I ever come back.
So we root, root, root for the home team.
If they don't win, it's a shame.
Cause it's 1, 2, 3, 4, 5...
Six strikes, you're out at the old ball game.
What did they say?
Pizza?
Wait, what is it?
How many?
What did they buy?
Something and cracker jacks, right?
Hot dog?
Peanuts!
I thought it was a pizza.
Pizza still works.
It does, right?
Oh shoot, dog.
Peanuts and cracker jacks.
Ow!
I don't care if I ever come back.
Oh shoot, come on, I'm throwing now.
I was doing so well.
There we go.
Okay, nine left.
Nine left,
come on!
I hope one hits Owl in the face.
Oh yeah, we were pretty robbed for that one.
We were robbed, we were robbed.
Oh come on, please, please, please.
I thought it would not be a foul.
That one was really far to the right.
Oh god, oh god, oh god, oh god.
We beat my record!
Uh oh.
Oh no, no, no, no, no.
I
was doing so well.
Oh god.
I was doing so well.
Real, real, real.
I like, in the beginning, I had like six in a row or something crazy.
I just didn't want to say anything because...
Oh my god, I can still swing even from back here.
Money to restore sanity.
Hey!
Ah!
No!
Go back to singing?
What should I sing?
Stop throwing and swing?
No, I'm putting you in time out because I'm letting it restart.
Stupid!
I'm not throwing, I'm letting it restart!
Dummy!
Can't you tell?
I had too many mess ups in the beginning!
God!
I wish though...
Oh my gosh, I still have 17 left though.
I wish that I could get through it.
Throwing the game, stop lying.
You just want to be put in time out.
You just want to be put in time out, stupid.
Put that man out of the park.
Yeah, it's called strategy chat.
If I mess up in the first five turns, I...
Just don't even... I just give up.
Swinging the bat at the owl.
What if I like...
Yeah, what if I like throw my bat at the owl?
And then he dies.
The world will cheer.
Death to you, owl.
Owl.
Owl, I hope the next worm you eat is your last.
And I hope it's a disgusting rotten worm.
I hope...
I hope when you're old and your little baby owls are having to take care of you, they throw up in your mouth to feed you because you can't feed yourself anymore because you're just so old.
And you know what?
You hate it.
You're just like, this is such an embarrassing life for me now.
I have to have...
I'm just like a baby.
I'm getting thrown up in my mouth.
I hope so.
What?
That's how birds eat.
Little baby birds get thrown up in their mouth.
Just like me right now.
I have to open my mouth.
Too far, streamer.
Okay.
Take me out to the ball game.
Take me out to the crowds.
Buy me some pizza and cracker jacks.
I don't care if I ever come back.
So let's root, root, root for the...
Worm team.
If they don't win, it's a shame.
For it's one, two or three strikes, you're out at the old ball game.
Oh, say can you see?
By the dawn's early light.
What so proudly we hailed at the twilight's last gleaming?
Whose broad stripes and bright stars through the perilous fight.
O'er the ramparts we watched were so gallantly streaming?
And the rocket's red glare.
Okay, Americans, calm down.
This is an American game.
Were so gallantly...
Gleaming?
I don't remember the words.
How the rocket's rainbow bombs bursting in air.
Gave proof through the
leg.
Was still there.
Okay, not that ball, but you know.
Yo, please.
All I'm getting are fouls and hits!
This is so unfair!
That was so a home run!
That was not just a hint!
I mean a hit!
Please!
Oh say, can you see?
Yeah, it's not possible, no.
Just four?
What's another song I can sing?
We gotta be really patriotic, apparently.
It works.
This land is your land!
Okay, never mind.
Wrong song.
They don't want to hear that one anymore.
Oh, Canada!
Country roads?
Almost heaven.
West Virginia.
Blue Ridge Mountains.
Shenandoah River.
Shit.
Life is old here.
Older than owls.
Owl, your days are numbered.
Just like this match.
Oh, never mind.
That's fine.
Okay, four.
Clip that and send it to Owl.
Oh, he knows.
He knows.
Owl City Fireflies.
You would not believe your eyes.
Oh, shit.
That was mean.
No!
Guys, I don't think this is the one either, though.
Why so many Fowls?
Because he's a Fowl.
Fowl City.
That's just New York.
Oh, come on.
That one was so fast and so close to my face.
Guys, it's not possible.
It's not possible.
You guys, be honest with me.
Do a lot of people struggle on Owl?
Is it just me?
Am I...
Yeah?
Okay.
It's just you.
Oh!
Oh my god.
Sorry, I accidentally clicked the status link.
Owl's the gatekeeper?
Okay.
I was...
That went in between the fence?
I'm sorry.
How was that a hint?
Who was going to go pick that up?
That one was far.
And I couldn't gauge it.
You guys, it might be time for...
Okay, you know what?
After this one, I'm doing a upgrade.
I'm going to do upgrades after this.
Acceptable to quit after Owl and be a...
No!
Why would I quit after Owl and still be a...
What?
Hell no.
If other VTubers also do...
If other people do upgrades too...
I can do upgrades.
Keep starting up.
And of course I will...
While you...
Oh my god.
Our map is...
It's like...
Oh...
What is this?
For my 3.8?
I'm like 0.9.
As the leagueing, Game run.
Oh, strike.
Striker!
Him or the hero used upgrades.
Not a foul.
It is a foul!
Foul.
It's just one foul after this.
Oh, it's not even possible for me to beat this.
I just realized.
It's not even possible for me to beat this level anymore!
Not with that attitude.
Yeah, let me just hack the game and insert more balls.
Everybody gets more balls.
Oh, that was actually not bad for just a random one.
Computer.
Increase balls and ball size.
Increase ball, ball size.
Ten is not bad, I guess.
It's over halfway there.
Alright.
How many points do I have?
So probably speed...
and meat.
Wow, power is 500 points.
Okay.
Like
that?
Level 3?
It's not meat, that's honey.
Max?
No.
Let's see how this... if this changes anything.
Let's see if this changes anything.
Oh!
Well,
you know.
It feels so much smoother moving Poobye right now.
Am I longest?
Really?
Oh god.
Where's the power?
Where's the power now?
Oops.
Where's the power?
Is it just a placebo?
Uh-oh.
Wait.
It's not the swing that's faster, right?
It's me that's faster.
Right?
Oops.
Yeah, Pooh's movement.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
141.7!
Okay.
Oh, come on.
Yeah, Pooh is lagging behind your mouse.
Yeah, right?
He was lagging so much before.
Seven.
Oh!
I think I made it.
Yes!
Foul!
That should have not been a foul.
Foul ball.
Hit.
Oh, no.
Oh, gosh.
I only have...
I don't have a lot of room for error, you guys.
I don't have a lot of room for error.
144!
11.
Oh, shoot.
That was me.
What the...
Uh-oh.
No, no, no.
Please, please, please, God.
That one was funky.
I don't think I can win anymore, can I?
Can I?
It's fine.
I was getting used to the new speed and stuff.
I was getting used to it.
I was getting used to it, you guys.
Can I beat my record?
Nope.
Okay.
Whoa, he's so fast now.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Pooh bear, Pooh bear.
Pooh bear, calm down.
Not even increasing my meat could make me...
Damn.
What's in that honey?
Poo says.
Give me more honey, Christopher Robin.
That's not a foul.
143.
Give me more power, Christopher Robin.
Performance enhancing on you.
Nothing will...
Stop!
Oh come on.
Nothing will improve my timing though.
Nothing can improve my timing I guess.
I missed baseball back before the poos were juicing.
No, I'm not gonna do any more upgrades than what I did.
Oh gosh.
Well, maybe I need to though.
I need more meat!
I think that should have hit but...
Um...
You're the oomph.
160.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Wait.
Okay.
You guys, I just can't miss.
I just can't miss and I'll make it.
Okay.
Oh, this one.
This hit would have...
Would have killed me anyway too.
That hit would have killed me anyway too.
Misses immediately.
It's like art.
It's like an art being this comedic timing, huh?
Is a poo an actual kind of bear?
I don't think so.
A poo bear.
Winnie the poo bear.
Oh, I almost hit Owl.
I almost hit Owl.
Oh my god.
Poo bear.
Winnie the poo bear.
Looking for fun.
Chasing some honeybees.
Poo bear, I know he's out there.
Oh.
Rumbly tumbly.
Something in a honey tree.
He's so... wait, I don't remember the words.
He's so adventurous.
He's sneaking out again.
But when you're alone, there's nobody home.
It's nice to spend time with a bear named Pool Bear.
Winnie the Poop.
My longest foul ever.
Plays the... the what theme?
I'm disappointed this wasn't referenced in Kingdom Hearts 3.
Oh my
god!
What was the point of increasing my power?
I don't think it really does anything.
Unless you did the home run.
No!
I knew that it wouldn't be home run!
I knew it!
That one was too fast.
I'm gonna have real carpal tunnel after this.
Shit.
Please, please, please!
Yes!
What if they do a Hololive version?
Please don't give Kay any more ideas.
Kay will do it and I'm terrified of that.
Please don't.
Please.
Okay, I gotta lock in, you guys.
Okay.
Lock in.
I'm locking in.
No!
Uh-oh.
I don't have very much room for...
Why are you so good now?
I don't know.
I don't have a new record.
Really?
Playing this game and streaming hard.
Come on!
I don't even see...
I don't even see it hit the wall.
Oh my god.
Like, the game actually lagged.
I think it lagged and just believed that it would be a foul.
Oh my god.
That was me.
Oh.
That was awesome.
You guys, I don't know what it is.
I don't know what's... what's wrong with me.
Minto, Minto.
She's our girl.
What the fuck?
It's the lag.
Totally.
Yeah.
Everybody say it with me.
It's the lag!
Oh my god.
That was mean.
That was so mean.
It was so slow that I was like...
Just... just... come on!
Pow!
Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on!
It's the hag.
Guys, this is not the run.
This is not the run.
Oh, yeah.
I can't even make it.
Yep.
Okay.
Oh, man!
Oh.
Three!
Two!
Okay.
Let's go.
Let's go!
The eagle fly higher.
Above the clouds.
I am God's toughest warrior.
Don't
get the same test paper.
square, square, square.
.
Uh-oh.
Sorry, Dwayne.
Dang it!
Are you contagious?
We
hit!
We hit him!
We hit the bird!
Yeah!
Blblblblblbl.
Baller 194 is dead.
saves It's working.
Wait.
Wait, that's a foul, isn't it?
No!
Otherwise we would have had it!
Oh
my god!
Oh my...
Oh man.
Also, I'm not doing any more upgrades.
I decided that I... I stopped it.
I wanted to stop with the upgrades.
The number of upgrades that I did, so...
At this point, I don't...
I don't think I need any more.
I think it's just skill, you know?
Yeah, so...
If you...
Please don't spam about upgrades anymore.
And if I do more in the future...
If it really becomes impossible...
You know, whatever, but...
I think we have enough, truly.
But right now, it's just a skill issue.
I think.
I know, actually.
It's just a skill issue.
Can we ask for downgrades?
You're already a downgrade.
You're my downgrade.
Actually...
No, the downgrade is streaming while playing this game.
So yeah, you guys are my downgrades.
Chat debuff.
Our Rellee's getting And finally something.
I think it's over.
I think the blue dump is over.
It's over.
We need to find a new strat now.
I think we need to find a new strat.
Oh shit.
Did that?
Oh no, that was a foul.
Uh-oh.
Oh no, no, no.
And another foul.
I can't.
This is not the run either because I can't afford to have any mistakes.
Yep, and there goes the run.
Use the mantra, I am Mint, I will commit, I will have a homerun hit.
I don't know clockwork if I can remember all of that.
I am Mint, I will commit, I will have a homerun hit.
I like the upgrades.
You're my best upgrade.
Are you winning, Mint?
Gosh, the first couple of levels were so easy.
And then Owl came.
Oh my gosh.
He's worthy of stage 6.
That's how they get you.
Oh, I believe in oneself.
Way too poor.
That cow.
Okay.
No.
I gotta lock in, I gotta lock in.
Screen person.
No.
Okay, stop reading chat.
I really need to stop reading chat.
Okay, okay.
My eyes are wide.
And ready to receive.
Ball.
Yeah!
How does it count as a foul though?
It's still...
It still went out of...
It's...
It's still...
It hit, I think.
It didn't go behind.
It just went a little to the right.
I see your wandering eyes.
Hey, shut up.
Foul!
Oh, shit.
Okay.
See, that counts as a foul, I think.
But, you know.
Oh my god.
No, no, no.
Please.
Please, please, please.
No.
Oh, it's a foul.
Fuck.
Shit.
Fuck you.
Ow.
You fuck.
Oh, fucking fuck!
It's just...
It's an owl's world we live in, you guys.
It's an owl's world we live in.
I can't...
If I make no mistakes...
Oh, wait.
Why did I just say that?
Okay.
Oh...
Oh my god.
How to
acho.
Take me out to the ball game.
Take me out to the crowd.
Buy me some pizza and cracker dice.
I don't care if I never come back.
So let's root, root, root for the home gym.
If they know it, it's a shame.
So which one?
Shit.
Two.
Three strikes here.
At the old...
game.
Owl.
How much do I need to bribe you?
How much do I need to bribe you, owl?
How much do you want?
Worms?
I got them.
What else do owls eat?
Little mice?
What else do you want?
Rats, yeah?
Little mice and...
Rabbit?
I can give them rabbit.
How much you want, owl?
How much you want?
I'll give you anything.
Please.
I'll give you worm.
I'll give you mouse.
I'll give you anything.
I'll give...
Oh shit.
Come on.
Just count it.
Whatever you want, it's yours, baby.
Please.
I'll sell my home to you.
No!
Owl!
I'll sell you whatever you want.
Whatever you want, owl.
Whatever you want.
You can have my first newborn.
It'll be really small and easy for you to eat.
I promise you.
Oh god.
Please.
You want some worms?
Worms.
I got you worms.
You want worms?
Shit.
You want...
You want some rats?
I got you...
Shit.
No, I don't have you shit.
I have you rats and worms.
Worms!
He wants worms!
Worms is the word.
Worms is the lucky word.
Worms.
He wants the worms.
I got plenty of worms.
They're all in my brain.
I will crack open my skull right now for you, owl.
I'll crack it open.
A cold one.
Actually, no.
My brain is warm and squishy.
And...
Probably really delicious and easy for you to eat.
Oh god.
Please.
Worms.
Luckily, you can keep your firstborn.
True.
He didn't want it.
He didn't want my firstborn.
All right.
Hello, darkness.
My old friend.
That's a foul.
I think they need to give us a hundred balls, not just thirty.
He wants your firstborn and your second.
You can have every single one of my children, owl.
You know what?
It's fine.
I'll just keep popping out babies and you can eat every single one of them.
A delicious nine-month baked meal.
Just for you.
Actually, I'll even...
I'll just start stealing babies instead.
You know what?
You can have the firstborn, the secondborn.
You can have my neighbor's borns.
You can have the bloodborns.
You can have all the babies.
Look, he's how happy.
He says, babies.
Give me more babies.
Give me sweet, tender little infants.
I like when their brains are soft and their head is mushy.
Yeah.
You can have every little baby in the world.
Mr. Owl.
I will sacrifice all the children for you.
You can have kids.
And then you'll eat them.
Kids for breakfast.
Kids for lunch.
Kids for dinner.
Kids for brunch.
Literally any afternoon tea and kids.
Please.
There we go.
All right.
Shit.
I got to still talk about the children.
The children.
He says, tell me more about what flavor these kids will be.
Oh, they'll be every flavor you ever imagine you want them to be.
You want a kid that's salty?
I got you.
Just make them cry a little.
Oh, their tears just really...
And I can even butter one up for you.
Oh, please.
Put one in some vinegar.
No, we don't like that.
Okay.
You want some...
What other flavors do you like?
Spicy kids?
Ones that throw temper tantrums?
I don't know.
Every brain is a little bit different for you, Mr. Owl.
Every brain.
Here's a little child.
Oh, this one?
Okay, Mr. Owl.
I'm going to have to take a kid away.
I'm sorry.
Please.
All right.
I'm going to go down.
I'm going to go to the pool and I'm going to go find you a baby now.
All right.
Where am I going to find a baby?
Mr. Owl.
I'm taking a kid away.
I'm going to the library and I'm going to go fetch a fresh baby for you.
Okay.
Mr. Owl.
Now I'm going to go to the park.
The park has plenty of children.
Okay.
Where am I going next?
Feast.
Mr. Owl.
It's your buffet.
You will have every child that you can imagine eating.
You.
It will be your buffet.
Mr. Owl.
Please.
I'm not giving you shit.
You stinking son of a bitch.
None of them are for you.
You're not getting shit from me.
Mr. Owl.
Time for Tigger.
And you know the wonderful thing about Tigger is Tigger is a wonderful thing.
His tops are made of rubber and his bottoms are made of strings.
Springs.
Not strings.
Bouncy, bouncy, bouncy, bouncy.
Fun, fun, fun, fun, fun.
The wonderful thing about Tigger is I'm the only one.
What the?
One.
I'm the only one.
The wonderful thing about Tigger is I'm the only one.
The wonderful thing about Tigger is Tigger is a wonderful thing.
How do you do that, Tigger?
How do you do that?
Advancee who is worthy.
Shit.
And you have to get 28?
You have to get 28?
Oh my god.
Oh no.
Hayai.
He's using Camel.
He's using stealth Camel.
It would be great if I could just get not Fowl's though.
Then I could actually beat him.
Right?
Oh my god.
That was too fast anyway.
We need thermal goggles, real.
But I keep just getting fouls.
Keep your eye on the ball.
The ball in question.
Hey, but we got five!
Six!
The wonderful thing about Tigger.
His taper's the wonderful thing.
His top's made of rubber.
His bottom's made of springs.
Bouncy, bouncy, bouncy, bouncy.
Fun, fun, fun, fun, fun!
Oh my god, I don't know why I'm...
Oh god.
I can't get the timing at all.
I can't get the timing at all!
Is he fun?
Are you having fun?
Maybe.
It just goes by really quickly, which is kinda nice.
Okay, yeah, time to start counting, for real.
And only four?
He only gives you forty?
He only gives you forty!
Oh my gosh.
Do people, like, max their meat so that they can...
I just realized.
What is this one in English?
Because I just keep calling it meat.
And I'm like, let's max your meat out.
What is this one in English, though?
What is it called in English?
Oh, it is meat?
Oh, okay, okay.
That's so funny.
Meat maxing.
We're meat maxing?
Isn't Christopher Robin, he does, like, all of the different throws, right?
Okay, let's see.
One, two.
I can't tell if I'm missing...
One, two!
Okay, maybe it's one, two.
Two!
I didn't even say the word.
One, two!
Yeah, we need to hit 28 of these.
This is winnable.
One, two!
The ref is... or the ump is against me!
This is still winnable.
One, two!
It's not winnable anymore.
Is it a piki-piki?
Yeah, it's like Tengoku rhythm.
Hey, Esu.
One, two!
Ow.
Foul.
One, two!
Okay, we can do this you guys.
We can do this, I think.
One, two!
Ah...
Is he throwing at different speeds?
He does, yes.
See, that's why sometimes it's slower though.
Oh, I was too far out.
Maybe it's not winnable.
I don't know.
Another foul.
Shame, shame, shame.
One, two!
Is that another foul?
Nope.
Count from when the ball disappears?
That's too hard for me.
One, two!
I count from when he throws.
There's no difference.
One, two!
One,
two!
Pocky!
One, two!
New record.
New record, new record, new record, new record.
Eleven.
Oh, oops.
My bad, my bad.
I'm like... I'm just pressing buttons at this point.
One, two!
Aha!
Haha!
One, two!
One,
two!
It's just a slower one, two.
One, two!
Haha!
Oh, foul.
My bad.
One, two!
Sorry.
Haha!
One, two!
Oh!
Haha!
One, two!
One,
two!
Is this still winnable?
I don't know.
One, two... Uh-oh.
One, two...
One, two... We got close though.
Well not close, but we got pretty far.
We got pretty far.
One, two...
It's Jover.
You can restart it?
I don't think you can actually.
Like when the ghost lady makes silly noises.
One, two... That one was too slow.
You're too slow!
I wonder if we can get to at least 20.
Yeah, good practice.
One, two...
Yay, we made it to 20.
I don't know about you.
I'm feeling 22.
Honestly, decent run.
Yeah, for real.
One, two...
Sorry, it is so annoying probably me doing this, but I have to.
Oh, I think I was too far away.
One, two...
Foul.
Dang it.
One, two...
That was too far away.
Switch to Nihongo?
I don't think so.
I think this is how I gotta do it.
One, two... Shit, I was too far away.
One, two...
How long has she been on Tigger?
Not very long actually.
One, two...
I just got to Tigger.
Yeah, Owl kind of did me in.
Owl did me in a little bit.
One, two... Shoot.
One, two...
It was like coming towards me.
Uh-oh.
Is it still winnable?
Nope.
Kind of, but very difficult.
Okay, now it's not winnable.
Now, it's not winnable.
It's okay.
It's alright.
Actually, while he does this, I'm gonna go get more tea while he runs out of balls.
I'll be right back.
I'm gonna get more drink.
You can watch him.
Guys, I went on an adventure.
I said I was just gonna get tea.
I lied.
I also...
Went to the bathroom.
And I also...
Um...
Got a snack.
But right now...
I was like trying to decide if I wanted tea.
But I'm gonna put some of this throat stuff.
Since I've been yelling a lot.
And since my throat is not very good today.
And I need to stop yelling.
If I yell...
Yell back at me.
Say, Minto!
Yell.
Don't.
Your throat.
You must recover your throat.
And I'll be like, yes ma.
Did you wash your hands?
Always.
I always wash my hands.
I'm pouring in this stuff for my tea.
Or, it's not tea.
Well, I guess it turns into tea.
But it's throat stuff.
While you are taking a break from your suffering, I just want to wish you a good time at Otakutan.
I will be there!
I'll see you there, Virulent!
I'll see you!
I'm so excited.
Oh my gosh.
This weekend I'm going to Canada.
Canada.
Oh, Canada.
Yeah, look after yourself, nerd!
I know I had to record some stuff.
One thing I had to record was for our... my duet with Doki.
At the concert.
Next weekend.
Not this coming weekend.
And...
And, sorry, you had to listen to this music.
I had my headphones off.
But I was like, oh boy, my voice is not very...
One, two.
My voice is not in good condition.
I had to record some other stuff, so I was like...
I was like...
Oh gosh, okay.
One, two.
Uh-oh.
You guys.
One, two.
What's happening?
Now I was recording for something that hasn't been...
announced yet.
Mysterious.
One, two.
Get that rhythm back.
Foul?
One, two.
That was fast.
Who is Juan and why are you telling him to chew?
One, two.
How many honeypots do we need to eat?
Two.
To get to 169.
Mint and Henny's winter podcast.
I think I'm done with podcasts after this one.
I really appreciate everybody who says that they enjoy listening to our podcast.
Oh gosh, I can't make any...
mistakes or else...
the run is over.
But I think after the podcast...
I...
Oh, that's it.
The run is over.
I prefer streaming over...
over the podcast stuff.
But
I'm really glad that people...
like it.
Is this a prequel to Poo, Blood and Honey?
Is that the horror film?
Oops.
Yeah.
Understandable, but I'm happy you tried it.
Yeah, me too.
Otherwise, I never would have...
I never would have...
known, you know?
So, yeah.
One, two.
Nope.
Why am I...
What's happening to the timing?
One, two.
Which is kind of crazy.
Like, you know...
I thought because...
you know, a podcast is just...
talking and streaming is also just talking.
Why would I like one and not the other?
But...
It's so strange that I...
don't really...
care so much for the podcast.
Not that I don't care about it.
That's not the right word.
It's...
It's that, you know, I...
I will have done it and I'll be like...
Yeah, that was fun.
But I think I'm good to...
you know, stream.
Yeah.
And...
What was I gonna say?
One, two.
That's what I was gonna say.
But it's funny because like when I...
was like doing...
started VTubing, like some people...
One, two.
Nope.
When they start VTubing, they...
One, two.
Nah.
They...
At least stream a little bit before they become a VTuber.
Two.
Dang it.
But for me, I was just like, nah.
One, two.
I'm gonna be a VTuber.
So...
One, two.
What if I had hated streaming too?
What if I had hated streaming?
One, two.
No.
That wasn't a foul.
Two.
Back to the business minds.
Utaite.
One, two.
No, I don't think so.
I already don't put out.
One, two.
A lot of covers, so...
I think there is a lot of...
One, two.
A lot of pressure with being utaite.
Troy, thanks for the gift.
I actually got something recently.
Hold on.
One, two.
When Barry and I were at MGSCon.
Um.
One second.
One, two.
I actually got something recently.
We were at the voice actor panel and someone asked...
You know, someone always asks, like, how do you keep your voice, like, well?
One, two!
Dang it.
No?
One, two!
And, um...
Lori Allen...
One, two!
Mentioned that she uses a singing straw.
And I remember Barry and I both looked at each other at the same exact time and we're like...
One, two!
No, we did not say that.
We...
One, two!
We looked at each other at the same...
Okay, the run is over.
But we were just like, a singing straw?
What the heck is that?
And so, I, like, looked it up.
And then I bought one.
And it's supposed to help with, like, your breathing.
And also for, like, increasing the power of your voice.
Which I was like, wow!
What?
One, two!
So...
I'm gonna try it.
How does that work?
I have no idea.
One, two!
A singing straw.
Yeah, but mine is a little different.
I got this thing called...
The sing ring.
And basically, you, like, hold it in your middle finger.
And then you cover up some of the holes.
And then you, like, sing into it.
And it kind of creates, like, a resistance.
Like that.
And it, like, helps, like, you create...
Like, helps you sing more...
Like, or rather, helps you regulate your breathing better.
And also helps you...
Yeah, it's like a kazoo.
But...
It's like a kazoo, but if it had...
If it had resistance.
So, like, almost, it almost feels like it's gonna, like...
Make my diaphragm like strong.
My diaphragm's gonna be so meaty.
It's gonna be so...
Oh.
Shoot.
Okay, time to pay attention.
One, two!
Minto abs.
Golly, I need the abs.
I've been slacking on exercising, you guys.
I'm gaining too much ectoplasm.
Which is why I'm kind of excited about being in Japan for a month, because I'll just be walk, walk, walking every day.
One, two.
Oh, shoot.
Dang it.
One, two.
Ring Fit.
Maybe once I get a better 3D tracking, I can do Ring Fit.
One, two.
Two.
I think also, you know, stress will always like...
Stress does a number on your body.
So...
Laugh and grow fat.
I'm doing maybe both of those.
Usually I'd say I'm doing one of them.
Two.
And then once, I think once I have more 3D, I'll be...
More motivated too, because I'll want to learn...
Dances and stuff.
You know, like that.
One.
Two.
This is not the run, you guys.
Oh god.
For someone who I...
Two.
I believe to scream a lot and go nuts during Wotagei.
Metal Gear Unveilings and Limp Bizkit songs.
You seem to take care of your voice.
Chords pretty well.
Thanks!
I try.
I try, I try.
Get your steps in, Minto.
I need to.
But at MGS Con, the first day, I got...
I got 20,000 steps in.
I did 9 miles.
I did a lot.
So...
And then the day after, it was like 16,000.
What do you mean the first day?
Like the day I flew in.
The day I flew in.
The day of the con, it was like 16,000.
Two!
My Oshi soft in the middle.
Stop!
I hate it.
It all just goes to my butt.
Anyway.
We use a PVC ball valve for breathing exercises.
Huh?
What's that?
Soft girl summer.
Why are you guys saying...
You guys are like making it feel like...
I'm like...
So, you know...
I'm just...
It's just a little bit, you guys.
I...
I wouldn't even say I'm chubby.
Okay?
I even asked my friend the other day.
I was like, am I chubby?
And they were like, no, you're not.
I was like, okay, thank you.
Stage 7.
Gosh.
Caught me off guard.
Two.
Come on.
One.
Two.
Alright, can we get off the topic of my weight, please?
One.
Two.
Can we actually...
One.
Two.
I don't want to think about it.
One.
Two.
Ghosts are weightless.
It's true.
I put it in my debut.
Two.
I weigh zero pounds.
Ectoplasm now weighs nothing.
One.
Two.
Dang it.
One.
Two.
Big supporter of the straw for vocal warm-ups.
Oh, nice.
One.
Two.
It's not exactly... I wanted to find a straw, but I couldn't find a straw.
One.
Two.
I want to have more and more thick mental arts.
Please stop.
Actually, please stop.
Thank you.
One.
Two.
What game would you not want to be Jumanji'd into?
One.
Two.
What game would you not want to be Jumanji'd into?
One.
Two.
Like Fallout or something.
One.
Two.
Oh, this is not winnable.
I just realized.
I'm so distracted that I'm like not even...
I'm barely paying attention to Tigger.
Two.
One.
Home Run Derby.
Did you roll for Dress Hina?
Yeah.
I got her.
I got Dress Hina.
And Summer Hoshino.
Yeah.
Okay.
Game is over!
Yeah.
I got Hoshino.
And I got Hina.
Okay.
I got 90 rolls and didn't get her.
One.
Two.
It took me like a hundred and twenty, my friend.
You don't want my luck.
One.
Two.
Oh, come on.
That was the same type of throw.
One.
Two.
Sounds like you need more Blue Archive funds.
No!
I'm mostly free to play.
One.
Two.
Dang it.
Meh.
One.
Two.
Mostly.
I pay ten dollars a month.
One.
Two.
For the...
For the monthly package.
One.
Two.
But that's all I buy.
One.
Two.
Because I think that is a good deal.
One.
Two.
Oh.
One.
Two.
I don't think I've ever been super...
Like so deep in a gacha that I would be willing to...
One.
Two.
That I'd be willing to spend so much money on it.
Dang it.
That one was really far over.
One.
Two.
Dang it.
One.
Two.
Because I know that gachas end one day.
One.
Two.
And it freaks me out.
It freaks me out.
One.
Two.
That I'll sink so much money into something.
And then it'll be gone one day.
I know.
Two.
Dang it.
Oh my god.
You guys, I don't think this is...
Two.
One.
Dang it.
Okay.
Some vtubers don't have your restraint.
It's because... I'll be honest.
Okay.
It's because I come from...
A life... Okay.
I'm gonna say this in the nicest way possible.
A lot of vtubers are young and don't know struggle.
And they don't...
They don't know what it's like.
You know, they...
They are still at home.
And so they are like...
They're like, yeah.
I can spend all my money on gacha.
But I was living paycheck to paycheck.
And so I have...
I have money discipline.
So that's why.
Didn't I get up to...
12 I think was my highest, right?
12.
Or I got up to 20 or something crazy.
People who spend lots on gacha are foolish.
Pay no attention to the costume gacha.
For all the gyaru on my account.
Oh yeah, it was 20.
You guys, I'm regressing.
Okay, locking in.
I'm locking in.
1, 2.
Still a foul.
Singing cardio.
2.
Plus singing straw.
Macho musical mate.
How is that also foul?
2.
Oh my god, no.
Please.
1, 2.
Locking in.
I'm locking in.
1, 2.
2.
See to ride in.
See...
I don't know what those mean.
Are you playing bingo?
What the hell does that mean?
Why are you playing bingo with your gacha characters?
It's Genshin.
You guys...
I don't know why I just can't get any...
into a Hoyoverse game.
They'll have the cutest designs.
They'll appeal to me in every possible way.
And I'll be like...
But like...
I just can't get into mihoyo.
I'll be like...
Oh my god, the cutest character ever.
I even had fun playing Genshin when I played it.
The two times I played it.
See?
Get called, boss.
See to...
What if I... Oh my god.
Can I get the ball backwards?
How?
Oh my gosh.
I'm not even...
I'm trying to hit the ball backwards.
VTubers are my gacha.
Minto is my SSR.
Guyself can't wail anymore.
That was a bad game, you guys.
Basically the same for the most part, are they?
One, two!
Oh my god.
Okay.
Alright.
One, two!
Not a foul.
Foul!
One, two!
Not a foul.
Foul!
One, two!
No yelling.
Thank you.
One, blue!
Oh, please.
The story is legit good.
It's actually so good.
Two!
One, two!
I mean, maybe after this, I might add some upgrades.
After this, I might add some upgrades.
It's fun gacha.
I mean, I don't doubt it.
I just can't.
I don't know.
One, two!
Oh, please!
Yes!
Two!
One, two!
Most people are fully upgraded or near fully upgraded.
It's just a skill issue, though.
Because I didn't do any more upgrades.
And I got the 22!
Two!
It's just a skill issue.
One, two!
I did well.
Two!
I did.
Oh, I just realized this is not beatable anymore.
Oh, man.
One, two!
One,
two!
One, two!
That wasn't close enough.
Look at this, though.
We're doing so well.
One, two!
Foul.
One to foul.
Please.
Tigger.
Tigger!
I'm gonna drink more of my tea.
I'm gonna drink
more of my tea.
And... game!
And...
game!
Burp?
I don't know how to burp.
Actually, I'm physically incapable of burping.
And...
Isn't that kind of crazy?
It's like I have a...
It's like... I don't know.
I forgot what it's called.
But...
Um...
Yeah, I don't...
I...
I forgot what it's called.
Same as that other Super Chat.
Donating to Beat Tubers made me stop wailing and move again.
At least this way my money goes to helping an actual person.
I...
Idols don't burp.
I don't think that's the case.
Fifteen.
Okay.
Oh, we can't even level anything else up anymore.
Two!
Oh.
Oh my god.
Okay.
One.
Two.
I forgot what it's called.
I'll have to look it up.
Because I was just like, what the hell?
One.
Two.
Can't burp and he's...
Isn't supposed to have spicy food or carbonated drinks.
That's me.
One.
Two.
You gotcha for one.
One.
Two.
Come on.
One.
Two.
But it's funny because...
I can't burp and it just makes like a funny noise in my throat.
One.
Two.
I'm not saying that girls can't burp, you dummies.
I'm not saying girls don't burp.
It's because I'm a girl.
It's like a thing.
I don't know what it's called though.
I don't remember.
Two.
Guys, I'm already...
Too many fouls.
How am I getting so many fouls?
No!
Why?
So many fouls in a row.
So
many fouls...
How many ladies are among the wisps?
Ladies rise up.
Ladies, where are you at?
After this one, I'm locking in.
After this one, no more talks of farts and burping.
No more talks of...
What else did we talk about?
Nothing else!
Only baseball!
Yeah, no more talks of gotcha!
No more talks of even ladies.
No more ladies talk.
After this one.
I get to 22 on like the second try.
I think I got too comfortable, you know?
I'm not focusing enough.
Okay, here we go.
Last one.
Okay.
Alright.
Baseball.
I'm locking in.
I'm locking in on Tigger.
Nice!
One.
Two.
Okay.
Locking in.
That was a strike.
Does not work.
That's a foul.
There you go.
One, Two.
176?
173.
One, Two.
Dang it.
One, two!
Alright, alright, alright!
The one, two works!
One, two!
I'm getting sweaty, you guys.
I'm getting sweaty.
One, two!
I'm getting sweaty!
Dang it!
It's a foul.
One, two!
Don't they allow like some fouls though?
You have like two fouls before it's a strikeout or something.
One, two!
Dang it, I was too far over.
Dang it, dang it, dang it.
One, two!
No, no, no!
Is this still winnable?
One, two!
Nope, not anymore.
It's over.
Oh man.
Guys...
My goal is to just make it past Tigger.
I almost said Twitter.
I just wanna make it past Tigger at this point.
One, two!
Oh no.
I don't think we'll be able to beat Christopher Robin.
I don't think today we'll be able to beat Christopher Robin.
Two!
Did Pikamee beat Christopher Robin?
Can't remember.
She did?
Oh she Rage Quit.
What?
She immediately walked away from Chris.
She's so real for that.
Maybe one day we'll have like a Chris...
Shit you.
We can have a Chris challenge.
One, two!
Is that a super chat to backseat me?
Dang it.
One, two!
I used the upgrade system a little bit, yeah.
But it doesn't... only the speed helps.
One, two!
Oh dang it.
Foul.
One, two!
Please not be a foul.
Oh, it's a movie reference.
One, two!
Oh shoot.
Okay, I need to stop looking at chat.
One, two!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay.
One, two!
Oh, okay.
It's over you guys.
It's over.
It's so over.
I got distracted by chat.
I got distracted by closed chat.
I might actually have to.
One, two!
And then I'll just talk to myself.
I'll pretend that nobody's here.
I'll pretend it's just me, myself, and I.
I'm not even streaming.
Me, myself, and I.
Okay, I'm closing chat.
Oops, I just made chat bigger.
Me, myself, and the game.
I can't see anything.
Wow, if that had gone in the water, would that have been a foul?
Two... nope.
Okay, now the game is really ruined.
The run is really ruined, but...
It's okay.
I'm just playing on my own time.
To nobody.
Nobody's watching.
Nobody's paying attention to me.
If I'm bad, there's no one to backseat me.
There's no one to say, You're such a bad player at this game.
You're so terrible at the game.
You're the worst at the game.
Okay, I've brought you guys back.
Hit the balls instead of missing them.
Okay, now I'm looking at you guys.
But not this time.
We're here for Tigger.
One, two!
Foul.
One, two, foul.
One, two!
Doesn't he start with 40?
Why are we already at 37?
One, two!
Foul.
180!
Holy moly.
One, two!
Someone signed me up...
for the major leagues.
One, two!
You guys, the fouls!
The fouls!
Fuck you, Tigger!
Tigger?
I don't know how you do this.
I don't know what...
Everybody sold their souls...
to Christopher Robin.
One, two!
Everybody sold their souls...
to Christopher Robin.
One, two!
Fuck you, Tigger.
Fuck you.
I can't even...
Oh, actually, this is...
One, two!
It's...
Nope.
This is not beatable anymore.
It's not beatable anymore.
You know, Tigger...
I hope you...
I hope you break your fucking tail.
I hope you never...
I hope you never jump on that tail ever again.
Look at him with his hands behind his back.
He's like, which hand am I gonna throw it from?
Which side?
It's the same side always.
But which way is it gonna go?
It's just gonna disappear into the ether...
because I'm a fucking wizard.
I'm gonna go to Disney.
And I'm gonna...
I'm gonna rip you up.
I'm gonna rip you a real new one.
That fursuit is gonna have...
It's gonna have five holes in it...
once I'm done with you.
One for you.
One for the body.
And one for everywhere else.
Come here, Tigger.
Oh, maybe I just need to get mad at him.
They will sue me.
Never let me back into your parks again.
I never want to, but I never want to see Tigger's face again.
Actually, someone invited me to Tokyo Disney.
While I'm in Japan this time.
And I'm like... I'm like...
What if... Maybe I shouldn't go.
Indiana Jones.
You're right.
I just got to think of Indy.
What do...
I don't think they have the owl at the parks though.
I don't think they have the owl because nobody loves him.
Justifiably, nobody loves the owl.
Good.
He has no love.
He has no fans.
Nobody is a fan of the owl.
All my friends hate that guy.
Everybody in the world hates the owl.
Two.
We don't even know his name.
Yeah, his parents didn't even love him enough to give him...
One.
Two.
A real name.
They just named him after his species.
How embarrassing.
One.
Two.
What if you were named human?
That's just weird.
One.
Two.
Okay, maid.
That's not my name.
Two.
You ruined my...
Thing.
One.
Two.
You ruined my swing.
One.
Two.
It's a title.
The maid...
The maid part is a title.
Just like Mr. Mrs. It's a title.
One.
Two.
Fuck.
Fuck you.
One.
Two.
Please.
One.
Two.
I'm drinking more tea.
Is it worth the wait?
Yeah.
It was so worth the wait.
Yeah, it was so worth the wait.
You're my kamiyoshi.
I think as a kid yoir was my favorite, too.
Related to him.
But...
It's kind of sad as a kid to relate to Eeyore, maybe.
Oh gosh, we haven't even... you guys, we haven't even gotten close.
We haven't even gotten close.
One, two.
Oh god.
That's in, that's in, that's in.
Nice.
That's in, that's in.
Okay.
Nice.
Wow, that was pretty far.
That's in, that's out.
Ooh, that's out.
That's in.
Dang it.
Sha!
I should have gone over a little bit more.
Nice.
Okay.
Dang it.
That's a foul.
I didn't think I was gonna make that.
Holy moly.
How do we do it?
Mamma mia.
Mamma mia!
Please stay in.
Yippee!
Okay.
Oh shoot, that one was a fast one.
Nice.
Straight down the kisser, baby.
Ah!
I should have gone over.
Guys, I don't...
Guys, I don't think this is doable.
This is not...
It's so strict.
Gosh, you can...
It doesn't allow for, like, any mistakes.
It doesn't allow for any mistakes.
At all.
It's crazy.
Oh, damn it.
That was...
Yeah.
It's the fouls.
I would have gotten fouls anyway.
I would have gotten the fouls.
Yippee.
It was personal.
I won't get penalized?
Isn't it a foul.
It's like, no...
No.
Please stop.
Oh, I wasn't... I was... my hand was not on the mouse.
I fucking hate you!
I hate you!
I hate you so much!
I...
It's out of the game?
I just want to reset it.
Escape!
You guys...
You guys want to hear my new keyboard?
Listen to this.
It was sent to me.
It's a custom mint keyboard.
Listen, listen.
It's so creamy.
Here, I'll turn off the noise gate.
I fucking hate Tigger.
That guy sucks ass.
I hope tonight he doesn't wake up and I hope... I hope he has the worst nightmare before he dies and stays dead eternally.
I hope he never finds love and I hope he also never finds joy.
I hope Tigger rots in hell for an eternity and never sees a happy day.
Ever again in his miserable life.
I hope his tail breaks.
I hope his eyes break.
I hope his mouth breaks.
I hope his...
I hope his ears break.
I hope his nose breaks.
I hope every part of him is in agony every day for the rest of his life.
I hope he is never healthy again.
And happy.
Never ever ever ever ever ever again.
Signed, Minto.
Doesn't it sound so creepy?
Doesn't it sound so creamy and nice?
Okay.
It's very satisfying.
One.
Two.
That's in.
That was in.
They're against me.
One.
Two.
That was two.
I got them tingles.
I know.
ASMR tingles.
One.
Two.
Shit.
One.
Two.
That's in.
No.
One.
Two.
Damn it.
One of those threats instead of a happy birthday song.
Stop distracting me, please.
One.
Two.
For sure.
One.
Two.
Oh my god.
Thank goodness for the speed.
Otherwise, we wouldn't have made that.
One.
Two.
Holy cow.
I don't know how we made that either.
One.
Two.
Holy moly.
One.
Two.
Damn.
One.
Two.
Ah.
Damn.
Two.
I keep getting fouls though.
I keep getting fouls.
One.
Two.
No.
How is that a foul?
I did not even move.
Shit.
Okay.
One.
Two.
Please stop donating to me.
I instinctually look over at the chat.
Please stop.
One.
Two.
You guys are ruining my game.
For real.
Blindfold run.
One.
Two.
Fuck you.
I fucking hate you.
One.
Two.
Okay.
I'm not drooling from rage, everybody.
One.
Two.
Why is the Japanese version more difficult than the English version?
One.
Two.
What makes it...
What I mean is what makes it more difficult than the English version.
If you know.
Oh, shoot.
Okay.
Harder to read.
That sounds like a skill issue.
One.
Two.
People didn't know about the upgrades because Japanese...
It's not really that it's harder.
It's just they didn't know the upgrades.
It's literally in the instructions.
It literally shows you pictures.
It shows you pictures.
You don't even have to read it.
One.
Two.
Maybe I...
One.
Two.
Shoot.
One.
Two.
Maybe because I look...
I wear weeb glasses.
One.
Two.
I wear weeb glasses.
The glasses I bought in Japan.
I can understand the Japanese pictures.
You know, since the upgrades though, I haven't gotten...
One.
Two.
I haven't gotten any just hits though.
I've gotten only home runs.
So, that does help.
That's in.
No!
That was in!
It went in the green!
Please recount!
Shoot.
It's in the green.
Yes.
It's in the green!
It was in the green!
It was in the green.
It's not the green that matters, it's the angle.
That's it.
That's it everybody.
That's game.
Tough time never lasts.
Only tough people last.
Blah blah blah blah.
Please.
I got 20 home runs.
Does it even matter?
Does it even matter if I got 20?
Immediate foul.
This game is foul.
This game is rigged.
I swear it's a dice roll on whether it's a foul or not.
I swear to god.
It's gotta be.
It's gotta be a dice roll.
Oops.
That's me.
Oh my god.
Excuse you.
Too close.
You're throwing it directly at my body.
That is a foul.
To you.
Tigger.
You're a fool.
See if I hadn't had the power on that, that would have been just a hit.
Damn it.
Why is everything a foul?
Why is
everything a foul?
Why is everything a foul?
There's no crying in baseball.
I'm not crying.
That's it.
The game is officially unwinnable.
I'm not crying.
You're crying.
I wish we could pay for more balls.
Tigger, I'll give you...
Please, Tigger, give me more balls.
Please.
Tigger.
Tigger, please, I'll give you more balls.
Please.
I mean, you give me more balls.
Tigger, just like 20 more balls.
Just like 20 more balls.
I'll even take 10.
I'll take 10 more balls.
Please, Tigger, just 10 more balls.
Please, Tigger.
I just need 10.
Ask if you want to eat babies.
Still the tutorial for Christopher Robin.
Shhh...
Eat shit, Tigger.
I hope you'll never get to bounce again.
I hope
you'll never get to bounce again.
Fuck you, Tigger.
Fuck you.
Fuck your family.
Fuck your mom.
Fuck your dad.
Fuck whoever created you.
I hope
they never... I hope... I hope they go to unfreeze his head down there, and he is just a pile of mush.
I hope Disney is just a pile of mush.
They were like, we got his frozen head and he's just...
He's just been... He's gelled into nothingness, so they can't even unfreeze him.
The mouse is coming?
Good.
Take me.
End my suffering.
I can't even win this anymore, so just...
You guys, I'm seeing the light.
Oh my god.
I'm seeing the light.
I think...
I think I'm leaving the afterlife.
Oh my god.
Where am I gonna go?
To heaven?
No.
I'm definitely going to hell.
Oh my god.
Maybe I'll be reincarnated as a bug.
And then Tigger will fucking squash me with his stupid ass fucking tail.
That he doesn't give a shit about who's in his way.
As he bounces down the hundred acre woods.
That guy's gonna pummel me.
I'll be in the ground with my one fucking antenna sticking out of the dirt and I'll be like, That guy...
That's the guy that took me out.
It's a bug's life.
Okay, I'm fine.
Okay.
I'm not fine.
I just keep getting fouled.
You need to lock in.
You're right.
I need to lock in.
Okay.
Next round.
I need to lock in.
Maybe I'll go get another snack.
Or rather dinner.
I don't really have dinner.
You need to lock in.
No, lock in next time, you guys.
This one was unbeatable from the start.
But I'm afraid that if I eat, I'll lose the timing.
You know?
The game was rigged from the start.
Thank you for the 10 gift, dude.
Food helped before, right?
Yeah.
Okay, I'm gonna go get my food.
While he keeps pitching.
I'll be right back.
I'll be fast.
I don't even need to heat it up.
I made it back just in time.
You guys wanna know my fortune?
Let's read my fortune from the fortune cookie.
Okay, guys.
What's it gonna say?
Okay.
Calm down.
The...
What's my fortune gonna say?
It's gonna say...
Oh my god.
There's a lot?
Okay.
It's gonna say...
It says...
Be gentle with yourself.
You're doing the best you can.
Oh my god.
All the condensation from the box is like dripping on me.
Oh
my god.
All the condensation from the box is like dripping on me.
No.
Be gentle with yourself.
You're doing the best you can.
How did it know?
What did I get?
This is Chinese food I got over there.
That's why I had a fortune cookie.
You'll have to hit one ball for every tear wisps have shed.
And haven't I hit enough?
Wait, it's actually from Tigger.
You're brave showing your face here.
You're brave.
Get him.
Get his ass everybody.
I'm eating so I can't.
But you guys get his ass.
Please.
Masking really nicely.
You got it boss.
She's been trying for four hours.
She doesn't know how to beat Tigger in Home Run Derby.
She's crying.
What's wrong with you?
Get
that guy too.
Get that guy too.
Get them all.
What would Pooh, how would Pooh's throw be?
What if instead of Christopher Robin, it was like Christopher Robin wearing like a skin suit of Pooh Bear.
And Pooh Bear is just like, suddenly there's a cut scene.
And he walks in and he's just like, he's like, ho ho ho, rumbly my tumbly.
They're just like, and Pooh Bear's just like, Christopher Robin.
And Christopher Robin is just like, I'm not Christopher Robin.
I'm Winnie the Pooh.
And he's like, it's just insane.
And he's like, there can only be one Pooh Bear in the Hundred Acre Woods.
And so Pooh is actually fighting for his life.
Did you beat the game?
I got nine home runs.
Four in a row though.
That's kinda cool.
I was really locked in for that four.
Solid Pooh versus Liquid Pooh.
Why?
Eww.
Stop!
Why would you say that?
I know your intention, but...
Please consider...
Please consider what you're saying.
Please consider what...
Okay.
I think I'm good.
Wait, one more chicken.
Better than Naked Pooh?
No, no, I think Naked Pooh is the best out of all of those.
Now my pants are all wet.
Okay.
Oh my god, so sorry.
Holy moly.
So loud.
So sorry.
My ears as well.
We all felt that.
I'm so sorry.
That's starting off great.
There we go.
Ow, I think I have a bruise on my...
Hold on.
Actually...
How did I get that on my knee?
How did I get the bruise?
Okay, why can't I restart the game?
I'm afraid of exiting out of the game.
Hold on.
I just have to cross my legs the other way.
Are you okay?
Yeah, it just was hurting.
I was crossing my legs and it was hurting so bad.
There's no way of winning this.
But...
The run is dead.
It is dead.
It's okay.
We needed a little warm up.
After a break.
We needed a warm up after a break.
Charlie horse?
What's a Charlie horse?
Isn't that in your butt?
Charlie horse?
Actually, the run was dead from the beginning, I think.
I thought a Charlie horse was a pain in your butt.
Am I wrong?
It's leg cramps.
When you wake up with leg cramps?
Oh, I've never had that.
No, mine is a bruise on my knee.
I must have run into something at some point.
No,
I'm not thinking of hemorrhoids.
I'm thinking of like a pain, a muscle pain in your butt.
I guess I can get them out of their band practice.
Wow Maybe you should stretch more.
What allegations??
What allegations?
You hurting my butt.
Butt pain and sciatica.
I have that.
That's a little different.
That's a nerve... well, I guess it would be a muscle thing is a nerve thing too, right?
Well, it's a little different.
I have sciatica.
So I know.
The butt pains.
The nerves of the butt.
My butt nerves are bad.
Actually, my hip is like slanted.
So like it just kind of caves in on...
and it shifts all the time.
Okay, lock in.
One, two.
Moving him closer.
I...
I have a better understanding of the timing of where he's at now.
So that's why I don't...
You see?
Damn it.
That was me being too...
Oh, that was me being too late because it was a fast one.
That's in?
Yeah.
Guys, it's so over.
It's so over.
This is not the run.
There should be like a cheat code you can input.
It gives you like...
like a set of...
goggles.
It's so over.
It'd take a miracle.
It really would.
It would take a miracle.
It's so over.
And
that's...
That's it.
Ugh...
I
wish there were save states.
Me too!
I'm running this off of Ruffle.
I don't know if they do it.
If it does save states for flash stuff.
I was doing so well, you guys.
I was doing so well!
I hate when the foul counts as a miss.
I feel like it should count as like...
You should have a do-over, you know?
At least a do-over.
Four off.
Saving between rounds is too much, I think.
Yeah, at least let you restart.
That's the big one.
Don't make me go through the whole thing.
Oh shoot, I was too far off.
That's in.
Nice!
That was too far over.
I'm focused.
Foul!
That's in.
That's a foul.
These fowls are gonna f-ing end me, man.
Oh no!
It's these fowls that are gonna f-ing end me!
I was
doing so well in the beginning!
Ouch!
My knee!
I'm ready to commit murder.
Kill Tigger.
Look at him with his stupid f-ing ball.
I hate you.
I hate you so much.
His stupid smug smile.
If I can't hit the ball...
I'll just slice and dice it.
You guys...
Tiger is on the menu tonight.
That's in.
Nice!
Shoot.
Well, they're endangered.
Yeah.
Good.
Actually, no.
I really like tigers.
I almost didn't make that one.
I almost did not make that one.
Damn.
I definitely did not make that one.
I feel like I'm actually in like a f-ing...
Like... Shonen... Like a sports anime.
Cause I have to be so... There's no time to rest.
I wish there was like a...
Next round start.
Oh.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh my god.
That was me.
What the hell?
Oh my god.
What's wrong with me?
What's happening?
What's happening to me?
Damn it.
I'll be honest.
I'm not even... I don't even pay attention to the music anymore.
I don't even...
I don't even hear it.
No!
You know, you counting down how many fails I have left doesn't really help me.
Okay, so please don't do that.
That's it.
Shoken desu.
Oh, sorry.
Today...
Um...
I went a little crazy.
I'm sorry if I said...
Wow!
I actually managed to go backwards!
That's more impressive than anything else, I think.
I have this knife so close to my eyes.
I'm going to gouge my eyes out!
For real!
I want to go back to an hour ago and I thought Tigger was no problem.
Oh, shoot.
That was me.
Sing a melody?
His throw is a different speed every time.
So you can't really do that.
You're so eloquent when you curse at the game.
Thank you!
Yeah, kill Tigger!
Kill him dead!
Pooh will have no friends at this point.
We're taking out everybody in the 100 acre woods.
Burn the floors down!
Yeah, 100 acres won't be enough for them to hide.
Guys, is this currently still winnable?
Yeah, never mind.
Just kidding.
I can do math.
It's kind of still winnable.
I just don't have very much room to fail.
Oh!
Now it's not winnable anymore.
Gotta restart.
If the game would let me!
I'm coming after you, Tigger.
I'm coming after you.
There's even bases.
But they don't use them.
I wonder if upping my speed will do anything.
Okay,
let's try that.
The meat and the speed.
The meat might help.
Shoot.
Four hours isn't even that long.
Been on the plane the whole day so I missed most of the stream.
Are you having fun?
I'm having so much fun.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Is the fun in the room what it does?
You guys are having fun?
I actually enjoy challenge games like this.
Depending.
This one is like repetitive enough that it makes me feel fine.
Are you guys having fun?
Yeah?
Is it because I'm holding a knife?
That you feel like you have to say that?
Yeah, maybe a little.
I don't feel comfortable answering that.
Okay.
Five.
Oh, that was my fault.
I wasn't over enough.
Sure.
Souls like when?
Maybe when I get back.
Oh, shoot.
That was fast.
Okay.
Nice
and diced.
Celeste.
Yeah.
That game is pretty brutal from what I've heard.
That game is pretty brutal from what I've heard, Celeste.
Shit.
Let's try.
I wasn't even thinking of Tigger.
Oh, wait.
Wait, did anybody see what my home run score was in a row?
Because it was like so much.
I was just trying to like ignore it.
Robin...
I
lost!
Shoot.
Wait, they only give you 10 chances to mess up?
And you have to get 40?
That's insane.
Oh my god.
Wait, I don't remember how to do that one.
Oh no, no, no, no.
That's insane!
Oh fuck, I don't remember how to do that one.
And it's really fast!
He's really fast!
Training wheels are off.
Oh fuck.
Shoot, shoot, shoot.
Oh my god.
Congrats on making it to the Dark Lord.
I think... oh my god, I forgot his trigger.
This is still technically winnable.
This is still technically winnable!
Dang it.
This is not winnable anymore.
Wait, I think... I think it actually still is technically winnable.
I think this is still technically winnable.
Dang it.
No, it's not.
Oh, did you just see me right click?
I pressed all the buttons.
Oh, that was me not being...
Oh, I'm not even close to the center.
He only pitches in the center though.
Interesting.
These rounds are long.
Yeah, I don't think I'm... especially because we can't reset the round when it's over.
I think I'm good.
Oh, I said he only pitched to the... wait.
I said he only pitched to the middle, but he just did it to the side, I think.
Let's see how far I can get though.
If I can get to halfway, I'll con...
If I can get to 20, I'll consider that a win.
Best I've seen anyone go on Chris is 39 out of 40.
So what happens if you win?
Oh, that was me.
Damn.
He throws at basically the same speed.
Nothing, you just win.
Oh my god.
I said that.
I said he throws at the same speed, but...
Get the self-satisfaction.
So nothing happens?
There's no like...
Congratulations!
You beat everybody!
Oh, whoopsie.
20!
Christopher
Robin!
It's only games that love their players.
Oh, shoot.
Oh my god.
I love that it's the invisible ones that I'm okay with now.
Watch this be a zigzag motherfu...
Oh, nevermind.
Look at him.
Look at that face.
Three home runs in a row.
So proud of you.
Thank you.
Hehehe.
Oh.
Kamii game.
Ouch.
Yes.
Oh my gosh.
Maybe one day we'll do the Christopher Robin special.
But, um...
Gosh, only allowing you to mess up 10 times is really, really brutal.
I think.
Oh!
We did it!
We did it, everybody!
Stage 1 through 7.
Pro Gamer Minto.
Not many people can say they beat Tigger.
Stand proud!
Yeah!
I won't subject you guys to that anymore.
The Tigger victory.
And, in my eyes, the Christopher Robin half...
Halfly done.
You beat Tigger so easily, but she is such a gamer.
You came in nano and I was just like, oh, I can't look dumb.
I can't... I can't look dumb when you're watching.
So...
I have to look cool.
I have to... I have to look like this is a piece of cake.
Congrats on hitting 23.
I wanted to mention the game Super Mega Baseball 4.
It's an arcade game that has co-op.
You might like it because of batting mechanic.
And because you enjoy this game.
Oh!
Yeah, I enjoy this game so much.
Thanks for the ping!
Congrats on getting as far as Pikamee.
Have fun at Otakutan.
Thank you!
Yes.
Next time for sure.
Yeah, yeah, Tigger.
Yeah, yeah.
Same time next week.
Same time next week, buddy.
Owl, I think, was the hardest, though, for me.
Owl, I think, was pretty difficult.
I missed the Tigger victory.
Could you do it again?
Okay!
Oh!
I think with Tigger.
What took so...
Well, I'm going to say this.
You know, you guys will probably be like, no, that's copium.
But I definitely, in between, started losing focus.
I would like focus...
I would like lock on and then for like 12 rounds, I'd be like, I'm just talking with chat and not paying attention to the game at all.
And I was just like, I should probably pay attention to the game.
No attention.
But then I started to lock in, and sometimes I would lock in and I'd be like, ah, it's too hard.
I would lock in and I'd be frustrated.
Then I'd lock in and I'd be good.
I could tell by your eyes.
Yeah.
Well, guys.
I'm going to be...
I'm going to be at Otaku-Thon this weekend, if you are as well.
If not, then, you know, that's fine, too.
I'll see you.
So I don't know when that...
I'll be honest.
I'm not sure the next time I'm going to be able to stream.
Hopefully sometime next week.
But next week, straight from Otaku-Thon, I'm going to Japan.
So it's going to be quite a bit.
So maybe it will be a week off of Minto.
A week off of Minto.
If so, I'm really sorry.
I'll try and stream sometime later next week.
Like, you know, Friday, Saturday time, you know.
Hopefully if I'm not too jet lagged.
Actually, the jet lag might be good because I'll be able to stream at a normal time for you guys.
But, wow, she hates us.
Safe travels.
Thanks, Sushi!
You make me want to have sushi.
Never heard of Otaku-Thon?
Otaku-Con?
Otaku-Thon!
It's in Montreal, Canada.
Yeah, yeah.
Stay safe, Minto.
Don't overdo it.
I won't.
Don't worry.
Minto, stream at an Asia-friendly time?
Probably.
I think it will be...
It will be depending on what my schedule is.
So, sometimes it might be like early...
Like morning...
Rather, it will be morning JST or night JST.
So, one or the other.
Which would be morning EST or night EST.
Yeah, yeah.
So...
We'll hold the maid cafe...
We'll hold down the maid cafe while you're in Japan.
Just like last time.
Thank you!
Yeah, I'm sorry that I've been traveling so much recently, you guys.
But after...
After this...
After I return from Japan, I will be not traveling for quite some time.
So...
Yes, yes, yes.
So, I'll see you all soon.
Bye!
I love you all!
Bye.
Bye -bye, Thailand.
Bye!
Take care!
Bye-bye.
Bye-bye, Australia!
Bye-bye...
Bye.
It's hot in Japan, so be careful.
I heard it was in Birmingham.
That sounds correct.
Merch store soon?
That... hopefully I can get it set up while I'm in Japan.
Hopefully I can get it set up while I'm in Japan.
I'm hoping like...
I was originally hoping for an August 1st opening, but it might be like mid-August.
And then things probably shipping out like mid-September or so.
Depending.
Mid to late September.
Well, actually that's... some things will come in in time.
Other things will be later.
Like obviously the dakimakura is not even done, so I haven't even been able to get it printed.
And...
But I might have like... you know, I might do it in waves.
So it's not all just everything at once.
Because also... then if someone's just like, Oh, I want to buy the plushie, but I also want to buy the dakimakura.
I can't do both.
If you know, you can do the plushie one month and then a couple months later, you can do the dakimakura.
Then it could be... it could work out, you know.
So... might stagger it a little bit.
For that reason.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okey dokey.
I'm gonna head out and I'm gonna go finish my food.
And my... and rest.
And... oh, I have to pack.
I have to pack.
I have to finish signing postcards.
I'm gonna go do that.
Thank you everybody.
Congrats on beating Tigger.
That right there is why you're my Oshibos.
Sorry, I was making a sandwich.
Thanks James Cameron!
Thank you guys for all the superdots.
For all the... all the donations.
I really, really, really appreciate it.
And...
Yeah!
I'm really worried that if I exit out of this game...
It'll not save.
You know what I mean?
I'm really worried that it won't save.
Should we test it out?
Will I have to do everything all over again?
Time to see.
Time to see if it saves everything.
It'll be one of those things.
It was all a dream.
Oh my god, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up.
Okay, ready for the moment of truth?
It saved!
It saved everything!
Yeah!
Go away!
Let's go!
Christopher...
Well guys, that means we definitely could do Christopher Robin.
Actually, hold on.
What if it wasn't Christopher Robin?
What if
it wasn't Christopher Robin?
See you in the Hunger Games.
You're not going against Christopher anymore!
I hate Christopher.
It's all about... you're going against Minto now.
Good luck and may your soul...
May... may... may Minto have pity on your soul.
Bye!
Okay.
Good night.
Have a nice day!
Bye-bye!
See you guys next week!
Or I may see you at Otakutan!
See you at Otakutan!
If I see you at... what is it?
Oh gosh.
I always forget what convention I'm going to be at with Doki.
But if I see you there, I'll see you there!
Or if I see you at VEXBALL!
See you there!
Bye-bye!
I also forgot to mention...
I forgot to mention...
Probably every stream...
Probably every stream while I'm in Japan will be Chibi Minto.
So...
I hope you guys don't mind.
That probably every stream in Japan will be Chibi Minto.
It's easier on my computer.
And everything.
So...
Yeah.
Thank you!
Bye-bye!
Otu Minto!
Oh!
I also forgot one more thing.
Okay.
This one is actually like pretty important.
Alright.
So...
I...