Coffee.
Can.
A.
S.
M.
R.
Am I dreaming?
No, Chibi?
Would you prefer that?
I'm big again.
I'll be honest, I'm not used to this.
I think I got so used to Chibi Minto.
It was hard going back.
It was hard going back!
I'm big!
I got coffee.
It's my first coffee of the day.
You're big.
Welcome back, Minto!
Thank you!
Coffee.
Big Boss Minto.
Big sippin'.
Why are her hands like that?
Which parts specifically are big again?
My heart.
And my brain.
Rhys, thanks for the gift!
Do you need to tweet?
Oh, thank you!
Oh my gosh.
I forgot to tweet.
Oh, I also forgot to do something else.
Sorry.
Hold on.
Uh, tweet.
Haaunting now.
She's so good at this, you guys.
Professional streamer.
I am...
Indy!
Yeah, anyway.
One year of experience.
One year of experience!
My best coin run was 9.9 million with ASCII on stage 3 hard.
9.9 million coins.
I don't think I have any coins.
I have 500 coins.
100 more years.
You get paid for this, so automatically a pro.
That's not how that...
That's not how that works.
You're expecting too much.
Hahaha.
A professional is someone who has a master's degree.
Probably.
They have published a scientific paper on the field.
Hi Yamato.
I'm paying you for your labor.
Congrats, you're a professional now.
I've never once participated in a tournament.
How can I be a professional?
Taking a big test tomorrow and haven't caught any streams recently.
As a result, unfortunately...
Amelia!
You got this!
You've got this in your big brain.
Paycheck.
Oh.
WrestleTuber?
No,
I was a host.
I was...
I was helping host.
I casted.
Yeah, that's not...
That's different.
You guys, I got Saina.
Howdy, professional streamer.
Good luck, Amelia!
Big.
Did you see that scientific paper on the toxicity of Ayame and Nakiri's hordes?
Wait...
Is that real?
I want to play Saina.
Is it okay?
People last time said Saina was probably like my type of play.
Well, of course, keep talking.
I want to go to the Halloween castle.
Tobe.
You can start with reason.
Oh!
Risu for coin farm!
Yes!
Yes, I've heard that Risu is so good for coins.
But you need to buy 4 out of 5 weapon limiter in the shop.
You can still get 100k coins of one brand on stage 1.
What?
No way...
Wait, I saw... I heard... I heard...
Marilyn, thank you!
Happy birthday to Mari from Blue Archive.
Yes, happy birthday to Mari from Blue Archive.
Let's see... Oh!
Do you hear my cat?
Do you want outpies?
I think she wants to leave.
Okay, hold on.
Give me a second.
Let me let my cat out.
Hi!
Usually she likes to stay.
Okay, um...
Maybe we should do Risu then.
I also got Risu.
I haven't played Risu.
I played a little bit of Sana.
Little tiny bit.
And by little, I mean like 2 minutes worth.
But I want to save most for stream, right?
Alright, let's try Risu.
Stage 1, Risu.
Big nuts.
After powerful singing that stuns targets for 3 seconds, Risu summons big nuts.
Cool.
Can you tell us how you escaped Wawa's...
Her vacuum?
That's like confidential.
I'm sorry.
Thanks!
You evolved from Chibi Minto to Minto Minto.
That's professionalism.
Farm 1 billion coins.
Yeah, I've heard that Risu is best for...
For coinage.
But I do not know why.
I do not know what makes her the coin master.
I'm so used to playing Fauna.
Not having to...
Aim.
So if I ever get to aim...
Sorry.
I don't want more nuts.
Non-stop nuts!
This is cute today too.
Thank you.
Big nut.
Greed stamp plus super chatto.
Ah...
You're a super...
You're a professional cute.
Non-stop nuts!
I appreciate you guys giving advice.
But try not to backseat too much.
Because you know I'm...
It's only my second time playing on stream.
And so I still am trying to like experiment.
And I still...
Oh!
I didn't even notice that guy.
I'm just trying to play and learn things myself.
But thank you.
Thanks for posting on Blue Sky.
I forgot my login.
For Blue Sky.
So...
Um...
I forgot my login for Blue Sky.
So I kept forgetting to login.
But if you use a Blue Sky, I'm on it.
And I will hope...
I will try to put...
Oh!
Wait.
Oh gosh.
It's like YouTube is integrated with the...
With...
With Twitter.
I wonder if the link...
I wonder if the link is integrated with Blue Sky.
So I can easily post there too.
When I start streaming.
Deez.
I've never seen...
I don't think I've ever seen DLC before.
Game one.
Holocoin every three seconds!
Is this the big money?
Deez.
Inflicts internal damage.
Reese's main weapon has a 10% chance to inflict damage equal to 20% chance...
Deez.
20% of a non-boss target's HP.
DLC is your skill.
Well, I mean, these are both skills.
We should go with the DLC first.
Because it's cumulative.
After gaining Holocoins five times.
Create another Reese's.
Don't touch me!
Burger.
Oh!
Okay.
Two Reese's.
Okay, I should...
I'm going to add another nut.
More Reese's!
Nut squared.
Unlimited nut works.
Gained two coins!
Yeah.
What was that noise?
Shadow Jutsu.
Kage no... Kage no Nut.
Oh, that ult's available.
Okay.
Shadow Nut Jutsu.
Yippee!
Dududu dududu dududu dudududu dududududu dudududu dududu...
One more nut!
I don't...
feel like...
The sake... Is the sake any good?
Is sake any good?
Is sake okay?
It's free.
Yeah, but...
Gain 1% crit buff every second up to 10%.
If taking damage by target, lose half the buff.
Depends on the build.
It's good if you don't get hit.
Risa doesn't really build crit.
Never turn down for Risaka.
You know what?
So true.
But I feel like if she doesn't have crit, then it's probably whatever, right?
It's my birthday.
JCTR, happy birthday!
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday JCTR.
Let's keep going with the DLC.
Coin.
Coin, coin, coin.
Oh my gosh, wait.
It's kind of hard to tell which Risu is me.
That's a lot of nuts!
Nuts awakened!
Oh my god, they bounce!
Oh my gosh, I kind of miss that movie so much.
The Kung Pao movie.
I wonder if that movie's aged...
gracefully or not.
You know what I mean?
Like I wonder...
if it's...
still like... I say this every time.
I use this as an excuse.
I used to be a Lion King 1 1⁄2 believer.
I was like, that movie was sooo funny.
That movie was like... oh my gosh.
On par with Lion King 1 and 2.
And then I was like, I'm gonna watch it with a friend.
And I'll show the world how good Lion King 1 1⁄2 was.
And then I was watching and I was like...
And I was like, not very funny.
And I was like...
I was like...
The funny part will come.
Just keep watching.
Oh, this part.
This part's really funny.
And that part would happen and I'd be like...
And I was just like...
Don't worry, it'll get there.
It'll get there.
And it just...
But it never did.
It never did.
Nostalgia's a cruel mistress.
But...
I feel like for Kung...
Pao...
That movie...
I feel like it was still funny.
Even now.
Oh, what's up here?
What do we got?
An anvil!
What's in ha...
Oh, I don't have much, do I?
Oh.
Maybe I could've saved it for later.
Oh well.
Watch along.
Shall we have the...
The council decide?
Funny...
Funny haha or funny...
Oh...
Watch Kung Pao just the other day?
Still amazing?
No way.
Oh, I haven't even tried the special yet.
Idol costume's amazing?
I do...
I...
Have used it...
In other...
Things.
Mint is a Disney sequel believer?
Depends.
Trying to think of like...
I mean, there's plenty...
Like...
Pocahontas 2?
I...
I love so much.
Because it's so bad.
It's so...
Bad.
Cinderella 3?
When she goes back in time?
Okay.
I'm gonna go with idol costume.
Sorry.
Oh!
See?
My luck is not so great, everybody.
Cinderella has the three parts?
You would be surprised.
Gosh, there's just nuts everywhere.
Which one do we wanna go for?
Um...
I don't know.
It's so funny.
They could explode into nuts.
Let's just keep going with the nuts.
Piggy bank.
Oh!
I should've gone for piggy bank.
Oh, my bad.
Sorry, guys.
Okay.
When we get piggy bank back...
Greed!
Let's just keep going.
Let's just keep enhancing.
For now.
Okay.
Oh!
Ow!
Oh, my God.
There's so many nuts.
Non-stop nuts.
Ow!
Okay.
They're fast.
They are.
Projectile up stamp.
Adds one additional shot.
Oh.
Does not affect...
Okay.
I...
We have a lot of those.
We have non-stop nuts!
For real!
Oh!
Non-stop nuts!
For real!
Holy moly!
That's a lot of nuts!
We'll just max that out while we're here.
I lost track of my...
Of my cursor.
But we're okay now.
Oh!
I want to try...
Let's try the special.
Once we get kind of surrounded, I'll do the special.
I don't know what it does, but...
We shall see.
I don't know what it does because I didn't read!
Oh!
Nice.
Hmm...
I still also...
It's hard because I still also don't know, like, what combines with what entirely.
Like, I know the bucket we can combine with the spiders.
Right?
Non-stop nuts September!
Yeah!
Right click?
Axe and bucket combine?
Oh, they do?
What do you mean click right?
I am.
Bucket combines with the lie.
Ah!
Click on the blue panel.
Oh!
This one!
Ah!
Yeah!
I know this one.
Oh!
This is the BL with the...
We don't have the BL yet, but maybe we should get the axe and try and create this.
Okay.
I think I'll go with that.
I like the whammy water.
What does...
I remember you can do something with the whammy water at the dorm.
I'm going psycho mode.
Let's do the skills.
Let's level up the skills first.
Not jutsu.
I'm just going in circles here.
What was this?
What?
Ah!
I'm stuck.
Attacks have 20% chance to reduce attack and defensive targets.
Oh!
Flower.
Ah!
Guys, we have nuts for days.
BL book.
All right.
Now I just got to work on leveling those up.
And we'll be...
We'll be good.
Uh
-oh.
Guys, I think we're surrounded.
Oh!
Risu, is it cute?
Wait.
Stat up?
I've never seen this before, I think.
Where does it...
Where does it go?
Is it like with the skills?
Try your special now?
It's just a stat?
Oh.
Okay.
People are saying to check to do the gorillas' paws.
Is that good?
Because we don't have much critical...
Everyone is so smart.
We don't have much crit chance, so...
Makes sense!
I'll try it!
And then...
What did that do?
Holy moly.
First...
The first target this weapon hits is marked.
The marked target will receive 20% of the damage.
What if I enhance greed instead?
More greed!
Okay, we were all on the same page!
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy you guys are also on the same page as me.
I'm so happy we're all on the same page.
We're money, money, money, baby.
More money, more babes, baby.
They say more money, more problems, but...
I have 99 Hololive members.
And...
They're...
Wait, hold on.
How does that go?
I have 99...
I have 99 problems.
Wait, no.
I have...
Wait.
I have the...
I have...
I have 99 girls and a problem is one of...
Wait.
Is how the...
Anyway...
You guys get what I mean.
You guys get it!
Don't act like you don't know what I'm talking about!
Don't act like I'm crazy.
Don't act like you don't know.
Don't act like I'm not...
Making total sense here.
I am!
I'm making total sense.
But you are crazy.
Let's go for the Psycho.
Maybe I have more problems than I thought I did.
Maybe I have more problems than I...
than I realized.
I like the Nightly Milk too.
I like that one.
I think.
I'm gonna... but I wanna go... I wanna get my...
Yippee!
I got 99 problems, but a mint ate one.
What?
Oh, I'll take that.
Guys, I... that's like the first...
rainbow box I've gotten.
Oh my gosh.
That's the first rainbow box I've gotten.
Like...
I haven't gotten one since playing the first time.
Let's see.
Let's go with the Gorillas, pal.
What can we... what can we level up?
Oh, let's do the book.
Upgrade.
Yeah, you guys bring all the luck.
My chat brings all the luck to the yard.
And they're like...
We're lucky, chat.
I'm a lucky, chat.
I can teach you.
But you'll have to super chat.
Oh!
Pekka pekka!
Swap flower.
Replace the third one.
Please teach me.
Today, the student surpasses the master.
Buff greed.
Hey.
Works for me, baby.
Max greed.
I'm greedy.
I'm trying to...
get another amp.
Like one of the good anvils.
So we can...
get the...
book and...
the BL book and the...
There we go.
And the axe.
Okay.
Yes.
Money, money, money, money, baby.
Money, money, money, money.
So many bouncing nights.
I know!
There's more money here than...
than like...
experience.
Oh!
We're halfway through!
Pshew!
Oh gosh!
Oh!
Oh my god.
That was so close.
Reisu!
Ouch.
Um...
How much health?
Oh!
I was gonna say how much health did I lose, but...
It's actually okay.
I'll take it.
Okay, they're close.
You did get hit.
No, but my HP is okay!
I'm a-okay.
Okay.
If I got hit in your dreams...
Do you guys like...
like collecting everything that you want first, and then maxing it out?
Or do you like maxing one thing at a time, you know?
I prefer to like...
make one thing stronger.
You know?
Oh!
Which one do I do?
Max, then grab build.
Yeah, I feel like that too, right?
Depends on the run.
I guess that's fair.
That's fair.
There's no wrong way to play.
Unless...
you die.
Then...
you played wrong.
And you got played.
That's...
just the facts of it.
Super Chanto time!
Let's do the book.
Thanks for the climb, Marfei.
Super Chanto time!
Oh wait.
Oh no, wait, that triggers you guys.
Ah!
Dun, dun, dun!
Thank you guys for the Super Chants.
Thank you!
Oh my gosh.
Mike!
Thanks for the prank!
I heard it's Super Chanto time.
Let's go more with the gorilla's paw.
We're killing it.
Where's all my money?
Why are you guys not dropping coins as much anymore?
Kei!
Kei, get out of here!
No!
Don't watch!
I'm embarrassed.
Go away!
No!
I'm gonna end this stream.
Go!
Go away!
Thanks for the donut rock.
Thank you.
Oh.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I have to...
The donut!
The trumpet!
Attack size.
What was this?
Add one additional...
I think I should have increased the projectile.
Right?
That way we have...
Chicken noodle!
Hello!
More nuts.
Right?
Strengthen the nut.
I really want the trumpet though.
Super chat time.
I want the trumpet!
Greed?
Wait, it says it's max though.
I can't.
Ignore trumpet.
Acquire currency.
I know that it's bait.
Funny over strong.
So true!
I can't strengthen...
Oh, it's already max?
Oh, shoot.
Okay.
Ah!
Nice!
Sorry.
Nice.
No!
Let's see.
What do we want to do now?
Oh!
Hmmm.
We can do this one.
This one...
The asa-coco?
More projectiles?
Oh!
Because we have that!
So true...
I'll take milk!
Nut milk.
Oh god, it's so annoying!
Back up, buddy!
Back up!
Oh wait, but this is...
Wait, oh I can upgrade it!
Does it cost money?
Oh, cost...
Oh, excuse you!
Costing money?
What do you think I am?
Made of nuts?
Get out of here!
Max out Super Chatto time?
Okay.
Don't worry.
We will.
We'll max it.
Let's just...
We'll get there.
They're ganging up on us!
The chump is in the deadbeats!
Stop it!
Are you guys enjoying...
The stream?
Oh my god...
Whoa!
Super Chatto time.
Says so stream?
Question mark...
What are you talking about?
It is!
Oh my god...
Oh.
What did I run into?
No!
I blame the trumpet.
What did I run into?
Actually, I also blame K.
Get out of here!
I ran with the deadbeats.
It's in my ectoplasm, okay?
Gosh!
Oh, that's so annoying!
Ow!
My coins!
Wait, I get to keep the coins, alright?
Yeah!
Disable weapon slots and upgrades for Max Green.
Wait...
Weapon slots?
Huh?
Money gained up!
You're all coming for your nuts.
Growth?
Where's growth?
Do-do-do-do-do-do-do!
Am I silly?
Oh, here!
Increase the damage of character main weapons.
Aha!
Enhance.
Oh!
That's a lot of money.
Fandoms.
Sorry, fan...
Wait, that's what I said.
Wait.
Fand...
Yeah, that's what I said.
I'm okay.
I'm good.
I'm fine.
Game bonuses based on accomplishments.
Oh, cute!
Weapon limit.
Is this what you guys...
Wait, limit the max number of weapons that may be gained in the game.
Wait, what am I... Why am I doing this?
Oh, is it so that I can get greed over and over and over?
Wait, it would be...
Race 2 is great.
Her attacks work exactly like nuclear fission if you turn up the spawn rate and max out her non-stop nuts skill.
Hmm...
It's for money build.
Oh, it makes it harder.
Ah, I think I'm okay then.
I'm okay.
I don't want to make it harder, you guys.
I just died.
I don't think I should make it any harder for me.
But I want to do Risu again.
I want to try Risu again.
And also...
I think I...
Okay, I know I just died using her, but I want to try the next level so that we can try and unlock the Halloween castle because I really want to play that one.
Money.
Yeah, we'll get money.
Don't worry.
Yeah.
You get money.
You know how you get money, you guys?
By playing the game.
That's how you can also make the money.
Say choose honestly or easier to farm money.
What a concept.
I know, right?
Let's do...
I'm going to enhance a little bit.
Let's go see what's going on.
Let's do like...
Let's do like stuff like this.
Let's do some like general overall attack.
Let's do...
Wait, what was that?
Increase attack speed.
Where is...
Where is haste?
The drops?
I did upgrade it.
I'm so stupid.
You need got it back.
That was haste.
I know.
Um, let's see...
Only這個是.
Sorry for the this.
One HP every five seconds.
Just like some quality, you know, some stuff that old.
And of course, money.
So, really, here's one.
HP every five seconds.
Just like some quality.
5 months of Spooky!
Lucky, thank you!
Thank you, thank you!
What else?
Pick up range?
Here, we'll do this one.
I'm going to do another haste.
I know I'm going to worry about critical right now.
Like the critical hit right now, because...
With Risu, it's not as important.
I'm going to...
Okay, this should be fine for now.
Where are you?
There you are.
Nuts.
Glad you're having fun, boss.
Thanks, Koki!
I am.
Oh!
Yippee!
Oh, I forgot.
There we go.
I was like, hello?
I am having fun.
I always have fun with you guys.
Wait...
Okay,
there we go.
I'm trying to decide what I want to focus on.
I feel like maybe the skills...
What the heck was that?
It was raining in here.
Give me a second...
Let's see.
Nuts!
Hello?
What's this one?
Wait.
Create a regular fan-spot.
No!
You guys!
I got... Hold on!
Hold on!
You guys are trying to kill me!
I get it that it's more money, but you guys are trying to kill me!
You guys!
You're trying to... Hold on.
Before we get this... Before we get this...
Let's... Let's... Let me increase my stuff first!
And then... And then we'll do this later!
It's the best option for money!
I know!
But it's...
Let me... Let me... Let me... Let me increase my skills first!
I don't want to just be overwhelmed!
Like I am right now!
Oh my god.
Let me... Let me...
Let me...
It might not show up again.
You want to say that?
You want to say that again?
It's a sign!
I hope you never listen to chat and let them mold.
It's like my favorite thing.
To be honest.
I also really like the body pillow.
I feel like a body pillow would be great for...
For... For this level.
This level is hard with the holo doll!
Do it no balls?
Is that a threat?
You can't say that I'm a chicken!
It's my weakness.
It will make me do anything.
Where's the money?
Hey!
Oh gosh!
You guys!
Ouch!
Mindy McFly!
Okay, more nut.
Ouch!
We're getting...
We're getting cornered!
Oh gosh, we're getting cornered for real.
I think we're going to do more nuts.
More nuts.
Guys, this is already looking kind of bad.
Oh my god.
This is already looking kind of bad.
This is...
You guys are going to make it so I can't beat this level.
You guys are going to make it so I don't beat this level.
Oh god!
I need help so bad!
Well it wasn't available before.
My ult.
I'll do it now though.
There we go!
Food!
That wasn't enough.導 wil Let's see.
Let's
see.
More nut.
attaching to eyes What
is my hitbox anyway?
Oh my god.
I thought that was it.
What the?
Why did it disappear?
I didn't click anything!
That was weird.
Why does it keep disappearing?
Why is it not clicking anything?
But my cursor keeps changing.
Why?
Why is it changing?
I'm so confused.
Wait, why is it actually doing that?
I'm not clicking!
Oh my god, there's like an army.
There's an army following me.
I'm not clicking, but it was doing that.
Weird, weird, weird, weird, weird.
Oh my god!
I wonder if I should do the bandage.
Or else I'll die.
Wait, there we go.
Oh.
I'm just gonna keep running backwards.
Why is it changing again?
What is happening?
It wasn't doing that the last round.
Is there something wrong with my mouse?
What?
What is happening?
Hold on, hold on.
I'm not concerned about the experience right now.
I'm concerned about my mouse.
Hmm.
I think I'm just gonna restart.
That's so funny.
Okay, well soon, Pill.
Someday when I grow up, I hope I can be a ghost just like you.
You can.
Just have a lot of regrets.
Oh.
We're already back.
That was so fast.
Okay.
Alright.
Mouse.
True mouse.
Alrighty.
Okay.
Let's go with...
Not that anime.
Oh no.
Someone who recognizes mouse.
True mouse.
Nut.
Lulu, you would want that.
You would want the nut.
Alright.
So far, my mouse is okay.
Theme song is stuck in my head for life.
It's under 17, so...
Of course I love it.
Let's do...
Okay.
Do I want the nut or do I want the BL book?
Oh...
Should I level up nut or do I get another weapon?
Nut.
Always nut.
Fanbeam does good...
Oh!
I know Fanbeam and Asakoko!
Yes, I know, I know, I know.
Keep on nuttin'.
Well, not for now.
That is good to just get some strength in.
But I feel like I need to...
In this level particularly, I need more like...
And...
It's hard.
It's hard because...
Yeah, the reduced time...
Like, we're so slow right now.
So it's like...
Minto needs DPS.
It's true, it's true, it's true!
Oh, that's a special cooldown.
I'm gonna keep nutting.
It might be a mistake.
I might be...
Going nut crazy.
I might be getting greedy.
Oh!
What's this?
Oh.
Wait, hold on.
Let's come here.
Come here, come here.
Oh, where did you all go?
Where did everybody go?
They were all here.
Nonstop nuts!
We're nutting too close to the...
Ah!
Too close to the sun.
It's true.
Okay, good.
Okay, okay, okay.
More nut!
One more nut!
Oh, that was close.
I see the...
Sorry,
I got anxious.
Super chat time!
But nuts!
But I want coins.
I have like no coins right now.
I only have 14 coins.
It's very sad.
Okay, we're gonna start focusing on...
Oh, see?
See the...
The more nuts...
Truly does help.
I also need...
Which one is it that creates the shadow nuts?
Which one is that?
Nonstop nut!
Mint wants super chat time.
No, no, no!
Oh, DLC!
DLC!
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, when that one comes up, we'll get that one next.
Thank you guys.
I wanna start focusing more on attack on attack attack.
Oh, my goodness.
I don't
wanna get cornered.
I don't wanna get cornered.
I think I'm gonna get cornered!
Oh, there's DLC.
Yes.
Super chat time.
Put the non-stop nut!
No!
This is too hard!
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe.
Catch a nut by its toe.
If he hollers, let him go.
My mom said to pick the very best nut.
And you are it!
DLC!
Nut...
6.
Oh!
Flower!
I'll take it.
No!
Wait!
I'll take it!
Oh my god!
Shady!
What time is it?
It's nut time.
It's bustin' time!
Thank you for the welcome super!
Thank you!
Non-stop nut!
Alright, alright.
Now I feel a little more comfortable.
We are... Oh gosh.
I said that and then I started getting a little uncomfortable.
I took a bit.
I took a hit.
What was it?
Asakoko and...
What's the other one that goes well with it?
With Asakoko?
I think I'm gonna grab the idol costume.
Fan beam!
Okay.
Fan beam.
Thanks
for the super joy!
Hold on.
One of the workers of Spirit Halloween.
He's a huge fan of MGS.
Can't wait for Delta!
Yeah!
Me too!
Let's do more coins.
Can't wait for MGS3 Delta.
Delta and MGS collection volume 2.
Me too!
Upgrade knight?
Wait, can I?
But it costs money.
It's fine.
We have super chat time.
Wow!
Enhance a weapon once.
I got an achievement.
Yippee!
I'm gonna do these.
It's literally only 50 coins.
In this economy?
That's everything!
Oh my gosh.
We've just been kinda hanging out in the same little area the whole time.
We're gaming.
Let's keep getting these... the...
Oi!
We'll keep working on the skills.
The skills.
Getting our skills up and high and mighty.
Oh!
Azakoko!
Wait.
Okay.
I do wanna get this actually.
Shoop!
Oi!
Ah!
Oh!
Sorry.
I had to itch my nose really bad.
Oh!
I had to itch my nose!
It cost me.
It did cost me.
Hold on.
It cost me everything.
These!
What nose?
That's what you guys sound like.
That's what you guys sound like when you don't know what you're talking about.
What nose?
Oh, my gosh.
It's just giving me all the same stuff over and over again.
What nose?
Whoa!
Everything exploded into nuts.
Oh!
I'll take that.
Okay.
So far, not so bad.
Oh.
Ah!
Sshh.
Once more, I pay my streamer tax.
Thank you, medic.
Thank you.
Introduce Matara to the plugin type Asakoko.
What do you mean by that?
The paw?
Paw for good?
I think you're right.
I think it's...
Mike!
Thank you.
We demand you cease and desist your false marketing.
You repeatedly claim that you are not cute and not small.
Further, you claim to be mint, but you are in fact turquoise!
No!
Our office will be in contact soon!
I'll take it.
You know what?
BL book?
I'll take it.
I'll take everything.
I'll take it all.
I'll take it all!
He so knows nothing.
Joke's on you.
I knows...
Close, close.
I knows a whole lot, okay?
What's your favorite character in...
in...
in Riko?
I actually didn't have a chance to watch so much because...
I was in Japan when, like, it all was going down.
But I... everybody really likes...
Oh gosh.
Gigi's character.
Did someone say turquoise?
Where is...
Shut up.
Sending money for legal, but...
GONathan?
Jonathan?
Yeah, yeah.
If I want to...
If I want to catch up...
How... what would... what would you guys recommend?
Like...
Because there's a lot of POVs.
And a lot of streams.
Get some Minto words of encouragement for the Wisps going through... stuff.
Oh no!
From someone who knows... knows the str...
Wait, I can't tell if you're serious or not.
Fauna Mart was a good watch.
Play all at once.
Okay.
I'll do that.
Let's just keep doing Asakoko.
For now.
So far, we...
Oh, whoa, whoa.
Hello.
So far, we're doing so much better this round.
Probably because we didn't get the money.
We're like the Halu.
Narissa and Erb.
Screw it.
Sorry.
I need the fan beam, right?
That's what we're waiting on.
Fan beam.
Oh gosh, oh gosh, oh gosh, oh gosh...
Oh gosh, oh gosh, oh gosh, oh gosh, oh gosh...
I'm getting cornered!
This is not good!
This is not good, you guys.
This is not good at all.
This is actually quite bad.
This is really bad!
I need the food!
I need food!
I see food!
Okay.
Boiker!
Watching from the hospital.
Daybreaker, I hope you're okay!
Boiker successful.
What?
Okay, I'm going to actually do the body pillow.
Yeah, let's do the body pillow.
Since we're struggling a little bit.
Let's do body pillow.
Holy moly!
Oh gosh!
What's up here?
Oh, anvil!
Let's see.
The nuts?
Do more nuts?
I say paw for damage.
Yeah.
I think so too.
All I need to do is survive.
All I need to do is live!
Oh my gosh!
I want to get to the next...
To the next round!
Well, this one's good actually.
Knockback is good.
I want to get to the Halloween castle!
Let's do.
Knockback is good.
I'm nervous.
I'm nervous!
Ay!
Chill out, get out of here.
I'm nervous.
Oh my gosh.
Oh gosh, I thought my ult was ready!
No-
I couldn't outrun them.
I couldn't outrun them!
I was walking backwards but I couldn't outrun them.
No!
Upgrade movement speed.
I think that's what we need to do.
We need to upgrade our movement speed.
Just by a little bit.
And I'm gonna do... haste.
Oh, never mind.
I can't afford haste.
I'm gonna do... cooldown.
What is fandom?
I can't buy it, but what is it?
Damn girl, you poor...
Shut up!
I just started playing!
What's wrong with you?
Use your free skills when you start.
Okay.
Well, next time.
Alright, we're gonna make it this time.
I believe.
What if I do endless mode?
Well, I can't really even make it until the end.
You know what?
No, it's just stage mode.
What am I thinking?
I'm trying to unlock the castle.
Oh, wait.
There we go.
I'm trying to unlock the castle.
Endless stage mode.
Not yet.
I want the castle.
I really want the castle!
I'm not really trying to money farm.
I just want the castle.
I know Risu.
Actually, probably Risu.
Well, okay.
I'm like doing half and half.
Right?
Cause like I want the money to...
I want the money to...
to...
buy more stuff.
But I also just want the castle.
Believe in castle.
Yeah.
Oh, that didn't...
Oi!
One more nut!
Yeah, we're multitasking.
What the hell?
Why am I getting cornered so easily?
Chill out!
Um...
Multinutting.
The castle is the friends we made along the way.
Nope, the castle is real in there.
Trust your skills as a gamer.
Yeah, that's why I'm gonna keep nutting.
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep!
Body pillow!
Oh!
See?
Body pillow.
Doing his job.
Oh!
Ow!
Oh my gosh.
Please.
No!
Oh!
Oh my gosh.
No, stop!
No, stop nut!
Nut, please!
Nut!
Okay.
We're doing it.
I think.
I just came here.
Hello!
Welcome, welcome!
Then a body pillow.
Just a little bit.
Just a...
Oh my gosh.
When it gets really tight and dicey.
Yep!
Hyah!
I wish...
Oh.
Wish I were faster.
Alright.
Oh gosh.
Oh my gosh.
I'm not feeling as confident in this one as I felt.
There we go.
Oh!
Hasakoko and fan beam.
Uh oh.
One more nut.
Fan beam!
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba.
Hyah!
Oh!
Nice!
If you get the solo weapon stamp, you could try a nut only run.
You could try a nut only run.
I could do that.
Only nut.
I must defeat this level first.
Oh my gosh.
Oh...
Oh god!
We're fine, everybody.
One more nut!
Oh
my gosh.
Please.
Why am I so weak?
What is that?
Gosh!
Oh...
I'll still take it.
Get out of here, Yago!
Not right now!
Oh my gosh, not right now, please.
Stop.
Stop!
Where's my... please.
My ult, please.
There we go.
Oh my gosh.
What is this one?
Decrease the... oh...
Oh no, wait.
Maybe I should just sell this one.
Maybe I should just...
Or... because I don't want to, like, enhance this one.
I think I should sell it.
But, like, I don't want to enhance this one because I'm going to use this...
this crit up one for later.
Leave it on the ground to use as an upgrade?
Just leave it?
Okay.
I'll just leave it on the ground.
We're littering.
We're littering!
Oh my god.
Maybe the fan beam was not such a good idea for right now.
Please give me upgrades.
Oh, you guys.
Ouch,
ouch.
Ouch, ouch.
It
hurts!
Um...
Oh.
Oh!
Okay, okay.
Nice.
I'm, like, missing every... every shot.
Truly, you miss every shot you take.
No shadow clones yet.
I know!
I'm not getting DLC!
Let's do Gorilla Pong.
Gorilla Pong!
Do-ble-le-le-lep!
Oh!
Wow!
Yeah, yeah, no, no, no.
Wow.
There we go.
Take that.
Which is like... soon.
Probably.
Right now we're okay.
We're okay.
Oh my god.
When I hear my health go...
No!
Do you guys want me to die?
This
would be a suicide mission!
Real!
Oh my god.
Do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do.
Non-stop nut.
Scared.
Shut up.
I am scared.
Greed!
Actually, hold on.
Swap.
And then you.
Oh.
You.
Strengthen.
Hahaha.
Money, money, money.
Oh wait, we have two more things over here.
I just noticed them.
You guys have probably been like, screaming like, Oh my gosh!
You have the thing- Oh!
You have the things over here!
I have that one.
Oh my god, no way.
It's a trumpet.
Why is- What's all the- DLC!
What's with all these useless drums?
Hahaha.
Apply.
Oh!
Oh my god.
Wait, what's this one again?
Yeah, increase attack slot?
Sure.
Yeah.
Oh wait!
Um...
I thought this was an up- Sorry, hold on.
I thought it was an upgrade one.
Um...
Big nut.
It's good for nuts.
Yeah.
I'm wondering if I should do spider cooking as like a...
As like a...
Outer defense, you know?
Boo.
Spider cooking, then get the bucket.
In this map, it probably is really good, right?
Oh my gosh.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Oh...
Oh my gosh.
Wait, so now I'm gonna upgrade you...
Nuts.
I'm gonna- I'm gonna- What?
The nuts.
Wait for Asakoko for the upgrade.
Now I'm gonna waken the nuts.
Holy cow.
Just ask yourself, what would Risa do?
The answer is always, oh my god.
So true.
So true!
Oh my god.
Oh my health.
Alright.
Okay.
We're shooting.
We're rooting and we're tooting.
Ah, Sokoku!
We got it back!
Oh, that was close.
I think it might be time soon to use my special once it appears to me.
Let's do the fan beat.
Let's just max this one out.
Woah, woah, woah.
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, now it's double.
Okay, let's go.
Okay, okay, okay.
DLC!
Ouch, ouch.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
I don't know who I just ran into, but... Oh my god.
Okay.
We survived!
Oh, ouch!
I don't need to use my special yet.
I think I'm okay.
For now...
What?
Don't forget to aim.
I'll be honest.
I completely forgot.
I completely forgot about aiming.
Why aren't you aiming left?
Because I completely forgot, okay?
Because after...
After the...
What's it called?
The fan beam started going both ways, I completely forgot about aiming.
Let's see...
Let's go with these.
Oh my god.
We did it.
Oh!
I don't think I want it.
I don't think I...
I don't think I want the bomb.
These guys look like little...
Avatar, The Last Airbender, little Aang's.
Where do I...
I'm like, do I max out or do I aim for Asakoko so that we can...
Because we have the fan beam.
The 35P?
Yeah, yeah.
Max Asakoko?
I think so too.
I think so too!
Oh my god, so much money.
Oh my god, so
much money.
Oh my god, so much money.
Oh, what's this?
A cold stamp!
Unhit if player does not...
get attacked by the target for 4 seconds, the player may become frozen.
And take 50% cold damage...
Wait, what?
The target gets frozen.
Buff the trumpet.
So true.
Did I just realize?
It's Miko.
Isn't it?
The 35?
I'm so stupid.
MikoP.
Japanese.
How are you real?
What are you saying?
You don't believe in ghosts?
Um...
Try it.
Oh wait, it's already maxed.
Elito Minto.
Nihongo Jozunt.
What?
I got Nihongo Jozunt like 5 times while I was in Japan.
I'm basically...
native speaker.
I'm basically native speaker.
The dudes must go, everybody.
The dudes must go.
Let's just...
I'm just gonna strengthen this one, I guess.
Yeah, I'm basically N1.
I can read every newspaper.
Attack size!
You guys, I can't always live for the meme.
When...
I want to haunted house.
No way.
You can read?
I can sometimes even speak.
Oh my gosh!
Look at them get frozen!
What
is the blacksmith?
We just unlocked this.
Normal anvils can be used twice.
Only applies to anvils since taking this item.
Oh!
It's good?
I'll try it since I have not ever had it before.
I like to try new stuff.
I'm adventurous, you guys.
I like to try...
Wow, there's so much money here.
Holy cow!
There's so much money!
Look at all this cash, cash, cash, cash, cash...
Oh my god.
Wait, I forgot.
Okay.
Those pizzas are her bad...
are the bad pizzas.
Okay.
Bad pizza, bad pizza.
Don't go towards the bad pizza.
Bad
pizza, bad...
She's frozen!
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
No!
Holy cow.
That could have been really bad.
Um...
So cute.
Weee!
Yoi, yoi, yoi!
That was unfair.
Freeze!
Am I still hitting her?
I wonder.
From this length.
Can't tell.
Pizza, pizza, pizza.
Bad pizza.
We did it!
Okay, guys, we're halfway there.
Oh!
We're halfway there.
Make me a pizza.
More toppings!
Keep going for the Asakoko.
We must max out.
Oh my gosh!
Oh!
Ah!
We managed to avoid drowning!
Alright, give me my golden anvil, please.
Dragonfire!
Oh my god!
Woah, woah, woah.
Now you need to aim.
Yes.
Let's just go with the spider.
Oh my goodness.
Okay, it's really hard to see though.
These new guys are like so small.
And my new attack is so large.
And takes up so much space.
You know what I mean?
It's so hard to see.
Holy cow.
Okay.
It reminds... Because the attack is so big, it reminds me to aim.
But it's also...
It's a lot going on.
There's a lot going on.
Oh!
I'll take that.
Yeah, I keep forgetting to lower the opacity.
Um...
I like the frozen one a lot.
Swap size?
My size up?
I think so.
Yeah, I think so.
Swap, swap.
Yeah, frozen has been saving me.
I'm gonna keep it.
Size doesn't matter, Minto!
When I was recording with Matara earlier today, we recorded the last episode of the podcast.
And um...
She called me a size queen.
Because...
Okay.
I like...
Well, you know what?
You're just gonna have to watch the podcast.
Yeah, you'll have to listen to the podcast.
I can't decide which one I wanna do.
Which one I wanna level up.
It's level 2, but it only does one level, right?
It's not gonna make this one max, right?
It's not gonna
make this one max, right?
Tune in to find out more!
Otsu summer!
Oh, so maybe we should just do that then, right?
Oh, it is max!
Oh my gosh!
Get your head in the game!
It's so good that we kept the frozen.
It really has been saving my BEARD!
What's that?
Reverse stab?
Is that... veils?
Weapons will fire backwards.
There is no other effect.
I get it.
She's Australian!
That wasn't an Australian accent.
Bobby.
Gorilla paw.
I've been waiting for that one to come back.
Paw, paw, paw, paw, paw.
Oh wait!
Wait, the knockback is good too though.
But maybe we should keep the cold stamp.
Anvil on the left?
There it is.
Oh I see it.
Oh wow.
Hold on, we gotta get through here.
Where's the anvil?
Oh, it's still over.
Nice, nice.
Oh wait, maybe probably monkey's paw.
Just kidding, I can't do monkey's paw.
Oh, it's already in.
Okay.
It won't let me do the monkey paw.
The paw.
The paw is maxed?
Oh, when did I max him?
Upgrade?
Upgrade.
Let's go baby!
Oh, bam!
I took a small damage.
Oh my god!
Get me out of here!
What do we want to get next?
Um...
Maybe the bucket?
Right?
Because then we can do the bucket and...
The axe?
I guess we could have done the axe.
Strength?
Oh...
I'm gonna take...
I'm gonna go with the body pill there, right?
Okay.
Alright, so far so good!
What's this one?
Weapon hits have 10% chance to stun enemies temporarily.
Also has a 20% chance to destroy enemy projectiles.
Whoa!
Everything is maxed though.
Hmm...
I should have gotten how to...
Shut up!
Sell?
Oh yeah, you can sell them.
I forgot.
Alright...
We're getting surrounded.
There's so much money.
There's so much money to be made.
So much money being made!
So much money.
I'm not as strong as I think I am.
I'm not strong enough to just stand here and take it.
Come on, come on.
Let's get some of these.
Oh gosh.
Oh god.
You guys, we're in trouble.
We're in trouble for real.
I'm getting cornered.
I'm scared.
We made it out.
We made it out somehow.
What the?
Where did they go?
Oh my god, this guy is fast.
Oh my god.
We're alive!
I should get the... I should drop it and wait for the axe, shouldn't I?
With the BL.
I should get the BL and then the axe.
Yeah, we're going to drop it.
BL enthusiast.
What item did I grab to get the... Oh my gosh.
The BL.
Oh.
The BL HP.
This is a stage.
It's not endless.
Oh my gosh.
Wow!
The body pillow.
I see, I see, I see.
Nice.
I love body pillow.
I'm going to run.
Oh my gosh.
I was taking damage and I didn't even realize.
Where is there any health?
Help?
I'm scared.
Anvil.
If I can get to it.
Oh, I forgot I can use them twice.
Wait, it's already maxed, right?
Oh yeah.
Okay.
Maybe I should...
Wait, wait, wait!
Sorry, sorry.
Scared.
No way.
Guys, this isn't good.
This isn't good.
Enchant the bucket.
Body pillow it is.
I think we should do the body pillow.
And then run!
Oh shoot.
Oh.
Oh, it's...
It might be mint over.
Everybody.
GG's.
GG.
GG world.
Goodbye cruel world!
Oh my god.
I'm stuck.
I'm stuck in the corner.
I'm stuck!
I'm never going to get past this stage!
Yeah, I had no ult.
I had nothing.
I had no ult.
Dang.
Upgrade!
Yep.
That's what we're going to do.
Because we got money, baby.
We got money, baby.
Let's do like the self-healing, right?
I wanna do more...
and attack.
Oh!
And the fandoms, that's right.
Wait, upgrade is what's under...
Oh, here.
There we go.
I just got called with great news after 8 years of teaching.
I finally got tenure!
No, I won't get fired unless I screw up royally!
Yippee!
I'm so happy!
Round for round!
Congratulations!
Oh my gosh, I'm so happy for you!
Piminto, it's my friend's birthday and he's a big fan of you.
Can you sing happy birthday to him?
His name is...
Mike...
Hoach.
Hoach?
Love you always.
Mike H.
You're pronouncing it correctly.
Carry on, Minto.
You guys, I think...
Mike... you can't...
Like, Mike is just a ruined name now.
It's like you see a Mike and it's...
You're so easily... you already...
My sensors are already going off, you know?
Supposed to be Hooch.
Mike Hooch?
To be honest, I thought it was a...
I thought it was like H-O-C-H and like the C-H was a K sound.
I thought it was like a Hawk.
You know?
So Mike...
Hold on, I have to do a dramatic pause to let enough time in between it.
Mike...
Hawk...
Two in one.
Increase the damage of skills!
Let's do that one too.
I think... let's try it here now.
We got way further.
After doing some more upgrades.
Alright, Risu.
I got you to laugh so mission accomplished.
Are you...
Usa...
Are you utilizing the food bug?
Try a Mumei!
I don't think I've tried Mumei actually.
Mike...
Hooch...
Hawk...
Really want me to become a pianist.
Struggle is real.
Mumei OP?
Da da da da!
Wait, hold on.
Someone mentioned something and I don't know if I upgraded it.
The pickup range.
Oh, there we go.
Okay.
Topic...
Can you say...
Happy birthday to my friend...
Mia Sho?
Is that a real name?
Mumes is really good once you awaken her weapon.
Okay.
It's pronounced Maya.
Maya Sho?
Ha...
That doesn't sound bad.
Maia?
Sho?
Doesn't sound bad.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday...
Maia Sho.
Why are you guys saying no, though?
It doesn't sound like anything.
Happy birthday to...
I'm so... I'm scared... I'm scared.
Sounds like butt.
It does not at all!
We need some more haste, my goodness.
Oh my gosh.
Bird feather!
Thank you for making a good night even better, Minto.
Glad you're having a good night.
Chris is attacked with 1% for every target currently on the screen.
Up to 100%.
In addition, getting a further 1% for every 100 targets ever defeated.
Stop saying 1!
You guys are like, hey Minto, we know that you have no upper hand.
Upgrades or anything, but what if you just like...
Made everything harder for you.
Oh!
For yourself.
I'm not good with the aiming ones, you guys.
If you haven't noticed.
I know there's already people in the chat that are like, um...
She just didn't aim.
That's why...
That's why she lost last time.
But you know, sometimes you forget to aim when you're...
When you're upgrading.
And then you go out of the menu.
You're not sure where the enemies are.
Oh my gosh.
Hello?
Why are...
What?
Where are you guys coming from?
Oh.
Take it.
You don't have to aim as much at level 7?
Okay, cool.
Congratulate their birthday with a fine bottle of Australia's premium...
Daikin's Cider.
And a fine wood liquor box.
Four?
I shouldn't go for the feather though.
Four is good.
The sunny glasses.
Increase XP gain by 10%.
And every level up.
Oh, the weapon damage!
Wow!
Oh my gosh.
Please explode!
Not you!
Um...
Sheesh.
Oh my gosh.
Wait.
Oh, oh, I'm trapped!
I'm trapped!
Guys.
I'm struggling a little bit here.
Okay.
Stop distracting me!
Food.
Oh, my ult is available.
Thank you.
Ah!
Oh!
Her ult is insane.
It was so good.
Um...
Trying to decide which one I want.
If I want to go for Civilization.
Actually, I'm just going to keep going with the Birds of Feather.
Birds of Feather.
Oh, yeah.
Now we're playing with portals, baby.
Ja, ja, ja.
Ja, ja.
Da, da, da.
Now we're moving.
Ja, ja, ja.
A friend.
Oh.
These ones I'm all going to get though.
Like the skills, they're all...
Eventually...
So I'm just going to keep going with the Bird of Feather.
I want the cold turkey again.
I want the turkey again.
Wait.
I need to get through here.
Excuse me.
I need to get through.
Here we go.
I got it.
Wait, I didn't see actually...
Whoa!
Whoa...
Bloodthirsty?
Looks like a shadow resaw?
Awesome.
Let's go with...
Gain 1 stack of Bloodthirst.
At 20 stacks, Mumei heals 10% HP and gains 3...
Wow!
Da-da-da-da-da-dum-dum-dum-dum-dum...
Da-da-da...
What can the glow stick be combined with?
I don't think I've...
I've used the glow stick before.
But...
With Fanbeam...
Might as well?
Yeah, you're right.
It's free!
It's free real estate.
Da-da.
Holy moly!
Sake or Fanbeam?
Or Idol song?
I don't think I have Idol song.
Let's...
Can I get water too?
Glow stick plus beam is good?
Okay.
We'll aim for the beam then.
I still have to aim because I have the stick.
But...
Yeah, you still have to aim a little bit.
Because it's like...
Depending on...
The direction you're going in.
You know?
Still gotta like...
Take out the guys.
It goes all over.
But not all over.
You know what I mean?
But it's still very good.
Oh, Civilization.
Four?
Why are we saying four?
Friend makes it less aim.
I see.
We'll wait for friend to come back then.
Oh my gosh.
I could ult.
But I won't do it.
Friend!
There he is!
Holy cow.
Ult time.
No no.
No no, not yet.
He looks like you?
Kinda does.
Is he collecting experience farming even?
Oh my gosh.
I forgot to aim.
Oh, ouch!
He is?
Oh my gosh, he's such a good little guy!
Do I want to do body pillow again?
Can I collect?
I'm a good guy.
Do I want to do body pillow or get the glasses up?
All good options, I know!
Sorry, I'm stretching.
Okay...
I have been not sleeping so well recently, so...
The stretches are good.
Good stretch.
Glasses to get it off the board?
I guess we are almost max... wait...
Glasses... or sk... hold on.
Items max at 5, right?
So that one is technically max now?
I believe, right?
Yes, okay, okay.
Good, good, good!
Gonna go with the glow stick.
I do... if we get idol costume again, I'll get it later.
Right now, I kinda... I do want it.
I kinda wanna...
I wanna get also some defense items.
I just wanted to get like a good...
What's the word?
You know, like I wanna get my build to like...
A decent attack and everything and then...
Friend!
Baseline?
Yeah!
Before I...
Before I like... you know, and then I'll do more defense stuff.
Da-do-da!
Gain 1% EXP per 2 seconds when HP is full.
The EXP rate slowly increases to 2% and is reset to 1% when taking damage.
Oh!
I think I'll take it.
Oh my gosh!
I hate!
Oh!
The vending machine!
Bloodthirsty!
Oh, but...
Oh!
Almost ran right into that.
Friend, what are you doing?
Come on!
Oh!
Hello?
The ult is ready?
Yeah, but I like to use it only when I truly need it.
You know what I mean?
I'm wondering if I should do...
Lab coat?
I don't...
I feel like I need some sort of defense.
Like a...
Like a passive defense.
Like the...
Cooking.
You know?
I think it's...
I think I need to have...
I'll apply this for now.
We'll have it for now and get you rid of it later.
Akutan.
Oh my gosh!
Even the friend has the...
The cooking!
No way!
That's so awesome!
It applies to him too!
That's so cool!
Ult VTuber.
VTuber!
Your ult is ready!
Right click!
Right now!
VTuber!
The meter is full and flashing!
There are two enemies on the screen!
VTuber!
Why don't you use your ult when there's two enemies?
It can destroy them!
VTuber!
I'm talking in the chat while you are playing the game.
I am telling you what to do, VTuber.
When you die and you did not notice my chat because you were playing the game, I will say, I told you so, VTuber.
I told you in the chat.
I typed it.
I typed it in the chat, VTuber, and you did not listen to me.
You deserve every death that you take.
I don't know what the...
Maybe the Whammy Water.
Wait.
Okay.
Whammy Water plus the...
I
don't know.
I don't actually know if I've ever used this one before.
Water plus glow stick combined?
Oh, they do?
Why is it not here?
Scroll?
I am.
It's not working.
VTuber should have died.
Go away, Kay.
Go away!
I haven't discovered it yet.
Oh!
Okay.
Let's get the water and let's discover it.
Oh my gosh!
We're going to discover something new together, you guys.
We're going to discover something new together.
Discover something new together.
You and me.
Wait.
What is this?
Decrease?
Oh.
You dare question the almighty chat?
Chat is correct all the time, every time.
No.
This is a new combination.
Never seen before in the history of gaming.
Exactly.
Okay.
Decrease damage of main weapon.
Yeah.
Okay.
So I'm going to strengthen peko peko.
Peko peko peko peko.
I haven't done this civilization.
Oh.
Wait.
How was this done?
Ah!
Wait!
Water!
Thanks for the dough!
Ah!
Oh, I'm cornered a little bit.
One second.
I'll read it.
Oh!
Money!
Be sure to grab the sake if it pops up too.
What?
Why?
Congratulations today, boss.
What did I do?
Two for sure, the nurse's horn.
Every time I get a special box, this one is always what I get.
As the special item, you know?
Horn pairs well with momai.
Okay...
Oi!
Alt now, VTuber.
VTuber.
It is time.
It is I, Chadder.
I tell you...
I'm gonna go with the horn!
Where did...
That guy just stood there!
That guy...
Works for me, baby!
Oh wait.
I was gonna say...
Super chatata!
A dead Gumball!
Are you proud of me?
Thank you for the 50!
Thank you for the pink!
Thank you so much!
Oh...
Blalala...
All of these are...
All of these are good.
Oh my god, you guys...
Thank you so much!
I was gonna say 10, but I guess we are spending 150%!
Thank you!
One or two.
Two... wait!
Two other random weapons!
80%... oh!
I like that!
I like those odds.
Lose the 80% gotcha.
I want to get the... there's some... yeah.
Yo buddy, I saw your post about how much you said Super Chats.
You need to calm down.
You need to calm down!
The Sake!
Gain 1% crit by every second up to 10%.
Sake is... so why... can someone explain why Sake is good with a Mumei?
It's definitely not buying the PS5.
Thank you for the Haku Super!
Thank you!
PSI... PSI... PS... PS... PS5 Pro.
Thank you for the Haku Super!
Thank you!
It's like Kaito all over again.
Super Chat time!
Sake Whammy Glow Stick.
Oh!
The Triple Whammy!
I find this to be a calming, cobbler.
I like pink.
Thank you.
Heard it was Super Chat time.
Super Collab!
OK.
All right.
We got the Sake.
OK.
Oh, oh, oh.
Ouch!
Oh my goodness.
Were we waiting on FanBeam?
No.
We were doing... we were doing glow stick.
Glow Stick Whammy.
Sake.
What do I want to do?
Let's do my skills.
Let's focus on the skills.
Let's focus on skills, baby.
Skills, skills, skills.
No skill issue here.
None at all.
No skill issue here, everybody.
Super, super chat time.
Chat time, VTuber.
Cutes the streamer, gets bullied by chat and gamedev.
This is unfair.
This is so unfair.
Skills, skills, skills.
Oh my gosh.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, where's the opening?
Stands for pinto.
Pinto beans.
Membership re-up time.
Does this count?
Thanks!
Exit victory!
Thank you!
For the body pillow?
But then I will have no more item slots.
You need body pillow since you have coat and sake?
Is that how that works?
The real otaku setup.
The glasses, the coat, the body pillow.
I will become the ultimate!
Alrighty.
So glow stick.
I'm gonna go with the glow stick.
This is just my whole afterlife, actually.
This is everything I live for.
Or, not live.
Everything I'm dead for?
Unlife for.
I'm gonna actually go with the spider cooking.
Okay...
Get- Ooyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoy.
Ooyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoy.
Oh my gosh.
Please, please, please, please.
Nice.
Alt equals LB.
Thank you.
Forget the whammy.
Water up.
It is just water, right?
Yeah.
Oh.
Okay.
If you're here, can you confirm or deny?
What is in the whammy water?
The world wants to know.
Oh.
Great.
Let's see what will happen.
It's a moment of a life for me.
Let's see.
Whoa.
It's not working.
Oh, it doesn't work.
There's a Youtube fan.
What was the worst thing in this video?
Guys, we are so movin'!
We are so movin'!
We're gonna be rich, baby!
Rich, rich!
Oh, glow stick max!
Okay.
So far, so good.
And Bill!
Where was it?
Umm... I'm looking for the arrow.
I'm blind.
I'm looking for the arrow.
Oh, I see the arrow!
Thank you!
Umm... probably Whammy... Actually...
Enchant Whammy?
Okay.
I'm trusting you guys.
Enchant the water.
Holy moly, I just noticed how many... how many pen lights.
Oh my gosh!
Ouch!
Oh my gosh.
I had to.
I felt like I had to.
Oh my gosh!
Okay.
I knew there was some... I knew I had health over there.
But we're getting kind of cornered over here.
Not very good.
Not a very good situation.
Okay.
A little better.
There we go.
Okay.
We're okay.
We're okay, maybe.
Oh!
Pizza!
Sometimes I think my friend is an enemy.
Oh shit.
Umm... Oh.
Oh my gosh.
Okay.
Alright.
We're alright.
We're okay.
This isn't Little Caesars.
This is Wendy's.
I'm like trying to aim for... at her?
Oh my gosh.
I need... I need more health.
Yay!
Okay.
I'm gonna do the Whammy Water.
Yay!
Let's just start cooking.
We're cooking.
Oh, wait.
I'm gonna save that.
I don't like these guys.
They're so...
Oh!
Wait!
Can I...
This and this, right?
There we go.
Snowflower Sake!
Okay.
Throw a bottle that shatters into snowflake.
Has 38% chance to cause Frozen!
Whoa!
This is actually so good for all these tiny little annoying guys.
All these tiny annoying guys down here.
Let's get this up.
Whoa!
Um...
I know.
We're like leveling up like crazy right now.
This is actually kind of insane.
Three?
Just keep going, Sake?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Because we gotta level it up.
We gotta max it out so we can do the Ultra...
Ultra collab, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
I know.
Oh, let's swap.
Swap.
And then...
Because... Well, we still have three empty weapon slots.
But let's do...
Decreed?
Okay.
Let's Strength and Greed.
Money, money, money!
Money, money...
Whoa!
Oh, my gosh.
Money, money, money, baby!
Oh, money, money, money.
Seymour!
Thanks for the five!
Get the head!
Next...
Next, I'll work on the cooking next time so that we can get it maxed out, you know?
I want to max it.
Holy cow!
Ta-ta-ta!
Ni...
Oh, wait.
Sake.
Just kidding.
Just kidding, just kidding.
Okay, next time.
I promise.
Next time, next time, next time.
Ta-ta-ta!
It's beautiful!
Beautiful!
Why are they still moving when they're frozen?
Oh, with the body pillow.
Inertia.
Dedication.
I said I would do the spider cooking.
I think I'm gonna...
I really want to max that one out so we can get it off the board.
Saving all that down there.
Max!
Ultimate Oshii combo.
Mint playing Holokura's Mumei and got the whammy one.
Aren't you just a winning Vijai?
Glad that I can play your Oshii!
Please!
Come on!
I don't want to get that health just yet, but I want the XP.
Oh, here we go.
Um, oh!
Researcher's Coat.
Chuu!
Arigato!
Thank you!
For as the kids say...
I'm really glad to be able to see you enjoying this game.
It suits you!
I don't know what suits me about it, but...
Thank you!
Oh, since we have this, we should do the lava bucket, right?
I don't think anything else combines, right?
Oh yeah, I wanted to see.
Oh, it is here now!
Very cool.
Now we...
We don't get burned by our own pizza, right?
I can walk on my own pizza, right?
Pizza's ready!
No?
Okay.
I figured that was the case.
I just wanted to be sure, you know?
Just wanted to be sure.
I'm gonna actually level up our body pillow.
So we can have more defense stuffs going on.
Oh my gosh.
Super?
No, I don't think I need to.
I think I'm okay.
Wait, Super, why do you step on the pizza?
Step on the pizza!
Yeah, I don't need the super right now.
We're all good.
Hammer?
Oh!
I see it!
It's right there!
Right there!
Wait.
Oh, I can't do it yet!
Oh wait!
I can do it!
Oh, I didn't realize it would appear.
Okay.
Here we go.
Let's go!
Snow Queen!
Freeze everything around, dealing constant damage!
Also increases crit chance by 20%!
That's my first time using the golden hammer!
I've tried to get it before.
Like in other games, I've gotten it in like little pieces at a time.
But I've never gotten the full hammer before.
Oh my gosh, and that frees up a slot!
That's so awesome!
Oh, level 50 is required!
Wait!
Oh, I see!
I see!
But so then...
When I was getting it piece by piece before...
Enchant the lava... Oh, that's so true.
Enchant the lava, yeah.
Why... Was it just because I was...
Well, either 50 or 3 collabs.
You gain a piece for every collab.
Oh, I see!
I see!
I'm learning so much.
Idle.
Oh, wait.
But that cooled out.
I have a question.
For Mumei's ult...
Have people said that it doesn't kill...
Like, obviously it doesn't one-shot a boss.
But does the boss still take damage?
I'm just curious.
No damage.
Boss immune.
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Guys?
If I die, I die!
I'm the captain of this ship!
I will go down with this ship!
Too late, Oh-Wey!
WHOA!
...
And it's all...
It's a cold night, just like Titanic and Alaska.
Maybe this is a Metal Gear reference.
I know you guys probably wanted me to upgrade the holo, but I want to get the bucket first, okay?
Anyway...
Welcome to Shadow Moses.
I probably shouldn't upgrade it anymore, right?
Or rather, upgrading it is going to be scary, right?
If I do so...
Upgrade holo last.
Okay.
I understand.
I understand!
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo...
Take him out!
Oh, he's fast!
Sheesh!
What do we grab?
Asakoko maybe?
Never go full holo.
One.
There it is.
Hello?
Oh, there it is.
Howdy.
Howdy!
I could still do the BL book and the Psycho Axe.
Well, I don't even think I'll be able to do it in time.
Where is... oh, here's the stars.
I was like, didn't I save some stars before for my ult?
Oh my gosh.
They're coming from all angles!
Yeah, I don't really have a lot of time left.
I could try for it.
I do get a lot of experience.
I do get a lot of experience now.
Oh my gosh.
Yago, you scared me.
The RGB stuff!
But we got a max greed.
As much as I want the RGB.
Greed comes first.
Money, money, money, money, money.
Money!
I feel like I don't really need to move much.
I can just kind of aim and...
I'll go and collect stuff, you know, when I need to.
Friend will do collection.
Oh, fanbeam is... has the extra... yeah, it has the...
The blue.
Let's...
Yeah.
I wanna max Asakoko!
You already did the Asakoko fanbeam.
What do you mean?
Like here?
This one?
Yeah.
We have done that.
You can upgrade Halu since your super super chatto gives you extra ATK.
Yeah, but I'm still scared.
Asakoko and bomb, though.
Let's just do Asakoko for now.
Let's max for now and then we can...
Trying not to grab the health.
Wait.
What's that sound?
Oh, here we go.
Okay, now we have to make a real decision.
Is the bomb the guy coming towards me?
People are saying bomb and the tail are... are those...
Well, I mean, I don't think I'll have time to...
You know...
To?
Okay.
Run!
Oh my gosh.
Wait, what's happening?
Oh
my god.
He's frozen?
Oh.
We did it?
I think?
My bombs!
Oh my gosh.
I thought it was their bombs.
I was freaking out for a second.
I'm not gonna lie.
I was freaking out for a second, you guys.
I thought...
Those are my bombs.
Maybe I increase my critical.
Maybe.
Or we could just keep going with the bomb.
Actually...
If we keep going with the bomb...
Flower.
Yeah, go for three collabs.
Yeah.
We already have greed maxed.
So...
Um...
Okay.
Let's try three collabs.
Cause an explosion.
Or...
Reduce...
Let's go with this one.
Pickle, pickle.
Alright, let's try and...
Three collabs, baby!
Three collabs!
Baby.
Maybe.
Baby, maybe.
Oh!
Good timing.
I'm gonna go back this way.
I don't like this.
I don't want to be caught in like all the areas with all the tables and stuff.
It's too difficult.
It's too hard.
Are you winning, Minto?
I think finally.
Maybe.
MAX!
MAXIMIZER!
Oh!
There it is!
Okay.
Wait.
But my holo bomb is not...
It's not enchanted.
Does it matter if something is enchanted beforehand or not?
Does it... It's fine?
Does it matter?
Oh, okay.
Ta-da!
Breathe in type Asakaka!
I don't know what this does, but...
I don't know what this does.
I don't know what's going on.
What do I even... What do I even do?
What do I even... What do I even do here?
I wish there was a speed up.
What is even the point of me going here?
Oh my god.
Run, run, run, run, run, run!
Okay.
Oh, oh gosh!
Toho!
Not the Danmaku!
Oh my god, please.
Not the Danmaku, please.
Am I even hitting her?
I don't know.
I don't even know if I'm reaching her.
Oh, there she is.
Toho!
Oh my gosh!
Ouch!
Ouch, ouch!
Are you sure about this?
It's eichuuun.
Wait, does this count for the bosses too?
Even if they become 33 percent stronger?
Only little guys.
Oh, okay.
I know this...
Where is my cursor, there it is.
Okay.
Oh!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Oh my gosh.
For real.
We did it!
I forgore.
That was like... peak gaming.
Fires rapid tears at random targets.
Lose three Holo Coins every second!
If Holo Coins is...
More than zero...
Increase attack by 30% and take 10% less...
Holy!
That's...
Hard stage.
Yay!
8-chan.
07.
Join the membership.
Losing...
Losing every second is diabolical.
It's diabolical.
Seriously.
Start creating things for the 10 gifted!
30% attack.
Negative 10% damage.
Membership can be really good though.
I can... I imagine.
If we do Gacha...
There's so many people I'm missing.
Who do you think...
Who do you guys think I should aim for?
I really like playing as Mumei.
Oh my gosh, Liquid Toast.
Your name reminded me...
When I was coming back from Japan, when I was at...
When I was at...
Oh my gosh, what's it called?
The customs!
I have the global entry or whatever.
And they were just shouting people's names.
You kind of register and it made the line go so fast.
ASCII?
Okay, I'll try ASCII.
I see Korone, I see ASCII.
But...
So they were shouting people's names to go on through.
And...
There was one person...
I guess their last name was Liquid.
And so all I hear from the customs guy was...
Liquid!
And I was like...
Brother!
How is your last name Liquid?
I was going to use this to pay for a kidney replacement.
No!
Let's be a solid guy.
Nah, I heard he's a real snake.
Probably like Dutch or something.
Oh, probably.
John Liquid.
Gotcha for Kyla.
Okay.
Alright.
Let's try ASCII.
Oh, no.
ASCII?
Sora!
Da -da-da-da-da-da-da!
Roboco-san, rank up!
Roboco-san...
Wait, that was a different outfit.
I got the outfit.
Debut!
ASCII and luck!
Let's go, let's go.
You only got a grand from the holo.
Try Sana next.
You don't have to aim.
I have tried Sana.
I really like Sana.
Okay, so now...
Um...
Oh, wait.
Kyla.
You can also do multiples?
Wait, how?
First try, baby!
Let's go.
Nice.
And then... someone said Korone too?
Oh, I see the arrows.
Wait...
Oh, I see, I see.
Okay.
I like to do one at a time, though.
Roboco is fine.
Oh, Kai!
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da!
Do you know the just released Calorie Mate Liquid?
Yes!
I'm gonna... the, the Calorie Mate game!
I'm gonna play it next week.
Of course I am!
Fubuki!
Yay, friend!
Um...
I...
I don't think I have Mio... and Koro.
Fubuki rank up!
The art is so cute.
So cute.
Friend.
Was that three in a row?
Ah!
Mio!
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Nice, nice.
Alright.
Koro, Koro, Koro, Koro, Koro, Koro, Koro, Koro, Koro, Koro, Koro, Koro, Koro!
Mio!
All the friends.
Okay.
Last one, I'll do.
Last one.
Got my VMP for Bow!
See you there, nerd.
See you there, nerd!
Tears?
I don't have enough, I don't think.
I don't know.
I don't remember how many tears it is.
I don't have enough tears.
Oh wait, the outfit!
I see him!
Oh my gosh, so cute!
Stop!
So cute!
Wait, wait, wait.
I love Kiwawa's kimono.
So much!
It's so cute!
I did get...
What was the Roboco one?
This one!
Yeah!
It's so cool!
It looks so good!
In sprite form.
Wait.
Oh, oh, oh!
There we go.
Oh my gosh!
Natsukashi!
Hehehehe!
So cute!
Hahahaha!
Where is God's fauna?
Get on it!
Where is Emofauna?
Hehehehehe!
Next update!
Yeah, right, Kei?
Right, K?
Maybe.
Okay.
No pressure.
No pressure, no pressure, right?
Everybody stop pressuring, K.
Everybody stop pressuring.
Okay?
Stop it.
Stop the pressure.
Just go to Twitter.
Actually, I'm on petition.org.
Emofana in Holocure.
Everybody, no pressure.
No pressure.
I'm gonna post this link, but no pressure to sign the petition.
Okay?
No pressure.
K, for you to listen to the...
petition.
Okay?
No pressure if it has...
um...
like thousands of...
signatures?
I think...
you might feel pressured if you see...
all the...
thousands of people begging for...
Emofana in the...
next update.
But no pressure, okay?
I'm just saying.
You should check out a free game...
on Steam.
It's called Only Cans...
of First Date.
It's overwhelmingly positive.
It's a marvel in...
modern day storytelling.
Only...
Cans.
Totally not...
a fake fact.
If you say Sundowner...
three times in the mirror at 3 AM...
Bunny Wargun...
will appear...
to present his...
criminal cybernetic gap for you.
Just like the good old days.
Sundowner, Sundowner, Sundowner.
Sundowner.
Do you guys think that...
they would ever make Metal Gear Rising into...
a musical?
Just like how they did with...
Beetlejuice?
Why am I sad after cheesing...
Cyberwolves?
Oh my gosh!
Look, our screen is really...
filled up now.
It's so awesome.
I will get... Actually, I want to just...
try for everyone.
I would really want to get everybody.
I want my screen to be full and...
exciting.
Kids are cruel...
Jack.
Kids are Cruel Jack would go hard...
as a song.
Kids are Cruel Jack and don't come back...
no more.
Gotcha, gotcha, gotcha.
We need Crony.
Hold on, I'm just gonna...
Oh wait, I already paid for it.
We need Crony.
Actually, ranking up Mumei...
is pretty good.
Not gonna lie.
I'm gonna do...
3.
No!
Oh, nevermind.
Well, if you include the one I just did, that's 4.
Spooky number.
Oh my gosh!
I'll forget!
Um, kind of the perfect pull.
Ever?
So now I think I... Oh, wait, do I have Bails?
Am I crazy?
I think I pulled her last...
Yeah, okay.
So we have...
all of...
Council promise.
Next we need Coro.
Coro!
Come home!
How many times have I pulled Mio at this point?
Mio likes you.
I know.
I have one more pull...
to be able to buy...
Corone with the tears.
Okay...
Um...
Oh my gosh...
Your screen is so full...
Okay...
I'm gonna do something insane.
I'm gonna do something...
absolutely insane.
You guys ready for this?
Are you guys ready for this?
One, two, three...
Oh...
Advent isn't in this, are they?
No, no, not yet.
They are not in.
All blinds... but Aki.
Okay you guys, I'm gonna do something absolutely insane.
Okay, are you guys ready for this?
Are you guys ready for this?
Insane.
Ready?
All for Mio.
Wait, does Matsuri show up on the front?
Oh, even though we didn't get the original outfit, we're all good.
You think I made the market for Ganyu?
It works, it works, it works, it works.
Who do I want to play?
Oh, wait.
Okay, guys.
Before I end stream, I want to do one more game.
I want to do the Haunted House.
We'll do more gacha next time.
I won't do any more gacha, I promise, I promise, I promise, I promise.
I'll just play and make more money so we can do lots of gacha next time, okay?
But who should I use for the Haunted House?
Gido Kronil.
Kaila?
Okay.
Wait, hold on.
Also, I have a little bit of money.
I can maybe buy some upgrades.
Oh, it's 10,000.
My bad.
I thought it was 1,000.
What do I want to upgrade, though?
Gold?
The money gain?
XP gain?
Where is the XP?
Oh, it does pick up XP.
Is this one?
Speed?
I might actually do the attack and...
I think that's it.
We'll see how we do here.
Where is she?
There she is.
Wait.
Spawn the rarest material deposit that deals 300% damage to all targets when hit.
When fully mined, Kaila gains happiness, granting 50% attack speed.
Haste for 10 seconds.
Alright, swing the hammer in front.
Okay.
Let's try the Halloween Castle!
I'm so excited.
I'm not expecting to beat this.
I'm just...
here.
Oh, my gosh.
The range on it.
OK Oh, my gosh, the range!
Oh, my– OK.
OK.
I get it.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll get it.
I get it.
I get it, I get it, I get it.
Maybe the black...
... connection.
No pressure.
I want to do it for the funny.
No pressure!
Okay!
Okay, okay, okay.
Hammer level 2.
Targets have a 2% chance to drop an ore deposit, which may be destroyed with Hammer Swing to drop ore.
Gaining 10 type of an ore will strengthen.
Strengthen what?
All weapons by 1, 2, or 3%.
You guys keep telling me to get credit card, but like what's...
Is it because...
Are anvils something special because she's a blacksmith?
Kyla spawns anvils.
I see.
Okay, I'll try it.
I'll try it.
You know me.
If I...
Since I have like so...
Little experience.
I want to try many different types of plays.
Okay, I'm going to get the blacksmith though.
I want to see it.
I'm going to destroy the statue.
Yeah.
What did this happen?
Shoot.
Okay, we're fine.
Everything's good.
Yeah.
I think I'm going to beat this level.
Wowee.
Took a little bit of damage there.
It's okay though.
Oh my god, it took some more damage there.
That's okay.
Maybe.
I'm not expecting to beat this level.
I'm going to try it out.
It's so cute in here though.
I feel so homey.
So many piggies.
What are Hachama's fans called?
I knew that.
I knew the Hattons.
I'm stupid.
I actually knew that one.
Oh my gosh.
Don't blow up on me, please.
Come back and circle around for the XP around here.
Fubuki's are Sukonbu and Matsuri's are Matsurisu.
Oh, I didn't know the Matsurisu too.
Kyla is good for using the ult as many times as possible.
Oh, okay.
Let me try it.
Oh, what is this?
What's going on?
What's happening?
I don't know what's going on.
One or four.
Sorry, I'm going faster than you guys are typing.
Awakened!
We got the awakened though.
Oh,
whammy water.
I'll take it.
Oh, she's fast now.
She's fast fast.
The range is kind of crazy.
On this thing.
Oh.
Blacksmith 2.
I'm cornering myself.
Oh my god!
How do we avoid all of it?
Okay.
Alright.
No pressure.
What the?
What the hell is that?
Oh!
Attack!
Oh gosh!
He's healing them!
Heals enemies.
Not on my watch.
100% damage to all targets within...
Wow!
Okay, let's do that one.
Not on my watch!
Die!
Did I kill him?
I think I got him.
His little ring is gone.
You got this man.
Thank you!
Hold on.
I can't read the rest of it.
But thank you!
I saw something about...
Oh.
Does the credit card work with the...
With blacksmith?
Like, is that technically summoning anvils too?
Since, I mean, it's summoning anvils.
Does that count?
Look at the popcorn!
Oh my gosh.
It's like...
It's so cute out here.
Oh.
That's so...
Oh, it does!
Okay, cool.
That's exciting.
That's fun.
Whoa!
Oh my gosh!
So cute!
Oh.
Ouchy ouch.
I don't know who I ran into.
But I ran into somebody.
Ult!
Oh, thank you.
Sorry, guys.
I keep forgetting...
Okay.
You know how I was playing.
I was playing before where I'm like, I only ult when I need to, so...
Let's go for the...
Credit card.
Ult.
Wait, two more...
Uh-oh.
I'm in a corner.
It takes time to get used to everyone's ults.
Thank you, Yuni, for being so understanding.
Normally, anvils can be used to ice.
Oh.
That's my...
That's my stuff.
Ta-da-da!
Whoa!
We...
Wow!
Oh, guys.
Guys.
The anvil will wait.
We will come back for the anvil.
And I see that there's an item as well.
Do not fret.
I see...
Peckle, peckle.
Oh my gosh.
We're getting a...
A little...
Oh my gosh.
I need to make sure it's still safe before I use it.
Um...
We might die.
And if I did...
Um...
It was a run.
If I die...
Asakoko plus damage is a good pick.
Yeah.
It was a run of all time.
I think if I could get some extra damage to help me out of here, it might be good.
Just for...
Just to help me...
Help me get out of here.
You know what I mean?
Help me...
Uh...
Not die.
Oh my god!
What?
I got stuck on the wall!
No!
I got...
I got stuck on the wall.
Don't die.
Ikusyo.
That's okay though.
I just wanted to try it out.
I wanted to try it out.
Enty.
Thank you!
Um...
I keep...
I am learning more and more of this game each time I try.
Um...
I like...
I...
I've played Sana.
I really like Sana.
I like...
Mumei.
Um...
I think I will like Kaila if I try her more.
Risu obviously good for the cash money money skill issue.
But um...
Yeah!
So fun!
Cronies fun.
There...
I mean...
I have played like...
Oh!
I...
I like playing Cronies.
I like playing Fauna too.
I've played literally like five people.
So...
I've played like five people.
There are many more.
I still can't say that I have a definitive main yet.
But...
I am...
Every time...
Getting more and more used to...
Uh...
To playing.
Thanks for the stream!
I hope you can stream it again when the new update hits.
It's going to have JP Gen 3 and 4 sent to allow!
Yes!
Dala.
All characters are fun in their own way.
No!
I mean...
Clearly so much...
Has gone into...
Thinking about abilities for each...
Each member.
It's kind of insane.
Um...
Dev team is cracked.
Truly.
Um...
But yeah!
Thank you guys!
For watching!
Thanks for hanging out with me!
And...
Um...
Probably...
We'll play...
Uh...
Again...
Whenever the next...
When...
Is the update?
Have they said?
October!
Next month!
Maybe!
Okay!
So then I'll probably play again next month!
Maybe!
That's my Oshii too.
She will be eternal in all our hearts.
Yeah!
Eternal!
Um...
Mmm!
October!
Cool!
Then we'll see...
We'll see...
Holocure again in October!
But I...
I will still play on...
On...
On my own.
Just...
I won't do gacha!
I'll just play.
And get lots of money!
Money!
Hahaha!
And upgrades and stuff too.
Probably.
But yeah!
Aki Daki!
Tomorrow I have karaoke!
Where I'm gonna be singing...
Any song...
Um...
Whatever...
Anime songs I'm gonna sing, baby!
Yeah!
And...
I'm excited!
I will see you guys tomorrow if I see you!
And if not, I'll sue!
Um...
Whatever!
Have a good day!
Have a good night!
And...
Um...
Thanks again for hanging out with me!
And...
What was I gonna say?
Um...
I think next time I play, for sure, I wanna go like really long, you know?
I wanna try the endless mode for sure.
Especially like...
I'll do it on my own and see how far I can get and things like that.
But...
You know, I feel like with that Mumei build we had...
I feel like we could've done endless mode...
I don't know.
I feel...
I felt like we could've...
Gone crazy.
You know what I mean?
I feel like we could've gone...
Pretty far.
Oh yeah!
See you guys...
Tomorrow!
Or whenever I see you.
Thanks for hanging out!
Bye bye!
See you!
My birthday is on October 1st!
Don't forget that!
Bye!