Hello!
Welcome back!
Master!
Lady!
Hello!
Grammy!
Hi!
Hello!
Wow!
Okay, security guy, sorry.
Welcome, everybody, to Fears to Fathom.
Um...
The... last episode?
Question mark?
Of this series?
I feel like he's not gonna make it the last one.
I feel like he has had such good reception with it.
And he even says still, if you have a story to share, send it to here.
I feel like he's gonna keep at it.
Oh my gosh, Jerry!
Jerry!
With a G!
Gary!
Jerry, thank you for the video!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
So, so, so early.
So early in the stream.
We're like freaks to Fathom.
But I've played all the episodes before.
But it's kind of silly that this is...
The potential last one might be the first one on my list.
Because it's my channel.
But which was your favorite?
Let's see.
We had Home Alone.
Um...
Because I'm pretty sure he said it was only gonna be five games.
Or at least the dev or whatever.
Home Alone...
Was the one with the... Wait, or was that Carson House?
I don't remember Home Alone.
Maybe.
Was Carson House the one with the girlfriend, right?
Iron Bart... Iron Bart!
Ironbark lookout.
Wait, then... I'm getting the settings all confused because there's two about a house and then two about going outside.
Yeah, the Yandere one.
Yeah, Carson house was the Yandere one, right?
Oh, pizza delivery.
I don't remember.
Yeah, Carson house was... you were house-sitting for a neighbor and you were texting a girl.
Yes, yes, yes.
Ironbark was the one... was that the one with the cult?
I think.
Yeah, this is the one with the cult that is like leaving skellies at your door.
Now the first two I don't remember so well.
Maybe I should put them on my channel because I can't remember how they were.
Like the one with the lasagna.
I hope there are more.
It's been nice to have these virtual urban legends.
It's fun, right?
And they're great games.
There are games that can be done in one stream, which are always sometimes more difficult to do, more difficult to find than you'd imagine.
Just a game that's kind of one and done, you know?
Which are great for streamers sometimes.
So, we should send a story in?
But I think he wants like realistic ones, doesn't he?
Perhaps.
I think these are all allegedly real, right?
Unless we could embellish one.
One time... one time I was... I was playing with a friend and she lived in not such a great neighborhood.
She...
It was a little bit dangerous, but...
Not so dangerous that we couldn't go out and play, the two of us ourselves, right?
And we were just taking a walk.
And...
I...
Remember we were just like hanging out like at the top of a hill.
And...
I...
Look over at one of the neighboring houses and I see a guy in the window staring at us.
And I'm just like...
That's weird.
But I thought maybe he was just kind of like...
What are these kids doing on my lawn?
We weren't on the lawn.
But we were just like...
Kind of hanging out in the street.
And then...
Like I look away.
And then when I look back...
He has...
A...
A camera!
Like he's taking pictures of us!
With a camera!
And I look at my friend and I didn't want to tell her because she lives here.
I didn't want to freak her out.
So I was just like...
A friend!
Let's...
Race down the hill!
Last one there is rotten egg!
And so we like...
Raced down the hill...
I...
I still think about that.
I was like...
Freaky...
So...
Something like that...
We just embellish it?
Make a freaky story out of it, right?
Mmmmm.
Mmmmmm.
Was the last one there a rotten egg?
Yeah, that's why I've got a big ol' egg head.
But that's my episodic horror.
That's my Freaks to Phantom right there.
Freak, Phantom, and origin story.
That guy in the window?
Me.
But yeah, so...
We're here at the Woodbury Getaway.
The Woodbury Woodbury Getaway.
Yeah.
And I guess we're going on a getaway.
This looks nice though.
It actually kind of reminds me of a Phasmophobia home.
I've been haunted for five months now.
F2F Episode 6?
Spears to Fathom episodes are never like hauntings.
They're never like that.
They're always like a real... Wait!
Which one?
There was one, was it?
It must be the hitchhike.
Where you go to the motel.
Right?
And then you're stuck in the closet and you have to...
You can't say anything.
Then I don't remember the Home Alone one.
I think Home Alone had the lasagna.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You guys remember.
You guys remember so well.
Another thing I wanted to bring up today... was today.
Was the last episode of the Minto Matara Summer Special Podcast.
So happy!
Last...
Summer Special Day?
I believe actually next week.
Hold on, let me check.
Last... day of summer.
I think next week is actually the last.
Oh no!
The 22nd!
22nd or 23rd.
Is the last day.
So technically the next episode... or rather we...
This is the last episode that would be in summer.
I did plan it well.
I did plan it exactly.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Where's the s'mores pictures?
Where are they?
I didn't get s'mores!
But I have a couple days.
Before summer's over.
I do, I do, I do, I do, I do.
Yeah, I really mathematized it.
But we have a bonus episode.
If you were not watching Matara's stream, I was on it earlier.
Just before this.
And I kind of... We have a bonus episode and I talked about it.
And our bonus episode is going to be...
Sorry, the music's a little loud.
Going to be an interview with...
With... with... with... with... with...
The famous... the famous... in Akihabara...
Mofuku-chan-sama!
Of Dear Stage!
So we got to go to Dear Stage.
And we got to...
We got to...
Film in there and interview...
Oh my gosh, hold on.
Let me show you guys a picture.
Oh my gosh.
It's...
Oh, oh, oh, TikTok.
Hold on, I have a picture I want to show you guys.
Oh my gosh.
Hold on.
It's like...
It was kind of like my dream come true.
And I...
Did cry.
Not on the episode.
Not while recording.
But definitely...
While I was in there.
Because I was like...
You can't usually take like photos and stuff.
You know.
Inside.
So to be able to...
Even record and everything...
Was just crazy.
Look at this photo.
Hold on.
Uh...
This is like...
My dream place.
This is my favorite place ever.
Oh my gosh.
Look at this picture.
Hold on.
Ta-da!
You can see us.
You can see the little Momo.
And you can see me.
Oh my gosh.
Isn't it crazy?
I never thought...
I would even be able to...
Touch this stage.
You can see even back here.
There's a little thing that says no photography.
But that didn't apply to us.
Yeah.
It's so awesome.
So hopefully...
You watch that when that comes out.
Because it was super duper important.
To me.
Basically...
Mataro went to V-Shojo JP staff.
And was just like we want to do this thing.
Can you please help us make it work?
So they did.
And it was really awesome.
Yeah.
Guess you're a criminal now.
Always have been.
Will it be on the podcast channel?
Yeah.
Will it be on the podcast...
channel?
So...
Yippee!
I'll post a photo later.
I have more photos too.
I was so like...
Oh my god.
I was so excited.
You guys ready?
To experience a fears to fathoms.
The fears to freakdoms.
Next week or sometime later.
Depends on when the editing gets done.
I think June our editor.
Is going to TwitchCon.
So I think.
If it's not next Monday.
It might be a bit later.
We'll see.
The fear.
We're on this game.
Woodbury get away.
Let's check it out.
Let's go.
New guy.
Fears to fathom.
Episode 5.
Woodbury get away.
December 8th.
Okay.
Oh no.
We're an office worker.
Needed coffee to get done with the day.
Oh no.
No.
This is.
I'm fathoming.
I'm fathoming the fear.
Oh look.
Look at my.
Wallpaper.
It's like Nyan Cat.
Oh my gosh.
I can.
Apex.
Legends.
What did it say?
I actually don't know.
What else should we type?
Let's go to.
Browser.
I'm feeling lucky.
Oh I'm lucky.
Okay.
Hold on.
Google is broken.
Put all business funds into your bank account.
And run.
I'm going to make a new folder.
I'm going to call it.
Homework.
Type invader.
Doesn't work.
Star.
Fatal error.
Uh oh.
It appears broken.
Uh huh.
Company.
Apache Synergy.
Velocity Grow.
Out Roth Capital.
Wow.
All these amounts go into.
Deposit.
Deposit into.
Minto Banking.
Perfect.
Approved.
Yeah.
Okay.
Good.
Good good good.
Okay.
We'll send that to boss.
What is type invader?
Oh.
What is this?
Leg.
Oh.
Oh my gosh.
No way.
Oh.
Okay.
Oh my gosh.
Wow.
This is awesome.
I wasn't.
I wasn't ready for this though.
Uh.
Play new.
Input invaders.
Typing of the dead real.
Oh.
Okay.
I'm.
I've trained for this.
I trained for this.
I'm ready.
Uh.
Oh my gosh.
Ah.
Uh.
Okay.
We're killing it.
It's not real words or anything.
What does this mean?
Oh.
Beat minigame with 70 plus HP.
Accuracy 100%.
Health 100%.
GG easy baby.
I'm kind of a gamer.
How do I get out of here?
Oh.
I'm kind of a gamer.
Oh yeah.
I needed coffee.
I'm feeling lively.
Why are all the lights off in my office though?
Wow.
The big city.
There's even people down there.
There's a lot of people walking for how late it seems.
Oh my god.
Oh sorry.
The car.
Why is it so dark?
Oh.
I couldn't leave just yet.
I had to get coffee.
Oh.
Okay.
Just kidding.
Uh.
Hold on.
No battery.
Wait.
No I was.
What's the.
No what's the menu?
That's me pressing escape.
How do I get to the.
I feel like the sensitivity is a little strange.
It's a little high.
I think.
Can I run?
Okay.
Kinda.
I hear something.
It's like a clinky.
Oh.
Oh hello.
Hey.
What do you want Sid?
I'm trying to get this done.
Uh.
Why are you being such a.
Why are you shaft tilting at me?
Oh my gosh.
I was just checking if you need anything.
Can't these clients ever make up their minds.
Still working.
Wait.
How is he working without even looking at the screen?
This guy.
He's a maniac.
Oh my god.
Still working on that report?
Yeah.
I'm trying to get this done.
I would wish him good luck.
But I don't think he needs it.
I think he knows what he's doing.
Don't burn yourself out.
Whatever.
Okay jerk.
Trying to be nice to you.
Oh as much as I wanted to leave.
Okay.
I want to look out at the people.
There's a lot of people walking.
There's a lot going on out there.
Alright.
Coffee.
What else we got here?
Can't read any of these post-it notes.
It's like reading something in a dream.
What's this?
Oh.
Maybe he wants some chips.
Throw something at him.
Yeah.
He wants these chips.
Hungry?
I swear if one more thing hits my desk.
I'm going to tell HR about this.
Oh my bad.
You're asking for it.
I swear.
Okay.
He's just going to repeat the same stuff.
Do you mind?
Some of us are actually working here.
Are you?
You're asking for it.
Okay.
That managed to actually land on his desk.
We'll take that as the win.
We got some fizz.
Wait.
Choose your drink.
We got a fizz.
We got a Mountain Pew.
We got a Red Cola.
We got a Energy Bowl.
We got a Prepsy.
We got a Dr. Fizz.
Which one would you guys like?
And it's 85 cents.
That's cheap.
A fizz.
Dr. Fizz.
Prepsy.
Energy Bowl.
I can only pick one you guys.
You guys gotta decide on one.
The children yearn for the Red 40.
No, it's Energy Bowl.
Not Red Bowl.
Okay.
Pick the doctor.
Dr. Fizz.
Oh.
Whoa!
Scroll up to open.
Right.
Press the mouse button to drink.
Wow.
That was crisp.
That was clean.
I was done with it.
Can I get more?
Oh.
Let's try them all.
Dang.
I tried to grab it.
Ready for this?
Throw an unopened one at that guy.
I tried to murder him.
I'll throw an empty one at him.
I was done with it.
Do you mind?
Gosh.
You're making such a mess at your desk.
Wait.
This is just rolling.
Maybe this place really is haunted.
Slowly and slowly.
Endless inertia.
There's nothing to ever stop it from moving.
It'll just keep going on.
I don't know.
On and on forever.
Slowly and surely.
Where are we anyway?
EPSOL Solicitor's Office.
Shepherd Title Group.
Suya Maritime Counseling.
What are these names?
I wonder how far it'll get.
If I walk...
Nope.
Even walking on top of it doesn't stop it.
Alright.
Where's my coffee?
Coffee.
Wait.
Did it just...
Oh my gosh.
It's also just going.
The cans yearn for the mines.
They're all going this way.
There's something down there.
Coffee?
Is that cheese in the freezer?
Where's the coffee?
Oh here we go.
Needed to prepare a cup of coffee.
Oh.
Which flavor do we want?
I want a light roast.
Okay.
How do I do this?
What is this thing?
My cup?
It needed water.
Check the calculator.
I think it's on the table.
Does it say 80085?
Oh.
I thought that was the power.
My coffee's looking a little red there.
Oh.
Needed a lid.
We like it.
We like it black.
Oh here it is.
My hands were full.
Uh.
Is that it?
Wow.
These sound effects are something.
Why is nobody else here except us?
Am I done with it?
Oh I'm done with it.
Garbage day!
I like how he's just my garbage can.
Wait.
Did it stop?
It finally stopped.
What does it say?
It's too blurry for me to read.
I can't read it at all.
What does it say?
Oh.
Hold on.
I turned down the quality.
So that's probably why.
Cause you know sometimes with these like indie games you can never tell if they're going to be like badly optimized.
And so I usually just turn them down so that like automatically so that um and I can't change it cause the menu just says no battery.
But I'll as soon as I can I'll make it cause sometimes you know they're poorly optimized and they're really laggy or...
something.
So why is over here so scary looking?
Needed to use restroom.
Okay I saw the sign over here.
Just charge your phone.
I'm trying!
Where's my computer at?
Oh here?
Can I?
Had to pee.
Okay.
Gosh.
This place is so creepy.
I don't like it.
Coffee went through us for real for real.
Had to pee.
I need this getaway now.
Pronto stat.
Wait can we just leave?
Hello?
Do we need a key?
Remember your cutout?
The face connect booth at AMIC it watches me sleep every day.
Wait you got it!
Oh I'm a girl?
Oh.
Gross.
This place is the worst bathroom I've ever seen.
Why are there so many sinks?
Why?
Why are these like the naughty sinks?
Why are there seats facing into the bathroom?
Are we not?
I'm scared.
There's a toilet meter!
Oh!
Did
you hear that person walk?
Was that the other?
Did he get mad because I threw too much stuff at him?
Is he mad because I threw too much stuff at him?
He walked into the bathroom!
Oh my god!
He's gonna kill me!
Don't look up!
Ah!
I'm sorry!
I hear footsteps.
Yeah!
Someone came into the bathroom!
We gotta wash our hands!
We didn't even flush!
Okay.
We flushed.
I think she didn't look left.
What's there?
Ah!
Okay.
Okay!
We're fine!
Oh!
Wow!
Wow, ma'am!
Sorry!
Didn't know anyone was in here!
Holy cannoli!
Mister!
You almost gave me a heart attack!
I'm so sorry.
Should've knocked before I came in, but there isn't usually anyone here this late.
Yeah, you should've knocked.
Again, I'm sorry.
I usually do knock, but I'm a little bit frustrated tonight.
Must've slipped my mind.
We're just having a conversation with this guy in the bathroom?
He seems a little excited to be in here.
What has you frustrated?
Someone keeps throwing coffee cups on the floor.
On the floor all over the office.
It's been happening for weeks.
Yeah, that's me.
Did someone raise you in a barn?
There's trash cans all over the office!
Act like an adult and use them!
I'm not sorry for my actions.
Well, I need to get back to it.
Don't want to be picking...
Don't want to be here all night picking up coffee cups.
Have a good night.
Oh my god, that's how I fold up my boxes too.
Did I just see a bug crawl across the...
ground?
Get me out of here!
I didn't even wash my hands!
Okay, hold on.
There we go.
Order of operations.
Dry, but don't wash.
What's this?
I don't even know what this is.
Oh, it's a towel dispenser?
Oh, we'll dry our hands...
but we won't take the towel.
Alright, let's get back to work.
Someone's calling me.
I can still hear him humming.
The guy is...
so loud.
Moshi moshi!
Um...
Go for Sidney Harper?
What does that mean?
Hey Harp, it's Mike!
Oh!
Mike.
Hey Mike!
I've been trying to call your cell for the last two hours.
It just keeps going to voicemail.
Is everything alright?
Oh!
My battery dies at the worst times!
Oh snap!
I was starting to think maybe you were ignoring me.
Uh...
Hi ghost lady.
Hello!
Thanks for the super chat.
Awkward laugh.
No!
I'm just gonna...
I'm just kidding.
Anyway, what are you still doing at work?
It's getting kind of late.
Why are you calling me at work?
It is late.
Why are you calling me Mike?
Um...
Just more overtime?
Damn Harp, that sounds rough.
Good thing I called to cheer you up.
No response.
Um...
About our trip.
Did you get a chance to book the rental house?
Just really wanted to see you.
And Nora.
I think Mike is into us.
Hmm...
I was going to do it after work.
No worries, Harper.
I don't want to stress you out.
As long as you book it tonight, I think it will be fine.
Is he... does he or does Mike like us?
Hey.
I was thinking since we both live in the city, maybe I could pick you up and ride together.
It would be nice to catch up.
He's picking me up!
You know, save on gas and relive the good old days.
Just a little bit of Mike and Sidney time before Nora gets there.
Mike Wazowski?
Mike and Sidney time?
Uh...
There's... I can't... I can't reject him!
I can only say yes?
Okay, sure.
Great.
I guess I'll let you get back to work then.
Okay, Mike.
I kinda like Mike.
Oh, wait.
One more thing.
Okay, Columbo.
When you book the rental, please make sure to keep it under $100.
Okay.
A thrifty guy.
Nora and I were talking and she's been on a pretty tight budget.
Things haven't been going very well for her.
I could just hang up without saying bye!
I could just be like, I...
I don't even say anything.
Also, you're spilling Nora's like...
dirty, you know, laundry like that.
You know?
But for Nora, I'll find something affordable.
It'll be just like the old college days.
You always had a knack for finding the best spots.
Remember that little cafe you found on our trip to Oregon?
I should really make the booking now.
The Nook Cafe!
Yeah.
I miss those days, Harp.
Harp?
I thought my name was Sydney.
I should really make the booking now.
Right, right.
Of course.
Sorry for yapping.
I'm just excited.
I guess.
Mom!
Mike sounds cute!
Nora?
I hardly Nora.
Stop!
Oh, my last name is Sydney Harper.
Oh, okay, okay.
Oh, he sounds cute.
All right.
Talk to you later, Harp.
Bye!
Maybe I'm judging the guy too hard.
I'm judging the guy too hard.
Okay, we're gonna make a booking, right?
So we're gonna go to browser.
We're gonna go...
What the?
That's not what I typed.
Sexy... No, no, no, no!
Stop!
I was looking up sexy hotels!
Sexy... No, no, no, no!
Please!
This man is trying so hard to catch a date.
Yeah, stop!
I'm not gonna say that name.
You cannot get me.
If I do it really fast, do you think the game will...
Sexy hotel!
Rentacabin.com!
I'm feeling unlucky.
It's my birthday!
I'm peeling and boiling potatoes in my hotel room.
In your hotel room?
How are you gonna cook that?
John, happy birthday!
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday dear John.
You're a pretty okay guy.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday!
Where are we going?
To hell.
Oh, wood.
Burry.
Search.
Alright.
$3.50 a night!
Holy moly.
Peaceful cabinet.
Oh, but it's got four stars.
$2.40...
This does not look like a $2.40 a night kind of...
$2 stars!
Okay, come on.
Why do we even have security cameras?
That's scary.
Cozy Lodge.
Woodbury.
Wow!
$1.99 a night and five stars.
This looks cozy.
It's got a smoke alarm.
I think those are mandatory.
I think you shouldn't just advertise that.
I think that should be a given.
A surveillance camera.
Private cabin in Woodbury.
$1.99 a night!
Okay, that's under $100.
What a coincidence.
It's my birthday, too.
Happy birthday, John.
Rios!
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, dear Rios!
Happy birthday!
Thank you so much!
$2.59!
Okay, but what if we get this place, the $1.99 place, and I cover most of it, you know?
Because it's got really nice reviews.
I mean, this one only has three stars.
But it's got fishing.
It was over our budget.
Oh, dang.
Dang it!
I have to do it.
I have to get this one.
Three guests.
Oh, that's how many we are.
Two bedroom.
Can we look at the pictures?
No.
Two beds.
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
Is this why he wanted...
Is this why Mike wanted a...
one under $100?
So that we could have...
a two bedroom location.
A two bedroom With two beds.
Mike, you dog.
Michael!
Ah!
For Supa.
Thank you!
Hey, I'm assuming you get hundreds if not thousands of stories sent daily.
So I'll give you a basic rundown of something that happened to me.
I'm sorry if some of it is written weird, but I was rushed.
Oh, so that must be the email that he got about the story.
Game Dev, right?
Hold on.
Sorry, I'm eating my dinner a little bit.
Yeah, we're gonna make Mike sleep on the couch for real.
What's for dinner?
Mac and cheese!
Had to make something fast.
When I was in my early 20's I worked at a big consulting firm in my city.
Life at the firm was a constant juggle of deadlines, client meetings, and trying to prove my worth.
Which didn't leave much room for leisure, let alone a social life.
The job paid well, sure, but at the expense of my mental peace.
I'm Sydney Harper, and this story takes place during one of those days.
One of my college friends, Mike, suggested that we take a weekend getaway to rural Vermont, which sounded like a perfect break from my cycle of work.
And my other friend Nora was quick to jump on board as well.
Nora either is third wheeling and does not read the room well, or she read the room exactly well and was just like, no no no Mike, I am not allowing this to happen.
The plan was simple.
We rent a small cabin, close our shift early on Friday, leave and be back on Monday.
Mike came to pick me up.
Two days later.
Love triangle?
Maybe Nora's into Mike.
Oh!
Is this Mike?
Wait!
Is he on a PSP?
Mike?
You're a gamer.
Oh, Michael Carter is calling me?
How do I hang up?
What do you mean hang up?
Oh wow, okay.
Just booked.
Do you ever answer the phone anymore?
Call me please.
Gosh.
Okay Michael.
Wait, we have a lot.
Yo Harp, how have you been?
Mike!
I'm literally so tired.
I was just about to turn in for the night.
Wibby.
Not much.
What the hell?
What?
What's so...
Typo.
Typo in the chat.
Just keeping things afloat, my friend.
How's the work at the new firm?
Pretty much the same as the old job.
Bibicor, thanks for the gifted.
It means, what about you?
Wibby.
I like my version better.
I
think I'm more used to seeing it as an actual U.
Instead of the Y.
That's what threw me off.
I think most people type W-B-U.
How's the work at the new firm?
Pretty much the same as the old job.
Just coding my life away, but the pay is better.
Anyway, I've been thinking about our chat from earlier today.
Oh Mike, like I really don't know.
Getting away sounds fun, but it'll be so much work to get packed and leave for the weekend.
All I'm going to do is think about all the work I should be getting done at the office.
You have to take weekends off.
Wibby!
Wibby at the chat!
Thanks for the super chat!
I can't tell if you changed your name or if that was your username already and you were like, who mentioned me?
Listen to yourself, harp.
We're talking about taking a nice dot dot dot, relaxing dot dot dot, weekend getaway and all you're focusing on is how to make all you are focusing on is how to make relaxing.
What?
I haven't had a real break in break in ages, Mike.
I'm not even sure I remember how to relax anymore.
I work all day and when I get home all I think about is work.
I didn't get finished.
It's hard to just unplug, you know?
And that's exactly why you should come.
Think of it this way, Sydney Harper.
You're like a battery full of power and productivity.
But what happens when you run the battery too long?
It loses its charge.
We've got to put you back on the charger, harp.
You'll go back to work after the weekend with more energy than ever.
20% more productivity, I bet.
Come on.
Why did he use the Lenny face?
I don't know.
Who knows?
Maybe you'll thank me later.
What?
Plus, Nora is really excited about it.
It wouldn't be the same without you.
Sorry, passed out last night.
Damn it.
Fine.
All right.
I'll check in with HR and let you know.
What do you mean?
It's the weekend.
You shouldn't have to check in with HR.
Take your time, harp.
And just know that whatever you decide, we're here for you.
Smiley heart.
Yo, harp.
Your cell keeps going straight to voicemail.
Everything okay?
Call me back.
I'm getting a little worried.
Just booked.
Do you ever answer the phone anymore?
Call me, please.
I'm off work now.
Okay, I'm headed that way.
Pulling into the parking garage now.
You downstairs yet?
Wibby.
Oh, it won't let me erase it?
Oh, gosh.
Wait.
Okay, there we go.
And here we have Sydney from Rent-A-Cabin.
Thanks for booking my property in Woodbury for December 10th to 12th.
I'm Rick, your host.
Let me know if you have any questions and feel free to contact me for anything during your day.
Looking forward to hosting you.
Thanks, Rick.
We're looking forward to forward it.
Just confirming the check-in time is 3 p.m., right?
That's correct.
The key will be in a lockbox by the front door.
Call me if you have any trouble getting it open.
Have a safe trip.
Great.
Thank you.
Oh, wow.
We have a lot.
Oh, my gosh.
Friends 3 ever.
What the hell is this?
Oh, my gosh.
What is...
There is so much going on here.
We're popular.
Harpy!
It's been over a year since I saw your stwipped face.
Ha!
It'll be fun, right?
It'll be like the girls trip we planned during our sophomore year.
The one that never ended up happening.
Lololol.
Yumi and Taylor?
Haha.
That was such a long time ago.
Why didn't we go?
Baxter took her to a concert?
I think?
We just never tried again.
You know, I can't be mad at her for not inviting us to the wedding.
We all just kind of lost touch with each other.
But we're gonna change that this weekend.
I'm so excited!
But are you gonna drive alone?
Yeah, I've done it before.
Don't you worry, girl.
I'll probably get there a little late, though.
One of my clients wants to do a review that afternoon.
You can probably tag with Mike, though, since you both live in the city.
Yeah, I'll talk to him about it.
We can burn up his gas.
Smiley.
Thanks, girl!
Can't wait to give you the biggest hug!
Me too too too!
People type like this for real.
What is Friends 3 Eva?
This is so cute.
Oh, this is the Taylor girl, right?
And she... Oh my god, this is so shady.
Nora posts about Taylor getting married in the group chat?
I'm assuming with Taylor?
Wait, who's in this group chat?
Oh, Michael.
Oh, this is Mike.
Okay.
Like, not forever.
Oh, I don't even think Taylor's in this group chat.
I was gonna say, that's really shady to be like, Taylor, look!
Wait, what's this?
Here's the thing, guys.
I'm on a tight budget.
Like, I'm eating ramen noodles for every meal.
Kind of tight.
Not to mention, I really need to put a new set of tires on the car.
If we could find something in the ballpark of $100 per night, I think I can still make it work.
I don't know.
Let me know if that's okay with you.
I hope I get to see you both soon.
Is this Lily Pichu?
Just kinda sound like her, doesn't it?
Hold on.
Here's the thing, guys.
I'm on a tight budget.
Like, I'm eating ramen noodles for every meal.
Kind of tight.
Not to mention, I really need to put a new set of tires on the car.
If we could find something in the ballpark of $100 per night, I think I can still make it work.
I don't know.
Let me know if that's okay with you.
I hope I get to see you both soon.
Is she the one setting up the bedroom situation?
Oh, maybe.
We know you're a millionaire at heart, Nora.
The fanciest woman we know.
Stop!
XD jump scare.
Oh, wait.
My hair is blocking it.
XD!
Lol.
XD Oh.
What is this?
Oh, my stuff.
XD Ding bong.
Hello?
What was that guy who was just like chilling in the elevator?
She can definitely afford more than $100?
This is definitely a setup?
Oh!
Ah!
Stay away from me!
The luggage is holding me down.
Ah!
Stay away!
She's got a pickup truck!
Hold on.
Let's throw it at him.
Why does he look like Jack's films?
Harp.
Hug!
Oh!
Ah!
That's still how you hug people?
What's wrong with how I hug people?
Why don't you hug me like you missed me?
Just a test hug to see if you smelled first.
What if we're just so awkward and terrible with him the entire time?
What if we're just like...
XD
You look good.
You can just throw your stuff in the back and we'll get on our way.
I mean, tougher handing.
No, I feel like we're gonna miss out on story if I...
you know.
Alright then, Harp.
Are you ready to hit the road?
Where's Nora?
She'll meet us there.
The route through the city would have been a detour for her anyway.
Alright then, Harp.
He's aggressive.
What happened to the guy with the PSP?
What did he do with Nora?
4.26 PM?
It was night time though, wasn't it?
Am I crazy?
This is kind of nice.
It was starting to snow.
Oh.
Um.
Uh.
It's kind of romantic.
Um.
The moon is beautiful.
Harp.
Isn't it weird?
We used to dream about escaping our college.
And now here we are.
Trying to escape from the life we wanted to live.
Funny how that works.
Yeah, eyes on the road, mister.
Change is just hard.
Like trying to adjust to the new job.
Uh.
How's your new job going?
We're working on this project that uses machine learning to predict market trends.
It's pretty cutting edge stuff.
Sounds like you're shaping the future.
Not quite Tony Stark yet.
But I'll take it.
Let's be nice to him, you guys.
Let's be nice.
Oh.
Mr. Rick.
You know, I never understood.
What do consultants even do?
I'm not sure.
Stop looking at me!
Oh my gosh.
What are we looking at?
What just happened?
Did you see that?
Did you see that school bus?
See what?
There was a school bus.
Why does that matter?
Maybe it's a project.
You know, someone's idea of turning it into a tiny home on wheels or something.
Yeah, I've read people do that on the internet.
Yeah.
Who cares if there's a school bus in their yard?
Okay.
Mr. Rick, it's nearly 5pm and I haven't received a confirmation text for you.
Oh.
Oh my gosh, we almost died, Mike!
We almost just died!
That was close!
You know, I read on the internet that in Native American lore seeing a deer cross your path is like getting a message from the universe.
Well, what is it explaining to us?
Okay, I'm trying to...
There's like 15 different things going on.
Um...
Just wanted to make sure...
Check in and make sure everything's okay.
The roads near Woodbury can be a little dangerous if you're not from the area.
Please let me know when you arrive.
We're on our way.
Should be there around 6pm.
The snow slowed us down quite a bit.
Thanks for checking in.
Okay, please confirm when you check in and travel safe.
Okay.
All right.
Oh gosh.
Should be about an hour and a half from here.
What?
An hour and a half?
You know?
Driving through the snow kind of feels like we're traveling through the intergalactic space.
This guy's such a nerd.
What do you mean?
Look at the way the snowflakes swirl around the headlights.
He's trying to make this so romantic.
Like the stars and galaxies rushing past us.
Okay, Captain Kirk.
Why are you on the road, please?
Oh my gosh.
It's kind of...
beautiful.
Stop looking at me, please.
He didn't say, like me.
He didn't even try.
Mike, I'm not feeling anything right now.
5.14pm.
Pretend to be asleep.
It's 5pm?
Why is it so dark?
Yo, Harp.
Check that out.
What am I looking at?
Pizza?
Moe's Pizza!
Oh.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Didn't you say this guy sounded cute?
I'm being judgy, okay?
But he's fine.
I'm being judgy, but he's a fine guy.
He's fine.
He hasn't done anything weird.
He's just a little awkward.
And he also didn't ask if I wanted pizza or anything.
You know, Harp, I gotta tell you.
These new GPS systems are something else.
This pizzeria is exactly where it appeared on my GPS.
It's like living in the future.
I'm so hungry.
I think I...
How hungry.
That's a very human thing to say.
He's lame, but inoffensive.
Exactly.
I'm so hungry.
I think I could eat a whole pizza myself.
Come on.
Say the line.
Say the line, Mike.
Me too.
Alright then, Harp.
Operation Pizza Pit Stop is a go.
Prepare to land!
I kinda like Mike.
He's a dork.
He's kinda stupid.
Okay, now's our chance.
We're gonna go to that motel.
We're gonna get out of here.
Okay.
Mike was waiting for me.
There's no invisible wall to stop me.
No!
It has vacancy!
What are you waiting for?
Oh my gosh.
Can we get hit by the car?
Oh shoot.
You scared me.
You're not too discreet.
Where is he?
He's holding the door open for us.
What do they got?
Cheese?
Veggie?
No salami?
Moe's special?
Mushroom?
Barbecue chicken?
Calzone?
Three dollars for like a single slice?
Enter my pin.
It worked?
Wait, what?
Did I just win the lottery?
What?
I'm gonna take out three hundred dollars.
Truck Kun was on vacation too.
Four thousand dollars?
Let's go?
How do I get my cash?
What the hell am I hearing?
I think there's like a TV going on in there or something.
We have four thousand dollars in our bank account!
Damn!
Mento just unlocked the TikTok chase glitch again.
Dinner's on me, Mikey!
Thank you for the card info, Mento.
I can super chat the freak phantomers.
You guys don't hack my bank account, okay?
Don't hack my bank account.
I'm just a city girl.
Oh yeah, Mike is the dork here.
Sure.
Well, it's just me and Mike, and uh, definitely ain't me.
I wanna see what the other, um...
Oh, we're on the road, Nora.
Let us know when you get going, okay?
Let's see what all this is about.
OMG.
Did you guys hear about Taylor and Baxter?
Let me guess.
Baxter got her pregnant, and now they're planning a Star Wars themed baby shower.
This guy is such a nerd!
I can see it now.
A birth announcement that says, the force is strong with this one.
Mikey...
Did they tie the knot?
Tell me they didn't get married.
I didn't get an invitation!
Mike, you are the biggest nerd I know, other than Baxter.
He would totally do that.
This is so cute!
All you need is love.
Aww, so happy for them.
They make me believe in love again.
Right?
I always thought they were so cute together.
I remember Taylor telling me how they met at a Beatles tribute concert in high school.
It's too stinking cute.
That's goals.
Hashtag goals, everybody.
Our college friends are moving on with their lives and getting married, and I'm here busting my ass and revising designs for a company I don't even care about.
Blah.
Why do the pictures look like a Sims 4 screenshot?
Oh my gosh, it really does.
Three weeks ago they got married!
Right?
Oh, oh wait.
Seriously, I feel you, girl.
May as well put a bed in my office because I feel like I live here.
We're practically zombies at this point.
Exactly.
And I miss the city.
My social life is officially dead.
Syracuse just doesn't hit the same.
What is this reaction?
Michael Carter.
I'll tell you a funny story of when I met the English voice for Solid Snake.
Wait, oh my gosh, hold on.
In my Mario cosplay and we both did our own impressions of them apologizing for beating each other up in Smash.
That's so cute!
Sounds so fun.
Can't believe it's been a year since the last time we saw each other.
Ladies, ladies, ladies.
I have a proposal.
To Sydney.
Not the same kind as...
Oh wait, oh gosh!
Not the same kind as Baxter had for Taylor.
What a proposal.
Stop.
Syracuse hates...
hate from NoraIsRealAF.
How about we find a rental house this winter?
Somewhere in Vermont maybe?
We can chill and relax for a weekend.
I'm 100% serious.
It'll be like our college days.
We can watch movies, eat junk food, whatever we want.
Maybe we can get high...
No!
Michael J.
Carter!
Not on my channel!
This is...
This is a drug-free zone.
I'm sure one of my old contacts could come through.
Also, I'm afraid of heights.
That actually sounds like a great idea.
Our own cozy little getaway for the weekend.
I heart it.
A getaway?
I don't know, Mike.
Sounds like a lot of work.
Plus, I'm swamped right now.
My boss just dropped two new clients on me this week.
Think about it.
Harpy?
A weekend away from all the stress?
No work?
No deadlines?
It'll be like a girl's trip.
But with Mike, lol.
Yeah.
Guy's third wheeling.
You say like...
You say it like it's a bad thing.
I don't know, guys.
I'll get...
I'll let... I'll let...
I'll let get back with you after I think it over.
XOXO, gossip girl.
Honestly, the more I think about it, the more I like the idea.
That's the spirit, Harpy!
Let's make it happen!
Alright, I'm in.
But there better be wine involved.
Alright, good deal.
I'll bring some pizza supplies.
Not the kind of wake and bake Mikey has in mind.
What's that?
Wake and bake.
But it'll be so good.
Oh no, and here we are having pizza without Nora!
Wake up.
And smoke.
No!
What does that have to do with pizza?
Harp, would you mind taking the lead on booking the house?
We've always had a knack for finding a great place to stay.
Me?
Book a cabin?
I suppose I could do that.
And then she does the voice message.
Nora, that's no problem.
We will make sure to get something reasonably priced.
We've got you, girl.
Cheap and cozy.
Don't say cheap, Harpy.
Makes me sound so...
well, cheap.
Okay, yeah.
Okay, cool.
Alright, pizza time!
Come on in, Harp.
Thank you, Mike.
What the hell?
Everyone in that pizzeria is frozen solid.
Residents are recommended to stay indoors and keep warm during this time.
What is this?
Let's check in with our field reporter.
Oh no, a snowstorm?
How's the weather out there feel?
Will Nora be able to get here?
I can't feel my hands, okay?
The studio should have really brought some snow gear instead of buying that new coffee machine.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
You can have some coffee when you get back to the studio.
Jerry, you cannot be serious.
You know my doctor said not to drink any caffeine.
Sounds like someone's having a bad day.
Maybe you should cool off.
You little shit.
Why can't you go out here and deal with the snow instead of me?
I've been working here for six years and I never get to report somewhere nice.
Listen, Phil.
I'm just clearly the better looking one.
Who's Queso?
You can worry about where you'll report once you get that rhinoplasty.
Rhinoplasty?
Why would I need rhinoplasty?
My face looks perfectly fine.
Who is Queso?
You could also use some Botox while you're at it.
Actually, maybe you should work as a studio light engineer.
The girls are fighting!
Behind the camera.
I think it would be a better field of work for you.
You only got your job because your sister works at the mixing board.
You would have never been able to work here if it wasn't for her.
I'd like to see you work the ENG sometime.
How dare you?
I'm a certified news anchor.
I wanna be in Fierce to Fathom.
I wanna be a voice actor.
You didn't do shit.
How about I come by the studio and we settle this like men?
Oh yeah?
Well let's do it, punk.
How's the weather?
We'll be right back at this commercial break.
Oh my god.
But the weather!
Oh.
My bad.
Sorry.
Is this a music video?
What is going on?
What the heck is this?
What is happening?
Woah!
Extreme sports!
Oh
my gosh.
He's gonna die.
Is
this a snowman?
What?
This is the commercial.
What is it selling?
Insurance?
Is that my office?
Oh my god.
There's a security.
There's a live feed of my office.
Oh my god.
They're playing Fierce to Fathom.
And no, we're not gonna penalize you for that, of course.
But it's mainly for you that I'm doing this.
I cannot get over.
Everybody is chewing in my ear.
Shut up.
Shut up every single one of you.
Please.
Oh my god.
I can't take it anymore.
Sorry.
I have that misoph- phobia.
Excuse me.
Evening, folks.
Looks like the cold's got everyone craving pizza tonight.
You fine folks know what you want to eat.
We'll get three slices each.
Okay, Mikey.
Deciding for me.
I'll go with pepperoni, cheese, and a veggie.
And for you, miss?
Uh...
Cheese?
Alright, what's your second slice?
Veggie?
The third?
Let's go with the Moe's special.
There's a setting in the options that remove chewing sounds.
No way!
Any drinks for you folks?
That should cover us.
What?
Wait.
No.
I want like a lemonade.
Come on, Mike.
That should cover us.
Just the pizza today, thanks.
Alright then.
Six hot slices.
Coming right up.
That'll be $22.50.
Oh, I'm the one paying!
Your order number is 27.
Grab a seat and we'll call you when your pizza's ready.
I thought you were into me, Mike.
How do I turn off the sounds?
You guys, how do I go into the settings?
There's no way to get into the settings.
Please.
How do I go into the settings?
If I press escape, this is all I get.
Oh my god!
How do I...
Tab?
No, it doesn't work.
Alt F4.
Oh god!
Tab out of the game?
No, it doesn't do anything.
Phone settings?
There is none.
Oh my gosh.
There's only like a little thing down here that I'm kind of covering.
It says messages and rent a cabin.
Oh god!
The chewing sounds are so bad!
Oh!
Hi, sir.
Sorry.
I wanted my own little soda.
How are you doing, my friend?
I'm pretty hungry.
Pizza does smell awfully good.
Going to grab a slice?
No, just looking for a little help.
Maybe I can help you.
Maybe you can.
But you go on and get some pizza first, eh?
Maybe we'll catch up later.
Alright!
Mikey's like, why are you flirting with that guy?
Why are you flirting with that guy?
Oh my god.
Hello?
How's the pizza?
The pizza's great, actually.
I think Moe's might have ruined other pizzas for us.
It's our first time in the area.
Oh.
Uh.
Are you from...
Wait, she said it's her first time in the area.
Where are you headed?
We're on our way to a conference in the next town over with my buddy here.
Your buddy is like Sasquatch posing.
Your buddy just wants to eat his pizza in peace.
Oh, we don't...
Oh, excuse me.
We're having a conversation here.
Oh yeah, we just stopped to eat whatever...
whatever a place looks interesting.
This place definitely has a cozy vibe.
How about you?
Local are just passing through.
I don't think I'm going to tell you where I'm going.
Yeah, we're just passing through.
You gotta exit the game to change the settings, unfortunately.
What?
That's so messed up.
Interesting.
Hmm.
We better get back to this pizza.
You have a safe trip and be careful in the snow.
You too.
Oh my god.
Hold on, Mikey.
I'm being social.
Craps is at it.
Whoa.
Craps, slow down.
You're going to choke.
Oh my god.
He's just shoveling down this pizza.
How's the pizza?
Well, my dear.
You absolutely can't go wrong with the pepperoni here at Moe's.
Every bite reminds you of a story.
So what brings you to Moe's?
Oh, so what brings you to Moe's?
I'm here on a road trip with my friend.
You've made a mistake.
It's a good choice stopping here.
Do you come here often?
Oh, my dear.
I've been coming to Moe's since 85.
This place is full of memories for me.
Though my daughter, bless her, she tries to keep me from eating too much pizza.
Yeah, you're desperate for that pizza.
I think you have an addiction.
I was kidding when I said all time for.
The pizza bite of 85.
Bad for a man my age, she says.
She worries too much.
Only have one of these heavenly slices about twice a month now.
Well, it was nice chatting with you.
Safe travels to you and your friend.
Thank you.
Oh, oh, okay.
I was not talking to you.
How's your day going?
Who are you?
I'm Sydney.
Look, Sydney.
We're just here to enjoy our pizza in peace.
Thanks for understanding.
You weren't here this morning for coffee break.
Oh, talk to all people.
All NPCs in the pizzeria.
I didn't talk to this guy, though.
Do you have any recommendations?
Get the cheese.
Just the cheese.
Okay.
This guy is going everywhere.
He does not.
It does not matter where he.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
What are you doing?
This guy is so short.
Are you lost, little kid?
What do you want?
Stop!
He's trying to fight me for real.
Another Tokyo map stream.
Going to Japan in November.
Wanted to know some recommendations.
Oh, I've only done Akiba before.
I don't know where else I could...
I don't know so many other places as well as...
Oh, who's that?
As well as I know...
No!
As well as I know Akiba.
Walked up to a girl wearing an MGS2 shirt.
Asked if she liked the game.
She was confused.
Then said she doesn't know him.
She just likes the shirt.
Glad people like Yoji, but I want to die after that L.
No way!
That is such an L.
You should have told her to play at No 2.
Actually, it was crazy.
I would see Metal Gear shirts all the time in Japan.
Like the Uniqlo ones.
I saw them everywhere.
It was kind of crazy actually.
It was a lot of the ones...
The one from Peace Walker.
With them wearing the boxes on the head.
And a lot of the Raiden ones.
Like the Metal Gear Rising one.
With Raiden.
It was the Uniqlo one too.
No!
Oh, it hurts.
Oh, it hurts!
I kind of want to see if this guy opens the door back up.
If we can go in.
What are these?
Oh, sorry.
My bad.
I know.
We are going to continue the game in like 2 seconds.
What does this say?
I hope you are not doing these crosswords on the job.
Oh, I am so close.
I am so close.
Let me in.
Push me in.
Come on.
Too bad.
Oh, wait.
I hate those things.
I should have read the sign before I ordered that.
Mike, what are you doing?
Mike?
It smells so good in here.
We'll join in with him so he doesn't feel so self-conscious.
Oh!
A voice message.
You guys are going to hate me.
I swear I'll get on the road as soon as I can.
But something last minute popped up.
I'm not going to bore you with all of the details.
The long and short of it is one of my clients needs a last minute change.
This is the only thing keeping the lights on.
I hate to leave so late.
But I gotta keep them happy.
Oh, no.
I'll have this logo done before you know it.
And be on my way.
I'm so sorry, you guys.
Nora.
Sad, sad, sad.
Be careful.
I hate that you're leaving so late.
Drive slow and don't worry.
I'll make sure Harp stays up to let you in.
Why don't you stay up?
What?
Did you listen to Nora's voice message in the group?
Yeah, I just saw.
Looks like she'll be late.
I guess we'll have to start the fun without her.
Cheap.
Safe.
Oh, order number 27.
You folks are right here.
You gonna get that?
Mike, be a gentleman.
And go fetch our food for us.
I swear.
I'm messing all this up.
Oh, now you get up?
You're just getting your own?
Mike, you're so selfish.
Don't stare at me while you eat.
Alright, you folks are all set.
Thank you.
I just can't with this guy.
He's fumbling everything.
Let's try...
Oh, God.
Oh, damn.
This pizza slaps.
I can't believe Nora is missing out on this bomb-ass pizza.
Shut up.
I'm mad at you right now.
Oh, God.
Can I mute it when this happens?
Yeah.
Nom, nom, nom, nom.
He's eating it up.
Oh.
Hey there, my friends.
Hello there.
I saw y'all pull in driving that nice old truck.
Are you just watching who pulls in and taking notes?
Gosh.
Okay, Sydney.
That's right.
Not to be a bother or anything, but I was heading down the road myself.
Seems like we might have been going the same direction.
Y'all mind if I hitch a ride with you?
Where's your car?
Who needs a car when there are fine friends like you to pass the time with?
Oh.
Okay.
Y'all wouldn't even know I was there.
Quiet as a church mouse.
And twice as nice.
So what do you say?
Care to give this free spirit a ride down that snowy road?
Um.
It's not my car.
Sure, you can come with us.
Oh.
Oh, but okay.
You were making all the decisions tonight, Mike.
But as soon as I make a decision, you have to say something?
Huh?
Hold on a second.
Don't you think we need to discuss this?
Isn't that what we're doing?
I'm not sure if we have extra space for another passenger.
Yeah.
Oh, oh, oh.
You know, you were fine with deciding that we didn't want drinks and deciding that we wanted three slices of pizza.
Right?
And deciding that I get to pay for the pizza?
Michael?
But as soon as I make a decision that I want to do something...
Oh, oh, what?
Shouldn't we talk about this?
Oh my gosh, Joy!
Thank you for the hug!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
I'm sorry, Minto.
Oh, not you, Michael.
Not you.
Never you.
Oh, he's right.
Only two seats in the truck.
Surely you can find just a little bit of room for me.
I can ride in the middle.
Hell, I'll even ride in the bed.
Aw, it's my friend's car.
I'm sorry.
We would give you a ride, but there isn't any space.
You gotta be shitting me, lady.
No space?
I know there's a middle seat.
You scared of me or something?
You ain't too kind, are you?
Unkind people meet unkindness themselves.
You best be careful out there.
Are you threatening us?
Yeah, get him, Mike.
Get him.
No, no, no!
Y'all got me all wrong.
Sorry, I'm just cold and tired is all.
Yeah.
Thanks.
That was weird.
Look, Mike.
We almost got killed because of your unkindness.
Are you serious?
How are you gonna let a stranger ride with us in the middle out of nowhere?
I was just trying to help.
Yeah.
Well, sometimes helping can put you in a bad situation.
What's up with your head, guy?
You're starting to freak me out a little bit, Mike.
Why is your head glitching like that?
I think Mike is possessed.
Alright, dad.
Gosh.
Back to chomp now.
Damn, Harp.
The crust?
What?
That's like the best part.
What's wrong with eating the crust?
It's kind of wasteful that too, don't you think?
I guess, but you wouldn't really eat the peel of an orange, would you?
That's not the same thing at all!
Mike!
What?
Meow meow meow meow meow Meow meow meow meow meow
Pizza's made of crust!
Yeah, when you eat an orange, you're not eating... like the whole peel is not involved!
Mike is kind of insane.
Meow meow meow meow Meow meow yum
Oh, thank you!
Oh my gosh, I wouldn't have heard that.
Try for just thank you.
10 out of 10 pizza ASMR.
I can right mouse button to burp.
Ugh.
Oh my gosh.
A burp so loud, even Nora heard it.
Ugh.
Oh my god, Sydney!
Real fear is the Mike we fathomed on the way.
Mike, you have no room to be judgemental here.
What is this?
You have no room to be judgemental.
That was me enjoying my crust.
Drive slow and don't... oh yeah.
Heart XD heart!
He doesn't want a real woman.
He's like...
He's like, oh my gosh, I used to be so in love with Sydney during our college days.
You know what?
I think this trip...
Oh my god, the grandpa behind him looks like an evil demon.
Like in some... look at him!
Doesn't he look evil?
Holy cow.
He's like, oh my gosh, I've always been in love with Sydney.
She was always so delicate and wonderful and kind and smart and beautiful in college.
She probably grew up to be like the most reliable, awesome person ever.
Little does he know.
Oh my god.
Oh gosh.
We're so close.
Holy...
That was good!
Joy!
Look at the bamboo ship!
Thank you!
Alright then.
Are you ready to hit the road?
Maybe we can beat the worst of the snow.
Give me the keys.
Harp, the weather is awful.
Why don't you drive part of the way home?
Take a break while I drive.
Michael...
This guy is moaning and groaning behind you.
Michael, I think you're being violated right in front of this guy.
What is happening?
Why is Michael in quotation marks?
I'm afraid of what kind of break you're going to give me, Harp.
You'll be afraid if you don't give me the keys.
What is happening?
Oh my
gosh, we need to get out of here.
Fine, but there's one condition.
What is it?
I get first choice of bedrooms when or if we get there.
Whatever.
It's time for Minto to drive.
He's been freed.
Y'all drive safe.
Yeah, I'm going to take over the wheel.
You're going to what?
Why is it so loud all of a sudden?
We could have gotten a water.
Come on, let's go.
Bro is enjoying that Zod too much.
Andragos, thank you for the 20 gift.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, Paige, for the super jet.
Pretty funny.
He doesn't speak many words.
Alright, let's go.
Oh, gosh.
That was like the longest detour ever.
You ready for me to drive?
Where'd that guy go?
He's not in the bed, is he?
Okay.
Here we go.
Minto Drifto.
5.49 p.m.
Good evening, Vermont.
This is your host on WKWB.
Your hometown station.
Bringing you the best tunes to warm your hearts on this chilly night.
As we embrace the first snowfall of the season, there's nothing like a perfect song to set the mood.
So here's a track that'll make you feel right at home.
Beep.
Well.
Oh my gosh.
This is like, giving me a real Christmas vibe, right?
It's pretty nice, actually.
Ghost Behind the Wheel?
Yeah.
What?
That's one way to take the scenic route.
Sorry.
Hi!
I was out of practice with the drivers.
I'm trying to get on the side of the road!
This song kind of slaps.
25 miles per hour!
What about 250 miles per hour?
Wait, which way do I go?
Oh.
Which is this way?
That's Woodbury, but...
Why don't we go this way?
We missed the turn at first.
I see.
I see what?
Joy, thanks for the 50 gift cards!
Thank you!
Uh-oh.
The car is stalling.
Uh-oh!
Oh gosh!
The car is stalling!
We can't make it!
I hope this isn't copyrighted.
It's not!
At the beginning, when I opened the game, it said that all the music is copyright-free.
So, we should be okay.
Hopefully.
Come on, car!
I just spent a year alone and never missed a soul.
Yay!
I could try my hardest and I'll never reach my goals.
I know that I'll need more love inside my heart.
What is here?
Oh my gosh.
Why are we going so slow, actually?
We should be getting pretty close.
Do you remember the address?
I think the address was 241 Woodbury Boulevard.
Wait.
Okay, I think we're good now.
I see one crazy driver.
Oh!
Hello!
It was a very cold night.
Why are we getting out here, Harp?
Actually, there's an invisible wall.
He's just following me.
Like a little puppy.
Okay, we'll turn around.
Got to talk to my actual boss about keeping my job soon.
So, I'm glad I could catch the stream.
Oh!
Good luck!
You are a value to your company.
Oh!
Harp, are you okay?
Do you want me to take over?
Says nothing.
I crashed by a truck.
Okay, it's really loud.
Today is a good time to start.
Oh, it's a little bit cold.
Back up the hill we go!
This is what happens when you go off the beaten path, I guess.
Oh, my lights are flashing.
The car is really breaking down.
Okay!
Shut up, please.
Alright.
Here we go.
You'll be running up the hill, running up the road.
Something, I'm trying to get to Woodbury.
I think we are almost there.
You got your license?
Yeah.
I'm licensed to kill.
Why is it so slow?
Did I really break the car?
Oh, come on.
Why is it so slow?
Yeah, do a little squirt, squirt.
Squirt, squirt.
Which way is it?
241, right?
Slow.
I don't think so.
I've been going slow this whole time.
Did I put it back on?
Look at that bobblehead.
We're here!
Hold on!
I told you, driving in the snow is no joke.
This guy!
It wasn't me!
I should have just let Mike drive.
I'm trying!
They're the one who ran into me!
Okay, the music is distracting me, you guys.
It's the music's fault.
Okay, 241.
This looks kind of industrial.
This doesn't look like a neighborhood.
We're gonna be there any minute now.
Right?
Should be getting close.
241 Woodbury.
Oh.
That's a cop.
Okay.
Act natural.
The real horror was Minto's driving.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Shackled by lust?
Jesus, that's free!
Wait!
I saw...
I saw a sign almost just like this in California.
Joy!
Thank you for the 50!
Such a rude driver.
No!
I saw...
Hold on.
I have a photo of it.
I took a picture of it.
Cause I was like, whoa!
It was a photo just like this.
When I went to...
When I went to AX.
Hold on.
I got it.
I have it.
Hold on.
That's off-key.
Wait.
When was AX?
Yes.
Okay.
It said... Hold on.
I got it.
I have it.
Hold on.
Where is it?
Oh!
It said...
Stop your OnlyFans.
Stop simping.
Save our families and communities.
Paid for by...
No simps.
Wait.
Which way is it?
This way?
Probably.
Paid for by no simps.
I don't want no simps.
A simp is a guy who has...
Onlyfans.
Thanks for the combo.
It should be shackled by lust.
Jesus sets... free?
What?
Which way is it?
I don't know.
Oh!
I drove past our cabin at first.
I did?
Is it this way?
This way?
How can I tell?
Wait.
What?
Am I going the right way?
Beep.
Behind me.
He told us the address.
I wish he would say like...
Stop here.
Oh!
There it is.
Right here.
We are here.
This should be it.
Hahaha.
I should have just let Mike drive.
I thought you were just going to keep driving there.
Alright.
We are here.
Oh!
It was a quaint little house...
in a quiet neighborhood.
Is that...
boarded up?
Why?
What is that?
Oh!
Oh yeah!
Let's get our stuff.
My things.
Open the door.
Oh!
The door was locked.
I had to get the key from the lockbox.
Oh!
What was it?
It was...
5176.
One.
Seven.
Six.
Yeah!
Perfect.
Don't forget to check in.
Yeah, I know.
Oh!
Here!
Ready?
My back hurts.
Hahaha.
Do we need to get you to the nursing home, old man?
Let's go in.
I really need to.
Let's just hurry up, Harp.
What?
The nursing home?
I'd like to place a delivery order for I.C.
Wiener.
Hahaha.
Go on in!
What is this part though?
Why is it boarded up right here?
Why is this...
This place is kind of...
dumpy, isn't it?
Why is the music so scary?
Oh!
What a great place!
I knew we could count on you!
It smells so nice in here.
Right?
But I really need to hit the john.
Take your time!
While I'm gone, can you put these groceries away?
There should be enough space in the fridge.
Sure.
Checked in.
Entered the cabin.
The house was cozy and well furnished.
Alright.
The music does not match the dialogue.
Yeah, I'm scared.
Okay.
What do we got in here?
We got yogurt.
We got...
Apples?
Milk.
We got...
Milk again.
That one actually worked.
We got...
Eggs.
Had to close the mini fridge before picking it up.
How do I close it?
Oh.
What was that?
Excuse me.
I'm trying to...
I'm trying to open this.
Oh, there we go.
We've got turkey.
We've got...
Bell peppers.
Joint!
Oh my gosh!
Thank you for another 50!
What is happening?
Thank you!
We've got...
Lettuce.
Okay.
How do I get this in the fridge?
Oh!
I just have to...
Oops.
Oh.
Wait.
Hold on.
Stop.
Let's stop it, please.
I didn't need to throw it at all.
There we go.
All good!
Oh my god!
Sorry about that harp.
You had to use the bathroom.
What's the issue?
Also, I see you there.
No simps for Minto.
Shackled by this mortal coil of existence.
Live no more.
Minto drives.
TV tables dry!
Thank you for the 20.
I'm dead!
Are you okay?
Long drive and all that pizza really did a number on me.
Hang on.
I really need to pee.
You can go ahead.
I'll start unpacking our bags.
You're gonna go through my stuff?
Thanks.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I have underwear in there.
Oh!
No, no, no!
No!
You freak!
You freak, you freak, you freak.
I had to pee.
Is that him opening the doors?
Can we close this?
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm scared.
The smell alone told me pizza had really done a number on me.
This is disgusting.
I don't need to know this.
Come on!
Game!
We have the pee meter again.
Escape to text Rick.
Okay, this is the most realistic thing now.
Oh.
I thought it was gonna be like a...
Hi, we've checked in.
I thought it was gonna be like one of those...
What's it called?
One of those like...
I type it and it automatically puts in something.
Oh, you can see through the blinds.
Nothing but metal gear memorabilia in the back.
See the crouch?
Oh, gosh.
It's gonna be one of these.
Wash your hands.
Guys, I'm not actually peeing.
Stop it.
Whose leftover stuff is this?
Why is it so dark in here?
Dry your hands.
Okay.
Oh my god!
Jesus!
You're scaring me so much!
You feeling better after the drive?
Much better now.
So, oh!
This is the most movement we've seen him done.
Ready to check out the place?
Sure, let's see what this place has to offer.
After you.
Okay.
Crosswords.
And the fire is already going.
This living room is bigger than my apartment.
Aren't you like a programmer?
Wow, nice TV.
Isn't this like also the 90s or something?
Like this TV is...
They don't have flat screen.
Who's that?
Could've swept.
Before we came in.
But alright.
Oh my god!
It's creeping me out!
Oh!
What is this?
Ouija board!
Play it!
But they don't even empty the trash!
Oh!
90s didn't have smartphones and K-cups either.
You're so right!
How did you think about it?
Nobody's out there, right?
Why doesn't this room have blinds?
Oh, sick dinosaur!
Chess...
Whispers in the dark?
The hell is that?
Excuse me.
What else we got?
We got the kitchen!
Hurry up!
Hurry up, Mikey!
Can't wait to cook here later!
When did you start cooking?
Don't let Mike cook.
I'm full of surprises!
Weak!
What's this door over here?
Oh!
You can go down there first.
Let's go up...
Let's go upstairs.
Unbiased vampire.
Boy, thanks.
Welcome to membership.
Thank you!
Thanks for joining.
Oh my gosh, Joy!
Thank you for another 50!
Thank you!
Please, your wallet.
Please, please, please, please, please, your wallet.
Okay.
We got a...
Maybe we should take this as a weapon?
I'll take this for now.
Okay.
What else we got?
Oh!
Ah!
Oh hey, you're here!
Who are you?
Welcome to my home sweet home!
What a lovely young couple.
No, no, no!
We're not a couple!
Mike took offense to that.
Oh!
You didn't have to sell it that hard, Harp.
I was just answering his question.
He didn't ask a question, Sydney.
He made a statement and you...
Never mind.
Oopsie daisy.
Silly me.
Didn't mean to cause a stir with you two.
We didn't expect anyone to be here.
Oh, um...
I was out looking for my cat earlier and remembered the TV has been on the fritz here.
Just thought I'd stop by and try to get it working again since the last few folks left a bad word for it.
You know, they say treat your guests like family.
My family doesn't go without TV.
The dramatic turns back to Mikey.
Speaking of that, now that you folks are here, let me show you around my sweet home.
I'd be a bad owner if I didn't give you the grand tour.
Oh.
About the TV?
My host was a middle-aged man with a nervous energy.
Right from the start, his presence made us uncomfortable.
This is why I don't do Airbnbs.
This is exactly why I don't do Airbnbs.
Because sometimes the owner will just stay at the Airbnb.
It doesn't make any sense why that's allowed.
Singer Invader from Space reveals truth about nut allergies.
Bites Tiger attacking police.
What's going on here?
Why is there a toilet roll next to the couch?
Oh my god!
What's here?
Here's your shower!
That thing will make you feel like you're bathing under a waterfall in the Amazon jungle.
Oh, this sink doesn't work unfortunately.
Not to worry.
I'll get it fixed for you real soon.
I've never been in one.
Are they dangerous?
What, an Airbnb?
It's just that it's not as well regulated as a hotel is.
Because...
Airbnb hosts can just walk in or they can put cameras in rooms and you don't realize it.
Let me show you the other bedroom now.
Why is there no lights in here?
Look, Harp!
This room has a nice ass!
View!
You think that's nice, mister?
Wait till I show you the deck.
First the ass, now the deck?
Follow me now, please.
Wait, I want to see the view.
Mikey, your standards.
Are you coming, miss?
Yeah.
I'm coming.
Alright, let's go.
I'm following along.
A laundry room.
Oh, nice!
Wow, this is actually...
Wow, this looks so nice!
Holy smokes, this is incredible!
Definitely.
Glad you folks like it.
This is one of my favorite spots.
The view of the creek is beautiful.
It's a great spot for fishing, too.
Fishing!
Alright, folks.
Let's head back in before I catch the cold here again.
Yeah, you don't even have a...
You just have a t-shirt on.
Like you're in Hawaii or something.
Wow, this looks so nice!
Oh, are you coming, miss?
Hold on, hold on.
It looks so nice!
Where's the creek?
What creek?
There's a creek?
Do you guys see a creek?
Am I crazy?
Is it that over there?
I can't tell at all.
Okay.
Storage closet.
It's probably frozen over.
Oh.
Here's the storage room.
Was looking for his cat, but isn't dressed for outside.
Sus.
You're right.
If you need anything, tools, extra blankets, what not, it's all in here.
If the power ever goes out, we can use this flashlight here on my right.
That's what I'm holding.
Storms like these, you never know.
We might not need it.
Trust me.
It's always best to know where your light is.
Alright, folks.
Let's head downstairs now.
Shutting the door.
Me first.
I'm gonna beat Mikey.
Haha, slowpoke.
Haha.
Alrighty, folks.
I see I already stocked up the fridge with some tasty food.
Yep, that's ours.
You see the knob?
Turn the knob for more cooling and down to cool it off.
I tend to keep it low in the winter.
The bill gets out of control.
Speaking of winter, I better show you folks the water.
The water heater.
Is that in the basement?
Okay, Mikey is just all powerful.
He can just go through any door he pleases.
Oh my gosh.
No access to guests.
I couldn't open the door.
Nothing to worry about down here.
Just the water heater and some old storage stuff.
Okay.
It's creepy.
If it ever stops working, just hit the button at the bottom.
The pilot light will fire right up and you'll be back in business.
Which button?
That button?
Okay.
Don't leave me.
It's creepy down here.
Oh, there's the breaker, guys.
Okay, we know the breaker for the future.
Hey, sir.
What's the deal with that room over there?
Nothing you two need to concern yourselves with.
I kinda use this basement as storage.
Renters don't need the space.
They really ought to keep upstairs.
Okay, well I was just curious.
Let's move on.
What is that, though?
Just some...
Oh my gosh.
I'm here.
What?
Sorry.
Did I mention?
Well, no.
Maybe I ought to keep it to myself.
The fella I bought this house from, well, told me his mother died down here.
Some guests have reported hearing voices at night.
Said they could hear something shuffling down here.
Not to scare you folks, but if I were one of you, I wouldn't really step down here.
Hehehe.
The looks on your faces.
Come on, now.
I'm just joking.
Don't leave me down here.
At this point, my creep meter was quietly pinging at around 6 out of 10.
Hold on.
Alrighty, folks.
Snow's starting to pick up.
I'm gonna hit the road now.
Gotta find that damn cat.
But you're not dressed for the outdoors.
Yeah, only 6?
We're only at a 6?
Sydney's tolerance is insane.
Thanks for showing us around.
By the way...
What was the name on the booking?
I must be getting old.
It's Sydney.
Ha!
Sydney.
That's right.
A pretty name for a pretty girl.
Room $50 a night cleaning $500.
I don't think this guy is our guy.
Is it just me or is that dude super weird?
Uh, very weird.
Anyway, let's go see if there's anything good on TV.
Actually, I'm going to take a quick shower.
Sydney, you just saw...
You just saw the man we just met and you're gonna go take a shower?
Cool, I'll find something to watch while you're in there.
Heh, me.
Let me know if it feels like you're under a waterfall.
Chuckle.
What a weird guy.
You're the weird guy.
Wait, what do you mean?
Hopper, welcome to the membership.
Thank you!
But...
Can I take...
Can I use this shower instead?
I was keen on taking shower upstairs.
No, I would feel so much more comfortable!
Okay, I don't feel comfortable showering next to him, but I would feel more comfortable showering next to him.
You know what I mean?
...
Wait, what?
I don't like it!
You're not even sure of this shower!
Oh, I'll take a shower!
Oh my gosh.
He's so big.
I don't like it!
Come on, come on.
Oh my gosh.
This is where we shower.
Oh, okay.
There we go!
If it's cold, we can tell Mike to go into the basement.
You know?
We don't have to do it ourselves.
I feel so much better.
I think.
Oh god, I thought he was gonna be standing there.
Run.
Run downstairs.
Run, run, run.
I took my shower!
Hey,
Harp.
Check this out.
I found this fishing rod in that shed.
Planning to catch dinner?
Now that you mention...
That would be a pretty epic addition to the trip.
Mike jump scare.
I had to show my roommate this...
This...
This TikTok...
Was it TikTok?
Might have been on Twitter.
I don't remember.
But it was basically like...
Some guy...
And she does this all the time.
He'll turn the corner and in the video the guy's like, Oh!
You scared me there.
Like the cameraman and then the other guy in the video will be like, Yeah, I live here.
You should expect me.
And he would just be like...
It would just be different scenarios.
Eventually it got up to like...
Him walking into the dude's room and being like, Whoa!
Didn't see you there.
You scared me.
The guy's like, This is my room.
This is where I would be.
But it's the same thing.
She'll always be like, Whoa!
You scared me.
I'm like...
I...
I haunt here.
Like...
You should expect me to be around the corner sometimes.
But also...
I'm so jumpy too.
So I get it.
Now that you mentioned...
That would be a pretty epic addition to the trip.
Let's do it.
But fishing.
You know.
Hell yeah.
Follow me.
There's another rod in the shed and we can both give it a shot.
What's the other rod, Mikey?
You just left the door open?
But it's so cold.
It's really cold out here.
Whoa.
You scared me.
There's nobody in the windows or anything, right?
Whoa.
Wait.
Look.
That looks like an easel.
Did they paint?
The music is so nice.
Oh.
He looks really serial killer-y right now.
Do you want to grab the other fishing rod harp?
Yeah.
Just give me a second.
Where is it?
Wait.
Oh.
I got to put this down, don't I?
Okay.
Let's go put it...
Like here.
Where we can find it easily, you know?
Okie dokie.
Grab the rod.
Okay.
We got it.
And some bait.
Oh, snap.
I saw a killer recipe for baked carp.
We'll need to catch three carp though.
You up for the challenge?
Oh.
I meant to do dot, dot, dot.
Well, first things first.
We need the right bait for carp.
Check out this bait information board.
Whenever you're ready, grab a carp bait and let's head to the creek.
We're going to catch some carp harp.
Please don't make rhymes with my name.
So common carp, cheese delight.
Stop saying carp.
I think we need a cheese delight.
Cheese.
Oh.
None of those work.
Let's go.
Oh, okay.
We're ready.
Oh, I needed to attach the bait.
Come on, harp.
It's this way.
RMP.
To put it...
Oh, I got it on there.
Okay.
Only cheese.
I guess it doesn't freeze over because it's a creek.
It's always running.
Wow.
This area is...
This area is so nice.
Okay.
Oh, that was going to be my seat, but sure.
Why did you...
I hope those carp are biting today.
Why did you walk on that side if you were going to take the chair closer to me?
This is kind of nice.
I'm glad I'm here with you, Mikey.
Shoo.
Where's my...
Where's my line?
Oh, he's got one.
Oh, he didn't take it.
Oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
Wait.
Oh.
What is this?
This is bizarre.
Okay.
We got it.
A bluegill.
Throwback.
Okay.
Maybe that's what happened.
Let's go.
Oh.
Geez.
What about yours?
No?
Okay.
That's fine.
What we got?
Oh.
A carp.
They say whenever there's one carp, there's always more.
Who says that?
Who's saying that, Mikey?
Let's go fishing.
Oh, dang it.
Didn't know you were playing Yakuza 3.
Mikey says it.
Stop giving...
Who is that?
Oh.
Who's that back there?
Who is that back there?
You guys saw that person walking?
You saw that person walking over there?
Where'd they go?
It was too far to cast.
Oh.
Okay.
Oh my gosh.
What if our...
What if our rod's tied?
Oh my gosh.
Why do I keep getting bluegill?
Throw away.
Don't cross the streams.
I got a carp.
Okay.
Woohoo.
Just one more carp left.
You've got this.
Oh.
Are you not doing anything?
What are you doing, Mikey?
Huh?
What are you doing?
Oh.
We're fishing.
Wishing I was always fishing.
Fish to fathom.
Something, something, fish fear me.
Woman love me.
Bluegill.
Throw away.
That's like not the guy that's staring at me right there, right?
That's just...
That was...
That's been there the whole time, right?
Guy per...
The guy disappeared.
So I can't tell.
Whoa, I'm a genius?
I'm so good at this, I'm a pro.
He's staring at Mike.
He's like, dang, that guy's so skilled.
Oh my gosh, it's tiny.
I think I got the rarest fish there is.
Please, this is so difficult!
Please!
Oh my god.
Please, fish!
Please!
This is so hard!
Please, just take...
Oh my god.
Okay, hold on.
Don't worry, Harp.
The fish are just playing hard to get today.
Kind of like someone else I know.
Whack!
Riz, maybe?
Hahaha!
No, Mike, I'm just not interested in you.
Take a hint!
Yeah!
Looks like we got three carp.
Do you want to head back and throw these in the oven for dinner?
Let's do it.
Mike is the true creep here.
How do I get up?
Wait, hold on.
Mike, how do I stand?
Oh, here.
I think it was space.
Okay.
Look, we even got a...
Oh.
Oh no, the creepy music is coming back.
No, no, no!
No!
I think he's hooked on you.
No, the creepy music is coming back!
No!
I like the music before!
I don't see anyone in the house.
Okay.
Huh!
While I'm cleaning the fish, do you mind prepping the marinade?
I'm not sure how to do marinade.
Just take a bowl and throw in ginger paste, cooking oil, black pepper...
Okay.
Wait.
Hold on.
This is...
Wait.
Can I get...
Can you write this down?
Throw in ginger paste, cooking oil, black pepper, salt, Italian seasoning, paprika, and yogurt.
I think we only brought, like, milk and beans.
Mike, I don't think we have all this.
Wait.
Huh?
Mike, the door.
To the door.
To the basement is open.
Mike, the door to the basement is open.
Mikey!
Mike, why can't you listen to me?
Mike, you never listen to me.
Okay.
Alright, so we need...
What do we need?
Yogurt?
Where do I put this?
In a bowl?
Okay, yogurt.
Salt.
Oh, ginger... ginger paste.
Ginger garlic paste.
Corn flakes?
No.
Salt.
Pepper.
Paprika.
Something's gonna be outside that window, isn't it?
Olive oil.
Paprika again?
Wait.
Oh, I did the Italian seasoning.
Okay.
Oh, paprika.
Okay, I'll finish.
What are those?
Oh, lemons.
Do you mind throwing the fish in the marinade in the casserole?
While I chop these veggies?
On it.
I'm scared.
Wait, where's the fish?
What'd you do with the fish?
Weren't they in here?
What'd you do with them?
What did you do with the fish?
Two carps?
They're in the cooler?
Oh.
No.
Where did I put them?
Oh, they're here.
This cooler.
Oh, okay.
One.
Two.
Marinade.
And veggies.
Oh, good.
Now could you add the veggies?
That's what I just did.
I read it needs to go for 30 minutes at 400.
I...
Did that?
Okay.
Cooking sim, for real.
Those carp are going to taste amazing.
I hope they're not...
I hope they're clean.
Like, I know that they're like from the wild, but I mean, what if there's like, I don't know, radiation in these parts?
Who knows?
While we wait for it to cook, how about we play some board games?
I saw some in the room next to the living room.
Which one?
Just grab whatever catches your eye.
Can't wait to see what you pick.
I saw some in the room next to the living room.
Okay, let me see.
You guys, should we do the Ouija board?
Should we do the Ouija board?
What's one that you...
If you've watched someone play this game before...
Oh my gosh, can you come over here though, please?
If you've seen someone play this game before, what's one that people...
What's one that you haven't seen someone pick?
Because I want to do one that you...
If you've watched someone play this game before...
What is one that you haven't seen someone pick?
What is one that you haven't...
Chess?
Oh, everyone does Luigi.
Okay, we'll do chess.
All right, time for nerd game.
That's a classic.
How about we go for something with a bit of mystery?
You said I could pick whatever I wanted.
Mikey, this is so unfair.
I hate you.
Something with a bit more suspense.
You suck!
You're so...
I can't stand this guy.
Let's try this one.
Whatever this Whispers in the Dark is.
I'm curious about it.
You can pick anything but that.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Maybe something with a bit more suspense.
This is like a murder mystery.
What are you talking about?
It's called Whispers in the Dark!
I cannot stand you.
Wanna get a game?
Just grab whatever catches your eye!
This guy sucks!
Mike!
I'm trying to be on your side here.
I really am.
But you're just being such a jerk.
Jenga.
Is this mysterious enough for you?
Does this have enough air of mystery?
Ah!
What the fuck?
What?
Tower stack.
Nice choice, Harp.
It's been ages since I played this.
Mike really acting like a girlfriend after asking what she wants for dinner.
I can't believe this is the suspense you wanted!
Okay, let's see how steady those hands are.
I hate you.
You're just throwing me out of the game.
Whenever you're ready, Harp.
What the?
Draw the loop.
Huh?
Am I gonna get jumpscared here and like...
What a hunt.
Stop!
Damn, Harp.
Do you practice this in your free time?
Shut up, Mikey.
On a roll here.
It's the first one.
Don't get so excited.
Wait, what about me?
You get to go twice?
What about me?
Boom.
Another perfect move by yours truly.
He's cheating.
Gonna make him lose.
How though?
I'm just gonna keep taking middle pieces.
I feel like there's gonna be a jumpscare here.
They're gonna make you concentrate on doing the circle.
And then he proceeds to say she's playing hard to get.
Way to go, Mike.
You guys, if you were trying to woo someone over, don't be like Mike, okay?
Oh, you scared me.
Didn't think you'd be streaming.
Don't be like Mike.
Too easy, right?
On a roll here.
Why does he get to go twice?
This guy is actually cheating.
This is so messed up.
I want him to lose so badly.
That was close.
I think as long as I do this right, it won't fall, right?
Harp, you're making this game look easy.
This is how it's done, Harp.
Okay, I'm playing the game well, too.
Not just you, all right?
So if I like do this one, you think?
Smooth moves, Harp.
Okay, now you're just taking stuff from the top.
Time to channel my inner architect.
Okay.
Okay, good, good, good.
All right.
Let's do this one.
Let's just...
Whoa, okay, okay, okay.
All right.
Okay.
See, they're gonna make you like be really concentrating on this.
And then they're gonna jump scare you with like a big bang or something, you know?
You're a pro, Harp.
Oh, he's going for the bottom.
He's going for the bottom.
I'm scared.
Oops, tower down.
Let's not dwell on it.
Another game?
Okay.
I guess this game has suspense.
Yeah, I guess so.
So I have to win, I guess.
How do I make him lose?
Oh my gosh, seriously?
But actually, how do I make him lose?
I'm just gonna keep taking the middles.
Is the fish not overcooked yet?
That's a half hour real time.
No, I'm just kidding.
Our little square.
What the?
What do you mean?
I drew it.
You're a pro.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Lose.
Yeah!
Oh, snap.
Didn't expect it to fall like that.
I think I've had enough.
Mike's not the same after working with General X.
That was a fun game, Harp.
You did really well.
All right, the carp should be just about done.
Let's grab some plates.
I'm starving.
Yeah.
Oh, I was like, what's this on the ground?
That's me.
I made a bit of a mess.
I wonder what happens if you do the Ouija board.
Oh, I think our show is about to come on.
You want to watch TV while we eat?
Sure.
I'll have to grab a plate.
He couldn't make the plate for me.
For some guy, for a guy who's interested in me, he's like not very considerate, you know?
Like sometimes, you know, if you're into someone, you like do things for them.
Like when you, you know, you're just like, oh, yeah, I'll make your plate for you.
Or, you know, just stuff like that.
Just small things that like, you know.
The bare-handed reach in the oven is insane.
There's a reason he's your ex.
What?
Mikey's our ex?
Hey, girl, want to get a good dinner?
I'll order for you, force you to play games I want, and at the end, make you pay for dinner.
Girls love that, right?
Wait, how is he our ex?
I don't, I don't think I got that lore.
We had to catch that show on TV while we ate.
Oh, turn it on.
Oh, okay.
Mikey can't do anything.
He's like, turn on the TV for us.
Oh, my God.
With a little bit of vinegar.
Gotta keep that fancy flavor in there.
The next thing we prepare is the mayonnaise.
Why is there always a weird TV show?
I'm gonna try this in a pan with Irish tofu.
I'm not gonna lie, this is gonna taste like shit.
What?
But here you are, anyway, listening to my cooking instructions.
This is the brine of the mayonnaise.
We gotta inject it with a little anesthesia to make sure it doesn't revolt against us.
It gets very angry once it knows we're trying to cook it.
I was done with it.
Harp, that was some damn fine food.
Twice as good since we caught the fish ourselves.
It was all right.
You don't have to rain on my parade, Harp.
It was no Moe's Pizza, but I thought it turned out well.
Hey, anyways.
I need to check my emails real quick.
Left my laptop upstairs.
That little place makes his living room look so cozy.
I'm gonna check my emails real quick.
I thought we were taking a break from work.
It's not work.
I'm just waiting on shipment details for my new DS.
I'll be right back.
All right, I'll clean up here.
I'll keep the TV on just cause I'm scared.
Well, I want it on in the background.
You know?
Okay.
What is going on?
Why is there always weird TV shows in this game?
Our ramen.
We don't see anyone out there, do we?
Okay.
How do I wash the dishes?
Oh, had to get the plates.
Yeah, I have them.
Had to do both of our plates.
Okay, I have them.
Dish washing.
I'm scared.
Something's gonna pop out of the window.
It's forcing me to dish wash.
Oh, Mikey!
Come back downstairs!
No!
I'm scared.
Use some soap!
That was it?
That's it for real?
Okay.
Oh.
Michael J.
Carter.
Oh, that's Mikey.
What?
Is this so rude?
Is this the way to get me in your bedroom, Mikey?
No.
Bye, Grandma.
Stay in your room.
You're not a man.
Okay.
I'm glad she ate that up.
I'm...
Leave.
Yeah, I'm getting out of here.
Bye, Mikey.
I really could just leave.
Okay.
If I really wanted to.
I could just run out of there.
I guess we have to be brave.
Which room is his?
This one?
Don't make sounds.
Walk slow.
Where are you?
Are you in this room?
I'm scared.
Is he there?
Is he the one under the bed?
He just wants me in his bedroom.
This freak!
Gotcha!
You're lucky I didn't break your nose.
My good looks are half my charm, Harp.
Don't mess them up.
I totally got you.
He just wanted me in his bedroom.
This freak!
That was fun, wasn't it?
It's not cool.
Come on.
It was just a joke.
You wanna go for the next round?
Next round?
How about a game of hide and seek?
No!
No, no, no, no, no!
Mikey's such a freak!
I hate this guy!
Who suggests this?
I'll get back to you for this.
Whatever you say, Sydney Harper.
Alright, you're on.
I'll count to ten.
Oh.
No.
I'm hiding in here.
I decided to hide in the basement!
Sydney, you're an idiot.
Sydney, you're so stupid.
I don't wanna play this anymore.
Why don't you go hide now?
I think the person who sent in this story, Sydney Harper, is dumb as hell.
I think she's so stupid.
I think Sydney is an idiot.
And probably deserves everything that's happening to her.
Okay, where am I gonna hide?
In here?
Couldn't open the door.
Oh.
Where do I decide to hide?
Oh!
What?!
Sydney!
Sydney Harper!
You are so stupid!
What?!
How?!
Okay, sorry that I had to mute the game.
It was picking...
So I think it was doing my streaming mic.
Which picks up the music as well.
So I had to like...
Or rather, it picks up the game, not just my voice.
So I had to mute everything.
Aha!
Got you!
That wasn't even a challenge.
That's why I muted my mic and it was still like the bar was still going kinda crazy.
I figured you would be good at this ever... since I never find you in the city.
Maybe.
Maybe you need to look harder.
Alright, my turn to hide now.
You better close your eyes and start counting.
Okay, I'm leaving.
I'm leaving.
Mike was hiding.
Can I get out of here?
I'm not gonna count in here?!
Oh my god.
One Mississippi.
Two Mississippi.
Three Mississippi.
Four Mississippi.
Five Mississippi.
Ten.
I don't like this.
I don't like Mike because he's an asshole to us.
Is he like outside?
Is he in the shed?
You think?
You think he's like out here?
Just take his car and go home?
Yeah, for real.
Anybody in the windows?
You in here?
Why is the music so scary?
What is this?
In the fridge.
Ice zone.
He's in the oven?
I wish.
Oh my god, the bear scared me.
Oh gosh.
Is there gonna be someone actually...
The door is shut.
He's on the deck.
No, he's not.
This is the chiller.
I'm not even saying it.
I'm gonna cancel your DS order.
That's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna cancel it.
You won't have it.
You won't get that DS.
Oh my god.
Oh, got you.
Wait, what?
Hang on, Harp.
I think I hear something upstairs.
See, I'm not talking.
I'm gonna mute myself and you'll see how loud it is still.
I have to mute the game as well.
I'm sorry.
I didn't realize I was using the wrong mic.
Hang on, Harp.
I think I heard something upstairs.
Fool me once, shame on you.
Fool me twice, you're gonna try this again?
Yeah, you're gonna try this again?
No kidding, Sydney.
I really heard something sliding up there.
You didn't hear it?
No.
I swear on my life I heard something.
I see the attic access door is... a door in here.
Why are we just standing here?
What?
Excuse me?
Yeah, you're taller than me.
Why don't you go?
I think my shoulders are too broad to fit through there, Sydney.
But one of us really should look.
Where are you hiding these broad shoulders?
Yeah, you tell him, Sydney.
Seriously, Sydney.
I don't think I would fit through.
Use the step stool behind you and climb up.
I wish every bad thing upon you ever, ever in your life.
Michael.
Michael Carter.
Sorry if your name is Michael Carter in the chat.
What is this?
This guy is the worst ever.
Do not shut the door on me.
Do not do that.
Oh my god.
There's gonna be someone up there and then I'm gonna have to...
Why am I quiet in the closet?
At least I can turn the light on.
I'm too scared.
He lies.
Couldn't reach without...
I'm on the step stool.
No, I'm on it.
Oh my god.
Oh, it's a cat.
Oh, it's just a cat.
In someone else's bed.
And clothes that are drying.
But mostly a cat.
It's just a cat.
And no one else in this corner.
You can pet the cat.
You gonna come with?
Come on.
Thanks for keeping that in the attic.
Come on, cat.
Sydney, are you okay?
What was up there?
Looks like you aren't the only...
pussy cat in the house.
I don't think he liked that.
What do you mean by that?
It was just a cat.
Oh, that's a relief.
I was worried there for a minute.
But why is a cat in the attic?
I think she was hungry.
Oh yeah?
Maybe we can give her one of the carp after.
I come find you again.
What?
I decided to hide in the tool shed...
in the backyard.
Okay...
I guess I decided...
to do that.
I guess that's better than...
the basement.
Okay, we're hiding in the tool shed.
Why are we still...
doing this?
Wait, I should shut the door.
Shouldn't I?
This makes no sense.
I know.
This is so...
bizarre.
This is not what like...
adults do on their...
time off.
Like...
This is so weird.
Do I just chill here?
You do this all...
the time?
Maybe I believe you.
I can't... Oh.
Where is he going?
I think he can see me.
Did you see that?
Did you see there was something...
walking in the house?
Oh, that was subtle.
Oh, Mike!
Mike, I think...
we're in trouble.
Wait, I think my computer's in trouble.
Uh, my wallpaper...
engine is glitching out.
Aha!
There you are!
Wait!
We're not gonna...
say anything about it?
Damn, Harp.
It took...
me a while to figure out you left the house.
Anything worth doing is worth...
doing well.
My turn!
Close those pretty eyes now.
I'm getting tired.
Look, I'll hide in the house.
We're headed back in anyway.
You find me and we'll go to bed.
Nooooooo!
I don't think we'll find Mike.
Where's Nora getting here?
One...
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Oh, stuck on the fishing rod.
Oh, golly.
Gosh, gosh, gosh, gosh.
I don't like this at all.
But there's someone in here!
Oh, that's not what I meant to do.
Please close the door.
I feel nervous.
What's that sound?
Oh, gosh.
Nothing in here, right?
Upstairs?
I know where I need to go!
Okay!
I just don't want to!
What if I keep the door open?
All the doors...
All the doors are open, so...
Are you including that one?
In here?
Oh, my God!
What's going on?
What happened?
Well, hey there!
Why the hell are you in here again?
I'm fixing the faucet.
You got a problem with that?
You should have told us!
Miss, this is my house.
I don't need to check in with you every time I fix something.
I've never seen anyone fix a faucet with a hammer before.
Ooh, you tell him.
You didn't ever fix many faucets yourself, young man!
Rick is kind of sassy.
Fake Rick.
Didn't think so.
I'd imagine you don't know what tools you need.
How long have you been here?
Just got here a couple minutes ago.
He was...
It came from the...
He walked from the right, though, right?
So he was in the basement, I think.
If you heard anything before that, it must have been that old lady.
Remember?
Um...
Look, we need to go to bed now.
You asking me to leave, miss?
Yes!
We're paying $100 a night to be here!
You're being too polite.
We rented this house and would like to have it to ourselves.
I...
We don't really want to have to call law enforcement.
Mike, please.
Actually, no.
Let Mike handle this.
Ain't no cops in Woodbury, son.
That is an absolute lie.
I've seen like three cop cars drive by the house.
I almost ran into one!
What are you talking about?
There's no cops in Woodbury.
You think they're going to arrest the homeowner for fixing the faucet?
I was just doing some work.
If you can't handle that, it's your problem.
Not mine.
You know what?
If you folks don't like me fixing the faucet, I'll leave you to it.
Yeah, let us fix it.
We don't need this anyway.
The tap didn't work.
Wow, it really is broken.
Okay.
Don't let the door hit you on the way out.
Ricky?
That's right.
Good night.
It actually is broken.
Maybe this guy is legit.
Is that it?
After locking the door, we debated what to do.
We agreed that there was something off about Rick from the start.
It seemed like he enjoyed making excuses to come over unannounced.
He wants to catch us naked.
In the end, we decided Rick was weird but probably harmless.
We attributed his behavior to an extreme lack of social awareness.
I think he broke it.
Maybe he broke it?
Maybe.
Look, we already drove all the way out here.
Let's just enjoy ourselves, Mike said.
But by this time, I was feeling really tired.
I decided to get some rest.
11.39 pm.
No!
Hello?
What's going on?
What's that sound?
I still have the flashlight.
Could not go back to sleep with those knocks at my door.
Hello?
Who is it?
Oh.
Not even the flashlight worked.
Harp?
Are you still awake?
He's knocking on my door.
My extreme lack of social awareness.
Like someone else I know.
Do you mind if I come in?
I'd like to talk about something.
At 4 in the morning?
Didn't the...
It said 4 in the morning, right?
Or am I crazy?
Sure?
Yeah, 4.30.
The storm is starting to get really bad.
I can hardly see the truck in the driveway.
I hate that Nora is out there all alone.
She'll be just fine, Sydney.
Don't worry.
I'm here to keep you safe.
That's nice of you, Mike.
Okay.
Hey, it's no problem at all.
Guys are supposed to watch over people they care about, right?
What are you talking about?
What a day, huh?
This wasn't exactly how I thought our getaway was going to be.
I'm going to go, Sydney.
It's been a strange day.
Can you believe that guy?
He just keeps wandering around the house like he owns the place.
Yeah, he does own the place.
You know exactly what I meant, Sydney.
He shouldn't just barge in the place whenever he wants.
We rented the damn house.
I mean, the guy is probably harmless, but I'm frustrated.
You've also been a little difficult to deal with.
Maybe I shouldn't provoke him.
I don't know.
You're right, Sydney.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
Why don't you come sit by me, Sydney?
Mikey?
I don't want to sit on the bed.
Mikey, I don't want to sit on the bed.
Leaving me already, Sydney?
I don't want to sit on the bed.
I don't want to sit on
the bed.
I don't want to sit on the bed.
Mikey, I thought you were awkward, but I was on your side for the long time, Mikey.
No, no, no.
Harp, you know, I've missed this.
I've missed this.
Us just talking.
It's been too long.
Nobody's talking.
Do you think Nora didn't come on purpose?
Do you think Nora is actually coming?
You know, you don't have to sleep alone tonight if you don't want to.
Would you be doing this if Nora was here?
What?
Oh!
You act like you don't remember our trip to Oregon.
Uh-oh.
I remember it being pretty awkward.
It didn't start out awkward, though.
Mike, we had a lot to drink.
Things happened.
They sure did.
I'm hoping maybe they can happen again.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, Mike.
I don't know what to say.
You just let me worry about the details, Sydney.
Oh!
What's, what's, what's...
Guys?
I think I'm about 70 miles away from Woodbury and my stinking tire just blew out.
It's snowing and I'm on the side of the road on Highway 11 near Killington.
There's a sign by the side of the road.
It's hard to see.
I think it says Kent Pond.
The snow is like half a foot deep and I can't get the lug nuts off the tire.
I hate to ask, but can you two come get me?
Okay!
S.O.S.
We are on our way.
Bibigirl, don't you worry.
We're coming right now, right on over.
We gotta go save Nora.
Right?
What a timing, huh?
I guess we can't leave Nora stranded.
No, we can't.
We better get ready.
No, Sydney.
You stay here and get some sleep.
There's no sense in both of us freezing our asses off.
What?
No!
Can I have an option to say no?
Mikey, please!
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
You're in pajamas and I'm still dressed.
You just settle in and I'll go help Nora.
That's really nice, Mike!
Can we please remember that there is a guy who keeps barging into our home?
I always like doing nice things for you, Sydney.
Let's split up, gang!
No!
This is the worst idea!
Please!
We'll finish talking about this later, okay?
Get some good rest and stay warm.
Oh!
No!
I'm coming with.
The door's not opening.
And my flashlight's gone.
I'm coming with.
It's freezing cold outside.
It's okay.
I'm in my pajamas.
It's fine.
There's no sense in both of us freezing our asses off.
Please, no, Mikey!
I won't let you go!
Please!
I'm sorry!
Joy, thank you for the Hakosufa!
No, Mikey!
Mikey, please!
I love this truck!
Please!
No!
Are you sure it's safe to drive in this weather?
Oh, why don't you get some rest while I'm gone?
Don't worry, I've driven and worse.
Besides, Nora's probably freaking out more than you right now.
No!
She's not!
Look, make sure you take care of yourself, alright?
Lock all the doors!
Yes!
You sound like my dad.
Can you blame me?
Before I go, how about a hug?
I mean, just in case you're asleep when I get back.
I kinda need one right now.
Where's my hug at?
Not now, Mike.
Sweet dreams!
Get some sleep, Cindy!
Mikey, please!
Don't leave!
Please!
Let's go get her.
I was keen on getting some sleep until Mike and Nora arrived.
Where's my flashlight?
Where's the flashlight?
Wait, actually, where's the flashlight?
Oh my god.
I told myself things would get better if I could just get some rest.
Nora always knew how to cheer me up and I needed it more by the minute.
With her arriving soon, I decided to rest in the meantime.
1239 AM!
Who's at the door?
Doorbell?
Someone was at the front door.
Where's my flashlight?
Wait, for real?
It's gone.
Where did I drop it last?
Do you guys remember?
It was in the bedroom, wasn't it?
The realization that someone was outside this late at night was horrible.
Alert the hiker!
I saw you there, my friend.
Please open the door.
I'm freezing to death out here.
How did he find us?
Is the back door locked?
I don't know how to lock it.
I can only know how to open it.
What do I do?
Get the gun?
What gun?
There's a gun?
Can I get a knife?
I can't see anything.
If I open the door, do I die?
Do you have any idea what time it is?
Look friend, I know it ain't ideal banging on your door in the middle of the night, but I'm in a bad spot here.
I was counting on a ride from some friends, but they are running behind and won't be here for another...
About two more hours!
You can sit on the porch while you wait.
I'm not even going to say anything.
The weather outside is getting pretty bad.
I was hoping you'd be a friend and let me come inside to warm up.
Just until my friends get here.
I'm sorry, but I can't help you.
Come on now, my friend.
If you were caught out in this blizzard, I'd give you a warm place to wait it out.
You're not coming in, end of story.
Oh gosh, he's going to get angry.
He's going to get mad.
He's going to get angry.
Are you...
plucking kidding me?
You're going to let me freeze to death out here?
I should have known you'd be a big...
A big B?
Here is you.
We're back at the pizza joint.
You think I didn't see you and your little boyfriend fishing in the creek?
That was him!
Oh my gosh, that was him in the background.
I figured maybe you'd give me a chance this time.
But looks like you're still...
unkind.
Get out or I'll call the cops.
Ain't no cops around here.
Why are there not cops around here?
Why do you guys keep saying that?
Speaking of...
Wait, did I hear...
Do I hear like a...
like a...
sound?
Like the breaker or something?
I don't see your fella's truck out here either.
I'm dialing 911 now.
Fine.
Suit yourself.
But the lights are working.
I think.
Actually I can't tell.
If I turn this on...
Okay.
What do I do?
Where do I...
But let me tell you something.
You'll get what's coming...
Why did the door open?
to you for leaving me out here?
Karma's a bitch, my friend.
Why did that door open?
Hello?
The man at the door seemed...
irrelevant compared to how tired I was.
Stop!
Are you kidding me?
Sydney.
I couldn't keep my eyes open.
I had to get some sleep.
Yeah, the light's on here.
This is...
Zero survival instinct.
At all.
Zero survival instincts.
Couldn't go to bed with the bedroom door wide open.
Oh my god.
What's going on?
What's
going on?
I might have to turn...
off the sound.
So if I have to do that, I'm really sorry.
Rick, I'm sorry to bother you again, but can you come back over?
There's someone...
They're Subwood.
We met driving down here.
He was banging on the door and started threatening me.
I'm pretty scared.
I think I hear him moving around outside the house.
Could you please come look since you live so close?
Watch, he's gonna be like...
Sydney, I'm...
I'm out of the state.
I can't come at all.
SOS, that's me!
That's me!
Hello?
What do I do?
Me too, too, too, too.
Hello?
Wait, it wasn't this...
Oh, he was throwing stuff at it.
It wasn't this dirty before, right?
Okay.
I'm scared.
There's a snowball.
Open the door, miss.
It's me.
It's who?
Oh!
He's got his hammer!
Are they in cahoots?
Wait, Rick is so fast.
Um...
Open door...
Oh gosh, this is giving me a tummy ache.
This is giving me a tummy ache.
Oh, hello!
What the hell is going on here?
Did you see anyone outside?
I might have seen something.
Could have been anyone.
Or no one at all.
What does that mean?
Explain the situation.
Yeah, I came as quickly as I could.
I wouldn't worry about him anymore.
Wait, is that the...
The screaming we heard?
Okay.
Oh my god.
By the way, where's your friend?
The guy who was with you earlier?
He...
He should be back soon.
Rickrolled?
So you're all alone here right now, huh?
Yeah, but my friends will be back soon.
Wait, why did we say yeah?
Are we stupid?
I think we're really stupid.
I think we're dumb.
I think we're an idiot.
Where are you going?
You should be leaving!
You're just gonna make yourself comfortable?
I think I'm gonna wait outside for my friends.
I still didn't feel safe opening the door.
Why do you feel safer with this guy in your room?
No way.
Thank you for the gift.
Thank you so much.
This girl...
I can't stand Sydney.
She's the enemy.
Oh.
There was another thing that popped up but it went away fast.
Storms like this bring out all kinds of folks.
Not all of them know when to stay away.
Huh?
What does that mean?
Oh no!
Here he comes!
Come back over?
What do you mean?
I live in Burlington.
I haven't been to the rental in weeks!
Oh my gosh, Rick.
The
game is...
No!
There's an invisible...
My
god!
The game is trying to kill us!
No!
Everything okay, miss?
Yeah.
Awful late for texting, isn't it?
Who you talking to?
You are not Rick, are you?
That's my friends.
They're almost here.
Is that so?
Yeah.
Thanks for coming by, though.
I'll be fine now.
You can head back if...
No, don't say if you want!
I should head back now?
You could leave the home!
Are you sure about that?
Yeah.
I just overreacted.
Maybe I should stick around.
Make sure everything's really okay.
None of these options are gonna lead to a good answer.
None of these options are gonna lead to a good answer!
Oh my god!
And I'm stuck!
If I need to run, I'm trapped, for real.
I'm just gonna say, you need to leave.
What did you just say?
Confront.
This is my fucking house.
I will leave when I want to.
What do you want?
I want what's mine.
This house.
And you!
You're trespassing.
Get out of here before I call the...
He's gonna say there's no cops here.
You need to leave right now.
I don't think so.
If anyone's leaving this house, it will be one of us.
You know what?
I'll go.
Actually, great idea.
Let me leave.
I'll just walk out the front door.
I won't come back.
Let me go.
You know?
If one of us needs to leave, I'll go.
What is he doing?
Ah!
Why are you so slow?
I don't know.
What?
Oh, whoa.
Whoa, hold on.
Hold on.
The game just like...
Oh my gosh.
There we go.
Okay.
And it like turned.
I had it like here.
There we go.
What just happened?
I hope it auto-saved.
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're good.
Okay, so...
What?
So while he's hanging out there...
Um...
So don't leave.
Maybe I... I don't want to go upstairs.
I think he'll notice me walking... Do I go into the basement and hide in the little closet?
Or maybe I go into the attic because he won't be able to get in there, right?
I think...
I think hiding in the attic because even if...
If, uh... What's his name?
Or... Wait.
Oh.
Maybe it doesn't matter.
Oh, are we sure he doesn't live in the walls?
I guess that's true.
I guess we go hide in that little storage wall then, right?
Okay.
Basement is closer.
True, true, true, true, true.
He kind of was like, What are you doing?
Oh gosh, okay.
We got to do all this again.
La, la, la, la, la!
Let's just like, uh...
Let's just...
Make it go fast.
It came as quickly as it could.
Wouldn't worry about him.
Uh... Rick.
Nothing personal.
We got Rickrolled for real.
Mike went to go pick up another friend.
Hmm...
Why is he doing...
Why does he act like this?
Here, I'm gonna preempt...
I'm gonna...
Get ready.
You know?
We'll have it get ready, right?
Oh!
It says something there.
But it goes by too fast.
Storms like this bring out all kinds of folks.
And then...
Come back.
Come back over.
Oh my god!
Everything okay?
Yeah, oh wait.
You're not Rick, are you?
What did you just say?
Um...
You need to leave.
I don't think so.
If anyone's leaving this house...
It will be one of us.
Okay.
I will probably have to mute...
Uh, the audio in the game.
So I'm sorry that it will be muted.
And me as well.
Because otherwise it just picks up...
My mic is too sensitive, I guess.
I think...
I think for that part...
I have to run into the closet.
The attic.
Oh my gosh!
It did it again!
I think I have to go to the closet.
For that part.
Sorry for your ears.
I was like...
Basically the phone went off...
And then he got me and I had to run.
So...
Hide under the bed?
I don't know if it would have let me.
I think I have to go to the closet.
And then be quiet there.
So...
I was just...
Sorry if I have to keep the audio off.
Gosh, I don't want to keep losing because...
Oh!
Hiding in the basement.
Perfect.
Audio, be gone!
No!
Okay, I have to go...
Oh my gosh!
They called me!
And then he heard me!
Okay.
It's like a...
It's like a different thing every time.
Nora, you bitch!
Yeah, he heard the phone.
So yeah, he gonna...
Okay, so...
Now can we go from the attic?
No, we have to do hiding in the basement again!
Okay, so I have to go into the attic.
As soon as... and...
They call me and I go hide in the attic maybe.
I don't know.
No!
My gosh!
You are muted too.
Yeah, I have to be!
Because...
My mic is too sensitive.
It doesn't have a noise gate.
My interface.
So it like...
Picks up everything.
Okay.
Go downstairs.
He said open the door.
Oh!
He's called 911.
Just got done talking to other guests on the phone.
I called 911.
Oh!
Do I just go?
I guess it's okay?
Can I take you with me?
Hehehe
It's safe?
Is it actually?
Okay, I'm gonna go.
Oh!
I can't sprint.
I have to be very slow.
Who's playing music?
What's that noise?
Hello!
I have my hands up!
Oh, I think he left out the background.
Jesus!
Oh my god!
Everything that happened after Mike had left.
Rick had called the cops.
The storm had quieted down by the time they arrived.
How convenient.
And of course, the man was nowhere to be seen.
On our drive back, the whole night played over and over in my head.
We think that the man we saw secretly lived in that cabin when it wasn't being used.
And planned on robbing us during our stay.
But cops seemed to think that there was more intent behind this man's actions aside from just robbing us.
What happened to the other guy?
Why is everybody so sussy in this town?
Rick asked me what the man looked like and after that, he didn't ask any more questions.
We think he knew more than he was letting on.
But in the end, he gave us a full refund.
I would hope so.
Lesson learned.
Don't ever leave the office.
Oh, survivor!
Wait.
What is that implying?
Why is he looking in the basement?
What's that implying, huh?
Oh, Lily Peach!
Yeah, you guys were right.
In that case, so die.
HAHAHAHA Just done with that.
Well...
It's the police!
OK, never mind.
Are they gonna find that other guy's body?
And this is so happy sounding.
La la la la la la la la la la la...
The', da da da da da da da da da, da da, da da da, da da da, da da, da da da, da da da da...
We made it!
Yeah, what happened to the hiker?
Thanks for playing Fears to Fathom.
This is why hotels over Airbnb.
I wonder... I don't remember the other ones having a credit like that.
I wonder if... Oh, hold on.
I see... I have to do this.
I have to do this every time.
Or else I'm like all messed up.
Yeah!
Bent up staying in an Airbnb next month for the first time.
What should I do?
Don't let any Ricks inside.
Even if your own name is Rick.
Don't do it.
Refund, refund, refund.
Don't get Rickrolled.
Don't play hide and seek in Jenga.
The hide and seek was so wild.
This guy is just like, hey, I'm interested in you.
Do you want to play hide and seek?
I wonder whatever happened with the sender and Mikey, huh?
He overstepped his boundaries a little bit.
I thought it was going to be a switcheroo and he was going to be the bad guy, you know?
But in the end, it was fine, I guess.
Just remember, if you think you have zero Riz, you could be worse.
You could be Mike.
Yeah.
But did anyone ever feed the cat?
I feel like if this guy was living in the attic and he has a cat, he can't be so bad, right?
You can't have a cat and be bad.
I don't think.
He killed you with a hammer.
I guess that's true.
He killed you multiple times.
Well, what if he was trying to use my body to feed the cat?
To feed the cat.
I've got a bell, but thank you for the stream.
Thank you.
I'm terrified of being Mike.
I'm fairly certain cats are most evil geniuses.
No.
For Rick, it was indeed hammer time.
He could just buy cat food.
Cats eat a little human as a treat?
Yeah.
Some eat mice.
Some eat humans.
I don't know.
I'm just sayin'.
But also, maybe, I guess he lived in the basement instead.
So who was feeding the cat if he lived in the basement?
Because he probably was in that room that was like, dude, no guests enter.
If you check the room in the basement, you see he was living down there and how he got into the house.
Wait, how do you check it?
Wait, how do you actually see it?
Thank you for the five gifts and thank you!
Walk?
Okay, smart aleck.
Probably when he's out and about.
I think you check at the reveal part.
Oh, like instead of hiding in the... in the um...
What's it called?
But it said we couldn't get the door open.
I think we can only get the door open when he opens it, right?
I don't know.
But this is fine.
I hope you guys liked it.
I hope you guys were feared to freakdom.
And yeah, this is a good time.
If they don't continue the series, I hope they do maybe other things similar.
But if they do continue this series, then you can count on me.
I'm playing them, baby!
So it was fun.
Yeah.
Fear to freak.
IT was fun.
Great stream event.
And another note.
I was wondering, have you finished Bunny Garden offline?
Uh, no.
I haven't.
Two!
Should I?
He's a killer, but has a cat.
Mint.
Okay, he's a yellow flag.
Sorry, can't stop me laughing now.
The blonde girl from Bunny Garden is getting an android.
I did see that, actually.
It's kind of crazy how, like, crazy, like, popular Bunny Garden popped off.
Pretty funny.
But...
Lethal Company-ass music.
I wanna be playing Lethal Company!
I love Lethal Company.
So fun.
Apparently there's, like, a new monster in it.
Maybe I should organize something for Lethal Company.
Maybe I should find some people to play with.
But yeah.
Um, I'm gonna go...
Uh, my dinner... I only had, like, a little bit, so I'm gonna go get another scoop.
Of mac and cheese.
And I'm gonna go to bed.
I've been going to bed...
Last night I went to bed at 9 PM and I woke up this morning at, like, 8 AM.
I got so much sleep.
Thanks for the fun stream!
Thank you!
Oh!
While I was hiding!
Um...
Joy, thank you for the Hakasupa!
And, uh...
Who was the other one?
Uh...
Daniel, thank you!
You're welcome!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
While I was being sneaky and unable to react.
I don't know if you could tell me...
Or if you could tell that my voice...
Or my... I was, like, lipping it.
I was like...
Thank you!
I don't know if you could tell.
Early in the stream there was a mention of a nut allergy.
And it gave me war flashbacks to second grade.
When a girl who had a nut allergy caused the cafeteria to stop serving PB&J.
And I was so mad!
That's not her fault!
When was there a nut allergy mentioned?
It's her fault!
I'm not gonna lie though, I would be pretty sad too.
Especially because, uh...
Uh...
The elementary school I went to had Uncrustables.
And I loved those.
If I couldn't have one of those, I'd be so sad.
Not the PB&J.
What are those?
Uncrustables?
They're... They're pre-made PB&J sandwiches without the crust.
So it's exactly what the name is.
Why can't they be crusted?
I think some people just don't like the crust.
Do you guys like the crust or do you dislike the crust?
Even as a kid I ate the crust.
I never knew... What's wrong with the crust?
Why are people such crust aunties?
I don't get it.
I love the crust.
Crust auntie here.
But I've never wasted crust.
That's...
Right!
You're so good!
Good, good.
That's so...
So good of you.
Crusty gang.
Yeah!
The crust!
Yes!
The crust is just kind of dry and bland, IMO.
I guess.
But you know, you have all the stuff on the sandwich to help you with eating the crust.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Crust gang.
Okay, guys.
Anyway.
Thank you so much!
I hope you guys enjoyed being a little feared.
And a little fathomed.
And I will see you tomorrow.
I have a collab, I think.
I'm pretty sure it's still happening.
And...
Yeah.
Okay.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, it's still happening.
I have a collab.
And I'm playing Pico Park 2 with a bunch of other people.
So that will be...
Something.
We'll see how that happens.
Arigatou!
Thanks for watching the stream.
I'll see you guys later.
Ittarashai!
Otsumito!
I have a POV?
Yeah.
I'll be streaming my POV, of course.
Bye bye!
Hai, todokete.
Oh, Sinam's like, Thank you!
Bye bye!
Otsumito!
Ittarashai!
Bye bye!
See you!
Bye!