Why does it seem so quiet?
I don't know why the music seems so different than before.
Welcome back!
Ladies and gentlemen!
Hello everybody!
I'm Mint!
Welcome!
Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello!
Minty fresh being a member again!
Thank you!
Thank you guys!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Hello, hello, hello!
Good morning, Minta!
Good morning!
Hello, hello.
Why is it so low?
If I turn it up... I don't remember it being that high.
I don't know.
I have no idea.
I didn't adjust the music.
Weird.
Anyway.
Thank you, thank you!
Thank you!
Oh, they're real.
Sharing my birthday cash!
Please don't sing for me, though.
It'll embarrass me.
I wouldn't embarrass you, Slice Saber.
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, dear Slice Saber!
That's you!
Slice Saber!
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday to you!
One more
time!
How old are you now?
Slice Saber, how old are you now?
You're not embarrassed, right?
Oh, yeah!
One more time!
You're almost a ghost.
You're almost like Minta.
Yeah!
Um...
Die without regrets.
Or you'll be a ghost.
Asking for the three digits.
What's your credit card number?
And the three digits on the back.
Plus the three digits on the back.
And don't forget the zip code.
Plus
the three digits on the back.
Where did you go to school?
And your first pet's name?
And what was your childhood...
Uh...
Childhood...
Sweetheart?
And your mother's maiden name?
What?
You must've been born with a dress without nee,
IU's date and birth date.
You must've been born with a dress without nee, IU's date and birth date.
And you're like a ghost!
You probably wasn't able to remember.
But you are just weird.
So, let's go back!
Now, I have to run!
And now apologies for my bad speaking skills.
Anyway...
It's Slice Saber's birthday and everyone is singing to him.
They're turning 37.
No way.
Oh my gosh.
Peng, you just...
Happy birthday.
Don't get me anymore.
Damn, I'm only 34.
Well, soon you can come back and watch this in 3 years and it will be accurate.
Namae, oh, she's trying to commit credit card fraud and going on a main cafe spree.
I would never.
Anyways, you guys, welcome back to Ghost Trick.
This is our third time playing, baby.
And last time we ended, it was so crazy.
Someone stole my credit card info, so I had to cancel the card I used to pay for membership in YouTube trying to charge me for 8 times in one day.
Was it... did YouTube steal your card?
Oh my gosh.
That's crazy.
I'm so sorry.
I've had my... I've had my card stolen only once.
And I... I know... I knew that it was stolen.
Because I went to...
I went to get some breakfast before work.
And my card declined.
And I checked my bank account.
And I was negative.
And I was like, that shouldn't have happened.
And they... they had...
The person had ordered like a bajillion pizzas.
So... yeah.
It was not great.
But you know...
Luckily, it only happened once.
Was it... was it Matara?
I wouldn't... I wouldn't let her get away with it.
You know?
Man, the best party ever.
Yeah, on my dime.
But honestly, I say a bajillion.
But like, he couldn't even order that many pizzas.
Because I did not have that much in my bank account.
Why are you stealing from some poor ghost like me?
Huh?
Thank you, thank you.
Kiss.
Stolen money is the best money.
I don't know about that.
Pizza party fun.
Yippee!
Spent all my money on seven pizzas.
Mine got stolen once and they spent 700 bucks on an office depot.
What are they buying?
Maybe they thought that you were like loaning them money to start their business.
You know what I mean?
It was a small loan, right?
Okay.
No more talking about stolen credit cards.
No more credit card business talk.
Okay.
We're gonna talk about ghosts and tricks.
I just had my card denied while shopping out of town because of suspicious purchases.
But someone used my card in California to buy guns and somehow that was approved.
Oh my gosh, wait.
That was, that has happened to me.
Because, because when my card was stolen, it was a different state.
But I have gone to other places before and had my card declined because they thought it was suspicious.
So weird.
But it's the story time.
We left off on a cliffhanger last time we played where we discovered the guy that Lin was been trying to get in contact at the police station.
And it's a special police station of people with special crimes.
And the guy that Lin is wanting to help is getting executed tonight in like an hour or something.
So we have to like, we have to kind of skedaddle.
Hopefully the audio will be okay.
If not, if it's too quiet during, I can adjust it as well.
So just let me know.
And I will.
Oh, five minutes.
Wasn't it five?
It was.
Actually, I think you guys are right.
I'm being kind of gracious.
It was five minutes.
Costco pizza slice supply drop.
Yummy.
Five minutes until he fries.
He's turning.
Getting being turned into fries.
I'm a soup.
Casual breed.
Thanks for one month.
Thank you.
Thank you guys for returning all the members returning.
Thank you so much.
Really, really appreciate it.
Can't believe it's been a month.
Oh my gosh.
Well, not a month since I've been back.
I guess a little over a month that I've since I've been back.
Yeah.
I kind of wanted to do something a little bit special.
So I decided to do the English karaoke on Wednesday.
So it's not much, but I have been cooking.
I have been cooking a lot of stuff.
Oh, my gosh.
Like, well, actually, most of everything that I've been cooking has been for my anniversary, which will be in July, which I'm like, oh, my God.
Can I?
Is it okay if I say that it's my four year anniversary?
Because technically, I didn't even get to celebrate my first year anniversary.
What?
But it would be kind of cool to say that it's a four year anniversary.
Because four is a spooky number.
Technically, we never even got to celebrate one anniversary.
So we will celebrate.
And I have some fun things that I'm planning for the anniversary.
I was like, oh, my gosh, I got to start working on stuff now.
Honestly.
I was like, sheesh.
One in four.
Actually, I was kind of like thinking of doing like that.
But I was like, if I do like one zero or not zero, one like one slash four or one in four, people might get confused.
I don't know.
Hey, I'm Minto.
Hope your day is good.
Work was pretty crazy.
But I'm getting hyped for this gym session with my Kamiyoshi is the perfect voice for it.
Yeah, let's go.
Gym time.
Then four in one.
Oh, yeah.
V has come too.
But wouldn't it be one V?
One V has come one.
Timer pause when you went to heaven.
Them's the rules.
You're basically a newer streamer.
No.
Oh, no.
Let's do all four anniversaries.
Yeah.
Four is one.
V is two.
Okay.
So next year I can say V has come too.
Yeah.
But anyway.
I'm still figuring it out.
We'll figure it out.
That joke is going to be so funny next year.
Back to you.
Back to V-ing.
Okay.
Let's not waste any more time.
Sorry.
I was like so busy though.
Because I was like, okay, I'm wasting more time.
Because like, oh my gosh, I woke up this morning and I was, I was emailing so many people and I was, I was, I was, I was doing phone calls.
I have phone calls and during the phone calls, I was, I mean, this is like not stuff that you'll ever see.
It was stuff that I know.
It was stuff that I needed to get done.
But during phone calls and meetings, I was, I was also messaging people about other stuff.
Oh, I was so busy this morning.
We will always be here for you.
You nerd.
Fun for days.
Miss V-ing.
Thank you, Josh.
I love for the pink.
Thank you.
Yeah.
But I was like, I was really, I've been really like kind of kicking butt to get stuff done.
And like, um, one thing.
I was, I've been in charge of is getting all the artwork for the Patreon for the postcards.
And so, um, it's been a lot of like back and forth between so many different artists and like they'll send something and I'll be like, and then I'll like respond and set or sent to Matara and be like, do you want any changes and this and that?
And like, I'm talking to like six different artists at once.
So I'm like, wow.
And then I'm also ordering the postcards.
And I'm also like, oh, and I'm also, uh, I'm having a busy weekend this weekend, which is why I'm having to take off a couple days.
And so I'm just like, wow, I gotta get ready for that.
I gotta get to do this.
I gotta record the podcast.
I gotta email this person back.
And like people are emailing me for like events and conventions and stuff.
So I'm just like, okay.
Or like other things that seem kind of cool.
So I'm just like, wow, I gotta email this person back.
So there's like been so much going on behind the scenes that I like wish I could share more of.
But I have been trying to work hard to do lots of stuff.
It's a lot to deal with.
Yeah, but it's so much fun.
It's actually so much fun.
I think if I, well actually not that I think.
The day, whenever I decide to not be a streamer anymore.
One thing that I really love is just like general planning.
And like I would love to like, I don't know.
Like maybe one day be like a manager to like a Vtuber or something.
Project manager mint.
Yeah.
It's fun.
I used to plan a bunch of stuff.
Even before Vtubers.
Vtubing.
And even as a Vtuber, I love planning stuff.
So, but trying to plan things and also...
Yeah.
Starting your own Vtuber company with gacha and idols.
How many directions did you plan things in?
What do you mean?
Um...
Hey, I helped with planning some stuff at like conventions.
It's probably the easiest way to say it.
So...
I got that reference.
Happy one month Ms. Fartome.
Thank you.
Poppy!
Thanks for the pink!
I couldn't make it for the last two streams.
But I'm so glad I can finally watch my fav streamer...
My fav Vtuber stream my fav game live.
Hope you enjoy the ride mint.
Thank you!
Thanks for the pink!
It's a much cooler ambition than working in a grocery store.
Hey.
Look, I didn't know.
I didn't know!
Bye.
Um...
What was I gonna say?
Oh!
Oh my gosh, you guys.
Yesterday...
I saw my grandma...
And my mom...
For Mother's Day.
And um...
Sorry, we'll get to the game eventually.
Holy cow.
But um...
I gifted my mom...
Um...
Uh...
This thing.
Let me see if I can get it.
Let me see if I can get a picture...
Say what it is.
Hold on.
Uh...
Okay.
Oh, I have to do this too.
Oh my gosh.
Okay.
Um...
So my mom is really into like meditating and relaxing and stuff like that.
And I found this thing.
And I got it on sale.
Thank God.
Because it was really expensive.
But it's called...
This...
It's called...
The Drift.
And it's like...
It's like...
It's like a...
You know those...
Those zen gardens?
Where you like draw like...
Draw in the sand?
It's like one of those.
But it's...
It's a...
It's...
You put a metal ball on it.
And it...
Kansai Drift.
Oh.
Yeah.
And like...
And then you...
You...
You put...
You get an app and you...
Beep, beep, beep, beep.
And then it draws a design on the sand for you.
And it's like...
Oh my gosh.
At one point, we were all just standing there.
In silence like staring at it.
And just like in silence.
We were all like watching it draw in the sand.
And I had to leave before my grandma.
Because my grandma went to sleep.
I had to leave before she got to see it.
But then my mom texted me a picture of my grandma.
And she was just...
Let me see.
She...
She sent me a picture of my grandma just staring at it.
She said, Thank you so much for the gift you bought me.
Grandma and I are sitting here in the quiet, just mesmerized by it.
It's a picture of my grandma just staring at this thing.
Like so...
Locked on.
It's so funny too because my grandma likes to wear headbands.
She always has, even when I was like a young ghost.
And the headband she was wearing this time was a black headband.
It was like around her head.
And I was like, Grandma, you got infinite ammo.
But she wouldn't stop talking about...
She wouldn't stop talking.
She would be like, She would be like...
My grandma is at an old person's home, right?
But she loves...
Usually I feel like old people don't like the old people's home.
But my grandma is obsessed with this old person's home.
She loves the old people's home.
She's like...
She's like, Don't ever take me out.
And we're like, We're not.
My mom is just like, Yup.
Because my grandma will be like...
She's like, I go up and down those halls.
And I keep everybody in check.
Yesterday she was just like, I...
You know, recently fights have been breaking out with the old people.
And with the doctors.
And she...
She just like always calls it one flew over the cuckoo's nest.
Every time I see her she's like, Have you seen one flew over the cuckoo's nest?
That's this place.
And I'm in charge.
And I'm like, Yeah, I know grandma.
Elderly uprising.
Well, she was just like, There was a fight that broke out.
And...
There was a fight that broke out.
And I went in there.
I went in there.
And I said, Hey, you fuckers cut it out.
Because I need that doctor.
Because I have to shit.
My grandma.
What do you mean?
What do you mean by that?
Grandma, mint is living the dream.
It's true.
My grandma man.
My grandma.
She said that she...
Oh, my grandma.
I'm trying to think of what else she's...
So, she kept talking...
She's like...
The whole time I was driving with her, she wouldn't stop talking about her explosive diarrhea.
I don't think I should share that with you guys so much.
Is your grandma a big boss or something?
My grandma doesn't hold back about anything.
Yeah, let's not share it.
Is your grandma Johnny?
Oh grandma...
Okay, shall we play the game?
Sorry, I just thought of that because I was just like...
I kind of want to get the thing now for me too.
So I can sit in the dark or sit in silence just mesmerized by this little ball drawing in the sand.
It's really mesmerizing though.
But they're really expensive.
I bought it because...
It was a combined like...
Mother's gay...
Mother's...
Mother's Day...
Birthday...
Did I say Mother's gay?
Your mom's what?
It was a Mother's Day birthday gift.
Okay...
Let's continue the game.
We're playing the game now.
Oh my goodness.
Okay, we have five minutes until a person is dead you guys.
We can't be laughing.
We can't be...
Search gay...
What is wrong with me?
First search gay and now Mother's gay.
You really can't talk your way...
Okay, no I can talk my way out of it because...
I combined day with gift, okay?
This is actually how my brain works.
Everything just is like...
You take all the words of a sentence and you go...
You go...
You take all the words and then you go...
And you smash it all together.
Okay?
Mother's gay?
Yeah, they are.
Both of them.
How do you know?
Hahaha...
I don't...
The other day...
The other day I was...
This is...
What did I type?
Hold on.
I was messaging someone...
And...
And they were like...
Do you have a deadline when you want this finished?
And I was like...
Whenever you have fun...
Because...
In my brain...
I typed have...
And so my brain just said...
Have fun!
So...
But I meant have time...
And I was like...
No!
Not fun time!
Don't have fun!
My brain is so weird...
Hahaha...
Enjoy your meal!
You too!
And...
It's just because...
Like I'll finish something...
I'll...
Like...
I'm so afraid to type on stream because of it...
Because I know like...
Ouch!
Ugh...
Sorry, my eye is bothering me...
I know that if I...
Type...
If there's a certain phrase that I'm typing...
My brain will...
It like auto finishes...
And it's just...
It's just...
Hahaha...
It's so stupid...
Because I type things that I'm like...
Why did I type that?
I don't mean have fun at all...
Hahaha...
Don't have fun...
Not very nice there...
Hahaha...
30 minutes and we've made it to the file select...
We're cruising tonight guys...
No!
We're starting...
We're starting right now...
Okay, everybody comfy!
Let's start the game...
Hahaha...
And please I can't breathe...
Stop being hilarious...
For like one second...
Hahaha...
Her brain is too far in the future...
I swear I'm...
I'm always clowning...
Alright...
Someone's dying you guys...
10.55 PM...
I went to try and rescue prisoner D99...
Even under ordinary circumstances...
That prison has a strange atmosphere...
But this time there's something even stranger about it...
Hey, I happened to enjoy it...
Enjoy the ghost yapping...
Thank you...
I'm calm...
I'm normal...
An execution...
With my memory gone...
I don't have a clear image of what that is in my head...
But even I can sense the strong feeling of foreboding that hangs in the air...
You don't know what an execution is?
Maybe I'm too late?
No!
Oh!
He's...
He's grooving...
Is it really quiet?
I'm really...
Hold on...
I even turned up the sound...
Okay...
Well...
I'll turn it to 9...
The sound is fine...
It's pretty quiet on my...
It sounds quiet even to me...
Hmm...
I'll turn it up just a little bit...
Okay...
So...
How's it going?
With the generator?
In the basement?
Why is...
Oh...
They're trying to fix it now...
It's gonna take a while...
They said...
They haven't even gotten the internal phone there back up yet...
Waiting for the inevitable...
Mint apologizes after being 3 hours late to her stream to explain that she was watching Circles in Sand stream...
Hey...
It's okay now...
I just hope...
The rowdies...
Don't rush the guard room...
Oh...
We don't have any rowdies here...
And what's more...
The one who committed the most atrocious crime isn't even here anymore at all...
Wait...
What?
You promised...
Not to talk...
About that...
Look...
Would you not get off with that weird flipping and flopping around?
I can't stand looking at it...
If you don't stop...
I just might have to...
How...
I'm not around you...
Where's the fanfic of these two?
This...
This is a glorious dance...
That's been passed down...
In my family for generations...
When you don't know...
What else to do...
Dance...
We call it...
The panic dance...
This is special detention...
Calling from the death chamber...
The internal phone is finally back up...
Oh...
It's pitch black down here though...
Until they get the generator going again...
How's it going up there?
The phone's been ringing off the hook from headquarters...
The death chamber...
Oh boy...
We can't let the existence of this prison become known to the outside world...
We'll have to round up the prisoners somehow...
I can't...
Is Bailey dancing?
Yep.
You should see him.
Wow!
Thank you for the 20 GIFs!
Wait...
Who is gifted?
Kita!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Take a video of it.
We can all watch it together when we're done.
Once the generator is back up, I'll record it with the security camera.
This is so messed up.
Someone is about to die and you're like...
Record that guy dancing.
And then we'll watch it after the guy is dead.
Oh my god!
I'm going...
The generator is still not up?
I can't keep this up much longer!
Believe me.
Nobody is asking you to.
Why don't you just stop?
Oh wait, this is the guy that has the accent, right?
He has a southern accent.
Will you dance instead then?
Are you kidding me?
Somebody has to do it!
Oh, he's going faster.
If that somebody is me, I'll keep dancing until I drop!
Oh my god, he's going even faster!
Despite how it looks, the situation seems pretty serious.
Bailey's dance is certainly intriguing.
Thank you for being awesome and as cool as heck!
Thank you, Kyory!
Thank you for one month!
But that telephone call that came in is even more interesting.
The man said he was calling from the death chamber, right?
Now that I have the extension number, I should go check it out!
Oh!
It's a trick?
Internal?
Special detention?
Was it that one?
Oh!
I assume the death chamber is...
Whoa!
It's so dark.
This is not good.
Not good at all.
Fortnite emote the panic away.
Yeah, I feel like a ghost is going to show up any minute now!
Now, wouldn't that be silly?
What?
B-b-b-ghost?
Hey, come on.
Show some respect.
There's a dead man here!
Wait, what?
That's right.
Me.
Wait, hold on.
That's right.
Me.
Mito.
Hey, Sissel.
I was dead before you, okay?
This is my shtick.
But whoo!
I never saw that one coming, did you?
Wait, so did they like electrocute him and it was so powerful?
It took out the power?
Who could have?
Anyway, the generator is going to be fixed soon, so I guess we hang tight.
Okay.
There's a dead man?
Who?
I guess darkness doesn't really exist in the ghost world.
Even without light, I can still see what's going on.
I can use the ghost world to help me find that generator.
A whole month already.
Thank you!
Lever.
Power supply.
Emergency light.
Water drop?
Oh, that will probably help me get down.
Wait, is that the dead man up there?
Uh oh.
Oh no, it's a spoon.
Wait!
This is the guy who's been crawling out this whole time!
Oh my god.
Wait, where did the water drop go?
This must be it, right?
Oh jeez.
Where did that wrench go?
Without it, I can't tighten the last bolt on the generator.
Work like a cave!
Or like a ghost.
This appears to be some kind of control panel.
I might be able to operate it.
But it doesn't seem to be responding.
It's too dark to really tell though.
I guess the first thing I need to do is to restore that generator.
So the wrench...
Hello!
Thank you!
I can't hold on much longer.
A line from the game just dug up a childhood...
child memory of the cliffhanger guy from Between the Lions.
Okay.
Huh?
Cliffhanger.
Cliffhanger guy.
I don't know.
I don't know that one.
Actually, I don't think so.
Cliffhanger.
It says Between the Lions.
It's Between the Lions.
That's why he's called Cliffhanger.
The real ones in chat give me.
I've seen these things before.
Some kind of tool for turning things.
It's leaning up against the wall.
If I knock it over, I wonder if he'll notice.
Darn, it's too heavy.
It won't budge.
Let's see.
What's this?
It's a light.
Maybe...
I can barely...
Dang.
Okay.
Let's wait for the droplet to form again.
Now if I go and drop...
Now I'm in the bucket.
I can't do anything in the bucket.
Toolbox.
Let's open it up.
Oh!
Oh, he saw it.
Oh, hey, there it is.
These guys remind me so much of like the...
What's it called?
The Genome Soldiers.
There.
Done.
Oh!
Yippie!
Wait, is this a good thing that we...
Is it a...
Oh!
What?
Wait, so if the generator is off and all the cells just open?
I don't think that seems very...
Um...
Now the lights are back on.
But what happened here?
The answer is still shrouded in darkness.
Better see if I can pick up on some more information.
Can't seem to shake this bad feeling I've got.
Me too, though.
And then we'll...
Go to here.
This one.
Wait.
Oh my gosh!
The timing has to be...
Pitch perfect!
Okay.
There we go.
What if I lower this lever?
Didn't do anything.
Did someone say the door to darkness?
Hey, do you think this execution was really the right thing to do?
What the heck are you saying?
I mean, I know this country has the death penalty.
But how many years has it been since we used this chair?
What do you mean, was?
Uh oh.
Yeah, I don't know.
It had quite a bit of dust and dirt on it.
I bet that's what happened.
All that debris dropped on the floor.
Well, I think it was divine retribution.
Don't be stupid!
The prisoner wanted to be executed, you know?
He's dead!
Inspector Jowd!
I guess I was too late.
So when are they gonna pick up his body?
They'll be sending over a car from the public cemetery pretty soon!
After we hand over the body and clean up the mortuary, we're done!
Yeah, okay.
Are we the baddies?
No!
No, no.
What else are they saying?
This chair scares me.
I don't want to repair it or get anywhere near it.
Why is there so much water?
Who knows when it's gonna blow... I knew it blew up!
Or let loose with the juice!
Just mint is the baddie, I think?
No, no, no.
Weirdest mortuary assistant DLC?
I'm not gonna lie, when they said mortuary, I also thought of mortuary assistant.
And then I remembered that is the scariest game I've ever played in my entire afterlife.
It's so scary!
Oh my gosh.
Loose with the juice.
Yikes.
Shut up, man.
Accidents can happen with anything after all.
But let's just get this thing fixed.
Come on.
If I'm executed by an accident, I'm gonna come back and haunt you.
I can make that happen.
Haunt me?
Why me?
Sounds like a pretty dangerous chair.
Hmm, a chair that gives shocks.
Can I use that somehow?
Oh, are you gonna kill them?
Oh my gosh, this little...
Kind of insane.
Wait, how do I get over there?
Uh...
Oh, the drips.
Wait, I can't reach.
Let's see what he says.
So Detective Jowd has already been executed.
Looks like there was a reason for that bad feeling I was getting.
But that's okay.
This isn't a big problem for me.
But if the body is taken from the mortuary, that'll be bad.
I have to use my ghost tricks to save him before that happens.
Yeah, but how do I get over there?
My arm's too short.
Um... lever!
Does it do anything?
Oh, there's a phone in there.
Nobody probably called from in there though.
I don't think I have the extension.
Is he napping?
What's he doing up there?
Hmm...
Let's see.
Where is the water?
The water... from there...
Hmm...
He's taking a little nap, you guys.
I guess we'll go back to him.
Oh, wait.
Power destroyed.
Oh.
What do I say here?
This guy seems to be taking...
Oh, he's actually taking a nap!
I doubt my paltry powers are enough to wake him.
Rest in peace, curry lover.
One month already, I love you and your grandma.
Ah, thanks!
It's kind of spooky when a ghost says it.
Can I...
Can I make it over...
No, there's no way.
Ah...
We have to ring the bell.
We have to go back and ring the bell so he goes home.
Uh...
Lower...
Row.
Time here still appears to be like a caged animal.
The only difference is I don't see any of the inmates.
Oh, wait.
It was the...
Wait.
And of course our death row inmate isn't here either.
Yeah, because he's dead.
What are you talking about?
Did the curry lover ever find his curry?
My time will soon be locked away from me as well.
I can't waste what I have left.
I better get going.
Trick time!
Yeah, so stop talking, buddy.
Oh...
Uh...
Wait.
Emergency button.
I better not set off the emergency alarm right now.
The inside of my head is already in a state of emergency as it is.
Okay.
Never mind.
Uh...
We'll go upstairs?
Oh my gosh.
Ugh.
All the...
Sometimes messes with my head.
No...
Meow.
My arm is too short.
Wait.
Can we go through the toilet?
Or...
Flash?
No...
Hmm...
Let's try going back to the guard room, maybe.
And seeing what's going on there.
Oh.
This panic dance has been passed down in our family for generations.
There's just one problem with it.
It's just...
There's only one more thing that we need to do.
Hey!
Go down there and look at the floor!
I like this guard.
I don't remember his name, but I like his perpetual smirk.
G-g-g-ghost!
Thanks for one month!
Guess it's hard for you to know when to stop talking too.
Wait,
this TV is now...
Was it always facing... wasn't it facing us before?
Or maybe not.
What's
going on here?
Honk!
Did they change seats?
Yeah, they did.
It's the panic dance.
Jump out of your pants.
We're panicking.
We're panicking over something.
Something has gone wrong.
What could it be?
And it deals with me!
The panic dance.
It's the panic dance.
Take off your pants.
When you panic, you get hot.
And that's why you don't need pants.
The panic dance.
It's the panic dance.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The panic dance.
What could be wrong?
I don't know.
But I feel really concerned.
The panic dance.
It's the panic dance.
Anyway.
How do
I get to the spoon guy?
I...
Where are my pants?
They're gone.
Were you panicking?
I'm in severe distress.
I'm overthinking it.
Or am I?
Does it not have to do with him?
I didn't mean to go that far.
Back.
Thanks for the pants.
Oh, the jeans.
Do I go to the bucket?
And do something?
No.
Doodle bob?
What do you mean doodle bob?
No, wait.
How am I supposed to get out?
There we go.
Manipulate.
This appears to be some kind of control panel.
I might be able to operate it.
I'll give it a try.
Beep boop.
Oh!
Oh my god.
I'm gonna kill them.
Some lamps came on.
Not sure what that means.
Maybe that changed the situation though.
I think they're about to die.
Oh wait.
Let's turn on the lever.
Let's kill these guys.
Execution!
Okay.
Hahaha.
I just got a shock.
You are shock.
There we go.
Bucket.
Oh, dang it.
Fast!
Oh, I have to...
Okay, okay.
Fast!
Shock, shock, shock.
And I'm gonna rock that piece.
Spooky!
Son of a...
And then I'm gonna rock the cart.
And then I'm gonna go back.
And here.
Oh, we're inside.
Same thing here.
Looks like this just...
This is just an internal phone too.
Doesn't call outside.
So the only places I can go with this telephone are...
Other phones within the building that I've already possessed.
Okay.
Spooky cart.
Flower vase.
Person's body.
Hey, can you hear me?
Where am I?
Oh, he's...
He's not alive.
He's awake!
This is the ghost world.
The land of the dead.
Detective Joud.
Who is that?
Is that me?
Oh boy, not you too.
This is getting old.
Thanks for the super child!
Guess I'll just give the usual explanation.
The dead lose their memories.
Oh, so I'm dead, am I?
I didn't realize that.
It's you guys, right there.
It's you, it's you.
You're looking a little thin.
You need to eat more.
That's why you can't remember anything right now.
That's fine with me.
Huh?
I don't like a messy room.
But I hate cleaning up even more.
Not having my memories is a welcome thing.
Now I don't have to have as much...
Trash to take out.
Memories are like trash?
Now that I'm dead...
What do I need with memories?
And things I don't need are just trash.
Not to me.
I need your memories.
Besides...
I promised Lin I'd try to stop your execution.
Lin?
It looks like I still have a few...
Bits and pieces of garbage left lying around.
Why does he call them garbage?
I remember now.
About Lin, Jowd, and the execution?
What about you?
Who are you?
You only remember those things because I told you.
Sir Jowdington right there.
I'm Sissel.
I'm looking for my memory.
Or trash as you call it.
Sissel...
Does my name ring a bell?
I think you know me.
Sorry...
It must not have been a very big piece of trash to me.
I wanna let you guys know...
That you're all big pieces of trash to me.
Okay?
You're all...
Big pieces of trash.
Thanks man.
Hahaha
I'm honored.
That's alright.
I guess you'll find out when you get your memory back.
But for now...
I'd like you to come back with me.
Back to four minutes before your execution.
This is gonna be so traumatic.
Oh my god.
It's not just a regular death.
It's an execution.
It's the nicest thing anyone's ever said about me.
Yeah.
This is the past?
Four minutes before my death?
That's right.
Sorry.
You'll get to see your own execution.
Don't smile and say that.
And then we're gonna change your fate.
But first, can I ask you a question?
Wait, four minutes before this guy is dead?
He's not even in the chair yet?
They got it done so quickly.
Lynn told you, didn't she?
About what I did?
Yeah, she did.
Well actually, we found out from a newspaper.
Then is it really the right thing to do?
To save a guy like me?
I don't know.
But Lynn believes it is.
Okay, let's get started.
Oh!
Jinkies!
Oh no!
It's stuck!
It's clogged!
Uh-oh.
This is what happens when...
This is what happens when you...
flush stuff other than...
poop down the toilet.
Wait, what did he say?
I was too busy thinking about poop.
It's time.
Thank you for the food.
That's a lot of ketchup.
No!
Don't you do it too!
What was in the trash can...
that you couldn't flush it?
Or that you couldn't throw away your napkin?
Uh-oh.
Oh my god.
They're all the same.
Sorry.
I keep yawning.
So the time's finally here, huh?
Too busy thinking about poop.
Eating choices?
Yeah.
I wonder how many years it's been.
The last time, you weren't even here yet.
I never thought I'd have to...
attend an execution.
But you know, I wonder why the justice minister...
suddenly signed the order.
There's definitely something up with that.
Hey, come on!
Let's just focus on our work.
This guy is such a doubter.
I love him.
Vivicore!
Thanks for the...
thank you!
Yeah, alright.
Ten.
Left, right, left, right.
Down, down.
Prisoner D99!
It's time!
Let's go!
Alright, men.
I'm ready.
Sorry to have to go through this...
Oh, sorry you have to go through this...
unpleasant experience.
What?
No!
We uh...
Oh well.
I guess it's all about collecting...
experiences.
For you...
and for me.
Oh my god...
Troy!
Thanks for the 20 gifted!
Thank you so much!
Thank you, thank you.
Can't get over his Chad face.
This guy is such a Chad face.
I think the Chad meme was based off of him.
Oh my god...
Prepare to test!
Throw the switch!
Wait, it explodes?
And then...
he dies?
So this is an execution, huh?
Seems to me there's got to be...
a safer way to do it.
It must be nice to have...
no memory like that.
It makes things more interesting.
I envy you.
I really do.
It's no laughing matter to me.
This guy is so awesome.
That was an example of a...
failed execution.
Although the outcome was the same.
Fail?
They haven't...
carried out an execution in a long time.
Wait, what if...
it was one of the guards?
We're going to switch...
the guard position and...
the Chad position.
They dragged that old chair out...
from under some mothballs.
And I guess it had a short.
So I guess that means that...
if I can stop the explosion...
I don't know about that.
Then I'd be executed as planned.
And I'd still wind up...
just as dead.
So what should I do?
Beats me.
You're the one who came to save me.
You figure it out.
He's not making this easy.
I mean, can you blame him?
I actually agree with him.
Rewind...
time.
Trick time.
Who you calling?
How's it going down there?
We just finished setting up the chair.
We're all prepared.
I see.
It's time.
Please bring in the prisoner.
But that chair!
It hasn't been used in a long time.
What if...
There's nothing we can do now.
It's time.
Alright.
I'll send the guards to his cell.
I'll have them call when they get into position.
Okay, we go there.
Did he just say, do it yourself?
Basically.
Oh my god, this guy is drunk.
I have this strange feeling of uneasiness.
I must dance it out.
How about you?
How do you feel?
I feel chubby and jittery.
And I can't sit still.
I feel like I might start dancing at any minute.
If you're gonna dance, let me know.
I'll get the video camera ready.
Nobody will listen to my concerns.
Concerns, huh?
So he's worried.
That man is always worried about something.
Whatever he's worried about, it always comes true without fail.
Hmm.
Listen to me.
That chair is dangerous.
I know, Bailey.
That's why I don't advise you to sit on it.
No, no, no.
That's not what I mean.
Machines like that are very sensitive to dust.
If the guys throw the switch and the chair shorts out, there might be a huge explosion down there in that death chamber.
Oh my god, he called the whole thing.
Oh, come on.
Nothing's gonna happen.
Besides, even if on the off chance it does blow up, we're way up here.
We'll be fine.
I know.
Why don't we go and test it out first?
No way.
I don't wanna get blown up.
You go by yourself.
So this spot would be safe even if it does blow up, eh?
What is it?
You have a new look in your eye.
Why can't I stop yawning?
If the switch in the death chamber is thrown, the chair will blow up.
The chair will blow up?
That's right.
And if the chair blows up, the execution can't be carried out.
True.
It only stands to reason.
And, if there's nobody in the death chamber when the chair explodes, nobody will die.
Precisely.
Very nice, Sissel.
You've hit upon some excellent points there.
Okay, I'm starting to see a plan now.
Sophie!
How do we have nobody in there?
Time is passing!
Oh my gosh, oh my gosh, oh my gosh!
Um...
Let's dial...
Oh yes, that's right, we can't use the phone lines.
Ow!
I can only move over phone lines in the past when it's in use.
Sadly, this applies to the internal extensions as well.
Get everyone up there.
Exactly!
Everybody has to come up here.
Or...
Or, or, or, or, or...
We somehow pull the switch early.
I think.
Getting the chair short out...
Why can't I stop yawning?
Hold on.
I'm gonna eat a cookie.
Cookie time, it's cookie time.
Maybe some sugar will help me.
Eat the ghost.
Ah!
I dropped my controller.
In the past world, I can't just use the phone lines whenever I want.
These guards seem to be in a fog.
I doubt they'll be using the phone much.
Maybe I need to start over?
Wait, no!
What?
What do you mean?
Wait, no!
Maybe I do need to start over.
I'm stuck here.
I thought he said he would call.
He said he would call when it's time for the guy to go there.
I'm just sorry I didn't get to see Bailey's famous dancing.
Getting the chair to short out when nobody's around it.
The plan is starting to solidify in my mind.
But I better find a different path next time.
From the beginning.
Did he say he would call?
I thought he did say he would call.
Hold back.
I think we need to attach ourselves to...
This guy, maybe.
Got it!
Oh.
Alright then.
Four minutes from now.
This chair will short out and explode and you'll die.
It's very sad.
If I stop the explosion, you'll be executed and you'll still die.
Sorry I was ever born.
I have to protect you from the explosion and stop the execution.
The key to this whole thing must be this chair.
I apologize for all your trouble.
Could you stop with the insincere comments?
Wait am I stuck here?
Oh!
Oh here we go.
Now it's time to go get the prisoner.
I'm going to bring the prisoner to you now.
Got it.
I feel like we have to try every spot.
Unless they call one more time.
But maybe they don't.
They might not call one more time.
I don't know.
I have no idea.
We can get...
We can go to the paper.
Okay.
Paper.
Open up the note.
Let it free.
Oh!
Alright!
My jam grooved off the clock.
Now get down there to Sausage Head.
Go!
Okay.
Oh wait!
Wait!
That was terrifying.
Oh god he is so gross.
Okay.
What is this for?
In the present world, four minutes into the future, Sausage Head was lying passed out in the tunnel.
Oh I wonder if the shock got him.
Not knowing about the execution, he must have kept digging and digging.
And the guards didn't notice he was gone?
So I guess Curry Man's future has now changed a bit.
Fate changed!
Okay.
Oh!
Uh...
Oh no I can't reach it.
But we need to get to...
Oh yes!
We ring this.
Because he needs to go back downstairs, right?
He needs to go back...
Why is he so freaky?
He needs to...
We need to go with him back in there.
Because that's how we get into the other room.
And he licks it.
Okay.
Attached to the spoon.
Yeah we're gonna use him.
We're gonna use him.
Come on!
Hurry it up!
Oh never mind.
I thought he would go back inside.
Um...
Just kidding.
But that's okay.
We can now go to his place.
To you.
And um...
The napkin.
What did he do with the napkin again?
Oh he also flushed the napkin!
He also flushed the napkin.
I think we have to be the napkin.
And then we...
When we get flushed...
We can then go downstairs.
Probably.
After looking in the trash can.
Yeah what's in there?
Open?
Oh!
Wait a second!
Woah woah woah!
Wait!
How do we get the circle?
I might have to restart.
Oh he noticed it's full.
This thing is as full as I am.
Oh no!
It needed to be!
Okay.
We know though.
We know now.
If he gets it...
I'm actually curious.
If he grabs this...
Will we be able to do it again?
I wonder.
We know now.
It's too late?
Is it because he's not eating anymore?
Oh shoot!
There we go.
I almost missed my chance.
Okay never mind.
It's too late!
We gotta restart!
He's not eating anymore!
He's just sitting there.
It's so sad.
Okay let's restart.
After fate change.
Okay.
That's okay.
Now...
Uh...
Your soup!
Do you have a favorite instant curry brand?
I've only ever bought Vermont curry.
But I feel like maybe I should look at others.
P.S.
prisons are the best.
Open all doors that the power goes out.
So that if there's a fire, it won't burn all the inmates.
Oh!
Which has happened before.
There has been fires in...
What was it?
Alcatraz?
Oh my gosh.
I wanna go to Alcatraz.
So badly.
I wanna go.
But the one day that...
Me and Matara can maybe go.
They weren't...
They were all full.
I just dropped my drink.
Hold on.
I don't know.
Oh man.
I think it's fine.
I just dropped the straw side.
Right onto the floor though.
So I can't drink anymore of it.
That's fine.
But yeah.
I really wanna go.
I've never been.
I've never been to San Francisco before.
But because of Off-Kai.
I can go.
I will be able to visit.
So I was like I wanna visit Alcatraz.
But I can't.
I can't go.
I don't know.
We might maybe try a different time.
If there's any openings.
Or if the place is open too.
But yeah.
I wanna go.
It closes really early?
Like 3pm?
No, no, no, no.
We looked at the website.
They have...
We were gonna try for...
They have night time tours as well.
And we were gonna try.
Even though she was scared.
I was like come on.
It's probably fine.
And I'm a ghost.
Like what?
I'm gonna run into another ghost?
Ring-a-ling-a-ling.
Ring-a-ling.
Oh my god.
Did anyone else play Dragalia?
Ring-a-ling.
The way he like slurps his spoon.
It's so weird.
Oh my gosh.
I have to be pretty...
I have to go pretty quickly with this.
I think.
Huh?
Oh Will.
I missed Dragalia.
Me too.
I missed Dragalia so much.
Alright.
What is the order here?
Maybe.
I might have to restart one more time.
But he looks like he's gonna have to restart.
He has to be holding his...
I think one...
Okay.
I think it's the timing of when he's holding the napkin over the trash can.
But before he opens it.
Right?
Yeah.
It needs the O.
It needs...
Now!
Yeah!
Wow.
Let me possess the napkin.
Perfect timing.
Ring-a-ling!
Time is passing.
Okay.
And now we're gonna possess the spoon.
Once he brings us up.
Can I reach it now?
No.
Not yet.
Time is passing.
Oh!
Spoon!
Ta-da!
Okay.
Very nice.
This is the most lax prison I've ever seen.
Ever.
Okay.
Alright.
Hurry up please!
Hurry up!
Oh!
Eww!
Oh God!
Okay.
Come on.
Crawl!
Crawl man!
Okay.
Sorry.
That guy was still in the hole but...
What just happened?
We just stopped to death.
The power's down throughout the whole facility!
No way!
If the power's down that means...
All the cell bars open automatically!
Damn it.
The internal phones aren't working either.
State of emergency!
Now the execution can't be carried out.
And your life is saved.
Crisis averted.
You're a pretty daring guy.
I really enjoyed myself.
And I think I learned a thing or two as well.
About what?
By the way.
Is it true what the guard said?
Cell bars open automatically?
Jailbreak!
Yep.
It's true.
It's a little drawback to the system.
If the entire facility blacks out...
The locks are released.
For the prisoners' safety.
But nobody thought it would actually ever happen.
So in other words...
Now is the time to escape if you're gonna.
Anyway, we managed to stop the execution.
Let's get back to the present.
You're still not out of the woods yet.
And now that guy's gonna get his memories back.
He can tell us who we are.
Oh my gosh.
Let me give you one piece of advice.
What's that?
When we get back to the present.
Head for the spoon.
Okay.
Spoon?
You'll see when we get back, Sissel.
Okay.
Time to go to the spoon.
Spoon, spoon, spoon.
Oh my gosh.
He wants to spoon me.
Now the execution can't be carried out.
Detective Jao is safe for the moment.
A new present has been born.
However...
Jao still isn't safe from execution, of course.
I guess I still have a job to do.
Help a death row inmate escape from prison.
Oh yeah!
Yippee!
We cleared the 1055 to 1109 challenge.
Challenge!
Jao taken by fate.
Nice!
That one wasn't so bad.
This level coming up is the worst level in the game?
Uh oh.
Okay.
I'm mentally preparing myself.
Yeah, that chapter was pretty short.
Now I'm back in the present.
And it's completely shrouded in darkness.
I can't see it.
But I can feel the tension in the air.
It's a state of emergency.
Yeah, it's not good.
You'll see why very quickly.
It's really rough.
Okay.
Thanks guys for the warning.
And that's only natural.
With the power failure, all of the cell bars opened automatically.
Plus now a death row inmate is loose in the darkness.
I did what I promised Lin.
I stopped the execution.
But that condemned criminal is now in just as much danger as before.
Okay.
To the spoon.
What are these guys?
Oh, these guys are working on it.
Let's go to the spoon.
Okay.
I'm here.
The detective told me to head for the spoon when I got back to the present.
So here I am.
And he is asleep.
Like before.
Oh!
He's awake!
Oh god.
He's going to...
The bell!
Better get back!
Oh god.
He's so scary.
This guy.
Blahblahblahblahblahblahblah!
Woo!
I'm back!
But first I have to find him.
Oh gosh.
Is this like a sneaking mission?
But... in this game?
Oh my god!
It's prisoner C-74!
Secure the prisoner!
Oh no!
I see.
It looks like there are hunters in this darkness!
I hope they haven't found Detective Joud.
Oh no!
Where is he?
He's not here.
Oh!
What's that red light?
Looks like the hunter's eyes glow red.
Oh no!
Doesn't look like escape is going to be easy.
Round!
Oh my god!
Look at him!
Wow!
He's just a ball!
Let's talk to him.
Ah, there you are.
I was wondering what I was going to do.
Are you the one who made that toilet bell ring?
That's right.
I still had another napkin lying around.
Thanks to that I managed to make it here.
How did you know how to do that?
I learned a few things about your ghost tricks during our time together.
Peak form.
I love him.
They certainly can be very useful powers.
But at times, not so much.
I knew that if the internal phones weren't working, you'd be trapped in the death chamber area.
So I quickly came up with an alternative route.
How did he know about the guy digging underneath this prison though?
Does everyone just know that?
A route that made use of Sausage Head's spoon in my napkin.
Wow, this detective is good.
He's pretty good.
Next time you praise me, go ahead and say it out loud.
He can read my thoughts.
I forgot.
Oh yeah, he did see me in there.
Right.
That's true.
Anyway, it looks like it's time for a strategy meeting.
An escape strategy, huh?
This could be interesting.
Let's do it.
Escape strategy.
Let's make sure we're both clear.
The key to my escape is this darkness.
Once the basement power supply is restored, escape will be impossible.
Okay, okay.
Thanks for the super chat, Vampire.
Thank you.
So we move under cover of darkness, huh?
I know I won't have much trouble with that.
But I'm afraid I won't be able to see.
So you'll have to lead the way.
Lead the way?
Cecil sometimes like...
Cecil sometimes kind of like Snake.
Lead the way.
Once you find a safe spot for me to move to, I want you to give me a signal.
Anchor, thanks for the super chat.
Okay, fine.
But how?
Second floor basement.
Lead the way.
The dead don't have voices.
Even if they did, we have to be quiet.
Don't you worry about that.
I have an idea.
Let's just try it and you'll see how it works.
This detective likes to just dive right into things.
Even more than Lin does.
I wonder if they're...
Related.
If they find me, I imagine they'll shoot first and ask questions later.
Did they shoot Sausage Head?
But if I die again, we can just start over, right?
He says cheerfully.
Prison secured.
I don't know if you know it or not, but this is a special prison.
There aren't any dangerous criminals here.
Except for me, that is.
Yes, I did hear something about it being a special place.
Sausage Man is fine.
He was in his cell.
Oh, so if you leave the cell, they'll shoot.
And because of the special status, they're not prepared at all for emergencies.
They have four timid security guards at most.
You would think that would make them...
The fact that it's a special prison would make them more...
Like, prepared.
It's meant real.
It's me!
I think I saw some hunters lurking in the darkness, though.
Those are the guards.
They're wearing night vision goggles.
I wonder...
Night vision goggles...
Who...
Who needs night vision goggles?
You don't even need those.
What stupid...
What a stupid invest...
What a stupid thing to try...
Night vision goggles?
Like, who even...
Night vision goggles.
They're special glasses that let you see in the dark.
Very handy things.
If I enter their field of vision, it's all over.
So it's all about staying out of the guards' line of sight, eh?
Make sure you guide me to safe spots.
Like, under the table.
Okay.
Now about that signal I want you to give me.
Yeah, how am I supposed to do it?
I've already been dead once.
I don't know if it's because of that or what, but...
I can sense your powers now.
Ooh!
You what?
For example, you're in the bunk right now, aren't you?
Yeah?
I guess you have a sixth sense.
I think it's more like a detective sense.
That doesn't sound right somehow.
Anyway, the details don't matter.
Do you see this R here?
Yes.
Where did that come from?
Do you see this R button?
Yes.
Here?
Snake, turn off the console.
I mean, Raiden.
Turn off the...
R button?
Let's use it as our signal.
How will that work?
If you press R, I'll sense it.
Then I'll move to wherever you are.
So, for example...
A spoon?
If you move to that spoon and press R...
I'll run to the spoon.
Simple, right?
All right.
Fine.
Let's start our escape plan.
Just make sure you guide me to safe spots, Cecil.
Ooh!
So...
Oh, okay.
What is...
What is this part?
Oh, bulletproof vest.
Okay.
All right.
So, if I move here...
And if I press R...
After...
After this...
After he turns around...
Wait!
Go under the table!
What are you doing?
He's gonna...
See you.
I was like, he's gonna...
Check out what the enemy is doing.
For now...
How about just aiming for the neighboring cell?
We can't hurry too much in this darkness.
Let's take it slow.
I tried!
Chowed?
Chowed!
Oh, okay.
Okay.
What is this?
Hatch mechanism.
Interesting.
Very interesting.
There's another guy here.
Interesting.
Okay.
Wait.
So, if I like go here...
I'm like, hey, come up here.
Wait.
Where...
Where's the end goal?
Is my other thing.
Are we trying to...
He's in the neighboring cell.
So...
I feel like if I try to get him over to the toilet, it's too far.
Unless...
Unless I take him to the toilet.
Unless I tell him to go all the way over here.
Go.
Run.
Oh.
Nice.
Okay.
So...
Oh!
There's another guy.
Where'd you come from?
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
I have to...
I have to wait for him to come back.
He's going up the stairs?
Oh.
I can't see.
He's going...
All the way up.
Look at him go.
He's going down the stairs?
He's...
Back to where we are?
Okay.
Let's follow him.
What do we have?
What is that?
Oh, that's the cover of the toilet.
Let's see where he's going.
Let's see where he goes, actually.
Is there anything over here?
There's...
What the...
Is that a guy lying down?
Oh, my God.
What?
He scared me.
What is that?
Oh, there's a guy in between.
What's this?
Oh.
Empty can.
Hmm.
This area under the stairs is a blind spot for the guards.
They won't find him here.
This spot is safe.
Oh.
Okay.
We have to wait for him to...
Will he...
Oh, gosh.
We'll have to start from the very beginning, though, if we...
Okay.
Will he, like, walk behind the guards, you know?
So, if I'm like, go...
Go...
Now.
Ow!
Wait.
How...
How do you see him?
Okay.
What just happened?
Apparently, there was a hunter lurking in the ceiling.
Could you do something about him?
It's so dark, I can't even see the bullet coming.
He dodged the bullet if it wasn't dark?
Okay.
Wait.
Is this the very beginning?
Oh, man.
Okay.
Close.
I think...
Oh, wait.
Open.
I'm gonna...
I'm going to open this up.
I'm gonna open up this little mechanism in the meantime, because I feel like we're gonna need it later.
Unless...
Did me opening that open all the other ones?
Hmm.
I don't think so.
Mint is so cute.
What do you mean?
Go.
Run.
Okay.
Very good.
All right.
Now, this guy is walking back.
Oh, my gosh.
What if I had gone?
And...
Oh.
No.
Wait.
Come back.
I
forgot.
I need to attach myself to him.
Whoopsie.
It's okay.
I can drink my water.
Whenever I make oatmeal, I make it in a mug.
And then afterwards, I make tea in the same mug.
And so, it's like kind of an oatmeal...
Oatmeal.
Like...
Because I like oat milk.
So, it's like an oatmeal drink.
It's so good.
Mug meal.
It's actually so yummy.
I see the vision.
Yeah.
So, it's like an oat.
It becomes like an oat-flavored tea.
What a weirdo.
You're the weirdo.
How do I...
Oh.
How do I attach...
How do I get to the hatch?
Maybe now.
Oh.
A valve.
Open?
Wait.
Oop.
Oh, now they're both walking.
Hello?
Okay, wait.
Wait, this doesn't...
Oh, I wish I could like drop this on his head but it's a valve.
Wait.
This doesn't seem very good.
Oh, wait.
Oh, I don't know.
Wait...
Does he just walk back up and close it again or...
Hold on, let's see what happens here.
What's he doing?
He's going all the way up!
I'm stuck here, actually.
If I close this, does he lay back down?
Uh, whoopsie!
Oh, this one's tough though.
The timing on this is really rough.
I think...
Oh, he fell again!
He fell again.
Okay.
Maybe...
Now.
Oh my god, that was so close!
Holy cow, that was so close!
Oh gosh.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, man.
We're gonna close that up so he stops dropping.
Come on, I can't reach you!
Come a little closer.
Get close to Minto.
What the...
Oh, I was like, hello?
Oh, wait.
Oh, I followed the wrong guy!
I don't...
Stop!
Close.
Oh, some...
I can't close this right now.
Somebody's falling through it.
Okay, now we can close it.
Where should we go next though?
Where can he hide next?
Wastebasket.
Toilet.
There's like nothing here.
Hmm.
Okay, he should come over here.
Not yet.
Like, here?
Okay, okay, okay.
There we go.
Wait, where do I go?
This part is tricky.
The valve seems important.
But the valve...
I can't do any ghost trick to it.
He just stops right there?
Oh no, he keeps going, he keeps going.
Where are we going?
Are you kidding me?
Oh boy.
No way.
No way!
No way, I have to go all the way?
Over there?
No...
Is that real?
Yes way?
Chat, is this real?
There's nothing...
Unless...
Unless the valve...
Unless... maybe if he hides in the ceiling, will they still see him?
Maybe they won't see him if he hides in the ceiling.
Okay, I'm gonna have to wait for somebody to come rescue me from the bunk.
Come rescue me from the bunk, please.
Keep going.
Walk.
Come here, boy.
Yeah.
That's right.
You know what?
It's better to try that than trying nothing at all.
Let's go to the valve.
And just sit in here, wondering.
You know?
If we die, we just get here again.
If we die, we just...
trick our way back.
Oh wait.
Uh...
Trick...
Oh!
No, no, no, no!
You invited me to come get you.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Not bad.
My bad.
Don't do that.
Okay.
Here.
Okay, he's gonna go down.
And while he's walking away...
He's walking that way.
He's gonna go...
Okay.
Go, go, go!
What do you want me to climb up into the ceiling?
I think I can manage that.
But as things stand, I don't have a...
Oh no!
Could you open that hatch and create an entry point for me?
Oh!
You lost your chance!
Oh wait!
Maybe actually this guy will be stuck on this side.
What?
Okay.
Okay, now...
Wait.
He's turning around!
Oh no!
He's going to get seen.
Is this guy going to fall through the floor?
I should have... Yeah, no time.
Mmm... This guy's going to fall through the floor.
There we go.
Okay.
Let's close the hatch.
Wait, they're both going up now.
Oh, but one will continue going up and one will turn around.
Okay.
Alright, as soon as he's passed.
Thank you!
As soon as he's passed.
Oh gosh, the timing on this is like...
Why do you have to stop right there, man?
There's no time!
Made some delicious al dente parmesan and cheddar cheese pasta with broccoli and chicken.
Please stop.
I'm so hungry.
I even perfected my roux.
I added some red pepper flakes.
It was really good.
Mint streams give me energy.
That sounds amazing.
Oh, also, Yanwei, I forgot to answer.
My favorite instant curry...
I actually really like the...
Um...
I really like...
I don't remember the brand, actually.
Hold on.
Let me look it up.
I've actually never tried the Vermont curry before, but I like...
Apple curry.
It's a golden curry.
The golden curry one.
I like it.
But I've never had the Vermont...
But I just add my own apples to it.
Golden.
I'll try that next time.
Yeah!
Whenever I make curry, I use the golden curry.
Oh!
Geez!
We're not gonna...
Maybe I have to...
Maybe I have to close this.
Again.
Because he's gonna come back.
I don't want him to fall down the stairs.
There he is.
And he goes down.
What?
The timing on this is whack!
The timing on this is so whack!
Because he immediately turns around, but this guy stops here.
Yeah!
The timing was okay before you dropped him.
Maybe, yeah.
Okay.
Maybe...
Nope.
Maybe I do need to drop him again.
To reset the timing.
Maybe this will help reset the timing.
Actually.
Okay.
This is a bit better.
Walk.
Nice!
Okay.
Trick.
And then...
Here.
Just go.
Go!
Oh my god.
That scared me.
I just can't seem to find the brick I need!
And you'll just have to make one.
Make one?
Try calling me to all kinds of different places.
I'm agreeable.
I can go pretty much anywhere.
Okay.
I can see why you guys said this is not a good level.
No, we have to...
Wait!
Oh, thank goodness.
We don't have to start at the very beginning.
Yeah!
The game is kind to us.
Okay.
Oops.
Good.
Come over here.
Oh, and it's closed.
Okay.
Wait.
This might actually be it.
This might be it.
Now close the hatch.
They won't see him now, right?
I love making super spicy curry with pineapple in it because the sweet mix with the heat is great.
But if I'm not sweating while eating curry, it feels wrong.
I can't have spicy, so...
No.
I like sweet curry.
But pineapple curry sounds pretty good too.
That's the most precise part?
Okay.
So now...
Oh, it's so scary.
Oh, wait.
No, no, no.
Stop!
Cancel, cancel, cancel.
Oh, wait.
No, I need to get to the...
I need to get to the...
Okay.
Wait.
I have to open this though, don't I?
I have to open this.
Yeah, now we make him fall.
Wait.
No, no, no.
Okay.
I have to be like super good timing because I have to open this.
Wait, I don't have to open it?
Oh, I don't?
Okay, let's just go to the bunk then.
Just roll?
Oh.
Okay.
Wait a second.
Oh, well, if I get him over here...
There's nowhere else to go from here.
So...
Oh, wait!
Come back, come back, come back!
Sorry.
Maybe, actually...
He can go over here.
Um...
There's nowhere like down here to lead him to though.
This guy turns around eventually.
Right?
A good...
A good officer would turn around and check his back.
A good officer would turn around and make sure no one's sneaking up on him in the dark.
Check the wall.
No!
Okay,
okay, okay.
Can I like tell him to come over here?
Now?
Turn around.
Oh my god.
Yeah!
Oh my god, please, sir.
Please.
If I move now, I'm going to fall.
Could you close the hatch for me?
Yes, yes, yes!
Can't you just jump?
Okay, now go?
Go?
Please go.
So, what do you think?
I'd say if we've come this far, we did it.
Great job, Cecil.
The basement generator has been repaired.
Restoring power to all areas.
Oh.
Uh-oh.
Run!
Don't just stand there.
But the question is, what now?
I don't have anywhere else to... anywhere to go, do I?
Maybe I'll go back to my cell.
You better be kidding!
But I'm still a condemned criminal, you know.
I doubt anybody would welcome me with open arms.
Why don't you try contacting Lin?
She went to see some justice minister guy.
So an escaped death row convict is supposed to just report in to the justice minister?
Is that it?
I kinda like that.
Hello, Minto.
Good luck with game.
Love your stream.
Thank you!
Thanks, Coldbreed!
Thanks for a whole month.
You have yet to be kidding me.
That would be nice, yes.
Alright, Sissel.
Until we meet again.
Wait, how does he escape from the prison, though?
There's still other doors with other people.
Oh well.
Let's just not think about that part.
Yes.
Now I've saved a condemned criminal's life and helped him escape.
Is that really the right thing to do?
I guess all I can do is believe in Lin at this point.
Why is there a big boss?
That's why you're the best boss!
Great job sneaking!
Thank you!
Oh, all four guards were at the cells.
No one was upstairs.
Oh, that makes sense.
Detective Joud was painting my picture in his cell.
He knows me.
I'm sure I'll be talking to him again.
Well then, why doesn't he even say something?
Hmm...
Thank you!
Chu!
Real military-grade NVG doesn't emit anything because it'd be easy to detect.
It's all passive light amplification with tech.
I don't understand it, so it might as well be magic.
Yeah, right?
If you think about it, it's kinda like...
It's like...
Yeah, it would be pointless to use it if you could see through a whole trail of light, right?
That'd be so silly.
Let's go to...
Let's go to the guard room.
The mortuary...
Anybody here?
Did you hear?
Yeah, we're supposed to repair this thing by the time they catch him again.
But I wonder why he escaped.
Hmm...
But it's so cool!
What, the light in the dark?
I agree.
The trail of light is like so awesome.
Splinter Cell misled a lot of people on artistic decision.
Aesthetic-wise, it looks great.
Practicality?
Not so much.
Reminds me of Godot.
I mean...
But that's like not night vision.
And his mask emitting light is like...
Kind of a big thing.
I wonder why he escaped.
I heard Detective Joud wanted the death penalty.
Right.
It's not like him to change his mind.
Maybe on this final night of his...
He just got a voice in his head or something.
It was me!
Yeah, me.
Maybe it told him to run.
Are they talking about me?
What kind of a voice do you think it was?
You know...
Something evil.
If you ever have Minto voice in your head...
Like a devil.
Or a demon or something.
Maybe a g-g-g-g-ghost?
I picture something with a pointy head.
Wearing sunglasses.
Something like that.
They ARE talking about me.
Can they see me?
Trick time.
That's so silly.
Alright.
Guard room.
Hey, how they know about your...
Pointy ghost head thing?
I don't know.
Sixth sense, I guess.
But Detective Jouds, until we meet again...
Came around quicker than I expected.
When I got back to the guard room...
The next fateful call came in.
It's the panic dance.
Hello, this is...
Oh!
Sizzle, are you there?
H-hello?
Oh, I'm not talking to you, officer.
Anyway, if you're there, Sizzle...
Come here immediately.
I'll be waiting for you.
If you make it in time, that is.
Wait a minute!
Oh my god.
Go, go, go, Sizzle!
Oh, wait.
Dial, dial!
I kinda wanna see what...
Officer Bailey has to say.
That call!
Who is it from?
I don't know.
Some weird call.
Ah, but who...
Will call an end to my dancing!
You're supposed to record it.
Yeah, well, once you get going like that...
I'm not gonna stop you.
It's a contest then!
Which will stop first?
My dancing, or the turning of the planet?
Yeah, good luck with that.
Alrighty.
External line.
Go to...
Oh.
Go to here.
Wherever this mysterious place is.
Meow.
Whoa.
On the other end of the telephone line...
The scene that greets me...
Tells me one simple fact.
Is Lynn dead?
Holy cow.
The soundtrack.
That our great escape plan...
Has ended in failure.
Never expected to see you here...
Inspector Cabanela.
I believe...
That's my line, old friend.
What were you doing here?
Believe...
That's my line too.
Clear.
Hahaha.
I came to...
Attend your execution.
They told me what time it was.
Couldn't get into the chamber...
So I was observing a moment of silence here.
And when I looked up my eyes...
Full of tears...
There you were, baby.
You're so adorkable.
What am I doing?
Why am I adorkable though?
It's just the way...
Things turned out.
Well...
I took part in what seemed like a fun game...
And here I am.
Here's what I wish, my old friend.
Wish it was anybody but me...
Who found you here.
What does he mean by that?
He is gonna shoot him?
Cause now that I've found you, man...
I have to turn you in.
You have to stay spotlessly clean after all.
You
have to stay spotlessly clean after all.
You have to stay spotlessly clean after all.
Thanks for coming.
I wanted to say goodbye to you.
Cause you are adorable.
What did I do?
As you can see...
I guess I'm not going to be much help to you.
What's going to happen to you?
Being executed tonight...
Is just about the only thing on my schedule, it seems.
No, no...
There must be something we can trick too.
Executed, huh?
Death is pretty much meaningless to me.
Anyway...
I guess we'll be seeing each other again.
By the way...
There's something I'm looking for.
That's right.
Your lost memory.
You know things I'd like to know.
Would you mind if I asked you a few questions?
In return for tonight's fun little game.
Is that it?
Oh...
Let's ask about the execution.
Let's go down to up.
Thank you, thank you.
Chuuu...
Mint is indeed cute.
Stop!
Someone's about to die.
And we're talking about me.
This is not how it should be.
Someone's about to die.
And all you think about is anime.
What's wrong with you?
Someone's about to die and you think about anime.
Anime girl!
How could you think about anime at a time like this?
Is your execution...
really the right thing to do?
I had a fair trial.
And that's what was decided.
No problem there.
But still...
This is the punishment that I should receive.
What if anime girl is cute?
It doesn't matter!
If I was about to die...
and want to think about how cute Mint is too?
Odd, but cute.
I am continuing this game.
I am continuing!
Forward!
In order to...
bring a final close to that case...
and put it to rest forever.
Kawaii doko ga?
Lin believes you're innocent.
She's running around right now trying to prove it.
Aw, you two.
You're all gross.
For disregarding this man's death.
Let's go.
Cute is justice.
Moe is justice.
Moe!
Moe is everything.
But it's not me.
Okay.
We're trash, remember?
I need to go get more tea soon.
Oh my gosh, this soundtrack is so awesome.
Okay.
Can I please get the...
to the game?
Is that all you have to leave her with?
No problem there?
I...
I was sentenced to the death penalty for killing my wife, Alma.
But to me, that's not all it was for.
We mourn in our own ways.
My cats are cute.
You're okay, I guess.
Cats are always the cutest.
You guys...
Oh my gosh, no.
I'm gonna save it for the podcast.
Oh my gosh, I'm gonna save it for the podcast.
Kawaii Koko.
What do you mean that's not all it was for?
Stop interrupting me!
Okay, I'm gonna go get some water.
Since you guys need to get this out of your system.
Get it out of your system.
I'm gonna get some water.
You guys, I wanna...
I wanna read the important things going on.
What's wrong with you?
Why would you interrupt right now?
Okay, I'm gonna go get some water.
I'll be right back.
Cliffhanger for like two minutes.
Actually, I'm gonna go to the little ghosties room too.
So like...
Five minutes.
Even less than.
Okay, be right back.
I'm
back, I'm back, I'm back.
Thank you for all the super chats.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
That was quick.
I said I would be quick.
I said so, I said so.
I said so.
I found a cute ghost.
Her name is Mint Phantom.
Scatter!
Did you wash your hands?
Of course!
Why would you ask me that, Dust Girl?
I always wash my hands!
Everyone scatter!
Okay.
Are we ready to continue the game now?
Are we ready to continue the story?
Are you ready?
Yes.
Okay.
Thank you for all the super chats, you guys.
What do you mean that's not all it was for?
I'm talking about something that happened even before this case.
I stole somebody else's life.
Thanks for the gift.
What?
The other murder.
It was 10 years ago.
I'll never forget it.
That day I saved the life of a little girl.
And I stole away the life of a man.
Oh, yeah.
A cute positive genius ghost.
It's me.
10 years ago.
The life of a little girl.
Could that little girl be...
Lin?
She told you about that?
Yeah.
She said you were her hero.
Now just calm down and drop that weapon!
Stay back!
If you come any closer, I'll shoot her!
I mean, you...
You...
Thanks for holding her up.
I hope I need to feed my cats.
10 years ago in a certain park.
A little girl was taken hostage.
Okay, this is a good summary.
Or a good...
Reminder of what happened before.
I was still young then.
Arrogant.
Stop, Spongebob!
No, Garlabob!
The world's cutest Minto!
Thank you for the Akadono.
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
Hmm...
But you couldn't tell me that yesterday, huh?
When we were playing...
When we were playing Lethal Company, huh?
Yesterday I did a Patreon stream.
And we played Lethal Company.
Do you want me to?
I will next time.
No!
Not at all.
I was still young then.
I didn't have any self-control.
Sounds like you guys.
I remember asking myself at the time.
Jaude...
Are you going to shoot this guy?
And this is what I answered.
Yeah, I'm gonna shoot that guy!
I was too starstruck.
It's okay.
If you're part of the Patreon...
The two tiers...
We'll do another one.
Another one.
If we missed out, don't worry.
My hand was shaking a little.
If my hand slipped, the man might die.
Even the little hostage girl was in danger.
Nevertheless...
That was my answer.
Yeah, I'm going to shoot!
Woohoo!
And the man died.
I took his life.
Yo!
It's pretty messed up.
Lin was never dead.
I never told the outcome.
She was so young at the time.
I don't deserve to be called a hero.
What I deserve is...
Execution.
Aww...
He has all that guilt.
But he was holding a little girl hostage!
I'm sorry, what?
So anyway, I started blasting.
That man pointing the gun at you right now.
They say he's your good friend.
Why is good friend?
In quotes.
And...
He's your...
Good friend!
History would say they were roommates.
We were.
When we were in the detective division together.
That was a long time ago.
I think we're going to have to kill this guy.
Damn!
Platypus, thanks for the money!
Thank you!
Now he's the head of the special investigation unit.
The top of the elite.
Getting ahead is the only thing he thinks about now.
And that white coat of his is the symbol of his determination.
His white coat?
For somebody looking to get promoted to the top, What's the one thing they're afraid of most?
Getting dirty!
Ghosts?
A blot on their record, of course.
Like a stain on a pure white coat.
Who would promote a man with a coat covered in stains?
If it was me, I'd go with the black coat that didn't show the stains.
Then why don't you change your red coat, huh?
The world is full of excellent candidates.
Even one mistake could be the end of a career.
But everyone makes mistakes, right?
Nevertheless, Cabanela has chosen the path of the white coat.
And he'd do anything, anything at all to hide his coat's shadows.
Oh, so it's not so clean after all.
Oh my gosh, take a UV light to that coat!
Take a UV light to that coat and see what it shows!
Huh?
Like send his good friend to the gallows.
That's because...
Oh, because that's the right thing to do.
I'm a condemned criminal after all.
Covered in ectoplasm.
No, I was thinking the blood.
What were you guys thinking?
I was thinking of blood.
That you, like, use the solution and then it shows in the UV light.
Ectoplasm?
I don't think ectoplasm would show in a UV light.
Oh, wait.
What?
Wait, yes it does.
Uh-oh.
I think I'm in trouble.
I think...
And that's why he has that gun pointed at me right now.
Alright, let's ask about ourselves.
The one that I've been the most curious about.
I saw it, you know.
That picture you were painting in your cell tonight.
That was me.
Which means...
You must know me.
I'm very sorry, but...
I can't talk to you about that now.
What?
Why not?
Maybe I really am Sissel.
Because I...
I loved you.
I don't know your true face?
Oh my gosh, my glasses.
Oh, I'm one of those.
I don't take off my glasses.
My true face?
I'm a detective.
I can only talk about what I'm sure of.
However...
I can give you one lead at least.
One month!
Yeah!
Roaring John!
Thank you!
A lead?
What is it?
A long time ago, I gave Lin something to hold onto me.
Onto for me!
The music box!
It was a music box!
Yes, yes, yes!
If you ever come across it, I advise you to open it.
It might jog your memory.
That wooden box I found in Lin's room.
In his apartment!
And that's the only help I can give you right now.
Oh my god, we were right next to it.
The whole time.
Are we about to watch him get...
get... get dead?
Ready to go?
My arms are getting tired.
You got it, baby.
Time for the big show of hauling you in.
Oh, he's not gonna shoot.
Don't shoot!
Oh, that's right.
Just let me make...
a phone call.
That's a big favor to ask so casually, my old friend.
Tell you what I'll do...
I'll pretend I'm not watching.
I'll be listening, though.
On that, you can rely.
Oogie, why does the paint change on his jacket like that?
Sissel, you've got your own path to follow.
You'd better hurry.
My own path?
Lin is at the Justice...
Sister's office right now, right?
It might not be a bad idea to say my final farewell to him, too.
Beep boop bop beep.
Moshi moshi.
Hello?
Everything's fine here!
Uh oh.
Lin?
Uh...
Is this the chicken kitchen?
I'd like to request a delivery.
Um...
The chicken kitchen is next door.
Aye, good day to you, sir.
Good day to you.
Oh...
Alright.
Hmm...
Sounds like she's in some kind of trouble.
It does, doesn't it?
Go help her out, would you, Sissel?
Sorry to keep...
Sorry to keep you waiting, Inspector.
Ready to go?
I bet Inspector Cabanela's probably like, Oh my gosh.
He really lost his mind in that jail cell.
Now he's talking to ghosts.
Hahaha.
Pring!
Oh, before I forget...
Don't shoot.
Oh.
I have a little something for you.
A hug?
What?
Are you...
Are you gonna hypnotize me?
What's going on?
Just like my doujins.
A present, if you will.
There's nothing else like it, baby.
If there's nothing else like it, don't throw it.
Oh.
What's this?
A pocket watch?
Considering my situation, it's the last thing in the world I need right now.
He needs more time.
He gave you more time!
Forgive me, man.
Let's just say I'm no good at choosing presents.
Okay.
This is it, Sissel.
I'm done with one thing.
Don't trust other people's memories.
Look for what you seek with your own eyes.
I'll remember that.
Actually, people's memories are very...
are very unreliable.
Witness testimony's not great all the time.
They're gone.
There's nothing left here.
No hope.
No cores either.
Okay.
Without any cores, I can't follow after them.
This is the end of my adventure.
I feel pretty dejected, but I guess I'd better go find Lin.
Fake memories are a thing?
A scary thing?
Yeah, I can imagine.
Parrot's memories, however, are rock solid.
Holy hell, is this Ace Attorney?
Yes!
Thanks for the super chat, Evan.
I'll follow the path Detective Jowd pointed out to me.
The path to the Justice Minister's office.
Where Lin went to try and stop the execution.
I don't remember saying this before, but this didn't stop.
Trava!
Is that what the song is called?
Oh my god.
Let's save.
And keep going.
1141 PM.
It's so late.
Why would the Justice Minister still be there?
Now that my assignment to stop the execution has ended in such an unsatisfactory way, I decided to go see Lin at the Justice Minister's office.
Oh yeah, it's here.
I forgot.
Detective Jowd's story about this other murder weighs on me heavily.
Should I tell Lin about it?
I just don't know.
Please attorney the phantom pain.
Why are there pills on the ground?
What is she doing?
Oh, she is... This time, Lin isn't dead.
Wow!
But the atmosphere makes me think it might be too soon to count my blessings just yet.
Thank you, thank you.
Chuu!
Lin is so cute.
Oh.
Chuu.
I'm glad Lin isn't dead.
Oh man!
Lin dead counter zero!
What in the world is she doing?
Help step ghost, I'm stuck.
Then again, do I really want to know?
What...
is she doing?
Sorry, I was drinking.
I almost spit out my tea!
Oh my god!
Uh... Lin?
What kind of greeting is that?
I mean, I know I'm a ghost and everything, but...
Well, and how did it go?
Was detective Zhao still alive?
He had already been executed by the time I got there.
I did manage to save him, but...
You did?
I'm so glad!
Wait, wait a minute.
Did you say but?
It's 3.30 AM.
Do I grab an ice cream?
Thanks.
Yeah, I think so.
I love late night ice cream.
What kind of ice cream are you gonna get though?
Uh... Ripped tea.
No, I drank it.
Luckily.
I told Lin about my adventure at the prison.
About that other murder though.
Couldn't bring myself to tell her.
At least, you know, as much as I wasn't a huge fan of the last thing where we had to do the sneaking mission, I appreciate the game trying out other methods of, you know, having us use the ghost.
Trick.
So I think that's kind of fun.
Inspector Cabanela arrested Detective Jowd?
I can't believe it!
Cinder K!
Thank you for the time gifted!
Yeah, a little break up in design is cool once in a while.
Yeah, and it wasn't so long.
She seems to have some yabai reading preferences.
My favorite ice cream is mint cookie crumble.
Woo!
You're making me hungry.
I feel the same way.
I can't believe that wherever I go, somebody is always dead.
Either you or someone else.
Sorry about that.
So who is that lying on the floor there?
Oh, you noticed him, did you?
That's the Justice Minister.
The man who signed the order to carry out Detective Jowd's execution?
He was already dead when I got here.
Shouldn't you have called for help in the case?
I guess so.
Lynn?
But I'm wanted, remember?
For murder?
I was hoping we could save him without me getting caught.
Oui, eh?
Oh boy.
The guy with the marriage troubles?
I think so.
Oh, oops, my bad.
Let's talk to him.
Let's see what he's got to say.
Hey, can you hear me?
Are you awake?
Hmm, he's dead but he still seems to be unconscious.
Could you rescue him now?
While he's still unconscious?
Instead of talking to him, I bet it'll be faster to see, just to see for yourself what really happened.
Yeah, I bet you're right.
Back we go then to four minutes before his death.
Rewind time.
Hold on.
I have some some dried mango.
Ow!
I'm gonna eat it.
Dried mango, 1131.
Yeah, this is the guy with the marriage problems.
What's he doing?
Oh, he's a jumpy bunch.
Emma!
Not Emma.
Oh, excuse me.
What?
Alright.
I'll do as you say.
This is terrible.
Mint mango.
What's going on?
Why doesn't she answer?
Um.
Is he gonna die?
From heartbreak?
Oh?
Oh
my god.
Medicine!
That explains the pills over there.
Pills here.
Oh.
Water!
Oh my god.
This poor guy.
This is so sad.
Oh.
Fucks.
Die!
Thank you.
Chu!
Something about a serious flashback with a somber music and then Spongebob saying arigato, arigato, chu is sending me.
Such a foolish man.
Oh, you woke up.
He's a contradiction.
Contradiction?
The more we search for the truth, the further into a dilemma we fall.
The world of men is steeped in contradictions.
If we choose this, we can't have that.
If a man tries to have his medicine bottle and water pitcher, too, he loses both.
Thank you.
What will we find if we put your maid cafe under UV lights, Mint?
Care to explain?
I don't know.
I mean...
I'm a ghost.
If I walk around, ectoplasm kind of gets places.
It's not my fault.
It's just how it is.
I'm like a snail.
I don't know.
To me, it looks like you could have had both of those things just now.
He didn't know the truth about the world.
That's why he died.
Such a foolish man.
Or maybe I should say a pathetic man.
That's more... that's...
the more fitting word.
I don't think this guy gets it yet.
That the foolish and pathetic man is him.
Is that why they call... is that what they call a contradiction?
By the way, what's your name?
Just call me a sicker of truth.
Sidestep that one, didn't he?
Ripperoni.
This one should be kind of quick though, right?
No need to think too hard about this one.
All I have to do is give him his medicine too.
Pretty simple.
But there's one more thing that concerns me.
What was that telephone call the justice minister got all about?
Oh yes, true, true.
It was right after that his health took an instant downturn.
I've never seen such a foolish, pathetic and strange man.
I think you'd better stop there.
Okay, well uh...
This body below is so creepy.
Emma!
Could it be?
Excuse me.
Wait, who's on the other line?
Oh!
Oh my!
Forgive me for calling so late, Mr. Minister.
Oh girl, you can call me as late as you want!
Who is this?
How did you get this number?
We have your daughter.
What?
Who is this?
Emily's tutor?
Would a tutor call you at this hour?
No.
Oh, say it one more time.
We have your daughter.
Nani?
My daughter!
Is she alright?
Tell me she's alright.
Here for yourself.
Papa, help!
I'm gonna be killed!
Oh my god, they turned her into a candle!
What do you want?
What are your demands?
I believe we already made our demand known the other day.
Oh, so it was you.
And have you complied?
Has the execution...
Oh!
Why do they want him dead?
Has the execution been carried out?
I didn't do it because of your demand.
I did it because that's my job.
Yes.
Yes, of course.
They should be contacting me any minute now with a confirmation.
There's no need for this kidnapping.
We're very thorough.
You'd do well to remember that.
A female ghost never talk about having a snail trail.
Because it's embarrassing, okay?
I keep it real.
And of course it goes without saying.
We're watching you.
If this information leaves that room, you'll never see your daughter again.
I trust you understand that.
She can keep my daughter.
Don't tell the police.
Is that it?
Exactly.
Use your job.
Alright.
I'll do as you say.
I'll make sure the execution is carried out tonight.
You have my word.
Uh oh.
Wait, but if we go there...
If we go there, he's gonna die.
Oh well.
Let's go see the sexy lady.
Mama Smurf, I'm coming for you!
So it was a recording of the little girl?
We're here.
Apparently, the police in this country aren't so easily fooled.
I had no idea word of tonight's deal had leaked.
Paparazzi!
Yep, it's a recording.
I'm gonna be killed!
Luckily, I managed to arrange it so that the justice minister could hear her... voice.
But what's taking the goods so long to arrive?
I'm starting to get concerned.
Oh my gosh.
You're so sexy when you're concerned.
Wait, time is passing.
Oh.
Yeah, because he's dead.
Wait.
I don't think I can go back.
I can't.
I can't go back.
I can't use the phone right now.
Like I said, all women are like traps.
That and this are hardly related.
When in the past...
Oops.
This looks so similar to the room that was in that guy's basement.
In the junkyard.
I think we're just gonna die here.
Uh oh.
This woman doesn't show any signs of moving from her spot.
And I can't use the telephone line either.
Looks like I fell into a trap.
No, I knew what I was doing.
Oh.
All women are like traps.
Some are sweet traps.
Others are bitter.
Don't you understand that?
Okay.
I think I'd better rethink things here.
She's like really just...
She's like a statue.
She's just really thinking right there.
She's just really...
She's just...
She's just standing there.
She's really like...
meditating so deeply.
Oh.
Three.
You can hit R to reset.
Yeah, but don't you want to spend more time with her?
I think he's dead.
It's so anticlimactic just sitting here.
You don't see anything.
Okay.
A mysterious kidnapping, eh?
I'd like to find out more about it.
But right now I have another problem to solve first.
Cause as little trouble for others as possible.
Now that's a rule to live by.
Never mind that.
Let's start over.
Okay.
From the beginning.
Alright.
Trick Time.
Oh, excuse me.
And now we can skip through all this.
Bwa bwa bwa bwa bwa bwa bwa bwa.
Bwa bwa bwa bwa bwa bwa bwa.
Emma Papa, I mean Papa, help.
I'm gonna be killed.
Bwa bwa bwa bwa bwa bwa.
I hate you, mommy.
Bwa bwa bwa bwa bwa bwa bwa.
Bwa bwa bwa bwa bwa.
Sexy voice.
Okay, good.
Stay here.
This is terrible.
Kidnapping, eh?
Once again, I'm not sure I know what the word means.
It's apparently the cause of the minister's attack.
I mean, it's in the name, Cecil.
They napped a kid!
I think it's in the name.
Oh, he's slow.
Such a useless man.
A useless man caught up in a useless case.
Why doesn't he understand that?
Anyway, we only have four minutes.
I better do something about that medicine.
Let's see.
Wait, what is he doing now?
Who is he talking to?
I have to call my wife.
I have to see if it's true.
Maybe they called the wrong person.
This minister doesn't accept the truth easily.
Oh, that's right, she didn't pick up.
He's morally bankrupt.
Is putting a kid down for a nap a crime?
It's a crime against their free will.
What if they don't want to nap?
Actually, that's kind of crazy.
Who wouldn't want to nap?
His wife won't answer for some reason.
A wife who doesn't answer her phone.
I think I know who that is.
A morally bankrupt man deserves a morally bankrupt wife.
Kids, apparently.
Why doesn't that man understand that?
Now I'm sorry I ever brought this guy along.
Me too, a little bit.
Let's examine the pills first.
So this medicine stops the minister's attacks, eh?
If I could, I'd spill them onto his desk right now.
But unfortunately, I can't even open the cap.
What a shabby excuse for a man.
Thank you, thank you.
Kiss.
You're a simp.
Sorry, you lost the gotcha.
But thank you.
He wears his important-looking uniform and sits working at his stately desk.
But what does he have inside?
Nothing.
A miserable, shabby excuse for a man.
I think you have already said quite enough.
Uh, oh wait.
If only he could at least drink some of this water.
Too bad he knocks this pitcher to the floor at the end of his four minutes.
Such a stupid man.
Once water is spilled, there's no getting it back.
And knowing this full well, why do people still spill water pitchers?
So true.
I don't know.
Those who do not learn from history are doomed to repeat it?
Let's flap the flag.
He doesn't notice.
He's so sad.
Why doesn't she answer?
I guess let's be the medicine bottle for now and see what we can do when he grabs us.
Let's run.
Otherwise, I'll say I planned this...
Oh my god.
Come on.
Start coming to life.
Oh,
he's coming.
It's!
Oh my god.
I've been waiting for this.
Swing the sword.
Raise the arm.
Oh my god.
Rock the basket.
Nice.
Swing the sword.
No, no, no.
Swing it.
I think he's dead.
Swing the sword.
Again.
Oh, melons.
Undo the hangar!
He's dead.
He's so dead.
Okay, well now we know that some of these things don't work.
Okay, let's see.
I thought that maybe swinging it would like...
Okay, hold on.
Do I really have just that short of a time frame?
To get this?
It's kind of crazy.
Oh,
it's already happening?
Okay.
Pew!
Let's see what we got here.
Raise the arm.
Thank you!
Turn the basket.
Rock the basket.
Oh!
I did something.
I'm not sure what that did actually.
I don't think that did anything.
It was an honor being able to play and verbally exchange words with you yesterday, Ghosty.
Sorry I couldn't save you from the facehugger.
My cookie tray wasn't strong enough.
It's okay.
You tried.
Undo this.
I don't think it does anything.
What am I supposed to do here?
Okay.
Next time, let's just...
Next time, let's stick around with him.
Maybe.
What does the curtain do?
I don't know.
I can't even reach it.
Maybe let's see if there's anything we can do with the water.
Okay.
It starts to die.
Starts to die.
This one was tough for me but I really liked it.
Okay.
Hold on.
Is there anything?
There's a flag.
We can also flap.
Does it do anything?
Oh!
Wait.
Did that spook him?
Actually, I'm not sure.
Oh.
There's like...
Can't use the phones.
Okay.
Even though we knocked it off the thing.
Let's find another path.
Sorry.
There we go.
I thought we could stabilize it or something.
No.
Okay.
I think we have to...
Oh!
The flag now!
You guys are so smart.
The flag to stabilize it.
The flag to be like...
Make it go.
Okay.
So I was on the right path with the flag, I think.
I have another mango.
Hello.
But that did not even work.
Reach for it!
There it is!
Everything else was a red herring.
Well, I was thinking initially.
I was like...
Somehow getting the mango...
on the sword and then...
golfing it over.
Putting it over.
But...
But I couldn't do that.
And there wasn't anything else over there that would really let me do.
I was confused.
There.
That should help.
At least he's now had some water.
Okay.
All good.
He's still breathing, apparently.
But he looks far from recovered, unfortunately.
Such a wishy-washy man.
He can't make up his mind whether to live or die.
Oh my god.
Okay.
At least now I bought some time to get his medicine to him.
But how do I get over there, actually?
Um...
Wait, now how do I get over there?
Oh...
Flap.
No.
Wait, how do I get over there?
The minister's fate has changed.
But the situation still seems the same.
I can't move anywhere now.
Did I miss something?
I think I saw a path.
Just for a second while the minister was drinking the water.
A path while he was drinking the water.
Maybe I should start over from the beginning.
Come on!
Sisoul!
Wait, while he was drinking the water?
Wait, no.
But I have to do from the beginning, right?
I can't do it.
Wait.
Hold on.
What's the fate change?
Is it while he...
When he grabs the water or...
No.
Okay.
From the beginning.
I...
Maybe it has something to do with the papers.
Maybe like a paper flew and I didn't realize it.
Yeah, because that's the only other thing we can highlight.
Or the documents.
Okay.
Let's hang out in the flag for now.
It's a split second, but it's there.
I missed it.
Oh, my God!
I'm out of control!
I am out of control.
Okay, I'm ready.
I'm ready to flap.
I'm ready to flap!
Reach for it!
Oh, that was too early.
Oh, come on!
No!
This guy is too clumsy.
He's stinking.
He's making butterfingers over here.
What's wrong with you?
Maybe he's right.
Maybe his ghost self is right.
Wishy washy man.
Do you want to live or do you want to die?
La la la.
Okay.
I'm ready to flap.
Once it's spinning around.
Flap!
There we go.
Okay.
Now let's go to the papers.
It was the picture.
Oh I thought when he went crazy.
I thought maybe a piece of paper flew off.
I gotta go to the picture.
I thought I missed a piece of paper flying in the wind.
Why people are being like why papers?
I said this from the very beginning.
I was like okay.
Once he lifts the water.
I'm gonna go to the papers.
And see if I.
Why did you do that?
You stupid ghost.
When I said it from the beginning.
That's what I was going to do.
I.
Why did you do the thing that you said.
That you were going to try.
Okay.
Reach for the water.
Flap!
Okay.
Picture time.
Spin harder.
And then it will probably blow the paper.
There that should help.
Blah blah blah.
Okay.
Wait if I spin harder.
How am I going to.
We read all of this.
There we go.
Oh.
How nice.
Alright.
Now we are here.
We are at the medicine.
Time for the next step.
About this medicine bottle.
The minister is going to make a full recovery.
I have to deliver this thing to him.
How is a ghost with no hands or feet.
Hey.
My hands are like this because I'm a ghost.
Supposed to do that.
I guess I'll just have to use my head instead.
Let's see.
Let's raise this.
Raise the roof.
Lower.
Oh okay.
I was going to say.
Okay.
I was going to.
Oh wait I can reach this now.
Never mind.
Close the curtain.
Time is passing.
Okay.
Spin.
I'm not quite sure what to do.
Oh.
Wrong way.
Maybe.
Roll.
Oh.
Good.
Undo.
Okay.
I'm just fumbling around right now you guys.
Hold on.
I'm fumbling around a little bit.
Let me see what I can do.
Let me see what's possible.
Um.
Rock the boat.
Melon.
Aha.
Okay.
So.
I roll the globe.
No.
Yes?
Wait.
Uh.
Yeah.
I roll the globe.
And then I hit it with the melon.
Would it be the globe?
Or would it be the.
Well actually.
It could be either the vase or the globe.
I'm not quite sure.
I think I need to restart though.
Cause I don't have a thing.
To roll.
I don't have.
Um.
But I need.
The globe to drop.
To knock down.
The vase.
I don't think it's supposed to be a catapult.
I think it's supposed to be.
Like.
Hold on.
The globe drops from here.
And rolls onto here.
And then rolls down.
And then.
When it gets to this side.
We use the melon to.
To.
Wait.
I'm not so sure actually.
Swing.
Take all the time you need.
I don't.
I don't have time.
Let's see what they say.
That was so close.
If the swing just had a little more reach to it.
I think it'd be.
I think I'd better look for something else.
Oh.
Uh oh.
Okay.
I'm gonna try spinning the globe next time.
And seeing.
If that works.
Goodbye mister.
From the fate change.
Okay.
Spin.
Harder.
Alright.
Here we go.
Alrighty.
I'm going ghost.
No.
I think this is the order.
The order that I did before.
I think is correct.
Because otherwise.
The painting will be facing.
Slanted this way.
And that won't help me with.
That won't help.
It'll just fly over the medicine.
It'll fly over the medicine right?
So.
Let's close this.
Raise the roof.
Salute.
Turn around.
No wait.
I didn't turn before.
Pause.
Spin.
See what happens here.
Ah.
But this can knock this over.
This one can get knocked over.
This one right here.
Wait.
Was it this way?
Hold on.
Oh.
Wait.
That's exactly what I said I didn't want to happen.
Read the thought bubbles for hints.
I don't.
I'm purposefully not reading it.
Because I do not want to hint.
I want to figure it out.
I don't want to hint.
I'm trying to figure it out myself.
Though I already feel that I messed up.
Though I feel that I already made a grave mistake.
Ah.
Globe.
Ok.
Wait.
I...
Well, like I said, if I do this...
If I... If i.
If I.
Why?
Wait, if I do this... But then I...
Stop posting!
Stop posting the answers!
I'm not reading!
Stop!
I said no hints!
Oh my god, time limit.
Okay.
Shut up, Sissel!
I know!
Let's see.
So many moving parts.
Honestly, a great puzzle to think through.
Yeah!
It is fun.
It's interesting for sure.
Okay, I feel like I'm just gonna have to try it.
And if it's not...
If it's not the correct way, I...
Do it the opposite way, I guess?
I suppose.
Wait, wait, wait.
No, we want the...
Yeah...
No, wait, wait, wait.
Trial and error.
Exactly, exactly.
Because sometimes...
Something might not go as you predict it will.
And I'm just kind of confused.
Oh!
Oh, it's time, huh?
Wow, it's so much fun.
This might be a good idea.
Okay, let's see.
This is going to be very then.
I'm gonna do this.
I'm not doing it...
You get it?
Do you get it?
I don't know what to do.
I believe...
Okay, I got it.
Okay, let's see.
I feel...
I feel like the vase will just fly into the air.
Just try it?
Okay, you're right.
Might as well just try something.
Wait,
if I...
Oh no, I need to... I need to turn it.
And then I need to rock it.
Rock it, baby.
Okay.
And then if I go here and do this...
It's called thinking out loud.
I'm an out loud thinker.
Why did the thought bubble come up?
It's scaring me.
It makes me feel like I did it wrong.
Okay, and now we go to here and here.
And to there.
And knock you down.
Time is passing.
And then we...
When I turned it around, it still knocked over the vase, didn't it?
I think so.
Spin!
Oh!
What?
Roll?
Oh!
Wait, can I roll that?
No, I can't roll that.
Oh, wait.
Oh, wait, am I catapulting it?
Am I catapulting?
Wait, hold on.
I need more time.
Don't rush me, game.
Wait, so if I put this in the middle.
This vase.
And roll this here.
And then, that knocks down.
This catapults the globe.
Okay, let's try that.
After the fate change!
Oh, spin harder.
Spin harder!
Okay.
Beep, beep, beep.
Blah, blah, blah.
So we go and then that also makes it so that falls on the melon falls oh wait no we have to have this fall down instead of the melon oh wait i want to go up i want to go up real quick
we undo this guy a little undo a little screws loose
Okay.
This way.
Spin!
It went the wrong way.
It went the wrong way!
Oh my god.
I remember getting tricked by that too.
Yeah, it's a little... it feels like a little...
Like, not misleading I think is the wrong word, but you kind of like... your brain thinks like, oh if it's facing the direction of the vase, then it will go to the direction of the vase.
You know what I mean?
Okay.
If it didn't take so much to get there, it wouldn't have been an issue.
I wish I could turn off the intensity of the ghost trick effect, you know?
That's the only thing that makes me... You know what?
I will turn this while we're here.
I will turn that.
Oh, I unlocked a bunch of stuff, but I don't know why.
I just unlocked it now, but okay.
Time is passing.
I'm working.
Okay,
now we turn it.
And then we spin it.
Okay, then we drop it like it's hot.
Time
is passing.
Wait.
Then we drop the globe.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Wait.
Wait, we drop the globe and then we drop the... drop the other vase, right?
Spin it!
Tap it!
Bonk it!
Twirl it!
I think so, yeah?
Right.
And then we... yeah.
And then we will go back and we would launch the globe.
I sure hope this works.
Oh wait, not turn.
Rock.
Woo!
Ah, yippee!
My
medicine!
Oh my god.
Whoa.
I don't think that's gonna help you, mister.
I don't think that's gonna help you.
Help you!
The minister finally took his medicine.
Okay, it took me a minute to get that, but we finally got there.
Yippee!
I think maybe he took too much medicine.
Such a greedy man.
He's supposed to take two capsules with water.
Why doesn't he know that?
Aw, cut the guy some slack.
There.
Oh, there.
See?
He took his meds.
Everyone be like him.
Too much medicine challenge.
We saw all of them go into his mouth.
But we don't know if he swallowed all of them.
That was a lot of work.
Yeah, it was.
You're telling me.
Well, hopefully this taught him a lesson.
Huh?
He greatly underestimated his dependence on his medicine.
I hope he learned something from this experience.
First, know yourself.
That is the key to everything.
I think you need to listen to your own advice, buddy.
Anyway, let's go back to work.
To the world of the present.
Take your meds.
And so the Justice Minister is now back to life.
But the furrows on his brow are even deeper now.
Oh, Lin!
And apparently our Lady Detective is the present cause of those furrows.
Look, Detective.
He was sentenced after a fair trial.
And the man himself wants to be executed.
But there was no evidence!
All they had was his own confession!
But it was no ordinary confession.
It was the confession...
of an esteemed detective.
Well, stay back!
I told you I don't want anybody coming near me.
Okay, you're sensitive.
Mr. Minister, please listen to me!
I might be able to gather new evidence in that case, too!
What?
So please, please, just give me a little more time!
I just got a call from the prison.
Your death row convict apparently just escaped.
Unfortunately, after all this time, it seems he now wants to dodge his punishment.
But...
When he is apprehended, his sentence will be carried out.
Well, he got apprehended, like, really fast.
So...
Tonight.
No...
But when the sentence was handed down, you were against enforcing the death penalty!
So why did you sign the order all of a sudden?
Well, I... I was simply performing my duty as Justice Minister.
That's all there is to it.
Doubling back about the faulty memories, does anybody else remember a...
British Lynn, or am I getting Mandela-affected?
Hmm, that's so mysterious.
I think you're getting Mandela-affected.
Right, everybody?
You're crazy!
She was never British!
Uh...
Okay, let's hit her in the head.
Wham!
Oh!
Oh, wait, that actually worked!
Ah!
Cecil, there you are!
Sounds like the Minister is being very stubborn.
That's right!
Hey, yes!
Oh, sorry.
Maybe we shouldn't have saved him after all.
Damn!
Let him...
The Minister has to be... or has to have the execution carried out tonight.
And he has a very good reason for it.
A good reason?
I told Lynn about what I learned about the kidnapping.
Kidnapping?
Sorry.
They kidnapped the Justice Minister's daughter?
Apparently.
Oh my goodness.
Mint-napping?
No, no, no!
But still...
That's still no reason to hurry forward with the execution.
Why don't you go ahead and say that to the Justice Minister then?
Oh!
Your daughter's life is not worth more than this man.
The poor man.
I hate to do that to him.
Oh, by the way...
Do you think you could carry me?
Hahaha!
Sure.
Not very handy, is it not?
Having no legs.
Oh my gosh.
She's got the whole world in a hand.
She's got the whole...
Wait, what was...
What is that black dot on the...
On the globe?
Oh, you can't get any closer?
The sword and globe combo is heavy.
Mime it.
Oh, it's the North Pole.
Thought it was a bug.
And I'm in here too.
Don't forget.
I guess that means a single soul is heavier than the whole world.
Maybe I'll use this thing to persuade the Minister to change his mind.
Good luck with that.
Dang.
Alright, let's see what he's saying.
What are you going to do with that globe?
Crack me in the head with it?
Oh, this?
Pay no attention to this.
Kind of hard not to pay attention to it.
I know, she looks like she's actually going to attack him.
By the way, and please pardon me if this is a silly question.
Were you talking to someone just now?
But of course not, right?
I mean, there's no such thing as ghosts, right?
Are you talking about me?
Mint Phantom?
No, there's no such thing!
This is a dream.
It's nothing but a dream!
Don't you remember me?
My dream is talking to me!
So now I'm a dream, eh?
Oh my gosh.
I'm starting to want to play Minecraft.
Mr. Minister?
We know.
We know about your daughter.
She was kidnapped.
Wasn't she?
And if the execution doesn't take place tonight, you won't see her again.
Maybe.
Yes!
Oh!
Oh God!
Your medicine!
He took the whole bottle though.
Uh oh.
I think we just committed a murder.
What am I going to do?
The death row prisoner has escaped.
If he isn't executed tonight, my daughter, my Amelie...
But what if that execution isn't the right thing to do?
Come on, Lin.
If you keep pressing him like that, he's going to die again.
What can I do then?
Oh, everybody's at a loss.
Time for me to trick time.
We have to do something about that kidnapping.
Until we do that, it'll be impossible to get the minister on our side.
That's the way I see it.
Gather info on...
Sorry.
Let's see what he has to say.
We meet again, Mr. Minister.
What?
I've never seen you before.
In any case, I'm a very busy man.
If you're a dream, please don't bother me when I'm awake.
I'm not a dream.
She's making me yawn.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I'm trying to get so sleepy.
Looks like it's just a waste of time trying to talk to this guy.
I think you're right.
Stubborn justice minister.
Please stop speaking ill of me inside my own head.
The voices.
The voices hate me.
All right.
Should we go to sexy lady's house?
Here we go.
I really should pay the kidnapper's hideout a visit.
After all, if we want the justice minister to come around, we have to solve this problem first.
I feel like I'm slowly moving away from my own mystery.
But I'm not the kind of guy who can abandon a little lady and a little lady in trouble.
So I guess I'm in this for a little while longer.
That was it.
1141 to 1210 AM challenge.
Save.
Should I call it here?
I'm wondering if I should call it here.
How many?
We got through what?
Three?
Three chapters?
Hold on.
Let me see where we're at.
A little lady.
Ten.
Oh, we're on chapter 11.
What?
11 out of 18?
Your call, boss.
I think maybe the next time we play, I'll endurance it until the end.
So...
Doing next chapter would make for a spice at your end.
Oh.
Is it...
Is it long though?
Is it super long?
It will be long, yeah.
Stopping here is okay?
Yeah, I think maybe I'll just...
It's a little long.
It's not really.
Hmm...
As long as...
As long as your puzzle solving skills.
Thanks, I think.
Sheesh.
Why am I getting insulted?
Like this.
One of the puzzles coming up stumps a lot of people more than the stealth one.
Oh, really?
Okay.
Hmm...
Maybe I'll just...
Since I can't stop the eye...
I can endurance it next time we play and we can go to the end.
So...
Oh gosh, that's a lot of chapters though.
That's probably gonna be like a 10-hour stream.
I guess that's an endurance.
I believe.
I'mma have to endure too.
I really thought we would get through more today.
It is only 10.30.
Hmm...
Try...
Best mom ever.
Great job cooking on those puzzles.
Looking forward to seeing how this ends.
Have fun with Ayami-sensei tomorrow.
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you!
I would book two more streams.
Yeah...
Maybe we'll do two streams then.
Okay.
So one next week and then one more the week after.
And then it will be good.
I'll finish it up before I go to Japan.
Actually, that works.
Because I wasn't planning on starting a new channel.
I'll start a new, longer series until I get back from Japan.
So once I'm back from Japan, we can start something new.
Okay.
Cool.
Two streams with about four chapters each seems chill.
I agree, I agree.
Cool, cool, cool.
Thanks guys for joining again today!
Thank you!
It's a little bit less of a cliffhanger, but...
There's still so much mystery going on.
Why couldn't he just say who we were, man?
Why is he keeping us in such a mystery?
Also, I want to make sure I'm well rested for Ayami-sensei tomorrow.
There's a little bit...
I don't want to say an announcement.
But...
Something kind of cool...
In tomorrow's stream.
So...
I think...
It would be fun.
And if you don't know Ayami-sensei...
She's so silly and fun.
I think...
It will be a fun stream.
Yes, yes, yes.
So...
Ayami is so cute.
I know!
I love Ayami-sensei so much!
So...
Yeah!
The push-push mama!
Push-push!
And Ayami is...
Ayami, does she speak English?
She does, actually!
Ayami speaks such good English.
I'm going to try and...
See how much English she'll speak tomorrow.
But...
She is coming to the United States for a convention this weekend.
And...
So she's going to ask me some questions about the U.S.
And she also wanted to kind of get to know me a little bit more.
Since this is our first ever collab together.
And...
But she was like so nervous.
She was so worried about...
She was like...
I wonder if anybody is going to come see me at that convention.
She's going to be at Anime Central this weekend.
She was like...
I wonder if anybody is going to come see me.
And then I checked yesterday for her autographs.
I was like...
I wonder how...
Like...
You know...
How her autographs are doing.
And they were all sold out!
And I was like...
Or booked...
Booked up, I guess.
I don't think they were...
I think they were free.
But they were all like gone.
And I was like...
I sent it to her.
Ayami-sensei!
You were so worried for nothing!
So...
Everybody be extra nice to Ayami-sensei.
Yeah!
They were out within the hour?
Oh my gosh, really?
Reminds me of a certain someone who always underestimates herself.
I wonder who that could be.
You know a lot of people.
But yeah.
So we're going to talk about her coming to the US.
And...
What she'll be doing at the convention.
And some other stuff.
Talking about me a little bit.
Well...
Maybe more than a little bit.
She was like so interested.
She was like...
I want to know everything about Mint.
And so I was like...
Okay.
So yeah.
She's the only BtoBer at ASEN this year.
Yeah.
Actually, you're right.
Oh my gosh.
But...
Exciting.
She wants to be a BtoBer.
She wants your three sizes.
That's not even a joke.
But yeah.
I'm really, really excited.
I hope then...
Next time we collab, maybe it could be like a game or something.
So...
I'll see you guys tomorrow then.
For Ayami.
And...
And then Wednesday for English Karaoke.
I haven't...
I have no plan set list.
So if you have any songs that you maybe are like, hey, Mito, I recommend this song, you can always leave it in the comments or you can leave it in the live tag on Twitter.
So I will look through it.
I will read it.
Anna Rock, welcome to membership.
Thank you.
Anything weird, Al?
Okay.
Goodbye, Virtual YouTuber Maidment.
Thank you.
Goodbye, Jordan.
Halo theme.
Limp Bizkit.
Tenacious D.
Oh, I know one Tenacious D song.
I don't remember what it's called.
I think it's the one that like everybody knows.
Don't...
But stop.
Stop recommending stuff now.
Stop.
Not yet.
Yeah.
Tribute.
Was gifted at membership, but now I'm recruiting.
Oh my gosh.
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
I appreciate it so much.
Oh yeah.
Stop.
Don't recommend songs now.
Recommend them later.
So recommend them when I have them on paper or on pixels so that I can remember.
Write them down at least.
Enjoy your trip to Alcatraz.
If I can go, but beware the island is the most haunted location in California and possibly the country.
Sell Block D and particular items.
The most haunted place on the island.
The island has eons of bad mojo.
It's okay.
I'm a ghost too.
And if any ghost tries to mess with me, I'll just punch them.
Which one is cuter for you, Minty?
Imperial Stormtroopers, Original Trilogy or First Order Stormtroopers, Sequel Trilogy?
Also, whose armor is cooler?
Captain Rex or Commander Wolf?
Okay.
Hold on.
I'm going to have to look up all of these real quick.
Okay.
This isn't the best Super Chat in the world.
This is just a tribute.
Okay.
Original...
Wait.
First Order Stormtrooper?
What's the difference between them and the original?
Oh, wait.
Oh, I see it.
Wait.
They look the same to me.
Am I dumb?
Cooler.
Captain Rex, Captain Rex, Star Wars.
Oh, I like his.
Or Commander Wolf.
Oh.
Uh...
I think Captain Rex' is cooler.
I don't know.
Commander Wolf for sure.
Wait, am I looking at the wrong pictures?
Commander Wolf.
Hold on.
Oh, oh wait.
Yes, Commander Wolf.
You're right.
I was looking at the wrong thing.
Yeah, Commander Wolf looks cooler.
I think.
Oh, sorry.
Everyone said base.
I don't know.
Rex is the best.
And they both look really nice.
I like the blue.
How could my Oshii betray me?
Okay, guys.
I'm gonna go.
I'm gonna go sleep now.
Thank you guys again for watching and hanging out with me today.
And we'll finish this up in two more streams.
Oh my gosh.
Do you guys want to see the coolest thing that I've seen today at all?
I'm still trying to decide if I should pre-order this.
It's so awesome.
Thanks for the fun stream.
Can't wait for the next part.
Thank you!
Wait.
Oh, I can't show you.
Oh no.
It's on the other screen.
And it's hidden.
I'm currently on my... I'm on my other...
It's on my other monitor.
I can't get to it.
Okay, never mind.
Okay.
I'm gonna go now.
Otsuminto!
It wasn't a Metal Gear thing.
Just tell us what it is.
Okay.
I saw it on AmiAmi earlier.
It's a...
It's a... It's a Rubik's Cube.
But it transforms into a mech.
But it's a real Rubik's... Well, I don't know if it's a real Rubik's Cube.
But it can turn into a Rubik's Cube.
Like the cube version.
And then you can also turn it into a mech.
It's so awesome!
I want it.
What's the name?
Chogokin Rubik's Cube.
It's so cool!
I was looking at it.
Alright.
I think... I was... Yeah.
Anyway.
Ignoring...
Ignoring what I just saw.
What was I saying?
I'd be a hypocrite if I didn't support you buying a transforming toy.
Nah, I was considering it.
I was just...
But I thought it was so cool.
But I don't know if I'll get it yet.
It's kind of expensive, so I was like...
And I already have some other figures I have to wait for.
So... You know...
Anyway.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you for hanging out.
See you guys tomorrow.
Bye bye.
Have a good night.
Bye!
Have a good night!
Get lots of rest.
Drink some water.
Stay hydrated.
Itterashai!
Bye-bye!
It's so cool!
Look at him!
He's just a guy.
He's just so...
But he transformed into a Rubik's Cube!
I think if I knew how to solve a Rubik's Cube, I would definitely get it.
If I was like a huge Rubik's Cube fan.
But just the whole thing is such a fun concept, right?
Mecha Rubik's Ultimate Form!
It's just a guy!
Yeah!
It's so cool, right?
Got T-pose.
It looks kind of... when he's not Rubik's, he looks kind of like a Tetris man.
Looks like the T... like a T-block.
A guy!
Bye-bye!