Oh, wait.
Go back to the main menu.
Go back to the main menu!
What?
There we go.
Kept you waiting, huh?
Howdy, Minto!
Hi, Minto!
Welcome back to Metal Gear Solid 2!
Yippee!
Yippee, yippee, yippee!
Yippee, yippee!
Good morning, Minto, even though it's afternoon.
Good morning, Minto.
What took you so long, Minto?
I don't know.
I think... I don't know.
I was distracted on TikTok.
But yes, welcome back.
And everything.
I'm gonna do my best to get through as much of the game as possible today.
But no pressure if I don't finish or do finish or whatever.
It's the Vinyl guy from the con!
I hope you enjoy it.
Also, your Q&A was fun.
We hope to see you back in Texas again.
Thank you, Breeze!
Oh my gosh!
I can't wait!
Oh my gosh.
The Vinyl, I'm so...
Thank you!
Can we have a quick recap from the previous two episodes?
Of course, Paul!
That's a great... That's a great idea.
So...
For those who are familiar with the game, we are right about to...
To...
Disable the bombs and then...
No, that is not Solid Snake.
But...
If you... Oh my gosh.
Thank you for all the super chats!
Oh my gosh.
Hold on.
I'll give you a second.
And then I'll read them.
Let me do the recap first.
And...
I'm trying not to, like, spoil.
So...
Basically...
From the very beginning...
Two years ago...
On...
In...
In New York...
The Hudson River...
Two years ago...
Solid Snake dies!
Solid Snake dies on the tanker after he fought Olga...
And after...
Ocelot...
Stole the Metal Gear...
He double-crossed...
Gurlukovich...
And...
Um...
Killed Gurlukovich...
The Russian...
Um...
Side...
And everything...
Um...
And he stole...
Metal Gear Ray...
From...
Um...
From the military...
And he was just like...
Ha ha ha...
This is mine!
And...
Um...
Then...
Solid Snake dies.
So sad.
So, so sad.
But then we move two years later...
On to the...
Um...
To the Big Shell...
The Big Shell incident where...
A group of terrorists...
Called...
Dead Cell...
Have taken hold...
Of the President.
Oh my god!
Not the President!
And...
Um...
They're...
But...
They're led by their leader...
Solid Snake!
Whoa!
Oh my gosh...
Not Solid Snake...
But he died...
On the tanker...
Two years ago!
What?
And...
Um...
So we are riding...
And we're going around...
And we've disabled bombs...
We...
Um...
Well, the guy who taught...
Taught us how to disable bombs...
Also blew up...
So...
Um...
We fought...
A fat man...
We...
Um...
Uh...
We met Fortune...
And she's really sexy...
Yeah...
We met a bisexual...
Um...
That was Vamp...
We...
Uh...
Met Plissken...
Who...
Um...
We've never met that guy before...
Ever before...
And...
Um...
Yeah...
Now...
We're trying to get to...
The president...
Um...
But first we must cross a field of...
Bombs...
That we must disable...
Blow up...
We must shoot the bombs...
Iroquois Plissken...
Maximilian!
Thank you!
First time being able to catch a Metal Gear stream live...
So it's lovely to see you in real time...
I hope you're taking care of yourself...
And that you have a fantastic day...
Thank you!
Yoshi!
Welcome back for two months!
Awesome to be here!
Love you guys!
Thank you!
Football!
Oh...
Today's not my birthday...
But it was on Thursday...
I kept missing your streams because of work...
Can I get a happy birthday please?
Of course!
Happy birthday to you...
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday dear football!
Happy birthday!
I think I got everything...
Did I cover everything?
Is that everything?
We saw some sexy ladies in lockers, some sexy ladies in the bathroom.
Schrodinger's snake.
He's simultaneously dead and not dead.
Yes.
There was a parrot?
Yeah, we saw a parrot.
Oh, Rose!
Nothing of Rose.
And Olga.
Yes.
Well, sorry, I said Gurlukovich, I forgot to mention his daughter, Olga.
We fought her on the tanker as snake, and now she's still working with Ocelot and not Solid Snake.
And, of course, Raiden has his lovely, lovely, lovely partner of... lifetime partner who he'll never abandon, who he'll never ever take for granted, who she is loyal and will never leave him either.
They're going to grow happy and old and die together.
And that's Rose.
And she...
And they never have any problems.
They're the healthiest relationship ever.
What did I ask?
Because I asked this to get different views.
What motivates you to keep going in life?
When things get stressful, what do you do to keep yourself from worrying about things?
That's a deep question, Yoshi.
Thanks for the super chat.
What keeps me going in my afterlife is...
The ability to see my Oshi.
If I can see my Oshi, then there's something worth staying dead for.
And I always worry.
Sorry, I don't stop worrying.
I don't know how to do that yet.
Good morning, Mint-chan.
Good morning.
Wish me luck.
I have multiple job interviews next...
Subplots!
Good luck with your interviews!
Oh my gosh!
Good luck, good luck, good luck!
But yeah, now I think I got everything.
So yeah, we're about to disable some bombs.
And...
Yeah.
We'll see how far I get today.
I'm thinking...
I don't know.
Andrew goes next to the 20 gifted!
Thank you.
Load.
How did we get to 2099?
Huh?
Wait.
How did we get to...
Huh?
Poor MGS2.
My brain is still comprehending Hideo Kojima's tweets about Deadpool Wolverine.
Yes.
I love Hideo Kojima's tweets about the new Deadpool Wolverine movie.
And how he was just like...
It's so awesome seeing Wolverine so ripped.
And so muscular.
And I'm like...
What do you mean by that?
Oshilove is strong, for real, for real.
Hi mint, my Oshii.
Hello!
Wow, it's been 99 years.
What does he mean?
I don't...
He means what he said.
That guy...
That guy always means what he says, right?
Oh!
Alright, let me get used to the game once again.
So, am I going to get a call from Colonel if I get too close?
Oh!
Raiden, you haven't destroyed all the control units yet.
Oh.
Use the first person view or the sniper scope to look around.
How's the audio, by the way?
Let me know.
The Otakutan 2024 schedule was uploaded on guidebook.
Looks like your meet and greet autograph is Friday, day one, evening.
Hoping there will be space in line if I line up.
Five hours!
Oh my gosh, Ghost of Mid, please.
You don't have to...
I have several meet and greets for Otakutan this coming weekend.
I have several meet and greets, so please don't feel like you have to line up so early, okay?
Please don't...
Please.
Just another day for Raiden, aka Agent Lovely Hips.
Best dancer.
Now it's time to eat chicken.
Yippee!
Yes, and I do have...
Let's see.
Let me get all my ducks in a row.
That's how I'm kicking.
This is how I'm...
Oh gosh, don't go overboard, Raiden.
All right, let's...
We have a sniper.
Where is our sniper?
Oh, here it is.
We have...
Look at that.
We have the PSG-1T Tranquilizer Rifle.
Tranquilizer...
Tranquilizer Rifle, yeah...
But we're going to use this one.
How do I zoom in on this thing?
Zoom with O.
Fire with square.
O...
Sons of Libra.
I've got to get that bird.
I'm going to get that bird.
Hold on.
Stop, Raiden.
Stop!
He's like...
Don't...
I think I got it.
Does it not shoot through the...
Does it not shoot through the thing?
Does it not shoot through the flag?
Oops, I pressed the wrong button.
Oh gosh, I don't want to run out of bullets.
You'll hear it if you get it.
I think I need to take some posesamine.
Where is my posesamine?
Or... wait a second.
Raiden has cigarettes!
Oh, I have ten of them.
Perfect.
There we go.
Okay.
I think I'll get it.
What the heck?
Okay, let's get the other stuff first.
Let's get the other things first.
Oh, move birds!
Move!
Okay, that's one.
I don't know actually how many there are.
Move birds!
Move!
I don't think I killed him.
There's two.
I don't know how many there are.
Three?
Wait, why are those still blinking though?
Also, I don't... Oh!
There it is.
Alright.
Wind!
Oh!
Oh, I got it.
Nice.
How did you guys... I can't hear it.
Am I deaf?
How many are left?
Raiden, you didn't get all the control units.
You weren't thorough enough.
I'm not done!
Take a good look at the airborne cipher.
You can see the control unit for the IR sensor.
Huh?
The control unit is right above cipher's camera.
Avoid shooting the camera at all costs.
Looks like if a cipher is shot down, the resulting signal will trigger an explosion.
The whole bridge would blow.
Target only the control unit on the upper part of the cipher.
Aim for the blinking light.
Blinking light.
Okay, I wasn't...
Let me finish my art!
I know there's a cipher.
Oh, here.
Oh, a blinking light?
Okay, I got you.
Oh, geez.
Oh, gosh.
Oh!
You sent the blinking light!
What the hell happened?
Raiden!
Snake!
You sent the blinking light!
Oh, gosh.
I mean, Plissken.
Sorry.
I swear that guy, like, just gets me every time.
Thanks for making AFES a fun experience.
I already bragged about meeting you.
It's the second most famous person in my friends.
I'm not even.
Thanks to your brainwrap panel, I now learned MGS is really about butts.
Yeah!
Thank you for coming to meet me!
Thank you so much.
Yeah, Freudian slip.
Freudian slip.
Same voice actor?
I don't think even...
I think they sound really different, actually.
I don't even think it's the same voice actor.
I think it's just, you know...
Okay.
Did I misunderstand what you said?
Plissken?
Plissken, oh Plissken.
Alright, alright, come on.
Come on, Raiden.
Raiden, Raiden, shaking hands, Raiden.
Raiden, Raiden.
Raiden, stop shaking your...
There we go.
Stop shaking your hands right now, Raiden.
I don't know how, actually, that managed to hit.
I'll be honest.
That didn't seem like it should have hit.
Because I was low.
Can I go down now?
I deactivated it!
Raiden!
But I deactivated them!
Okay.
That's a no.
This is...
This is what's gonna take the longest.
In today's stream.
Just trying to...
Okay, well now I know.
Okay.
And one more over here.
No, we're not finishing.
Shut up!
This part?
Yeah, we're not finishing this part today.
Yeah, guys.
Sorry.
Oh, dang it.
No, come on, Raiden!
Raiden!
Ow!
Oh my god.
This is the...
Colonel didn't even...
Actually, was that Colonel?
He didn't even sound like he was sad about me dying.
He sounded so disappointed.
He was like, Raiden, what are you doing?
Raiden!
Okay, I'll take the...
I was trying to do it without the Pizazzamine, but I'll do it with it.
Okay, guys.
We won't blow up this time.
This is the run.
Can I still get it?
Even when it's behind the flag.
I never actually knew if I could...
Oh yeah, I did.
Okay, nice.
Then there's the one...
What's the blinking light?
Oh, at the very, very top?
Maybe?
What's the blinking light?
Bulletproof flag.
The flag was...
still there.
Oh say...
Uh...
Pizazzamine.
Green light.
Did I not get the green...
Gosh, this part's so silly.
Plissken?
I thought I got the blinking light.
Okay, I'm gonna aim for the tippy-toe.
No, no, no, no.
Yippee!
Okay, and...
Oh, I remember this one.
Is that all of them?
Oh, gosh.
I don't remember...
what other ones there are.
Was there any that I need to lay down for?
Because we'll...
They tell you when we're good, so...
They tell you when we're good.
Plenty of laying down ones.
Why?
I don't know why I'm...
Mustache Man!
Why?
Thank you for the welcome to...
Looking forward to more episodes of everyone's favorite telenovela.
Reglas de la...
Natural...
Naturaliza.
What?
Oh!
I see it, I see it!
Oh, yes!
That's... Duh!
The one that I got before!
This one.
Does it mean?
Uh...
Zoom in.
Enhance.
Sorry, birds.
I'm gonna destroy this party.
Why can't I move just slightly?
Oh!
There we go!
Yay!
I don't think I hit one.
Did I?
I don't think so.
Pew!
Alright!
Okay, are you guys ready?
Wait.
I have a grenade launcher.
I don't have a stinger.
Do I get it here?
I sure hope so.
Let's go!
They'll toss you one?
Okay.
I'm all ears.
Is it in good shape?
Full tank.
I'm heading for shell one now.
What about that Harrier?
It's not on the heliport here.
Good.
I'll set this one down there then.
Can you cover the hostages?
They're being held on level B1 in the core.
It's... yeah.
You didn't happen to find any other places where hostages were being held, did you?
No.
Nothing like that.
Okay.
How many hostages are there?
There's a few short of 30.
One dead and several wounded.
The Kasatka's cargo area will hold 13 max.
What about the other Kasatka?
Kasatka?
I sabotaged it.
It can't come after us if it can't get off the ground.
No.
We'll have to make two trips.
Can you fly a Kasatka?
I have a pilot who's flown the civilian model.
The Ka-62 and VR.
There's not a whole lot of difference between the military Ka-60 and the civilian model.
No.
Cleared for takeoff.
Let me introduce you to my partner, Otacon.
Otacon?
Hey, Raiden.
Nice to meet you.
It's Brutus!
Over here!
Damn!
Raiden, I'll talk to you later.
Oh my god!
It's Sna- I mean, Plissken!
I'm sorry.
I'm the worst.
Colonel, I need some answers from you.
Who exactly is Plissken and his partner?
I know what you're thinking.
It keeps coming back to Shadow Moses.
And now this Otacon...
A.K.A.
Hal Emmerich, Ph.D.
A Shadow Moses survivor.
Rose?
Snake and Otacon both became fugitives after Shadow Moses wanted to act as a terrorist.
...in that section where Colonel is just angry.
...an anti-Metal Gear organization.
They sabotaged and destroyed countless Metal Gear units throughout the world.
And were responsible for the incident two years ago that necessitated the construction of the Big Shell.
Snake and his partner aren't terrorists.
Wait.
What do you mean Snake and his partner?
You mean Plissken?
I look back on what I've done here so far.
And things like training and sense of duty alone won't get you through a sneaky mission like this.
Jack, are you okay?
Are you okay?
I can't think of the right word, but it has to be pure will.
Backed up by courage or ideals or something like that.
He's starting to believe.
The Solid Snake that saved Shadow Moses couldn't turn into a terrorist.
Yeah.
Maybe that's true.
But they went down with that tanker two years ago.
We even recovered Snake's body.
Yeah.
And the DNA test results on the body say it's him.
It's him.
Jack, I know what you're saying, but Snake is dead.
Hmm.
He can't be here.
Not sure how I feel about that.
Not even as this Dr. Hal Emmerich.
But that also means that he can't be the terrorist leader behind this thing.
Yeah, he died.
He died.
No more Solid Snake.
Whoa.
Uh-oh.
A Harrier?
No.
I love that guy.
I love that guy!
No Harrier.
We're good to go, guys.
A trash bag!
I've been waiting for you.
A messenger from the Patriots.
A messenger
from the Patriots.
No, not just around here.
I'm the boss to surpass Big Boss himself.
Solid Snake.
No!
That is not Solid Snake!
No,
that is not Solid Snake!
What a pleasant surprise, brother.
Save it.
Don't say you've forgotten me.
Oh my god, the...
Snake!
That was Snake?
No.
Who was you?
Solid Snake 2.
Snake?
Take cover.
Ahhh!
Oh my god, you're gonna blow up the whole bridge!
Oh my god, he's so awesome.
Stop impersonating him!
Yeah!
Identity theft is real!
Brother, I'm a whole different game from Liquid.
Nano Machines.
Oh my god.
I cried.
Wow!
Um, hi!
There's someone else on the bridge here.
Please...
Oh my god.
Oof!
The voice acting is so low compared to like the sound effects and the audio and everything.
Ah!
No, complain.
There it is.
There's the Harrier.
We're
in trouble.
It's the Harrier.
He's getting...
Just shave him!
Wax him!
If he's Harrier!
Oh.
He's a shrinky baby.
How can a plane like that be sneaky?
The world needs only one big boss!
Oh my god, Top Gun moment.
I'll drown you fools for interfering!
Ahhh!
My
ears, please!
Right.
This is the Stinger Missile Launcher.
Yippee!
The Kasaka can't stand up to the Harrier.
Why not?
You have to shoot the Harrier down.
Oh, okay.
It's happening in the bay right now.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no.
This is a little far out.
But we do eventually get to the bay.
I thought you meant like this is happening in the bay right now in New York.
Hahaha.
Okay, I'm going downstairs.
Goodbye!
Okay.
How do I remember to do this?
Oh!
Oh my gosh!
Please get... Why are you sending it to me from up there?
Okay.
Where is it?
Where?
Oh, Stinger.
Oh my god.
Blalalalalala.
Oh my goodness!
Oh gosh, I have to remember how to do this fight.
Where is he anyway?
Oh.
He's on this side.
Beep, beep, beep, beep.
Where are you?
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
I think he's upstairs.
Oh yeah, there he is.
Ah!
Oh.
I think I ran into the wall.
Everybody.
Classic.
Minto move.
Oh.
Get out of the way, Plissken!
You're scaring me.
Oh my god, there he is.
Shoot the copter.
Take cover!
Take cover?
I think.
Is this when he starts doing everything?
Where is he anyway?
Oh.
Oh my god, he's so fast.
Yeah, it would be great if I...
Hahahahaha.
Bozo!
What are you going to take...
What are you going to take care of, huh?
Oh my god.
Is that the best you can do?
Well, if you would just give me a chance!
I'm just standing here.
Hahahahaha.
Let me in!
Mom said it's my turn!
This thing is so fast.
Oh my god.
Ah!
This is when he starts blowing everything up.
Hahahahaha.
Oh.
Go in!
For the kill!
I would have just hit the wall.
Am I even going to get a shot at getting this guy?
Where is he?
Where'd he go?
Oh, there he is.
Come on!
Oh my god, it...
Oh.
And
I wait.
Risk it, go upstairs.
Why do I need to go upstairs?
I'm cozy down here.
Is that the best you can do?
You have...
You have not hit...
You maybe have hit me once.
Come on!
Is that the best you can do?
I'm literally standing still!
Solid dust?
Best you can do.
My butt.
Where are you?
Oh my god.
Oh, there he is.
Just...
I always loved how when you shoot a semtex, the whole bridge blows up.
But with these two...
I know, right?
It's so unfair.
Where...
Oh no!
Okay.
Oh!
Oh my god, he did hit me.
Oh god, he did get me.
Okay, I'm good now.
Got hit by a missile, no biggie.
Nice!
Hit you!
There we go.
Did I get him?
I don't think I did.
Shoot.
No, I don't think I got him!
Wait, can I get him here?
Come on, come on.
Oh, I don't think I will.
I think I'm gonna blow myself up if I try.
Ah!
Oh!
Can you get up, Ryland?
Is he gonna get me?
I think I should...
Yeah, I know.
I was totally looking the wrong way.
Where does he come from?
He like comes usually from like this.
Where is he?
Ah!
Oh, you're bleeding again.
This guy is so all over the place.
Fire, fire.
Get his butt!
Just take the shot!
There we go.
These camera angles crack me up.
I'll shred you to pieces!
Oof!
Gosh, he's got so much health.
What are you taking care of anyway?
What are you doing?
His butt is so prominent.
I swear!
In the HD collection!
I think they nerfed Ryland because...
He looks good in this game.
He looks good, good in this game.
I'm not!
Oh my gosh.
You!
Oof!
My man just says oof.
So funny.
Oof.
What is this?
Die!
Yeah!
You're tougher than I thought.
I'm just sitting down here, dude.
I'll let you go out in style!
Did I get him?
Nice!
Oh, but not like...
Not super...
It's not a super good shot.
Nice!
Still got him though.
It's hard finding him sometimes.
Oh!
Woo!
Take the shot!
Oh, I didn't get him.
Bit by bit.
Yeah, bit by bit.
Ugh.
Oh, gosh!
He's out here somewhere.
We'll get him.
Oh, there he is.
Run!
Nice.
We get that nice, good old head-on collision.
Did I get him?
I can't tell sometimes if I get him or not.
Die!
What a tough walk, boy.
Okay.
I'll let you take care of...
Oh!
Is he on the other side?
Where is he?
Oh!
Shoot.
Dun, dun, dun.
Okay.
Oh!
Oh, this side?
Oh, he's doing his like far away thing, right?
There he is.
There he is!
Got a lot of smoke coming off of you.
Buddy.
You're
not looking so good, man.
This thing is...
It's just indestructible.
Yeah!
Oh, my God.
That was like the small...
Oh!
It's like the smallest amount of damage ever.
How much...
How many bullets?
Oh, I still have a lot of bullets.
But I don't know if I'm gonna be able to get him in time, to be honest.
There he is.
Oh, maybe I can.
Maybe I will.
We'll see.
Die!
Oh, dang it!
Oh, my gosh.
Can I get him from here?
Wow!
Okay, let me try again.
It's the little...
Oh, nice, nice, nice, nice.
Okay, good, good, good, good.
Is that the best you can do?
Okay, he's back on that side.
And...
Shoot!
I didn't... I didn't get him.
Oh, thank you!
Where?
Oh, up there!
You're gonna make me run for it?
Come on!
I'll let you go out in style!
I usually
like to get him...
during that part, but...
Hey!
I'll let you go out in style!
Bye, Solonit!
We got his eye!
Into the ocean!
Oh!
There's something coming up!
It's my throw-up.
It's my throw-up!
Whaaa!
All right.
So dramatic.
That's Metal Gear!
It's already active!
Oh, my gosh.
It catches it in his mouth.
It's the cutest thing.
Look how cute!
Ray is just like a little puppy dog.
How can you not think Ray is the cutest thing ever?
There's a blade in his mouth!
He's so cute!
Oh my god, what a show.
You got this, Raiden!
Level 2 grip!
Yeah, if we hadn't had the level 2 grip, we would have fallen into the ocean.
True facts.
Oof.
You might want to get, like, an eyepatch or something for that.
Who are you telling that to?
Vamp?
Does he care?
They got my eye!
Me eye!
Where is he going?
Vamp, go!
He's like...
He jumps into the water and swims away?
Like, where is he going?
Oh my gosh!
Please, Plissken!
He's just... Oh my gosh, he's watching the show.
Oh my god.
He's like...
When I see some buns, I get hungry.
Oh, there he goes.
What a freak, this guy.
It.
It's running on water.
He doesn't even call Vamp, like, a person.
Vamp is an it.
Oh my god.
Vamp, the true strongest character in the series.
Raiden doesn't know what to think about any of that.
Raiden, you alright?
Yeah.
How about you guys?
Yeah, you have some splainin' to do.
The chopper?
We need some time for repairs.
The chopper.
The president's all yours.
Can I ask you something?
What?
Are you THE snake?
They said you were dead.
Big shell's only like three inches deep.
No, not me.
There are still too many things I need to do.
Oh my god!
Snake, you're a legend, and that's why I need to ask you this.
Yeah.
Legend.
A legend is nothing but fiction.
Someone tells it, someone else remembers.
Everybody passes it on.
I'm here because I was assigned to this mission, not because I want to.
Be snake.
If I could, I'd be out of here in a second.
So it was snake after all.
How could you come back to all this?
Why keep fighting?
There's something my best friend said to me once.
What?
We're not tools of the government, or anyone else.
Fighting was the only thing I was good at, but at least I always fought for what I believed in.
What about the DNA results from that body?
That was Liquid's body.
He and Snake are identical on the genetic level.
Liquid?
For our own protection.
We stole his frozen body from some organization.
That's crazy.
Kind of a hassle though.
That's all there is to it.
We just took his body.
Are you to me an NGO?
Insofar as we're a non-profit organization of civilians advocating a cause, yes.
The cause happens to be the eradication of Metal Gear.
Yes.
We work on our own.
Philanthropy.
But it's a cause worth fighting for.
Why would you stick your neck out for something this risky?
That's the way I used to look at it.
Four years ago.
I was holed up in the middle of nowhere in Alaska.
Drinking too much.
We have a responsibility to the coming generations.
You had dogs!
What are you talking about?
What responsibility?
Keep track of the mistakes we've made as a species.
Crazy how Plissken disappears and Snake shows up.
I know.
To fight for change.
And that's what keeps me alive.
History says we're very complex.
You think you can change the future?
I'm not as arrogant as that.
What you do isn't grassroots activism.
It's more like terrorism.
Hey!
No it's not.
I mean, maybe it is.
But our group, Philanthropy, received some information.
A new Metal Gear prototype was being developed here.
And terrorists were planning to raid the facility.
The information came from a very reliable source.
So you're here too.
We're here to stop all that.
Very reliable.
But I also have a personal motive.
Looks like the terrorists have his sister in the big shell.
Oh my god.
We're here on our own.
Not under anyone's orders.
We have our own battles.
No.
Otacon's here for someone.
I'm not.
This is a military mission.
So?
O-okay.
Jack, are you alright?
Just barely.
You almost gave me a heart attack.
Here you go again.
It wasn't intentional.
I know that.
And I know I need to stay stronger.
Say a prayer for me, Rose.
So I can come back.
You will make it back.
I'm with you all the way.
Remember.
That means a lot to me, you know.
Aww.
I'm going to save the data.
Okay, Jack?
Yes, thank you.
Alright, now we're about halfway through, right?
So...
Good stuff.
Twenty-nine to nine.
These two are so inseparable.
What?
They're the best ever!
Colonel, Metal Gear's already gone active.
It's not too late.
You can still prevent a nuclear strike by securing the President.
And preventing password confirmation from taking place.
Okay.
Get to the President.
He's in the core section of Shell 2.
I'm checking the satellite images.
Looks like you can get to the core from the other side of Strut L.
The core hasn't gone under yet, from what we can tell.
Follow the railings down.
Then jump onto the pipes.
Okay.
The only viable strut in the outer perimeter is the L.
That attack just now doesn't make any sense.
It's like they have no more use for this place.
Colonel, you were monitoring the codec calls.
That man was the real Snake all along.
Yeah.
Maybe.
Don't let your guard down with him.
Why do you say that?
Because they were never a part of the simulation.
They're an unknown factor.
Maybe.
You can take this simulation and...
Yeah.
We're out here, we bleed, we die.
I'll say it for you, Raiden.
Shove it up your ass.
Calm down.
I suggest that you do, Raiden.
Shove it.
Even if that is Snake.
That has no bearing on your mission.
Colonel.
You and Snake used to be allies.
You and Snake used to be on the same side.
I don't understand.
I read about you and Snake in In the Darkness of Shadow Moses.
I don't give a damn what that piece of trash said.
Do you get me?
You've changed, Colonel.
Colonel in this game is so...
So...
He's so mean.
He's so mean in this game.
Why you gotta be so mean?
Oh, wait.
The coolant is this one, right?
Here it is.
Snake broke his heart.
Okay.
Now I won't accidentally burn myself.
What?
Oh!
Wait!
Wasn't there a ration in there?
Aww.
Oh.
Oh, man.
So much for that ration.
No!
Puskin, can you send me another, please?
I forgot that it was gonna fall.
No!
I just cartwheel over...
Wait.
How do I...
I don't remember, actually.
Do I just cartwheel over?
Oh, gosh.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, on the other side.
The one with the bird poop?
The side that's actually trying to kill me?
It's a leap of faith.
Jack!
What's going on?
Answer me!
Jack?
Jack!
It's Jack, right there, floating.
Never learning how to swim.
No faith.
Wait!
We can get the ration now.
Maybe.
Hold on.
Okay.
I'm not gonna...
I'm...
I'm listening to Mei Ling.
I'm not gonna be so stupid to always try for the...
You know?
I don't have to...
But...
What if I just...
Run down?
Grab it?
Run up?
What a gamer.
Yeah!
Okay.
All right.
I have to...
Oh, gosh.
He'll grab onto this, right?
Mei Ling is right.
You're just that good.
You missed the boat.
Here we...
Lean onto the railing.
No!
This isn't happening.
Jack, you have to answer me!
Jack!
Nice one, gamer.
Thank you.
Oh!
Someone's calling me.
Wait, what?
My cell phone is going off.
Hello?
Use the cool it spreader...
God damn it!
I know!
What do you think I've been doing?
God, how did you get this number?
How did you get this number?
Happy April 30th!
Please remember to live, laugh, love in these trying times.
Thank you.
I don't remember how to do it.
I remember having to go to that pipe over there and be careful of the bird poop and everything.
I just don't remember how to get over there.
Live, laugh, grow fat.
Flip over the railing after pressing on it.
Oh!
Thank you.
You think this is a good spot?
Over a little bit.
Level 2 grip, baby.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, Raiden, Raiden, Raiden.
You're scaring me, Raiden.
Okay.
Crawl, crawl, crawl.
I hate this part.
Crawl, crawl.
This is even how speedrunners do it.
They're too scared.
They're too scared of this part.
They crawl too.
Everybody crawl.
Oh, my God.
Jump.
Yippee!
Okay.
We're all good.
Oh, no.
Almost.
Almost there.
Grab it.
Grab, Raiden.
Grab the...
Go.
Lift up.
Lift.
Remember the basics of skateboarding.
Oh!
It's on fire now!
Wait!
Was it always on fire?
Did that just happen?
Run!
There are guys here, aren't there?
I don't have a nerd.
Aren't there guys here though?
Where do they come out?
Scoot, scoot, scoot.
Jump!
No sir, no sir, no sir.
Oh my gosh.
I have to get them to move closer.
Perfect.
Nobody else, right?
Nothing here.
Oh no.
Dangling.
Dangle, dangle, dangle, dangle.
Dangle, dangle, dangle, dangle, dangle.
Dangle, dangle.
Isn't this where the AK-74 suppressor is?
Wait, really?
Hi Mint.
Hello!
Wait, is it actually?
Are those guys still asleep?
Or...
Who am I hearing?
Who am I hearing right now?
Oh, this is where they're...
This is the windows.
I remember this part.
Oh gosh, I remember this part.
I wonder how far can I get from...
dangle dangling.
Oh my god.
You'll encounter nothing.
Gosh, he saw me so fast.
Uh...
Just a vax?
They won't be able to see me.
Oh my god.
Just a vax!
Just a...
Do you think he can tell?
Just
a vax!
Just a vax!
Those other guys are still asleep.
Maybe I'm okay.
Maybe I can go.
Bam, bam, bam.
I don't think I can crawl here, because I'm pretty sure at some point the, um...
From what I remember...
Oh my gosh, I can't use it here.
Oh my god.
Oh no, no!
That's not what I meant to do.
Don't the floors give out though at some point?
Go up, go up.
When do we get beat on?
I'm scared.
Soon.
Are those guys still asleep over here?
No way.
Oh gosh, I wish I could take them out again.
There's too many guys!
Go away!
You know what?
Screw it.
Let's just crawl.
For now.
I can't see where they are.
Oh!
Okay, but this is...
Maybe okay.
Now I can at least see where he is.
You know?
Oh,
alright, nice.
Level 2, grab baby!
Bye!
Bye losers!
Bye idiot!
Wait!
Oh wait.
Oh god, it looks like always he's looking directly at me.
Right?
Freaks me out.
Okay.
Now...
Careful.
Can I...
Wait, how do I get past that part?
Can I just walk past it?
You can crouch mid-press.
Duck?
Okay.
Thank you.
In fact, we'll just do that the whole way, baby.
Wait.
I think...
Oh, look at... this is such a nice view!
I think this is where we get peed on.
This is for you guys!
Wow, what a... what a...
Wow!
He's just going everywhere.
Okay.
Thanks, Kojima.
Oh my god, there's so many of them!
Oh, the codec!
You're right, thank you.
I hope I didn't miss it.
Codec while peeing.
Wait.
Did I miss it?
Hold on, let me try again.
Is he still going?
No!
I think I missed the codec.
He doesn't care.
I guess Rose doesn't care if I get peed on or not.
Does he do it again?
We'll wait.
Oh, I'm going to go in my pants.
You're really excited about getting peed on?
No.
I was excited for you guys.
Call him again.
Cardo!
Don't worry about it, Jack.
It's okay.
Rose?
That is, as long as you take a shower the second you get back.
Do we have a deal?
You look so...
sad.
I got so caught up in this I forgot.
Skirt check!
Skirt!
Today I have a skirt on.
Skirt check!
Skirt!
Certified freak phantom moment.
I did not put that in the game.
Okay?
I did not decide that that should be a mechanic.
You know?
Oh!
I think I can take it out from here.
Dang it.
Wrong part.
I always forget.
It's the bottom part.
Oh, and it's gone.
Okay.
Am I good to just...
I want to take it out before I run over there.
You know?
Let's see.
Come back!
At least it wasn't Johnny.
Sorted!
Welcome to membership!
Thank you!
Will we get him?
You know what?
Let's just go.
Oh!
I'm all full!
Wow.
Just gonna... okay.
I'm gaming.
When you develop the...
this game, how many people tried to stop you from adding this?
It was definitely a...
a...
decisive...
divisive decision.
You know?
Oh my god.
Oh my god!
Hey!
What if I take out?
Like...
What if I... What if I... Like...
What if I...
I'm just gonna run for it.
Why are you giving me so much stuff?
Oh no, it's all...
It's broken.
We gotta go into the core.
Now I can take it out.
Probably.
What the?
There we go.
Where's the other ones?
Oh, there.
Dang it.
These things are so...
These things are so particular!
I think if I...
Nice!
Okay.
And now you...
Nice!
Okay.
They're so particular.
I think we got all of them.
Nope, I hear one more.
I hear one more.
Oh god!
I think I can hit it from here.
There I can hit it.
Or if I had good aim.
Second R2, man.
Okay.
Okay, sorry.
I just like to be safe.
I don't want anybody to catch me.
Anything like that.
Where am I going?
Her aim is just like mine for real for you?
Really good?
I'm going to the core of Shell 2.
Get to the core of Shell 2.
The core of Shell 2.
Before the enemy can use him to reconfirm the nuclear launch code.
So it's not this one.
What's over here anyway?
I can't go in here.
No.
Beep beep.
Shell 2, baby.
Hmm.
Is that guy still up there?
Where does he go?
Okay.
Are you guys ready to believe?
That was just a test.
Do you guys still believe in me?
Right?
Oh my god, Raiden.
Why can't you walk in a straight line, buddy?
You're a proud friend of mine.
Gosh.
If I were a bird, I would not be hanging around this place any longer.
Okay, okay.
You can do it.
I wonder if I... yeah.
Oh gosh.
I believe I can do it.
I have trauma from this area.
Gamer.
Olga!
My father had some unfinished business with him.
Olga.
Calm yourself.
Your personal feelings.
Then screw your plan.
I've been waiting for this day for two years.
And I will send him to the bottom of the ocean.
Right next to my old man.
She's not gonna see you.
The launch comes first.
Very convincing.
I don't trust him.
Don't talk that way about one of your own.
He's not one of my own.
He left my father to die.
Remember?
Olga, we'll talk later.
We need to get started on the final checks for the unit.
Alright.
I'm headed back there.
Okay.
The upper connecting bridge to Shell One is down.
What about the chopper?
The cam-off is out of action.
Take the oil fence from Strut L.
Okay.
I'll tell my men to start pulling out.
Not yet.
Their retrieval comes last.
The intruder is still at large.
Snake.
What about the other man?
He's got luck on his side, certainly.
He survived that explosion.
Snake.
Listen, Olga.
The code confirmation is in one hour.
Keep the president alive until then.
Okay.
Easy.
I know.
No one gets in here.
Keep him alive.
Of course.
Keep him al- Oh, the currents.
What does that mean?
Uh-oh.
Uh-oh!
The door stays shut unless the president manages to take out that circuit panel.
I could do it.
I would win.
With my bare hands.
I almost said I could do it with my bare hands.
We leave for Russia when this business is done.
I want half the money for that.
Of course.
That was part of the agreement.
My bare hands.
We start living for ourselves after this.
If there's anyone who wants to stay here, I want you to take good care of them.
Gladly.
Of course he will.
Cream of the crop.
It's time they went free.
Are they?
What happened to rebuilding Mother Russia?
Cream of the crop?
The world is a different place now.
Cream of the crop.
Just as a reminder, I'm going to say this again.
One last time.
Don't try anything on us.
They just built this room with high voltage floors.
With the contractor.
I know, right?
Oh, man.
I'm in front of the room where they're keeping the president.
Everything all right?
No sign of flooding.
But I can't get close to the door.
The floor is electrified.
Don't test it.
You'll be bacon.
Any suggestions?
Remember the Shadow Moses VR training?
Take out the circuit panel?
Right.
When did I do this in Shadow Moses?
Try ventilation ducts.
I think I see one.
Look for a remote control missile launcher.
Okay.
You can guide it through the duct.
Oh, wait.
I did do this.
Target the circuit panel.
Got it.
Make sure you don't hit the president.
Mr. President!
The president is wired with nanomachines.
John Segan is one of my favorite VHS series.
I love Solidus.
Me too.
It looks like the walls have a built-in radio shield.
I was thinking with the ducts.
With the ducts.
I was like, I never launched a missile through ducts.
Understood.
Ducts.
Ducts?
Oh, God.
This is where I was hiding?
Oh, my God.
Sorry.
Oh, God.
I see this...
I see this hallway and I want to start crying every time.
Mr. President!
Can you hear me?
I have like a...
I think this is why I'm a ghost, honestly.
I have a trauma from...
From just this room.
From just...
Oh, hello?
What is this?
Oh, I got to get the Nikita first.
Thank you.
I remember there not being any guys around here yet.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
My rations.
Oh, this one?
Has a bunch of things in here.
Anyone else?
Oh.
That's it though, right?
Anybody?
Anyone else?
I don't see anyone.
Oh!
Oh, I thought it was the actual thing.
I'm so stupid.
What's that?
Nothing here.
Chaff.
Yeah, it's just the ammo.
I thought it was the actual thing.
I forgot.
And this...
Why would there be... Oh, here's the nerd.
Why would there be security cameras in the...
In the break room?
Mr. President!
He's close to the wall.
Oh my god!
It's just like in MDS1 when you see Otacon!
Who's there?
Come here, come here.
Come here.
Who?
Who's there?
Is that a Metal Gear Solid reference?
Who's that?
Knock it off!
I don't remember the music being so loud in this game.
Where the...
Voice acting is not so loud.
You know what I mean?
I don't remember.
Where do I get...
The Nikita missile?
Where do I get it?
Colonel!
The only way to the President is past this electrified floor.
Use the remote-controlled missile to destroy the power source.
That will cut off the high-voltage current to the floor.
Locate a remote-controlled missile.
Turning it down?
I wonder.
Do you guys think the audio is okay though?
Oh, Snake.
Do you guys think the audio is okay?
If you can hear?
Alright.
I don't want it to be too low.
I feel like this is one of those games where like...
The audio should be as loud as me.
Sounds good?
Okay.
What can I do for you, Jack?
I wanna hear some drama.
You got any drama for me, Rose?
Rose, oh Rose, my beloved.
Still windows.
Oh, 10 hours, exactly!
Jack, have you remembered what day it is tomorrow?
You said you had something you wanted to talk to me about.
What was it?
We'll talk about it tomorrow.
Why does it have to be tomorrow?
So I can build up enough courage first.
And so you won't run away.
I would never do something like that.
Liar.
Every time I wanna talk about something, you suddenly remember that you have some work you have to do.
Or you get a stomach ache.
If that's not...
You know it's true.
What are you so afraid of?
There you go again.
And I won't try to run away.
You are such a liar, Raiden.
Well then, we'll talk tomorrow.
So you have to come back, okay?
Sorry, Rose.
We can't do anything tonight.
I got a headache, you know?
He's still here.
What?
Give it up?
He's like, this wall!
What's up with this wall?
Oh, let me call Snake.
That's right.
Oh my god, it even says Snake now!
Bye, Snake.
Thank you so much.
Snake, do you know where I can find some remote control?
Remote controlled missiles?
I saw something on B1 in the core of Shell 2.
But be careful.
Contaminated seawater is broken out of the tanks.
Thanks to that explosion.
Most of B1 is probably flooded by now.
We gotta swim.
Oh, ping pong!
Mr. President.
Who's there?
Ding-dong-ditch.
Time to avoid drowning?
Yes, but also no.
Yes, but not yet.
Yes, but soon.
I hope there's no bugs down here.
I hate those.
I don't see a way.
I don't see a way to...
make the music...
You know, back in the day, they didn't really have options like that.
To increase the music and also...
Like, you know, or turn down the music.
Things like that.
Alright.
I'm new here.
Welcome.
Get ready for peak gameplay.
Oh gosh, I forgot how to swim.
Colonel!
Colonel, teach me how to swim!
I forgot how to swim.
When you're on the surface, you can swim in corresponding directions using the up, down, left, and right movement of the left analog stick.
using the up, down, left, and right movement of the left analog stick.
Thank you.
Push the punch button to dive down from the surface.
Okay, okay.
Now, look at the cans.
Now, where...
Okay, I keep thinking that the blue parts are...
Oh god.
Ow!
Why are you calling me underwater?
Colonel, B1 is completely flooded from what I can see.
What?
How?
Bryden?
Are you a mermaid?
What?
I'm fine with swimming.
Merman?
Okay.
I'm stroking.
Looks at the cans.
Yeah, you would...
You're talking fast.
...left and right to face those directions.
The O2 gauge will appear...
You're under your life gauge while you're underwater.
The gauge corresponds to the amount of air you can hold from a single deep breath.
Once the O2 gauge falls to zero...
I'm gonna die, Colonel.
Colonel, I'm gonna drown.
Colonel.
Oh, gosh.
Colonel, I'm gonna drown.
Okay.
There was something down there, wasn't there?
I don't...
You know what?
Let's just explore.
Because I truly don't remember where to get it.
Oh, this is a dead end.
Isn't it?
Wow.
Good job.
Idiot.
Oh, wait.
Yeah.
There we go.
Yeah, we're just gonna go on an adventure.
A little adventure.
You know what?
The game has really traumatized me with, um...
With, uh...
Oh, there was something in that room, wasn't there?
Oh, la la.
Looks like a certain...
Traitor.
Kingdom Hearts 2.
That game...
Hold on.
I wanna go check this room again.
I'm pretty sure there was something in here.
That game has the worst...
Swimming...
Oh!
Night vision goggles!
There we go.
You're welcome, everybody.
You don't even have to tell me.
Kingdom Hearts 2 had the...
Absolute worst...
Swimming mechanics ever.
It was so bad.
Oh, wait.
Was it 2 or 1?
Maybe it was 1.
Kingdom Hearts 2...
Had the rhythm game.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kingdom Hearts 1...
Was the really bad one.
Kingdom Hearts 2 had the rhythm game.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Who the heck swims like that?
I don't... I think by this point...
We know Raiden is not okay.
Raiden's a bit of a freaky guy.
Oh my god!
Raiden!
Rubber ducky!
I'll be honest.
I thought the mines...
Showed up...
In the second part.
I'll be honest.
That's my bad.
For not remembering.
There it is.
Okay.
Don't rush me.
I'm already drowning...
In here.
I'm drowning...
In time.
Oh gosh.
Is there a...
Wait.
Up.
Oh god.
I'm really not okay.
We're fine.
I'm just...
Bleeding out a little bit.
I have some bandages.
Don't worry about it everybody.
There we go.
Was there anything in here?
This is where we go to later.
So we have to...
Go find the president first.
Okay.
Glad I went down here though.
Now I remember.
What is that?
Right there.
Floating.
Is there anything over here?
Oh gosh.
Right in.
I forgot your thing goes down faster because you have less health.
Go up.
It's the raven figurine?
Wait.
Actually?
Are you a mint enough maid to rescue the president?
Of course I am!
I won't let anything happen to the president.
Don't worry.
Scout's honor.
Oh I'm running into a wall.
No.
That probably didn't spark confidence in you.
Scout's honor.
Nothing will happen to the president.
Ah.
No mysterious heart attacks?
No.
None of that nonsense.
What is this?
Shadow Moses?
No.
This is the big shell.
We don't have stinking heart attacks here.
Except for aims.
But that guy already had a heart problem.
I think.
So you know...
He doesn't count.
Raiden looks so stupid on the stairs.
I love him.
I know.
Right?
Okay Mr. President.
Watch this.
Idiot.
Knock it off.
Stupid president.
The president's dumb.
Um.
I wish I could get that other ration.
The one that I didn't need earlier.
Gosh.
I ate two.
Dang.
Mines in the water.
And like destroyed all my health.
Are these still down?
Yeah.
You're such a prankster.
I know.
I'm just a pranking guy.
Oh.
Here we go.
Swimming builds an appetite.
I know.
When I was a kid.
Every time I would go swimming.
My mom would make me peanut butter crackers.
So I think about that.
Ahhh.
Press square to aim in first person.
My
best.
He's really got child bearing hips from this angle.
Look at that indent.
The sneaking suit lifts and separates the cheeks.
To prevent them from laughing.
I know.
Look at that.
They are spread open.
Oh my.
Riding.
Oh.
Wow.
Golly.
Riding.
Spread open.
Look at that.
Look at them.
Are they not?
Alright.
Don't worry about it, President.
Don't worry about it, Mr. President.
Oh my god.
They are so fast.
This way.
Watch out, Mr. President.
Hahaha.
Mr. President.
Trying to.
Hahaha.
Oh my.
Wait.
I guess I can't get other stuff in there, can I?
Not yet.
Stop it.
Stop sending that missile to me.
Hahaha.
Stop launching missiles at me.
What's wrong?
Stop it.
This is not funny.
There we go.
Okay.
Time for funny cut scene.
Mr. President.
President Johnson.
Happy birthday to you.
So you're finally here.
Your equipment, that skull suit, isn't exactly standard military issue.
Happy birthday, Mr. President.
Are you all right, sir?
Is this some kind of sick joke?
I thought you came to kill me.
Happy birthday to you.
I'm prepared to face the consequences of my betrayal.
What are you...
What the...
You're a man?
I know.
You can't tell by the cheeks, but...
Well, who are you?
Foxhound, sir.
Foxhound?
Raiden's totally unfazed.
I see.
Now things are starting to make a little sense.
He was reminded of a previous life.
Whoa, grabby.
Switch over to nano communication so nobody can listen in.
Oh my god, Mr. President.
My hog?
Do you need me, sir?
Yes.
Surprise prostate check?
I don't think that's where your prostate is.
Have managed to input the code sequence necessary for launching a nuclear strike.
I don't think that's where that is.
That's correct.
I punched the sequence in myself.
You're working for them?
If you asked me two hours ago, my answer would have been yes.
Eureka, Sensei.
Who's I?
They're keeping me alive until my vital signs are reconfirmed.
They betrayed you?
I wouldn't quite put it that way.
I wanted power.
They sought destruction.
Huh?
But why stoop to terrorism?
I wanted absolute power.
Oh my god.
You're the president.
You have power.
No.
I'm just a figurehead.
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't have any control.
The real power is in the Patriots' hands.
The Patriots?
The truth behind this country.
I don't know anything.
I'm not surprised you've never heard of them.
Very few are aware of their existence.
Even among those with code word clearance.
Huh?
Politics, the military, the economy.
They control it all.
They even choose who becomes president.
Putting it simply, the Patriots rule this country.
The Patriots?
No.
Hard to believe, isn't it?
But it's the truth.
The space defense, income tax reduction, and national missile defense programs.
Every policy that's been credited to me was actually done according to their instructions.
Space defense was initiated by Congress.
That's what the Patriots want the country to believe.
It's all a show.
Democracy is just a filler for textbooks.
Think about it.
Do you actually believe that public opinion influences the government?
No.
This country is shaped and controlled as the Patriots see fit.
The people are shown what they want to believe.
What you call government is actually a well-staged production aimed at satisfying the public.
Huh?
Don't look at me like that.
I'm legally sane, you know.
It's not your sanity that worries me.
Huh?
The Patriots.
Even I don't know who the actual members are.
Are they financial, political, or military leaders?
No one knows who the Patriots really are.
Even my instructions come from a cutout.
All I've been told is that every key decision is made by a group of 12 men known as the Wise Men's Committee.
Wise guys.
Your office?
The White House?
Merely puppets.
Pawns in a game.
Oh.
By pledging my loyalty, an insignificant son of a senator was awarded the presidency.
Of course, that wasn't the only price I had to pay.
What do you mean?
Even if a pawn becomes a queen, it is still just a playing piece.
I wanted to leave my own mark in history.
But my ambitions were to be a member of the Patriots.
The guy in the bottom right looks like Van Gogh.
You'll understand someday.
I wished to be a member of the Patriots.
I wanted to wield the power of a king instead of being an expendable pawn.
And that justifies acts of terrorism?
Yes.
I'd intended to use the new metal gear as a bargaining chip.
Bargaining chip?
But I underestimated Solidus.
He actually wants to challenge the Patriots, even if it means the destruction of the world.
What are you saying?
Whether you believe it or not, the balance of power rests in the hands of the Patriots.
They regulate the country's various interests through controlled presentation, staging a drama that is palatable to the general masses.
Can you imagine what would happen if they ceased to function?
Picture a massive political vacuum, getting rid of the Patriots.
A space that every power monger will try to fill for their own greedy ends.
It happened last week, you guys.
I'm talking about an unregulated power struggle.
Panic.
Civil war.
Chaos.
Fox alive.
Like it or not, the Patriots is an organization that must continue to exist.
No they don't!
So you changed your mind because you wanted to avoid global chaos.
Global chaos.
When I told Solidus that I wished to prevent disaster, he replied that pawns would never become players.
And who is this Solidus?
You don't recognize the president?
My predecessor.
George Sears.
President Sears!
That was the name the public came to know him by.
I knew him by his code name, Solidus Snake.
Why does nobody recognize the president?
He was the third snake preceded by Solid and Liquid.
A survivor of the Les Enfants Terribles project.
Les Enfants Terribles?
Neither solid nor liquid.
He was a well-balanced masterpiece that the Patriots saw fit Handsome guy.
However, he fell out of grace with the organization four years ago.
When acting on his own, he started an incident.
Four years ago?
Why didn't you vote for him?
That's right.
At the time, the DARPA chief, Donald Anderson, together with certain influential parties, initiated the development of Metal Gear Rex and an advanced nuclear warhead.
I voted for him.
However, this did not fall in line with the Patriots' plans.
What's more, Solidus decided on his own to send his most trusted man, Ocelot, to provoke Liquid Snake, bringing about the said incident.
As a result, he succeeded in obtaining Rex and the data on the warhead.
But in doing so, he ended up revealing the existence of both Rex and the Genome Army.
A blunder that earned him the wrath of the Patriots.
That sounds like an awesome game name.
The wrath of the Patriots?
Solidus was removed from the presidential office.
No, that is not Solid nor Liquid Snake!
I thought he resigned.
That's the story given to the general public.
Following his resignation, the Patriots selected me, their new pawn, for the presidency.
But that would mean that the presidential race was...
That was quite a show, wasn't it?
It was a well-scripted drama staged by the Patriots for the benefit of the public.
What are your policies?
It's the diaper chaff.
The diaper chaff.
Huh.
Following his resignation, Solidus' health was scheduled to fail him, bringing about his untimely death.
Capped?
Correct.
But before the Patriots could execute their plot, Solidus went underground with the help of Ocelot.
As he avoided pursuit, Solidus gained control of Dead Cell, winning over Colonel Golukovich's outfit.
From there, he bided his time knowing that his opportunity would soon arrive.
What opportunity?
The completion of the new Metal Gear project.
An opportunity that would even his odds against the Patriots.
By stealing the Patriots' most valued project, he would be able to place them in a very uncomfortable position.
It's the only chance he has for survival.
You make me uncomfortable.
Once he has the new Metal Gear, he'll declare war against the Patriots.
Yeah!
No!
Metal Gear is already operational.
No.
Not yet.
He's jealous of the other two and Big Boss.
What you saw was Metal Gear Ray.
Hijacked two years ago from the Marines by Ocelot.
That was not the new Metal Gear.
Show me the Wikipedia article.
Then where's the new Metal Gear?
Right here.
You're standing in it.
To be more precise, this entire Big Shell facility is the new Metal Gear.
What'd you say?
I love Raiden.
The main structure extends from the foundation all the way down to the ocean floor.
The connecting elevator is located on the B2 floor of the Shell 1 core.
Arsenal Gear.
That's the code name for the new Metal Gear.
Arsenal?
Nobody gives love to Arsenal Gear enough.
He's a big ol' turtle.
We're talking about an impregnable fortress carrying a load of over a couple of thousand missiles, including nuclear warheads.
All protected by a horde of mass-produced Metal Gear Ray units.
Mass-produced?
The Ray unit was originally designed for the Marines to be used as a countermeasure against the Metal Gear variations throughout the world.
The Patriots had Ray redesigned to protect the new Arsenal Gear.
So now anti-Metal Gears are guarding a Metal Gear.
Ironic, isn't it?
That's not all.
Arsenal Gear has full access to the military's tactical network, giving it the ability to exercise absolute control over our nation's armed forces.
Not to mention our nuclear armament.
In short, Arsenal was created to be the core of our country.
What kind of idiotic weapon?
Weapon?
No.
You're not seeing the full picture.
Arsenal Gear is more than just a military tool.
It is a means to preserve the world as it is.
It will establish a new form of control.
The Patriots will use it to keep their place as the country's true rulers.
Right now, they feel pressured and threatened.
By what?
They fear an overabundance of digital information.
The world will drown in the coming flood of information, and they along with it.
The Arsenal plans include a system to digitally manage the flow of information, making it possible to shape the truth for their own purposes.
In short, the Arsenal system is the key to their supremacy.
The key?
Yes.
The GW system GW!
is the Patriots' trump card.
Arsenal Gear will be fully operational when GW is successfully integrated.
Once operational, it will be a completely new form of power for the Patriots to wield.
Ryden is just like, what are you talking about?
I had hoped to seize the project from them and be in a strong bargaining position.
GW?
Bargain for what?
I'd hoped to trade my way into their ranks.
The Solidus preferred rebellion.
I love Solidus!
His only crime was gunpowder!
To break the Patriots' control of the business community is also a key factor in his offensive effort.
Outer Heaven?
Listen, there isn't much time.
The football served as the key for activating Arsenal Gear.
I've already input the necessary code sequence.
It won't be long before GW begins to establish connections with other external systems and Arsenal Gear becomes fully operational.
Stop them before that happens.
That is your role.
You've got to find Emma Emmerich.
She's the only one who can stop that thing once it's been activated.
She's the system programmer for Arsenal Gear.
Everything is going over Ryder's head right now.
I believe she's somewhere on level B1 in the core of this building.
I thought the levels below us were flooded.
I'm sure they won't let her die just yet as she's the only remaining programmer for this project.
According to Ocelot, she was being held in a locker room located in the northwest part of level B1.
What do you mean?
They're just not going to let her die, but it's flooded.
They're going to stop the ocean?
This is card four.
I'll give you access all the way to Emma's location.
Yippee!
Give this to her when you find her.
What is it?
A program for disrupting the control functions between GW and Arsenal Gear.
I hope your suit is waterproof.
Take Emma to the computer room on level B2.
Shell 1 core.
She'll know how to load the program into the main system.
A virus?
That's right.
Modeled after Foxty.
A biological weapon designed to selectively eliminate personnel with a specific genetic code.
But why do you have it?
It's a failsafe.
And Ocelot forgot to search me.
He's the president!
Why wouldn't he have it?
That disk is the only way you're going to stop Arsenal.
Okay.
Do you feel IBS?
Do you feel a little funny?
Well, I've told you everything you need to know.
Yeah.
Okay, bye.
There's only one thing that remains to be done.
What's that?
Get you out of here, president.
We're going to save you.
Right now.
Come with me.
Now, kill me.
No!
There's no time to argue.
My vital ID will start any second.
If you kill me now, you'll at least prevent the nuclear strike.
No!
Cut it out!
Do it!
That's your role!
That's not my role!
It wasn't me!
I didn't pull the trigger!
I didn't do it!
That's abusing your right to free speech, Mr. President.
Oh my god!
Ex-president.
The president!
Why did you...
Alas, my finger must have slipped.
I'll see you around, carrier boy.
Oh my god!
Don't forget him.
Without free will, Why would Ocelot do that?
there is no difference between submission and rebellion.
Carrier boy.
My only real choice is to put an end to this charade.
Let me at least have the freedom to end it myself.
Always question Ocelot's motives.
What are you?
Find Emma.
Okay.
Stop Arsenal.
Order.
As your commander in chief.
I'm counting on you.
Mr.
President.
Oh no.
Mr. President.
Mr. President, I'll take you somewhere nice.
Come here.
Come here, Mr. President.
Okay.
Just rest.
Rest there, Mr. President.
Rest well, Mr. President.
Oh my god.
07 for Mr. President.
Nice.
More bullets.
Um.
Colonel?
We have a problem.
No response?
What else could you be doing?
Snake?
No response!
What else could you guys be doing?
Oh, wait.
Okay, I have one last person.
He'll always pick up.
No!
The room is jammed?
Then why do I still have my map?
Wait, hold on.
We got goodies to get.
We got goodies to get, everybody.
What else is in here?
Oh, am I stuck?
Oh.
Oop.
There.
I can't go any further?
No way!
That's it?
That's it for me?
Okay.
How?
How am I stuck though?
I can't bel...
This doesn't seem like the type of game that would do an invisible wall, you know?
Battle Gear never seems like the type of game that does an invisible wall.
What is this guy?
Uh...
Colonel, the President is dead.
I see.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Where do we go from here?
Your mission was to rescue the President and eliminate the terrorist threat.
Oh, well...
However, given the recent turn of events, we will honor the President's last directive.
You must put a stop to Arsenal gear once and for all.
Yes.
Do you actually think there's any truth to his story about this big shell facility being a front for Arsenal gear?
I don't have the security clearance necessary to verify the facts.
However, he was the President.
He was the President.
I'm sure he knew what he was talking about.
Aren't you forgetting that he was part of the terrorist plot?
All the more reason why I believe his information is reliable.
Huh?
Maybe.
Ooooooh.
Gah!
The Colonel has a point, Jack.
Hey!
Yeah!
Ugh...
What are you talking about?
Find Emma.
She's supposed to be located on level B1.
B1.
In the core of that building you're in.
Yep.
Right?
You've got to find her before Arsenal becomes fully operational.
Okay.
Hurry, Jack.
It's up to you to make sure that the President didn't sacrifice his life in vain.
Okay.
Understood.
Raiden, out.
When do you ever say that?
What's your status, Raiden?
Snake, the President, he's been assassinated.
What?
There was nothing I could do.
What about the nuclear strike guard?
He died before his vital ID could be reconfirmed.
When does he ever say that?
But that Ocelot guy obviously killed the President on purpose.
Why?
It doesn't make any sense.
They had to know that they couldn't launch the nuke if they killed the President.
Maybe there's a way to launch without reconfirming the vital ID.
Or maybe they found a more effective weapon within Arsenal gear.
You knew about Arsenal gear?
Yeah.
Why didn't you tell me about it?
You never asked.
I was just assuming you also know that the Big Shell's a front for the project.
You mean, did I know that the Big Shell, a fully functional environmental cleanup facility, was designed to camouflage Arsenal gear?
Yeah, I did.
It's exactly what the President and Ames described.
A massive cover story.
Oh my gosh, so good.
The good news is that it hasn't really done much in terms of cleaning up the environment, so we won't have to worry about any toxic gas being released if we have to blow the house down.
Okay.
Right.
And when did you find out about all of this?
I don't know.
It took a while, but we uncovered the info around the time you took out that mad bomber.
What a troll.
I know.
There's no doubt that Arsenal gear is being built here.
And it was all set up two years ago.
On that day.
All of it.
Two years ago?
What really happened here?
Hudson River.
I took these photos two years ago.
Oh my god!
I have these pictures.
They were on the news on several websites.
If I remember right, the reporters blamed you for sinking the tanker.
The news!
That's right.
Otacon.
Me.
We were used.
Terrorist action.
Water though!
At least that was the plan at the time.
Can I go?
I want to see opinions.
I've gone through VR training of the tanker mission before.
Yeah.
Well, I doubt it accurately simulates the events of that mission.
They took a picture of me.
Serious environmental disaster.
I'd infiltrated the dummy tanker to obtain proof that a metal gear was under development.
I did that.
Shortly after I made it aboard, an armed group of people came to the tanker and said, The armed group led by Colonel Gerlukovich raided the ship and gained control.
Oh my god.
Olga and Ocelot were among the raiding party.
The world.
Yeah.
And him.
Who are you talking about?
A man that was supposed to be dead.
Oh.
Their target was also Metal Gear Ray.
But Ocelot eliminated Colonel Gerlukovich and Marine Commander Scott Dolph, and he hijacked Ray.
Oh, Reparoni.
Yeah.
I don't know what kind of deal was going down.
All I remember is what Ocelot said at the time.
Something like, I'm taking it back.
Ooh.
Ocelot then sank the tanker, along with the soldiers of the Marine Corps.
This is a great summary.
Best character, Dikido.
Dikido.
How did you manage to get out?
Otacon managed to have a small boat ready for me.
Yay, small boat!
That was the easy part.
The tough part was not getting dragged down with a sinking tanker.
Small miracle when you think about it.
It turned out that the whole thing was a setup to lure us.
Yeah.
The photos of Snake, taken by the Cipher, were released to the public.
In turn, we became the world's most wanted environmental terrorists.
Yeah!
It was definitely a move aimed at putting a stop to our anti-Metal Gear activities.
But why did they choose Snake?
Because he's sexy.
Since the Shadow Moses incident, Snake became sort of a hero.
Oh my God.
Everybody saw him naked?
I think the Patriots weren't too happy about that.
You knew about the Patriots?
When did that happen?
Yeah.
To a certain degree.
Oh, I did all of that.
Actually, this is real footage.
It seems like everyone knows about them except me.
Look how cool I look.
They didn't choose Snake to be a hero.
So they decided to do a senior campaign.
Oh, I did that too.
I did that.
This is all real footage that I did.
I think the Patriots wanted to make an example of him, so everybody would think twice before opposing him.
Otakot's family has a history of small boat.
That's it.
They set all this up just to nail you guys.
No, there's more to it than that.
The Marine's Metal Gear Ray project, headed by Commander Dolph, was carried out in opposition to the Navy's Arsenal Gear project.
You think that was so cool?
Yeah.
I know.
To be more precise, the Patriots considered Metal Gear Ray to be a thorn in their side.
Hence they attacked the dummy tanker and stole Ray.
Stole Ray.
I remember when you were doing this.
They followed this up with a perfect plan.
They immediately sent a fully loaded tanker to the same location and sank it, then set up the facility to camouflage the development of Arsenal Gear.
And we fell for it.
Two more puppets in their show.
A lot of this stuff is from cut content.
Yeah, I remember he had like a Titanic-esque scene where you had to run out with all the water going.
Shh.
No, he was underground, keeping a low profile at the time.
Then it must be the Patriots.
If that's the case, what's Ocelot doing alongside Solidus?
Just being a double-crosser, triple-crosser, quadruple-crosser.
Doing what he knows best.
We can figure this out later.
The nuclear strike's been prevented, but Arsenal still has a massive payload of missiles to deal with.
Right.
If the opposition gets control of those missiles...
Ryden, you've got to find Emma.
Wait a second.
Isn't Emma Emmerich?
My sister.
What's she doing here?
You got me.
She's a computer whiz who specializes in neural AI and ultra-variable volume data analysis using complex logic.
Neural AI.
I think her world and weapons development is beyond me.
Whatever her reasons, we need her in order to stop Arsenal.
Ryden, find her.
I'm on my way.
Okay.
Time for Ore no Imouto ga Konnani Kawaii Wake Ga Nai.
Neuro-sama.
I love being able to freely wander this area.
I'm treasuring it.
I'm not taking it for granted at all.
Neuro-sama.
Guys,
I will need to go to the little ghosty's room, probably before we go into the next fight.
Wait.
Did I get everything?
Yeah.
Okay.
Coming.
I will need to go to the little...
But
we remember where to go.
We go to that one room and we go...
With the handle.
Good.
No bugs.
I hope the lower level doesn't have any bugs.
That would be awful.
You guys...
Oh my gosh.
You guys can listen to this ambiance.
Oh my gosh, it's kind of relaxing here.
This is so nice.
You can just listen to the water flowing.
This actually sounds so...
This is really nice, actually.
It's like the sound of...
The electro...
The electronic...
Like the whir of the machines and...
I need to pee now.
Okay.
Potty break for everybody.
Can we listen to Raiden talking to himself?
Wait.
What do you mean?
How could he talk to himself?
I am going to save real quick though.
See if Rose got anything to say.
What can I do for you, Jack?
You can give us some...
The sweet, sweet tea, my dear Rose.
Okay.
Jack?
What is it?
I've always been alone.
Huh?
I'm so lonely.
Lonely?
Rose, we've always...
Rose!
Not always.
What do you mean?
You've never slept beside me.
What are you talking about?
I...
After we've been together in my room...
Sorry.
You stay awake all night.
Or you head for the door.
Is this really the time to bring this up?
Why, Jack?
Why?
Listen, Rose.
I'm right in the middle of a mission and I...
Why?
Why can't you hear me?
Why can't you relax when you're with me?
Look.
The mission...
I...
Why don't you open up to me?
Rose, I...
I just can't.
All I ever wanted was to share your dreams.
To spend a meaningful evening with you.
Girl, I'm about to go drowning.
I just wanted to find you by my side when I woke up.
Is that asking too much?
I just wanted to save the game.
It's the night.
I'm scared of the night.
It's got nothing to do with you.
Scared of the night?
Maybe.
What's that supposed to mean?
I can't relax when you're with me.
Maybe.
Jack, you wouldn't even let me in your room.
I need privacy.
I just can't be bothered.
Don't go into my room, Rose.
Bothered?
What I wanted to say was that there are certain things that I have to keep to myself.
Oh, my God.
Do you remember that time I forced my way into your room?
Oh, no.
We'd known each other for almost a year.
No, no.
And you blew up.
Yeah.
You didn't.
It was the first time you ever raised your hand against me.
I was so worried about you.
Look, I'm sorry.
It wasn't you, Violet Nature, that scared me.
It was your room.
Your heart.
Stop it.
There wasn't anything in your room.
Only a bed and a small desk.
It looked like a prison cell.
Rose?
No television set.
No family pictures.
Not even a poster.
Rose, I only used that room for sleeping.
A lifeless room.
Rose.
I didn't expect to get this.
Almost like your empty heart.
I don't know.
That's why I tried to keep you out.
I thought I was beginning to understand you until I saw that room.
I didn't expect to get this.
Would you have been happier if I had a picture of you hanging on the wall?
Oh, my God.
That's not what I was trying to say.
I don't know.
Enough, Rose.
We'll talk about this later.
After the mission.
Right.
Oh, my God.
I understand.
I didn't expect to get this codec just now.
Oh, my God.
I didn't expect to get this.
Why are they together?
It wasn't you that scared me.
It was your room.
There was nothing in there, bro.
Why are you living in a prison cell?
It literally said no furniture.
The military dudes spying on them must be frustrated.
Oh, my gosh.
Let's see what Snake has to say.
I don't know.
Oh, God.
Hey, come on.
Man, come on.
Okay.
Oh, goodness.
I'm so glad we...
Oh, gosh, I'm so glad we got that codec.
Okay.
You just hang out with Raiden real quick.
I'm gonna go fishing.
You guys, hang out.
I'll be really fast.
I just gotta pee.
I'm gonna be like that Gerlukovich soldier.
I'm gonna do it off my balcony.
In honor of him.
I hope nobody's standing below.
You don't understand, Rose.
There are certain things I have to keep to myself.
Slyly brushes his BL manga into the bed for you.
Jack and Rose have a relationship as long as...
Loving as it is unhealthy.
So good.
Okay, VRB.
VRB.
Gonna go do it off my balcony.
I'm back, but I want more tea, so I'm gonna go get more.
So I'm gonna be just a little second more.
Shout out to everyone playing Blue Archive who decorates their cafe like Raiden.
Oh my god.
Shout out to you, Oimo!
VRB.
Again.
But I'll be fast.
I hope there were no weird messages.
While I was gone.
I hope there was nothing strange.
Give him a shower.
I did get a snack though.
I got watermelon.
Watermelon!
The perfect summer snack.
Yummy.
Nothing in my bed.
What would be in your bed?
Oh, definitely not Raiden.
I love watermelon.
It was fun meeting you this weekend, Mint.
Can't wait for the new school show.
Oh my gosh, yes!
Have so much fun.
Do you salt watermelon?
Sometimes.
But I'm not really a salty fan.
Okay.
We ready to go?
Let's go.
Oh my god, my eyes.
Okay.
Let's go.
I think I can make it this way since we have high health.
We've got high health.
Oh.
Hello?
Raiden, are you reading me?
This is Otacon.
What's your situation?
Wet and miserable.
This place is flooded.
I was hungry, why aren't you coming?
What's that?
What?
Yeah.
I was in my room.
I learned later that E.E.
was calling me for help.
She didn't doubt for a minute that I'd be there.
You could see the pool from my room, but I didn't realize at the time that she needed my help.
What were you doing?
Oof.
Um, um, uh, post-collar.
Yeah, but my father didn't.
So you blamed yourself and left your family.
Yeah!
Sorry.
E.E.
seems to believe that was the case.
The fact is, I betrayed her.
And you think she can't swim because of the traumatic experience?
I haven't seen her since that day, but yes, I think so.
I got a letter from Julie, her mother, after they moved back to England.
In her letter, she mentioned that E.E.
couldn't swim anymore, that she refused to even wear a bathing suit.
Damn.
If she still can't swim, we're in trouble.
Level B1 in the core is pretty much flooded.
I didn't do it.
Look, maybe you can help her overcome the trauma.
You want me to help her get over it?
Well, it's still gonna take some time to repair.
Sorry, kid.
Emma's rescue is up to you.
Thanks.
An underwater mission.
Well, this is a first.
Look, I'll see what I can do.
I suggest that you drum the map of the building into your head, cause you won't have time to look at it when you try to bring Emma out.
Yeah.
I'm counting on you, Raiden.
I covered most of the core when I had to take out the C4s.
If there's anything you need to ask me, call me on the codec.
I'll do that.
Can I ask you...
Snake?
Why are we here?
Why?
B1C.
Okay, back.
There we go.
Just to suffer?
Just to suffer.
Okay.
Alright, Raiden.
Okay, good.
They didn't have time to reset up the mines.
I think we're...
Oh, wait.
Oh.
Hold on.
This way.
I think we're good.
Oh!
Oh my god!
But they had time to set up rushes!
Let's go.
What is that?
Wow.
I'm glad the posters are surviving.
What's that?
Oh.
Okay.
Cool.
It's this one.
But what's this one go to anyway?
Can we even open it?
Oh.
Oh, it won't even let us.
Okay.
Here?
Wait.
What button am I supposed to press here?
Oh, there we go.
I was trying the action button but it was being weird.
Oh!
No surprises!
Ah!
No surprises, please!
Oh!
Ah!
Still man!
Oh, he's a still man now.
Oh my goodness gracious.
Um, hold on.
Uh, is he still there?
Oh!
Uh.
Oh.
You're my boy.
Stop asking questions.
Snake, I found him.
Hold on.
Oh!
Oh,
thank you.
Oh.
Oh!
Oh...
Oh.
Oh My Gosh.
Oh!
Then, head north and you should reach filter chamber number two.
Oh, what?
I know you- wait!
I found him!
Emma's probably being- Maybe Colonel?
Colonel, I found him!
When you're on the surface, you can swim in corresponding direc- I give up.
This poor guy.
They're like, we don't have time to worry about a dead man.
He's already dead!
Oh gosh, uh, up?
Okay, how do I get through here again?
Over?
And under?
And around?
Oh, this way?
Right?
Under?
Yeah, and over?
And uh, oh shoot.
Uh, around?
That's a wall?
Oh god, um, I'm gonna end up like Stillman?
Under?
Oh, what's that?
Grab it!
Riding?
Riding!
Riding, turn around!
Okay, just go up.
Okay.
Maybe I have to stare at him and then call.
Or maybe.
Laugh and grow fat, Stillman.
Come on, grab it!
There you go, buddy.
Am I going the right way?
Oh gosh.
Up.
Nope, no.
Go down.
And here.
And then go up.
Here.
Oh, not high enough?
There we go, nice, nice, nice.
Yeah.
Stinger bullets.
You know what I mean!
What's here?
Okay.
Cool.
Let's get our breath.
Wow, that's a huge ration.
And let's avoid some... mines, I believe?
Or?
Oh wait, maybe in the next section?
Okay, I sure hope I'm not ambushed here!
Soggy ration.
That's how I like them.
I don't want to see any bisexuals.
I'll cry.
No!
AHH!
Also, I love Raiden's response to seeing a man who he literally shot point blank in the head.
Still alive.
Oh my gosh, it's really surreal.
I met like so many of these voice actors.
Now that I think about it.
I met Phil Lamarr.
Like a week ago.
That's crazy!
No!
So cool.
I know, right?
Okay.
What the-
Are you- Are you calling me a catch?
Phil Lamarr voices everyone and everything.
He probably voices me.
Purified hydrogen bomb?
Why is it when Snake repeats everything it sounds good, but when Raiden does it, it just makes him sound like an idiot?
The clean thermonuclear bomb is at an experimental stage and is handled differently.
Clean?
Specifically.
You don't want to say spice, like you'll stop looking in the mirror?
The nuclear threat still exists.
Six months ago, we lost everything we believed in.
We were abandoned to take the fall in their cover-up.
We were labeled as killers, responsible for the mass murder of civilians as well as our own allies.
I can't tell what's going on in this picture.
And the public believed every word, turning a deaf ear to whatever we had to say to the contrary.
Is that Fatman and then Vamp?
Our only goal is to wipe them from the face of the earth.
And destroy this world of deceit they have created along with them.
You're insane.
Insane?
We might be the only ones telling the truth.
Vamp is cradling someone's head.
Aww.
It's Raiden's inherent talent.
Kind of like how when you say things, they sound cute.
Final check for activating arsenal has been completed.
All arsenal personnel report to your station.
Who is this guy?
Well, it sounds like arsenal's ready to go into operation.
Damn it.
You're still hoping that the girl can install that virus you're carrying around.
How do you know that?
You know?
It's a shame you're not going to be around long enough to hand her the program.
That isn't seawater, you know.
It's a byproduct of the microbes contained in the pool.
The buoyancy is practically non-existent thanks to the high oxygen content.
I've heard about that kind of water literally recently.
Take a good look at your grave.
Like I saw kind of a video about it.
Ta-da!
Oh my god!
No!
We have to fight Vamp!
Okay.
Let's kick his butt.
Oh gosh.
Okay.
I don't remember how to do this fight.
Can I take him out here?
Or does he...
Oh gosh.
There he goes.
Okay.
Alright.
I'm just going to take care of these real quick.
Okay.
Nice.
There he is.
Can't you like shoot him in here?
Oh god.
Where is he?
Oh.
Can't do it while...
I can't do it.
Not while he's being a ballerina.
Woo!
Yes Vamp!
Yes!
Wait!
Can I...?
Jerk.
I
don't remember how to do this fight.
Sorry guys.
If you're just like...
Hey do this.
Oh yeah!
Stinger in the water does work too.
That's right!
That's like how you cheese it, isn't it?
Doesn't it work?
Stinger in the water.
Oh god!
Where is he?
Hey buddy!
Where you at?
Is it a cheese?
I think it's technically like that.
Well, I mean, I say technically as if like there's a right way and a wrong way.
Stop being so fancy with me!
Sorry I'm not using the tranq.
I just really, you know what, I don't want to use it on him.
Oh, he's over there.
I know if I bait him... and then... Oh!
No!
I missed my chance!
He's like good for like two seconds.
Oh my gosh!
He scared me.
Okay, so after he throws...
Oh, he's...
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Right now, right now!
Ah, shoot!
Okay, I'm remembering a little bit.
Might just be slow, you know.
Oh, not Nikita.
Just kidding.
Where you at?
It's like so... such a little amount of...
Whatever works.
Whatever works, you know?
Oh my gosh.
Are you stupid?
You didn't even hit me once!
You aimed at the entirely wrong direction!
I should have gotten a better shot though.
That's my bad.
Oh, it takes out like his stamina.
Maybe it's not good to do it then.
We'll just wait until he comes back up.
He just wants to show off.
Yeah.
I kind of want to swim in there though.
That was too slow.
Maybe... I think actually I can...
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
I can punch him.
Just a little bit.
Every little bit helps.
I go and struggle with everybody's sexual skills.
What do you mean by that?
Gosh, I'm so slow with aiming.
Oh, maybe I should just go for his... You know what?
One or the other.
Whatever.
Maybe I should just go for his stamina then, you know?
Never realized the melee works on him.
Oh shoot, I forgot that...
Ow!
That was the first hit on me.
Hey, come here.
Oh my god, he's getting really aggressive with me!
Yo, get off right then!
Oh my gosh.
Phase 2?
Phase 2, I think?
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Oh my god.
Suddenly I started sucking.
I
don't think I got him though.
What the?
Oh my gosh!
You sucker!
Why are you able to get me so well?
Oh my god.
What
the?
Oh my god.
Don't choke.
I'm trying.
He stopped being able to attack my...
How do I shoot him now?
Wait.
Oh.
You
can use the big guns?
Stinger him?
Okay.
Yeah, let's just go back to that strat, right?
That was so close.
Holy cow.
That was close.
Yeah, try and get me as I run away!
I'm a coward, I'm a coward, I'm a coward!
I like how he falls back into the water.
Tactical retreat, so true.
That's right, yeah.
Actually, I don't care if you're okay.
I can't wait for your very timely death.
Back into the sea with Yi!
He avoided it.
Oh my god.
He's so fast!
Go back into the sea!
Stop!
You're so fast!
You're being too fast!
Oh my gosh.
You're being too ridiculous right now, VAMP.
You're being ridiculous right now, VAMP.
Ain't you not gonna go back into the sea?
Phase three.
Shoot!
I know he's...
You can get him after he has launched the three.
It's just hard to tell.
When he's gonna do it.
Sometimes he jumps around.
Sometimes...
Okay.
Let's see.
He's got the zoomies.
Which one would be better?
I have more bullets for the M4.
How...
Guys, I have a question.
How do I...
Auto-aim.
How do I turn it on?
Oh my god.
How do I...
Turn on.
Auto-aim.
Oh shoot.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
I'm too slow though.
Okay.
Oh
my gosh.
I'm so bad.
Yeah.
Throw your thingies.
Oh my god.
It's a freaking wall.
Throw them.
Oh my god.
Vamp.
Take any damage please.
Where is he?
This is getting stupid, vamp.
This is getting stupid.
This is...
Look at... look at... everything is littered with your... with your... little... things.
Oh my god.
That
was pretty funny, I'm not gonna lie.
It's okay.
Combine.
How?
How do I?
Yeah.
He spins.
He does his little...
Oh my god.
Bleeding out again.
Maybe I need to hit him and then shoot?
Can't remember this...
freaking part at all.
Ouch!
Okay, let's see what else I got.
This is stupid.
Will he... be able to... dodge this?
Please ma'am.
Please.
Why?
I tried shooting!
Is it...
Can I shoot in first person in this?
I have no idea.
I'm not auto-aiming!
I'm not auto-aiming.
If you are just like, you can't auto-aim, I'm not doing it.
Oh my god.
Just come down here!
You...
You piece!
Please.
Please!
Ooooh!
Finally.
I never want to see your stupid face again, Bap.
Drown in that water.
Drown, drown, drown in it.
God.
So dramatic.
Sorry.
Sorry that last part was so annoying.
You're not in it!
You killed him but now he's dead.
Yippee!
Literally like two thirds of that fight was me running around in a circle.
Next is the easy part of the game.
Then you should see her, right?
I don't have the right to see her.
We can talk about this later.
Raiden, I think you'd better get moving.
Emma's in the locker room to the north, right?
I'm on it.
Okay.
I'm Otacon.
Yay!
We lost a couple rations though.
But, you know.
We'll get him.
We'll get him back!
Thanks again.
Okay, watch out.
Watch out!
Go down.
Go down?
Go up?
Go up.
Go down?
Where do I go?
Go up.
Go...
Somewhere?
Oh my gosh, I'm in the wrong room!
Raiden...
I didn't...
It just threw me into that room.
Oh, Raiden, why are you so thick, man?
Wait, this is the same room!
Raiden, go this way!
Oh my god.
He's so thick.
Down.
Body armor!
Yeah!
Oh, we're gonna need that later.
For sure.
We're gonna need that.
Oh my god.
Oh, turn around, Raiden!
It's not worth it!
Oh gosh.
Go up.
Is there anything in that room?
I can't remember.
Down.
Oh, wait.
Oh.
I wasn't...
You guys, I swear, I swear to you.
I was not...
I was...
I didn't even press circle.
I swear to you.
I swear to you!
Raiden's bleeding out.
I got a bandage.
Where is my bandage?
Bandage.
Boop.
I'm lost.
I think I do have to go into that really cursed room.
Wait.
Did I go all the way back to the beginning?
Where am I?
Stick drip the ping!
Yeah, exactly, exactly.
Oh no, wait, it's this one.
Right here, right?
Oh wait, this is... no, yeah, it's this one.
Cool, right?
Okay.
Wish I had a node right now, node right now, node right now.
Oh, possess a meme.
Book!
C4.
Get bullied, nerd.
I wonder how much she's like her brother.
We all know they have one thing in common.
Here's the one thing in common.
Are you alright?
There it is.
Who are you?
Raiden, I'm getting you out of here.
Get me out?
You're lying.
Where are you taking me this time?
What are you talking about?
The best escort mission I've ever seen.
Of all time.
I'm here to help.
This is my redemption arc.
Here, I'll prove it.
This is my redemption.
Do you have nanos?
This is my redemption arc.
Well, do you?
I do.
This is my redemption arc.
Everybody on this project has them.
Okay, good.
Let's try.
Beep, beep.
Can you hear me now?
Nanocommunication?
That's right.
I have nanomachines too.
Her little hairs are so cute.
Not one of them.
That's what I've been trying to tell you.
The little one sticking up there is so cute.
And you came to rescue me?
Actually, I need your help to stop Arsenal.
I understand you're the only one who might be able to do it.
And who told you that?
The President.
Really?
I need you to come with me to Shell One.
Your brother's waiting for you there.
My brother?
Uh-oh.
Come on.
We have to get moving.
I can't.
This place will be flooded soon.
Come on.
Oh my god.
Take his hand.
Take the pretty boy's hand.
Oh my god.
She's just like...
This is just like my Japanese anime.
This is just like my Otome games.
Oh my gosh.
Be shonen.
What?
Why'd you...
Better move.
Yeah.
I can't swim.
At least she'll get to wash her pants.
Leave me.
You can swim.
You used to love it.
How do you know?
Your brother told me.
He's really here?
Yeah.
That's right.
He's here to rescue you.
I don't believe you.
He would never come for me.
And I'm telling you he's here.
Waiting for us at Shell One.
No.
He left me.
My mother.
When we needed him the most.
When my father died.
All he could think about was himself.
Emma.
We can go over all that later.
But first we have to get out of here.
No.
I hate water.
It's hopeless.
I can't swim.
I hate water.
It's wet.
It's coarse.
Gets in my pants.
I can't swim.
You can do it.
I can't.
Oh my god.
Come on.
Deep down inside you know you can swim.
I can't keep my eyes open in the water.
Endless blue.
The water.
It wants me.
It won't let me go.
All right.
Let's go.
Then close your eyes.
I'll guide you.
I was injected with something.
My legs.
I have trouble moving them.
Listen Emma.
Just hold your breath.
I'll be the rest.
She has so many excuses.
I could never tell if that was actually true.
I mean the way she walks like it does seem like she had something injected but like she just seems so...
First we'll have to build your chamber too.
Then we'll take a break.
You know.
She just seems like she has all sorts of excuses.
All I have to do is hold my breath.
That's right.
Yeah.
How long?
Just a little while.
Are you sure?
Of course I'm sure.
That's how I got here.
I don't think I can do it.
I'm not good at holding my breath.
Look Emma.
I have an idea.
I'm not good at holding my breath.
Put your ear against my chest and listen to my heartbeat.
Your heartbeat?
Count the beats.
Don't think about anything else.
When you reach 100 open your eyes.
You know it's so...
By that time we'll be on the other side.
What?
Give me a signal if you think you're running out of breath.
What will you do then?
Hold on.
I'll say it after this.
I'll swim faster.
Hold on.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Ryden you have a girlfriend.
Hang on tight.
She's so small.
Okay.
Let's go.
She's so cute.
I'm closing my eyes.
Take some deep breaths.
Deep breaths.
One and a two and a...
Three.
Wait.
What is it?
I don't know.
Let me take off my glasses.
You know you should wear contacts.
There's nothing wrong with my eyes.
You should wear contacts.
You're ugly with your glasses.
Trying to be different from the other girls?
No it's not like that.
I like glasses.
And there's this guy I like who used to wear them.
Your first boyfriend?
No.
Somebody more important.
Anyway they bring me luck.
Yeah.
I see.
That's why...
Why do you have a girlfriend?
Why did you take them off then?
Okay.
Let's go.
Emma no!
Ooh la la.
A three.
Okay.
This one.
She has small breath.
She has small breath capacity.
Okay.
What I was going to say is...
There was like a rumor, but it went around, right?
How they were just like, if you use the posesamine, if you use this, then it'll slow your heartbeat and she'll be able to hold her breath longer.
But it's not true.
But then also, it's kind of misleading because they give you this right before you see her.
So it kind of... it feels like it would be true, you know?
So a rum... a rumor!
Wait.
Yeah.
I guess so, right?
That does sound true for this game.
I know, right?
It sounds like it really would work, right?
Especially because he then also says, listen to the sound of my heartbeat.
And then this is supposed to... well, I don't know if it actually stops... if it makes your heartbeat slow down or whatever, but...
Old Gaming Magazine said the same thing.
Yeah!
It was always not real.
Misleading.
I got... I got a... I got a cute babe on my back.
How do you feel about that, Rose?
I feel like I need to break into your room.
Rose, just forget about it.
No, listen to me.
I said I did it because I was worried about you, but it wasn't just that.
What?
I was suspicious.
I thought there might be someone else.
Someone else?
Another woman.
Rose...
In my room?
I really thought so.
Because sometimes you're so horribly cold.
We watched...
You know I wouldn't...
We watched King Kong together.
I'm serious.
Sometimes I feel like you're pushing me away.
So I...
Did you get in?
Yeah.
Are you satisfied now?
There wasn't anyone there, was there?
No.
No, there was no one there.
There was absolutely no one in your room.
Not another woman.
Not me.
Not even you.
Rose...
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to apologize.
I wanted to apologize and then insult you.
I wanted to apologize and then, you know...
Hey, Jack.
Why do we keep going back between 2000 and 2099?
What's happening?
I think my PS2 is broken.
Let's see...
See?
Take care, Jack.
Wait, she doesn't care about the girl in the back.
Maybe... maybe in the next rooms.
Okay, hold on.
We just came from that way.
Did we go this way?
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah, yeah.
What's in that other way, though?
What is in the other... should I... did I get everything in the other place?
You know what?
Maybe it's fine.
Okay.
Good job!
Emma!
Good job, Emma!
Put Emma down first?
Okay.
Let's go back.
Yeah.
I want to make sure I got everything.
Sorry, guys.
Loot Goblin time!
Got a Gobble.
Nope.
Turn around.
Turn, turn, turn, turn, turn.
Oh, my O2, though, is going to be kind of... not so great because...
Oh.
Also, let's put on the ration first.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, I did get everything here.
This is where I accidentally blew up.
But this room had, like, two bombs in it.
I don't know if it has anything else worth it.
Okay.
You know what?
Never mind.
Let's just leave.
Okay.
I got it.
Sorry.
I like to double, triple, quadruple check everything.
Okay, guys?
That's fine.
It takes me no time to get there and back.
See?
I'm fast.
I'm speedy.
Speed, speed, speed, speed, speed, speed.
Okay.
Now we can take her hand.
Look at her.
She's sitting there.
She's waiting for me.
You okay?
Are you traumatized?
Let me rest.
Oh.
Just for a second.
Okay.
Me too.
Oh!
I'm regaining life.
I didn't realize that I was bleeding out.
What does she think of this?
I am so tired.
Okay.
All right, complainy pants.
What do you think of...
this?
Oh, gosh.
You actually lose so much health.
I'm so tired.
I'm tired.
Jack in the box.
You okay?
All right.
Let's go.
Come on.
Get up.
Oh, sorry.
Come on.
I don't remember how I...
How I take her hand.
Come here.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Come on.
Let me grab your hand.
Grab her hand.
Oh, sorry.
Oh, triangle.
Thanks.
I was trying to grab her hand.
I'm awkward, okay?
Gosh, I have no furniture in my room.
Don't blame me.
Just going to chill here.
You did good.
You did go...
It's coming.
I concentrated on your heartbeat.
It reminded me of when I was a kid.
My brother had a heartbeat.
So did my dad.
I remember my brother giving me a piggyback ride.
I was sleeping with my ear against his back.
I could hear his heartbeat.
Sounds like you were close.
We were back then.
We were stepchildren in our parents' second marriages.
She looks so much like Paj.
Wherever my brother went, I used to tag along.
So cute.
My brother didn't have any close friends.
Damn, girl.
It's fine.
It's Huey.
It doesn't matter.
We both wanted to be loved so much.
So much that we used to pretend.
Pretend?
Yeah, we used to play house.
My brother was the husband and I was the wife.
But it was always just make-believe.
We were only kids.
Just make-believe.
You know what I mean.
I never had a family.
Oh.
But I think I know what you mean.
Okay, way to bring it... make it weird, Raiden.
Here it is!
Raiden, what's your status?
Colonel?
I've got Emma Emmerich here.
We managed to avoid drowning.
Yeah!
Get her over to Shell One as soon as you can.
That's going to be hard with the connecting bridge on the upper level destroyed.
Didn't Olga say something about taking the oil fence at the bottom of Strut L?
Yeah, I remember that.
You should be able to go down by way of Strut L.
He said the thing!
We've managed to avoid drowning!
What about Emma?
She's been injected with something and she can't walk without any help.
The worst part about being socially awkward is when you try to hold a girl's hand and you end up breaking her neck.
I know.
And hold down the action button to give her a hand.
Oh, you could have told me that sooner.
Take your finger off the action button.
Emma can sit and wait until you help her back up.
Colonel!
And be careful.
You won't be able to use any weapons while you're leading her.
Okay.
Now head for Strut L.
Yeah.
We're on our way.
We're on our way!
Raiden, we've infiltrated the computer room.
What's your situation?
Emma's safe.
We're heading your way.
Good job.
Shell One's deserted.
Looks like everybody's aboard Arsenal.
I had a look at the system, but there's nothing I can do.
EE's our only hope.
Right.
I'll put her on, then.
Huh?
EE?
What?
How?
I'll use my codec as a relay.
Ahem.
Here she is.
Huh?
How?
Oh.
EE.
EE?
Is that you?
How?
EE.
Stop calling her that.
Why are you involved with Metal Gear?
Huh?
You knew our family's dark history and still got involved?
What's wrong with you?
I should have known.
I'm sorry.
Answer me.
Why are you repeating the same mistake?
She has no thoughts.
I can't tell her.
I wanted to hurt you.
I can't R1 and R2 her.
I wanted to see you suffer.
EE?
You abandoned me.
No.
That's not what happened.
All right.
That's enough.
Huh.
Who are you?
I'm a friend of Otacon's, Emma.
Otacon.
Enough with the sibling rivalry.
That's not what this is.
We haven't got time for this.
Ryan.
He has a nickname that's better than mine.
Get her over here right now.
I...
EE.
Gotcha, Snake.
I'll head over there with Emma.
Most of the enemies aboard Arsenal, but I suggest you be careful.
Maybe.
Make sure Emma gets here in one piece.
Ryden, take care of my sister.
Don't worry.
I'll get her there.
Yep.
Most...
The enemies should be all...
All of them should be on Arsenal, right?
Oh.
Wait.
What was that?
Oh.
Just kidding.
My cell phone's going off.
Hello?
Be careful.
Claymore Mines are set there?
There are?
Wait.
Actually?
Also, how'd you know where I was?
You freak?
Where's my Mine Detector?
Sorry.
I don't remember where a lot of stuff is.
What's that?
Just a lasso?
Oh, mind detector, there it is.
Wow!
They just set these here!
Like crazy!
Why are they there?
That's so funny.
Come on, E.E.
Let's go.
Okay.
Oh, my heart.
To troll you.
Well, who would go the long way?
Guess me.
Oh, gosh.
I've never walked that direction.
I don't think I remember that either.
Yeah.
Did something happen to the president?
No.
No!
Dramatic flashback.
It's dead!
It wasn't me, though.
You actually wrote this virus?
It's not really a virus.
It's more like a worm cluster.
Worm.
It's actually a delayed-effect autonomous program that's designed to invade GW's cerebrum...
A worm?
It's useless.
You know what GW is?
Of course.
I created it.
Huh?
You look surprised.
Uh, well...
Cat got your tongue?
I'm sorry.
I...
How about the Patriots?
Ever heard of them?
Yes.
But I only know what I've been told.
How is Emma told so much at her... like...
Can you tell me what you know?
She's, like, so young.
Sure.
But it's hard to put into words.
Thank you for the 10 gifted.
All right.
Thank you.
Are you reading me, Emma?
Yes.
Loud and clear.
The President said that Arsenal gear was the Patriots' key to supremacy.
That's as good a description as any.
What exactly is it?
It's a massive data-processing system capable of controlling information on a global scale.
A data-processing system?
That's right.
The system's a social device for maintaining the Patriots' control.
Emma actually reads her work even.
You've lost me.
Well, in this day and age, information emerges from every direction and is freely distributed.
A variety of information gathered by servers employing the latest in high-speed communication networks and P2P technology is rapidly circulated to individuals.
In fact, the speed of this circulation process is accelerating on an almost daily basis.
The Patriots seem to be afraid of this development.
Apparently, they believe that their role will shift from dominant to dominated.
Whoa.
Let me give you an example.
You're aware of Solid Snake's anti-Metal Gear activities, aren't you?
Yeah.
Yeah, I know a little about it.
Well, that's just a small sample of uncontrolled information.
I can guarantee you the Patriots did not want Solid Snake's name publicized.
Whoa.
Now, look at it like this.
Political scandals, corporate corruption...
Scandal.
Up until now, the Patriots have managed to keep a lid on these and other self-serving events.
But with their existing data-processing system, they're no longer able to effectively control the flow of information generated at the individual level.
With the new created system, they can fully regulate digital information.
High-level information can be categorized in stages, given clearance levels, and deleted as necessary.
Where do I know this voice from?
It's Jennifer Hale.
By deleting such information, the Patriots can shape the course of history as they see fit.
Somebody's bound to catch on.
No.
The memory capacity, not to mention the lifespan of the average individual, is extremely limited.
On the other hand, digital information lasts virtually forever.
It doesn't deteriorate.
So?
The alphabet.
26 letters, right?
It could have been 30 letters.
What if the four deleted letters were controlled by a program?
Impossible.
My brain.
It's not.
In fact, something similar is already in the web.
My brain here is just whole.
Do you know how many genes exist in an individual?
About 30 to 40,000?
Right.
That's what was announced at the turn of the century.
What?
There's actually 100,000, according to the original theory advanced by the scientific community.
Information regarding the remaining 60,000 remains.
The gene was suppressed by the Patriots.
Why?
How would you know?
Do you know what a gene looks like?
Did you count them yourself?
There are research organizations.
Of course.
And their reports have already been subtly altered.
They're even beginning to believe the doctored reports.
GW is a system that allows the Patriots to decide what will be recorded in tomorrow's history.
So what we're talking about is one huge censorship system for deleting information which might be inconvenient to the Patriots.
Exactly.
The actual physical core for handling the task, GW, is installed in Arsenal.
It's the only system in the world with an optic neural AI that has a parallel processing capacity of 980 trillion Hamets.
I suppose that being a specialist in neural AI and complex logic played a significant role in your association with the Metal Gear project.
That's not the only reason.
What do you mean?
I guess there are plenty of other reasons.
Yes, there are.
I understand.
Do you?
So Arsenal Gear was actually designed to protect the GW system, wasn't it?
Um, yes.
It's armed with everything, including nuclear weapons.
Why did you create something like this, Emma?
What the hell?
But is the AI actually capable of controlling everything?
No.
GW is only the system's core.
It's only for deciding what data is stored or deleted.
The actual subsystem for executing the task exists within our social structure.
What?
You freak.
Do you remember the panic that gripped the computer industry prior to the end of the century?
You mean the Y2K problem?
Y2K!
That's exactly it!
Yeah, Y2K!
If you call, our government supplied the world with a countermeasure program using the internet at full capacity.
Y2K.
CloudStrike.
The program was distributed to every government organization, every key facility throughout the world.
In addition, the same program was included in an OS application for distribution among the public.
Definitely making out.
Let me guess.
The Y2K countermeasure contained a program designed by the Patriots.
Yes.
And everything supplied from that day onward contains the same program.
Impossible.
Do you know how a computer operates?
Do you really know the basic principles on how data is exchanged?
Uh...
Nobody's aware of it, but there's a subsystem...
I forgot our previous prompt.
...that's about to be activated.
Is that why Solidus wants to burn out every electrical circuit in Manhattan with a nuclear blast?
No.
Probably.
But the overall system isn't actually complete.
What?
It still lacks the necessary factors for judging situations.
I heard they were planning a major experiment in the next few days to provide complex data for GW to study.
And suddenly all this happens.
Sound cute.
Emma, it's not your fault.
If it wasn't for the terrorists...
Yeah, you're right.
I-I mean...
Well...
I think that's about all I know.
But you still...
Right.
I'm...
Uh, thanks.
But the...
I think we'd better head for the computer room.
But I think you still...
My bird in the computer room.
Is he safe?
Your bird!
That noisy overgrown parakeet?
Excuse me, he's a parrot.
And he's my best friend.
My only friend.
He's very cute.
Well, the bird's okay.
Good.
Did you know that in the old days, miners used to take a canary into the mine shafts to detect toxic gas?
Yeah.
That's what he's for?
No.
I really needed someone to talk to.
Why'd you bring that up then?
Right.
I think we'd better get moving.
Look at that guy.
He's so cute.
We've got a little longer to cover than the last time.
I'll give it my best.
Yeah.
Whatever you do, don't open your eyes.
Why not?
There's a dead guy.
A dead body, not a pretty sight.
Why do they have to do it again?
It'll be too dark to see anything.
Who put more mines there?
Who did that?
I don't know.
Okay.
What are those sticks in your head?
These?
Decoration?
They're lacquered chopsticks.
They hold your hair in place.
Did you know that they're pretty popular in Europe and South America?
What are those sticks in your head?
Can't say that I do.
You're not only cute, but smart too.
Oh.
I'm much more than cute.
She's so cute.
Okay.
Let's go.
Raiden, you have a girlfriend.
How did they let her keep a pet in the workplace?
They didn't even let her work.
I don't know how her pet is in a completely different area.
Hey, Rose.
How do you like it now?
Jack, is that you?
Yeah.
You like her on my back?
You like this?
You like what you see?
Well, Jack, it sounds like you and Miss Emma are getting along just fine.
Rose?
I've been monitoring your every move and conversation.
I can't say it's been fun.
Give me a break.
I'm only trying to keep her spirits up.
Is that right?
Yeah, yeah.
Absolutely.
My mission is to get her to the computer room.
That's all?
Yeah.
You're lying.
You're attracted to her, aren't you?
I'll admit she's cute.
Cuter than me?
Oh, my God.
Rose, you're beautiful.
You know how I feel about you.
Have you remembered yet?
You mean April 30th?
Yes.
It's your birthday, isn't it?
Wrong.
You're not even warm.
What is it, then?
Forget it.
I don't know.
You don't even know her birthday?
I'm just a little jealous.
Rose, you better get moving.
Good luck.
He doesn't even know her birthday.
He's like, it's your birthday, isn't it?
This guy.
Ryden, take Emma and go to Strut L.
Okay.
There's a ladder down onto the oil fence on the ocean surface from that strut.
Wait.
Tell me more.
The most toxic relationship in MGM.
Okay, Ryden.
Let me talk to Emma.
Oh, okay.
Sure.
Okay.
No arguing.
One condition.
No problem.
Put her on.
E.E., is that you?
Yes.
What do you want?
Why did you get involved in weapons development?
A lot of people will get hurt.
Even more will die.
I'm talking about the destruction of homes and cities, radioactive contamination for years to come.
You, of all people, should know the horror of nuclear weapons.
You know about our family's dark history.
Yeah.
Why, E.E., why?
You left me.
No fighting.
You made my life a living hell.
I didn't have a choice.
Don't lie to me.
The pool.
You could never look me in the eye after the accident.
You took the easy way out so you wouldn't have to face me.
That way you could avoid responsibility every day.
The girls are fighting.
You ran.
You ran away so you wouldn't have to face the pain.
No.
That's not why I left.
You left me and took the easy way out.
That's not true.
I left the house because...
You're a criminal, just like me.
A criminal?
I know what you did.
You manipulated our account on the network.
Look at what you're doing now.
You're nothing but a cracker.
A what?
I'm just applying my knowledge for the cause.
The cause?
What cause?
Justice?
For peace, E.E.
I'm not like Snake.
I can't carry a gun and face the enemy.
That's why I do what I do best.
Oh, right.
Nice justification, Hal.
Forget about being a criminal.
You'd make a great lawyer.
Maybe she meant hacker.
That's why I do what I do best.
That's enough.
Mr. No-nonsense coming in to stop them from fighting.
Emma.
What's up, Raiden?
Out of my way.
Let me talk.
You want to talk to Otacon?
Yes.
I'll put him on.
Yeah?
What is it?
Up to now, scientists have continued to be active participants in war.
What's your opinion?
What's your...
Oh, the way she leans in.
There's no doubt that war has been an ideal event that fuels the progress of science.
What's your opinion?
But therein lies the truth.
We scientists must establish some form of work ethic.
It's a tragedy that both the government and the military act as sponsors to modern science.
What are you talking about?
The atom and hydrogen bombs were born from laboratories owned and operated by universities and private enterprises.
Los Alamos and the Lawrence Livermore labs were run by universities.
She's popping off.
There's nothing strange about that.
Weapons development and universities.
This may come as a surprise.
But science requires that information be...
...exchanged freely.
You're referring to the will of Professor Oppenheimer, aren't you?
Hacker who breaks into secure systems.
See?
I told you it was hacker.
I never thought that my research results would bring about misfortune to others.
That was until the Shadow Moses incident.
I have no regrets.
Damn!
That's where you're wrong.
We scientists know the dangers of...
Oh my god, Emma!
It's up to us to protect the people.
She's like, I like nuclear weapons.
We can't allow it to be exploited by nations or their politics.
Man and nuclear weapons.
Nuclear weapons cannot coexist.
Mere mortals were never meant to handle nuclear fusion.
Science defines me.
Watching the brother and sister nerd rage.
My government respects me.
Can you tell me what's wrong with that?
Can you?
Okay.
That's enough.
Oh my god.
Well, let's see if there's one more, okay?
I had a huge crush on Emma.
I don't blame you.
Snake.
Let me talk to him.
Oh, yeah.
Otacon's busy right now.
You'll have to settle for me.
What?
Oh, okay.
I'm sorry.
Now, what do you want?
Hal's wrong.
Science doesn't exist to benefit the world.
Rage.
Then what is it for?
Science is for the individual.
Nerd rage.
For me, it's a way to realize my dreams.
Sounds pretty greedy.
You can't realize your dreams without greed.
And what's your dream?
Take revenge on Hal.
To beat him in his own game.
Nerd fight.
I am going to make him regret the day he left me.
I am going to make him realize he was wrong.
Of all the idiots in the world.
Idiotic.
I think that's enough.
Idiotic?
It's my goal.
My reason for being alive.
Hal is wrong.
He's only being used by his country.
He's pitiful.
Even you guys are using him.
Me?
I'm using science to achieve my own dream.
Real bright, lady.
That's exactly the line that scientists are never meant to cross.
Oh, my God.
Right.
I sold my soul for revenge.
I will never forgive him.
Yeah.
Don't pretend this conversation never happened.
No.
You tell my brother exactly what I said.
I'm sorry.
Emma.
What?
You're speaking your mind.
Not your heart.
Whoa.
Just leave it at that.
Okay.
Oh.
Awkward.
Should I check one more time?
It's so entertaining to listen to them go off.
The rumors about Big Shell being a big cover up are all true.
It seems like E.E.
just took a leap.
Huge leap here.
Sure.
There are some facilities to clean up the pollution.
But they're not running at full capacity.
Don't you think it's funny that even though two years have gone by since the incident, they haven't managed to clean up all the crude oil?
Of course, the media doesn't report that kind of thing.
I think they're having fresh shipments of crude oil brought in to replace the stuff they've cleaned up.
Ah.
The story you were told about toxic chemicals being released if the plant were blown up also seems pretty fishy.
I don't think it's actually true.
Information is being suppressed on a huge scale.
Super Step Sister Method?
Get me out!
You guys seem to think that the new Metal Gear is worth all the money.
I mean, all the effort and money they're spending on it.
So I've been lied to all along.
Yeah, man.
No.
I think even your CO didn't know what was going on.
And that's probably what he's been telling you.
I didn't mean by the Colonel.
I meant by you.
Huh?
We never lied to you.
We just didn't tell you everything.
That's all.
Lying by omission!
You know, you're a pretty interesting guy.
You're just like Snake said.
What did he say?
That you're a weak, simple, and ungrateful person.
You're a simple -minded, stubborn fool.
A weak, simple-minded...
Oh, don't worry.
He didn't mean anything bad by it.
Nothing bad?
Well, what could possibly be worse than that?
That lying, useless, backstabbing, mincing son of a...
Raiden, I'm his friend.
I know him better than anyone else.
I know he's not that kind of guy.
He's raging!
Yeah?
So what?
And, uh, by the way, there's one more thing you should probably know about Snake.
What?
He's bisexual.
He's right here.
Ah!
Neck.
And he's not even close to you?
Yep.
Did he hear... every word?
I'm...
I'm just going to get back to the mission now.
Oopsie!
Oh my gosh!
I thought that was a mine!
Oh my god, I thought that was a mine!
Oh my gosh, I was so scared for a second.
My whole body flinched.
Oh gosh!
Oh!
Ah!
Oh my gosh, I thought it was a mine.
Cheese, Louise.
Cheese, cheese, cheese, cheese, cheese.
Oh my gosh, okay.
This way.
Down, down, down.
By the river.
There are no mines in this room though, right?
Close your eyes.
I'm sorry, I'm bad at direction.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Who the heck is Louise?
My favorite part of this game so far is how many small details there are.
So many interactions and conversations I didn't see when I played it.
I know, right?
They're so fun.
Snake!
You've got rations.
Okay, I think I'm good.
What is it?
Oh, I prefer rations over Rose's home cooking.
Not bad, huh?
Sorry, I thought that maybe I would get something while looking at him.
While zooming in on him.
He looks pretty bad shape, not gonna lie.
Sorry, I didn't mean to like skip the cutscene.
Okay.
Alright, there's bombs down here.
There's bombs.
There's bombs, I saw them.
Okay.
They replaced him, maybe.
Rush.
Hold on.
Wait.
Oh gosh, I'm going the wrong way.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, was that something there?
Oh god.
Oh god, oh god, oh god, oh god.
Sorry, I'm...
Oh my gosh.
But there's a rash in there.
I have to go that way anyway.
Okay.
Oak, you're solid too.
Raiden, please dump your girlfriend already.
No!
Stay with her forever.
I love the excitement.
Oh my god.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Just go this way.
Oh my god, Emma!
Emma!
That was crazy, wasn't it?
That was wild.
Wasn't it?
Woohoo!
Yeah.
Look at the water.
It's disgusting.
Why is it...
Why is the water making noise?
Eww.
Okay, here we go.
She'll be fine.
She'll...
She's fine.
Okay.
Alrighty.
We're here.
Don't worry.
See?
And no bugs inside.
No bugs.
Shoo!
Come on, Emma.
It's okay.
Bugs?
I hate bugs!
Come on, come on.
You look so sad.
Come on.
Bugs!
I hate bugs!
Freeze them.
I'll freeze them for you, girly.
Yeah.
Just a little bit more.
Where'd they come from?
Nasty.
Oh.
Bugs!
I hate bugs!
Yeah.
Me too.
Especially pink ones.
Oh.
This does a really great job.
This is every exterminator's dream.
Okay, Emma.
Don't look so sad.
My goodness.
Oh.
They're hidden in there.
Let's just go.
Come on.
Mata in shambles?
Good.
Trank her and carry her over the bugs.
Maybe we could do that.
Oh, God.
You guys.
Oh, my stomach's starting to hurt.
No.
My tummy's starting to hurt at this part.
You guys, I have a bit of a trauma here in this area.
If you know, you know.
But I have a bit of a trauma in this area.
Oh, God.
Did he disappear out of existence?
Oh.
What is he doing?
Oh, my gosh.
Okay.
I'm gonna take her this way.
I'm gonna have her hide.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, God.
I don't think you guys understand the emotions I'm feeling right now.
Oh, my, gosh.
Oh, God.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, gosh.
You guys...
What happens here.
Oh, shoot.
Oh, my gosh.
There's somebody there.
No.
Just the bugs.
No, no, no, no.
Go.
Oh my god,
my cat!
Oh my god!
Wait, Pies!
Pies, stop!
Stop climbing my chair!
Okay, I'll let you out, hold on!
Pies, please, Pies.
Pies, Pies, Pies.
Pies, please.
Oh my god, hold on.
I gotta let my cat out of my room.
Pies, I'm sorry!
Okay, just one second.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh gosh, oh gosh, oh gosh.
I'm wondering if I should just kill him.
Sorry, buddy.
Oh, wow.
You're a tough guy.
How?
Okay, there we go.
Okay.
Don't worry!
I'm gonna handle this room first!
Emma!
You guys, I can't have him waking up, okay?
It's too scary here, okay?
You have to...
Understand!
Please understand!
Doesn't he come out of...
That hallway on the right?
Okay, let's just go get Emma.
Come on.
Let's go.
Well, you can wait in the...
You can wait in the waiting room... in the...
In the...
In the lounge.
Here, you're in the break room.
There you go.
Take a...
Actually, there...
Oh, I was gonna say, there's no couches in...
There he is.
What's his route?
Let's see what he does.
Get her a cola, too.
Now, does he look up?
Because if not, I can just stand and...
You know...
And grab him.
Which way does he turn?
Oh...
Okay, we can just stand over here and wait for him.
Perfect.
I'm feeling...
Oh, God, I'm...
I'm feeling it, Mr. Krabs.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry, man.
Is there something else here?
Oh.
This is for my own good.
This is for...
This is for me.
Sorry.
I have to do it.
I have to do it to you.
I have...
I have to...
You guys, it's for my own...
Please.
It's for my own well-being.
This is the part I've been dreading the entire game.
Please understand.
All right, come on.
Yeah, Emma, don't look.
Close your eyes.
Close your eyes, okay?
Come on.
I'm gonna put you in that hallway, okay?
Yeah.
I'm gonna put you in here.
Don't look at the blood.
It's fine.
Don't look at it.
Don't even notice it.
That's me.
This is...
This is me, right?
I'm tired.
Okay.
Can I just leave?
All right.
I know I seemed dramatic right now but I don't...
I don't know if you understand.
I don't know if you can...
If you might under...
I don't know what to do.
Turn around.
Can't I peek up over ledges?
How do I peek up over ledges?
I can't remember.
It doesn't mean fall!
Oh my god, that was close.
How do I peek up over ledges?
L2, R2, and first person.
Okay.
Emma.
Emma, it's over.
Emma, it's over for us.
Emma.
What are they going to do to her actually?
I'm curious.
So
anyway, I started blasting!
Oh shoot, where did you come from?
Emma.
Emma, we can't leave this place.
Emma, we're in trouble.
Emma.
We're in trouble.
Emma, we're in trouble.
Emma.
This is a bad run, Emma!
Emma!
The run is over, Emma!
Jack, please answer me!
Jack!
Oh gosh, you can actually kill so many guards, they stop coming?
I don't believe that.
I don't believe that to be true at all.
You okay?
That was all just a bad, bad dream.
That actually went...
Um, worse than how I first have done it.
That was actually worse than before.
That's so funny.
Funny how that is.
Funny.
That bastard.
Oh god.
Oh!
Wait, he didn't notice that, did he?
Nah, he was too busy sleeping.
He was busy being a sleepy guy.
Come on.
Oh, hello?
Come on, girl.
We gotta run.
We gotta go.
I'm gonna put you over here again.
Don't worry.
I'm gonna put you over here.
Yeah.
And I'm also gonna put both bodies over here too.
I'm gonna put both bodies over here too.
Oh
no!
Wait, that was my...
Wait, wait, wait!
Wait, wait!
Oh my god, wait!
Open!
Now fall asleep.
There we go.
Okay.
Um, let's get his butt.
Alright!
You come here.
Come here, come here.
Come here, come...
Oh.
Come here, come here.
Come on, come on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Eternal sleep for you.
Nice eternal slumber...
for you.
Emma, don't look.
Close your ears.
Hey!
Um...
Give me something before you go.
Really?
Cheap.
This guy...
There we go.
Alright.
Come on, Emma.
Yeah, he is stingy.
Okay.
Alright.
One guy...
You know what?
Let's actually move him a little bit...
inward.
So nobody can see him either.
Right...
here.
Then we'll put your friend right on top of you.
Come on.
Isn't this so brutal?
I don't want them waking up!
They wake up and they'll be like...
Oh!
We got an intruder guy.
Uh-oh.
Better I...
I guess I better...
attack everything.
Oh!
And, you know, call for backup and do everything terrible.
Okay.
They won't wake up.
They do!
Don't they?
They'll wake up eventually.
It takes forever.
Yeah.
And I take forever to...
to get through this part.
Okay?
So...
We're even.
It's fine.
Actually, when does this guy come through the elevator?
Is it timed or...
Good night.
This is the only time when murder is okay.
Okay.
I'll leave you.
Well, this is not a safe spot either.
Hold on.
Let's wait for the other guy to leave.
I don't know how much he can see.
Let's turn around.
I don't want him to see me walk in front of the stairs.
He will see me walk in front of the stairs.
We know you enjoy the killing in this area.
Yeah, I do.
And I'm not afraid to admit it.
I enjoy the killing in this area.
I will kill for sport.
Okay.
Lay down.
Let's see.
Wait.
I think I'm too low.
I'm too low.
Wait, maybe if I do this...
Maybe I can get him from far away.
There we go.
I can't see him.
Oh, he's gone.
Oh, wait.
Please,
put me out of my misery.
Uh-oh, the misery.
Oh, my heart is going like a bajillion miles per hour.
Oh my god, please!
Where are you?
Raiden, why are you so short?
I'm tempted.
No, it's fine.
It's fine.
No, I won't do it.
I won't do it.
I'm just gonna steal your stuff.
Oh, wow.
Wow, you got the big...
You got the big guns, okay.
I don't remember where to do this... how to do...
Oh gosh.
I'm too short.
Oh, I can get him!
But I think someone will wake him up.
I think I should've waited.
I think someone comes around.
Let me see if someone comes.
Oh, my hands are so sweaty!
Oh my god, my hands are so sweaty!
My hands are so sweaty!
Oh god, everything is gripping.
I'm gripping!
Can you please turn?
I see...
Oh, there we go.
There we go.
Okay.
Stop!
Okay, let's go.
Lolly, lolly, lolly.
It's your adverbs.
Here.
Okay, I'm gonna leave you.
Right here.
Okay?
Okay.
Don't do anything stupid!
Oh, gosh.
There's that guy up there.
What does he do?
What is...
What do you do?
Is there another guy?
Is there anyone else?
Is it just him?
He's asleep.
Please go back to sleep!
Please!
Please Get up, get up, get up.
Take my hand.
What can I do for you, Jack?
Oh god, Rose!
Jack, how far do you think the Patriots' digital control extends?
I don't really know, but it probably influences a lot of what goes on in our everyday lives.
Even mundane things like which movies and songs become a hit and what kind of clothes we wear?
I think taste would be the easiest thing to manipulate.
I mean, think about the kinds of film and bands everyone wants to go to see.
It's whatever's at the top of the chart.
What are you talking about?
And if the charts are made up...
Exactly.
But you can't really control individual taste.
It's too closely tied to personality.
Thank you.
I don't know about that.
Trends have always been about following the leader.
Not necessarily.
The age of direct personal interaction is over.
So is the idea of word-of-mouth communication.
Rose, you have any friends you've met online?
Yeah, I do.
How many?
Well, if you count only the ones I talk to a lot, I'd say about 20.
20 people?
One or two tops.
Rose, you have 20 friends on the internet?
That's how it is for everyone, I guess.
Oh my god.
Even if your online buddies had fake identities and were circulating false information, you'd have no way of knowing.
That's an insane amount of friends online.
Right.
And there'd be no way for you to know for sure.
Well, what about people who do meet face-to-face then?
My hands are shaking so much.
Like us.
Oh my god.
Have you ever really shown me the real you?
Why was that so easy?
I wouldn't even know the real me myself.
But you're being honest with yourself now.
That's going so easy.
Well, that's how I see it.
Well, how am I being honest?
I've never seen you show so much feeling.
Fear, anger, even a kind of giddiness.
It may seem a strange thing to say, but you're living out loud for the first time that I've seen.
I'm just trying to get the job done.
This is war, you know.
I do know that.
Okay, back to the game, everybody.
I see you're different from your usual restrained self.
What about you, then?
I always want to be open with you as much as I can.
What the heck are you talking about?
Did I get all of them?
Which one?
Which strut?
Okay.
All right, now that I've... oh my gosh.
Oh, I feel so much relief.
Right, take Emma and head for Strut L.
Oh my god.
Strut L is on the south end of that KL connecting bridge.
Oh.
Okay.
Snake, are you online?
Raiden, I may have to sign off for a while.
Anything wrong?
Just a small errand.
Don't worry about it.
What's it about?
Here goes.
I'm going offline.
No!
He's offline.
Okay, Strut L.
Oh, gosh.
This part's kind of annoying, too, though.
Come on.
Oh, the anxiety was the real enemy all along.
Yup.
PSG.
Chaff.
Oh, my bad.
Sorry.
Here we go.
La la la.
Walking along.
Oh, be careful.
Oh.
Be careful.
Oh la la la.
Here we go.
Snake hates us, you guys.
He hates...
Oh,
no.
Guys, it's so...
Wait.
He can't see me.
Idiot.
Is there anybody else?
Just him?
Where'd you come from?
He must have come up the stairs.
Sometimes, their vision is like...
Sometimes, I feel like they actually have 180 IQ.
And sometimes, they're just dumb, dumb little guys who can't see two feet in front of them.
All right.
Let's go, Emma.
Come on.
Oh, wait.
I have to get the coolant.
Don't I?
Don't catch on fire.
Emma.
Stand back.
Watch.
As a pro takes the reins.
Oh.
Sorry.
It's still on fire.
Okay.
Don't go, Emma.
Don't...
Emma.
It's still on fire.
Let's go now.
Oh.
No.
These guys aren't genome soldiers.
I just like to say that they all have 180 IQ.
Okay.
I hate this part.
Oh, no.
We have...
We don't have a card.
Beep, beep.
Damn it.
What's wrong?
This door is security level five.
Five.
I don't have card five.
Damn.
You're such a baby.
Giving up already?
You're such a whiny baby.
I don't have card five.
Ta-da.
What the...
In European extreme, they're like insects directly telepathic paying your location.
You should have told me you had it.
God.
The truth is I just remembered it myself.
Why are you so mean?
Who cares if it...
You would have...
You didn't need it earlier.
Why are you such a jerk, Raiden?
Gosh.
Must have 195 IQ.
Yeah, pretty much.
All right.
Let's save.
I know.
I just...
I save so often.
And this one, because I love the drama, he has card five cheeks, though.
How could he be so mean to Rose, to Emma?
Oh, okay, she's got nothing to say to me.
All right, Colonel?
Okay.
I hope she's good with heights.
Okay, we don't have a nerd in this area.
But I hear them.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait.
Where is that guy?
It's just the one guy, I believe, right?
Did I just say nerd?
Oh, sorry, node.
Where is he?
Doesn't he?
Doesn't he come over here?
Am I crazy?
Hey, guy!
Huh?
Where is that guy?
Where is he?
I'm scared.
I'm gonna...
Cool it!
I'm so... not cool it.
We'll get him when he walks over there.
No worries.
Oh.
Okay, hold on.
Oh, shoot.
Oh, there's two guys!
There are two guys.
There's two guys.
I believe...
I believe there's two guys.
I think there's two guys.
You guys, there's two guys.
There's two guys!
Oh!
Uhhh...
Ah!
Okay.
Now let me take him.
Now he's down.
Now get your brother.
Enemy in the area.
Increase security level.
What are you talking about?
Understood.
Your friend just passed out!
You guys, extreme caution.
Emma...
I might have...
Emma, don't just sit there.
Emma, I might have made a mistake.
Emma...
Emma, I think I made a mistake.
Emma?
I think I made a little whoopsie.
Emma, don't be mad at me.
Emma, why don't you look at me anymore?
I thought he was going to go get his friend and wake him up.
Oh, she needs a box too.
Are they going to come over here?
I sure hope not.
Why am I even wishing for that?
Emma?
Emma, just stay put, okay?
Just you stay there.
Do they think about your actions, Missy?
In the timeout corner over there.
We're just waiting for the caution to run out, okay, Emma?
Don't worry about it, Emma.
She can't hear you.
She has her AirPods in.
Alright, let's try that again.
Let's try that again without messing up this time.
Okay, Raiden.
Now, what we need to do is not mess it up.
Some instincts as a gamer.
Oh gosh, can this guy see me?
Okay, now investigate your friend.
Your friend just fell asleep.
Are you going to not notice him?
Or...
Okay.
Oh, oh, he did.
He just kicked him awake.
Oh, shoot.
Okay.
Do you have any stun grenades?
I think I do, but Emma will also be stunned, will she not?
Oh, he's going to walk over.
Okay, let me see if I can get him now.
Oh, there we go.
There we go.
Okay.
Come on, Emma.
We just needed him in position.
Oh, oh, oh.
Okay, we're good.
Let's go.
They're asleep.
Sleepy fellas.
Such sleepy fellas right there.
Drag her by the legs.
But if you drag her by the legs, she will...
You can't go through doors, I'm pretty sure.
I don't think you can take her through doors if you drag her.
Come on.
In through here.
And down the hatch.
Big shells.
E.P.S.
soldiers.
Alrighty.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Are you afraid of heights, Emma?
Are you okay?
You're good with heights too?
It's crazy how much and how little of the game we have left, isn't it?
What if we...
I have a question for you.
What is it?
How do you feel about heights?
I can't say I like heights.
The water's higher on my phobia list.
I'm self-centered.
I'm self -centered?
Well, we have to go down the ladder.
How far down?
Just a little bit.
Too high.
Why do I feel like we've had this conversation before?
How little is little?
About 130 feet.
Huh.
Think you can do it?
Would you take no for an answer?
How are your legs?
Better.
The numbness is gone.
I can climb down on my own.
It's cute when the numbness is gone.
Okay, follow me.
So cute when her numbness is all better.
She's got little legs that work.
Here we go.
Sweat.
This is...
It's about to be one of my favorite, like, vistas of the game.
Don't look up or skirt right in.
Oh, she's wearing shorts.
Okay, never mind.
What a thrill.
We're darkness and silence through the night.
Make sure to have the d-mic ready.
Oh, you know it!
Right...
The sunset, it's beautiful.
Here.
If we don't hurry, it'll be the last thing we see.
This whole area is like my favorite...
Oh, here!
Here, here, here, there.
This is my favorite scene in the game.
Or like, view in the game.
It's so pretty.
It's so nice.
It's so cute.
Okay.
I'm ready.
So beautiful here.
Raiden?
Ow.
The oil fence.
There are ciphers and several guards.
Raiden, you're carrying a PSG-1, aren't you?
It's time to play sniper.
Not bad.
This spot gives me a good view of the targets.
You're going to have to cover Emma until she crosses to Strut E.
I'll get there and provide some support of my own.
Yay!
Think you can handle it?
I can.
I know the drill.
I faced a similar situation in Advanced Mode Level 4 VR training with the PSG-1.
Advanced Mode Level 4 VR.
I guess it's better to go.
Nothing.
Make sure you don't hit Emma.
No promises.
Right now, with Arsenal's boarding in progress, security should be at a minimum.
That doesn't mean it's going to be easy.
Given the situation, they probably got claymores in place to make up for the security shortage.
Oh, I forgot about the claymores.
You're right.
Make sure you use your thermal goggles.
I have the thermal goggles.
Okay.
I'm heading for Strut E.
When Snake tells me to use thermal goggles, I don't mind so much.
I'm going to clear a path for you from here.
How?
Sniper fire.
You're kidding.
Trust me.
What if I fall into the sea?
I can't swim.
You were doing pretty good a few minutes ago.
Okay.
Think you can do it?
Loud and clear.
Would you take no for an answer?
What's that supposed to mean?
No.
All right.
Get going.
You'll be fine.
Okay.
What's that supposed to mean?
Time to blind yourself.
True.
Oh, golly.
All right.
Here she goes.
And here we go.
Let's grab some ammo.
And let's get into place.
Let's get into position.
Oh, that's right.
Oh.
Okay, everybody.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, possessive means too.
Where is it?
Sorry.
I can never find everything.
Okay.
Thermal goggles.
Let's go.
All right.
You good?
We're good.
Look at her.
Let's get this guy.
Let's take this guy out.
Nice.
And the ciphers.
Let's start taking those out.
Oh, dang it.
It was the possessive means fault, everybody.
Wasn't me.
It wasn't me.
I know I don't need it for this part, but...
Oh, my God.
There we go.
Okay.
A ARE.
Okey -dokey.
And...
Take this guy out.
Oh...
It's over here, right?
There's more.
Look at her go...
Ah!
There's another one!
Oh, are you kidding me?
Are you kidding me right now?
Are you...
Sleep!
All is well!
Where are the other ones?
Oh, let's take this out.
Can I zoom with this?
Zoom in with... oh.
Am I just not looking in the right places?
Oh, that's a guy.
That's a man.
There were other mines though, weren't there?
Let's take this guy out.
I think I got him.
Shoot.
I think he'll fall asleep.
Yeah.
Mine's on the third bridge.
Oh!
I'm just taking stuff out while we wait.
You good?
Everybody's sleepy, sleepy.
Sleepy, sleepy, sleepy.
Everybody's sleepy.
Nobody's awake.
Don't do it Raiden.
Oh, your shaky hands.
Raiden.
Nice.
I don't need no sesame...
Oh, directional mic.
Oh my god, that's a man.
Hold on.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Wait, sorry.
I need this first.
Oh, that's a bird.
Scaring me for a second.
Where's the directional mic?
The mic is with the mic.
Where is she?
There she is.
Go Emma, go!
Did they stay asleep?
Or did they wake back up?
Oh shoot, oh shoot, oh shoot, oh shoot.
Um, I think I should be good.
Good Emma, don't worry about it, girlie.
Don't worry, I got you.
Don't worry, Emma.
Emma, I got you.
Emma, don't worry, don't worry, don't worry.
This is Snake.
Can you hear me?
Yeah, loud and clear.
I've reached my sniping position on Strut E.
I'll provide support fire from here.
Thanks.
Do me a favor and take out whatever I miss.
Just call me when you want me to shoot.
Oh, okay.
Alright.
Oh, my bad, sorry.
She's gonna...
This is where the de-mic is most important.
But also...
We can de-mic...
Over here...
Where is he?
Where is that guy?
Someone's talking to himself.
Where is he?
Ah!
Oh, my god, sorry.
I'm so sorry, Emma.
Emma!
Emma, I'm so sorry, girl.
I'm so...
Don't worry!
You're safe!
Keep...
Oh, gosh, there's another guy here.
Oh, my god, wait.
Oh, your friend is...
Oh, my god, there's multiple of them.
Why are there so many of you guys?
I don't think I hit a sniper.
I don't think I hit a single...
I don't think I hit a single shot.
Hey, can you, like, all fall asleep...
So I can do the funny stuff?
Where is she?
Wait, where did she go?
Oh, there she is.
There we go.
I got you in my sights.
Snake can help.
I know.
Okay, there we go.
Alright.
All clear, probably.
Yeah, I'll call Snake to do the rush.
Thanks, Snake!
Damn, I don't think I can do this.
Snake, take over for me.
Take over me.
Oh, you can zoom in with the mic.
I'm going to show you how sniping should be handled.
Take a good look.
Okay, thank you.
Take out the mines.
My sniping field will be limited to the area you're watching through your PSG-1 scope.
Keep a good look out on Emma's surroundings, even while I'm shooting, alright?
Okay.
D-mic time.
Hold in first person.
Move with left analog stick.
How did all this happen?
This poor girl.
You okay?
Just step over.
What am I doing here?
Just step over them.
It's fine.
How did all this happen?
Can you take out this one?
Snake!
Take out this one!
Nice.
Any...
Any mines down there?
Take out that one.
Nice.
Good job, Snake.
There he is.
You horn dog, you.
How did all this happen?
Wait.
Nice.
Okay.
Now we can do the D-mic.
Wait, did you just kill that guy?
Oh, no.
He's still...
He's still kicking.
Here it is.
A girl?
What are you doing here?
It's not my choice, thank you very much.
You're not gonna shoot me.
No.
Why not?
Otherwise you'll get hit with diarrhea.
One of the few things I learned from Shadow Moses.
What are you talking about?
Don't worry about it.
I have no idea what you're talking about, but does this mean you're letting me go?
Well, you could have found a nicer way to say that.
Oh.
Better hurry.
Don't mention it.
Just run like hell.
Oh, God.
Oh, no.
This place is about to sink.
Just get out faster.
Johnny!
Wait!
What's your name?
Don't have one.
Okay, fine.
It's Johnny.
Hey, if we run into each other again...
What a weird guy.
Okay, now we have to be serious.
Okay, there's a lot going on around here.
Okay, let's...
Here, let's...
Take this.
I'm gonna try and...
Shoot this guy.
Snake, you can do that too.
Okay, you can do that.
Oh, my God.
Snake!
You said you would do it!
That was me.
Oh, my God.
Here, I'll take out this one.
There we go.
That was me.
Oh, that was Snake.
Snake, what are you doing?
There she goes.
Snake, you have any words?
Snake, you got any words for Emma?
Are there any claymores?
I think I got all of them.
But let's just check.
Let's check.
Oh, wait.
What's that?
That's a bird.
Yeah, we're good.
Oh, wait.
What's that?
See?
She'll make it in one piece.
She'll be totally fine.
Oh, the sun is so bright.
Snake, you got any words?
Not bad at all.
What do you mean by that?
Phew.
Snake!
We both can't aim.
Snake, our aim is both bad.
Wish they'd give me more medicine.
Oh, you got it.
You're good.
You got it.
Phew.
Alright.
We got this.
Just a little more.
Not bad.
He was talking about me.
Snake.
I'm so sorry to tell you this.
I'm so sorry to tell you this, but...
Alright.
Yay!
We did it!
Doesn't he have a really gross line about...
He does.
He has like a line where he's just like...
I'd date her or something.
Oh my god!
No!
Oh my god.
Please!
No!
Why are you back?
Vamp!
Don't shake.
Just shoot!
You have him!
You have him in your crosshair!
Shoot!
Yay!
Vamp!
Send no one ever.
Wait.
Hold on!
She's like...
She's like joking.
I'm like...
Hold on!
One second!
I can't!
Oh, did I hit...
Oh my god.
Please, controller.
Bye forever, Vamp!
Never wanna see your ass again.
Please.
Emma, you good, girl?
You okay?
No!
No, Emma, Emma, Emma!
Emma!
It wasn't me!
I didn't shoot her.
I didn't...
No, I didn't shoot her.
Where was this aim?
Where was this aim before?
No, I didn't shoot her!
No, it wasn't me!
Oh god, oh god, oh god, oh god, oh god.
Bandage!
Bandage, bandage!
It'll fix everything!
Stop the bleeding!
Pressure!
Something!
Don't pull out the bullet!
That I didn't shoot.
Raiden, you wanna get over there or something?
Raiden, you wanna make your way that direction?
Raiden, you wanna...
Let's just codec the situation.
Raiden, Emma's been stabbed.
Stabbed!
Bastard!
How bad is it?
She's conscious.
But the bleeding's bad.
I'm bringing her over there right now.
Raiden, get that disc over here as soon as possible.
Going to survival dealer.
I'm afraid her time's running out.
I'll be there.
These other guys can take missiles to the face.
But...
But one little stab stabby stab and that's it for her.
What's up with that?
Being stabbed hurts.
That hurts.
Emma took like 10 bullets.
I know!
Oh gosh, oh gosh, oh gosh.
Oh wait, isn't there a timer?
Wait.
Oh shoot, I forgot about this part.
Snake, what's your situation over there?
Emma seems to be doing something to G.W.'s defensive capabilities.
All we need now is your disc.
Okay, I'm on my way.
You better hurry.
I don't think she's gonna make it.
How's the bleeding?
But there's like guys I have to worry about too, isn't there?
Oh shoot.
Completely forgot.
Oh wait, actually?
Understood.
Oh, the coast is clear?
Wait, uh...
Snake, I see someone moving.
The coast does not appear to be clear.
I repeat!
I repeat, the coast does not appear to be clear!
Oh, it's this guy.
He's listening to his music.
Timer.
My bad, sorry.
Where am I going?
Snake, where am I going?
Sorry.
Raiden, we're in the computing room on B2 of Shell 1's core.
Emma's not doing so well.
Get over here as soon as you can.
I'm talking to this beautiful girl from Korea.
I think we might be sold.
B2 of Shell 1.
Now we're...
We're...
Wait.
Oh.
B...
Oh!
Oh no!
Wait.
Huh.
Which is... This is F.
Where's B?
Oh, B2 of Shell 1!
Okay, B2 of Shell 1.
Okay, sorry.
My bad.
Okay, B2 of Shell 1.
Hold on.
I think this guy is right here.
We have to wait for him to leave.
Okay.
He's jamming out!
Sorry.
Sorry, man.
Okay.
It's this way, right?
Oh my goodness.
Raiden!
Can you not get caught on everything?
I'll send you an invite to our wedding.
Okay, I'm looking forward to it.
Alright, bye.
Bye-bye!
Wrong way?
Arsenal's launch has initiated a security lockout.
Otakons managed to override anything that leads to the computing room.
This is no time to get sidetracked.
Hurry!
Sorry.
Wait.
Nice.
Box number five!
Hahaha.
Is it this way?
Okay.
I've never seen that code before.
Because I'm stupid.
Oh my god, please.
Oh, I had it, but the controller pressure.
There we go.
Oh my god.
Got it.
Um...
Anything else that I should be worried about?
Oh shoot, I have to go back through this thing.
Uh...
Hut!
La-la-la-la-la.
Level two grip strength!
La-la-la-la-la-la.
La-la-la-la-la.
The coast has never been clearer.
Hahaha.
B2, we gotta go see our little bird.
I don't know why.
I think if he had said...
He did say the computer room, right?
My brain is just a little silly.
I was like, where is that?
Okay.
Alright.
And it's clear in here, right?
Oh
my god, my eyes.
My eyes.
Ugh, my eyes.
Get it together, Raiden.
How could you not have seen those?
Can you imagine if it did the whole cutscene with the thermal goggles on?
Oh no.
Punished for getting sidetracked.
This game is such a troll.
Gosh, Raiden, your hips are whack in this game.
How's Emma?
I think he got some internal organs.
We can't stop the bleeding.
How?
I'm here.
Got the disc.
He's trying to be quiet.
To, like, be respectful.
Emma set everything up.
Apparently all you have to do is pop in the disc.
Otacon, stop loving women.
Okay.
Ugh.
That should insert the virus into the AI.
Is it working?
Just leave it to Emma.
Uh oh.
An antibody agent?
Wow, this is...
Damn.
The connection's been cut.
Is the virus upload complete?
I don't think so.
The count stopped at 90%.
Otacon.
I don't think Emma's made any mistakes.
But a portion of the worm cluster might have been altered after the disc left Emma.
Uh oh.
By the Patriots?
Will the virus still work?
I have no idea.
Shadow clone.
Hal, is...
Is everything alright?
Snake is so sweet.
Everything's alright.
Good.
At least I...
I won't be adding another page to our family's dark history.
Yeah, that's right.
What if the virus doesn't work?
I either destroy that thing or take out Solidus and his men.
How do we get on board?
Don't be so loud, Ryland.
I don't think we can.
Unless somebody inside gives us a hand.
Mmm.
The bird.
Hal...
I...
I always...
What is it?
Hated your glasses.
Wanted to see you again.
Oh.
Music bit.
There we go.
You don't hate me?
Never.
I never wanted to get in your way.
I never wanted to hurt you.
That was Arsenal.
If I followed in your footsteps, I could be closer.
I just wanted you to look at me.
Look at me as...
As?
As a woman.
I could never do that.
Don't be so honest.
Please.
Sorry.
Can I...
Can I ask you one last favor?
Sure.
Oh god.
Call me Emma.
What?
Please call me Emma.
Why is that such a weird request, Hal?
Otacon, please.
Oh god.
I'm already in pain.
What's wrong with E.E.?
Otacon,
you!
Emma?
Oh god.
Answer me.
Bruh.
Oh god.
It's just so painful.
He
doesn't like to...
Otacon cries.
Every woman in this game series must suffer because of Otacon.
Oh god.
I didn't...
I didn't leave you.
Because of the accident.
I had...
I had a relationship with your mother.
Ugh.
She seduced me.
What's wrong with the dying girl?
My father's death was no accident.
Good.
He took his own life.
Coward.
It was my fault.
All my fault.
No.
Forgive me, Emma.
The world doesn't need Huey.
The world doesn't need your father.
Father's a...
Poopy dookie hen.
Oh god.
Ahhhh.
Not the bird.
It's the bird that makes me cry.
Love me some Huey hate.
Oh yeah, baby.
Oh, the bird.
Oh.
Howl.
I miss you.
Attention.
Arsenal gear is ready for launch.
Inoculate the upper levels immediately.
Sounds like they're cutting this area loose.
What do you mean?
It means we're gonna sink.
We have to get the hostages out.
What about the Kama repairs?
Done.
We won't be able to get everybody aboard.
We'll just have to take as many as we can.
My sister...
...
...Won't be able to come with us.
I'll save you.
We will be commencing the countdown shortly.
Personnel in the upper levels, head for the evacuation area immediately.
That sound?
I know it's a wolf but it gets me everytime.
I am always the survivor.
God, oh da god.
Why, Wolf?
Ya...
...
..
Oh my god.
Make me cry every time.
Wait.
It's okay.
We've got hours.
You mean, I'd only get in your way?
No.
Wrong.
Only you can save those hostages.
You got it?
Right.
Listen, the two of you won't be able to destroy that thing.
Eliminate the enemy.
That's your only option.
Yeah!
Boys!
Oh my god.
As long as that bird stays quiet, we are good.
He needs support, Snake.
He needs...
Leave it to me.
He needs support.
Yeah!
No!
Get
out of here.
Oh my god.
Ow.
I miss you.
The bird is a paid actor.
You said other things.
You said other things earlier.
I heard them.
This bird is so goofy.
It's so sad and so goofy.
He's like, I'm out of here.
You and me.
We're the same.
Gosh.
I'm getting emotional whiplash here.
Both you and I.
We were always alone.
That is Otacon.
He's a simp.
Really appreciate how much Snake cares for Otacon.
He does.
Snake's a really good person.
Waiting for somebody.
Somebody who would love us.
But we were wrong.
You can't wait to be loved.
You have to go out and find it.
Go out and find it.
Four years ago, I realized that you can't just wish for a happy family.
You have to make it happen.
Now you have one.
I only wish I knew that sooner.
Now you have a happy family.
I learned that I could love.
As you probably did.
Emotional damage break.
I'm loving your playthrough of the MGS franchise.
Only one I've never played it.
Is Floor.
You think he's gonna be okay?
You can watch us play Floor then.
He's tougher than he looks.
Consider it done.
Our shows are so entertaining.
Now, how do we open this thing?
You can come out now.
Oh my god!
Ninja!
A ninja?
Oh my god!
No!
Snake, what's this all about?
Time to go night-night.
Bedtime riding.
How do you do that?
Nighty-night riding.
You're changing sides now?
Change sides?
I don't recall saying I was on yours.
Damn it.
Snake!
Who's the ninja?
Gray Fox!
Sea Woman!
Oh god girl!
Look over here!
Oh
god!
She's been working with Snake the whole time!
Gray Fox Sea Woman.
Hmm mm!
We get quite a few cuts here and now.
If I remember correctly.
O-O-Ohhh, aaaaah!
Oh
no, Titanic Reel!!
Oh ho ho!
Good job Otacon, good job!
He did his job well!
Hmmmm mmm mmm
Jack, are you reading me?
Do you want to save your mission data up to this point?
I do.
Thank you, Rose.
But, it's... it's Raiden.
Oh, he saved Meryl, not Otacon in MGS1?
How is he alive?
Your mission data has been saved.
You know, he got out.
Is he still alive?
He was when Otacon brought him here.
This is just like MGS1!
I checked everything, including the genome data, but there's nothing on this guy.
NSA...
I'm just a guy!
FBI...
Check my bloodstream.
He doesn't exist in any database.
It's got gunpowder in it.
He's a non-existent operative from a non-existent organization.
I suspected as much.
However, I know this man.
You know me?
Wake him up.
I thought he was dead.
I thought he was going to slap me.
The parallels, I know, right?
A lot of things have been quite similar to MGS1.
It's kind of crazy.
Solid-S!
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Kisachi booty.
Jack the Ripper.
Huh?
Okay.
You know this fellow?
Fellow?
You remember me, don't you?
You've grown.
By concentration of cerebral implants.
Have they altered your memory, too?
It's time for Jack to let her rip.
Look at the eight pack he's got going on.
This is my son.
Huh?
I taught him everything.
This is my son?
Oh, my God.
The eye patch.
Solidus.
Jack.
I never thought I'd see you again.
You know me?
You don't remember.
Oh, my God.
Your name.
Your skills.
Everything you know, you learn from me.
What?
Show me.
The eighties.
A civil war.
You were one of the best among the child soldiers that fought in that conflict.
Oh, my God.
Right in the child soldier.
When you were barely ten years old, you became the platoon leader of the small boy unit.
At the time, your outstanding kill record earned you several nicknames, including White Devil and Jack the Ripper.
Whoa.
White Mamba.
Jack.
I was your godfather.
Oh, my God.
I named you.
Little baby.
When the war ended, you disappeared from the relief center.
I wondered what happened to you.
Small boy.
I should have known they would recruit you.
Dun dun dun.
It's an interesting coincidence.
If he's a lackey for the Patriots, I doubt he knows anything of interest.
What should we do with him?
Strip him down.
We'll use him like you suggested.
Oh.
What about Dead Cell?
Ignore them.
Dead Cell?
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Dead Cell's basically dead.
All that's left is Fortune.
Happening again?
Could it be that he's here, too?
Liquid.
He's already stripped down.
In another hour, we demonstrate the power of Arsenal gear.
Oh, my God.
Attack with standard weapons, of course.
Yes.
Proceed as planned.
Nice.
At last, report all is well with GW.
Hmm.
Oh, my God.
How about the troops?
Arsenal.
It looks like he's skimming something.
The men are being refitted with Arsenal gear equipment as ordered.
You're the spitting image of Big Boss.
So, Solidus was doing all this while Venom was building a zoo?
Yeah.
I guess you're right.
Well...
Is that so?
Perhaps I should be grateful to this kid for that.
I guess so.
It's funny because Solidus is...
This is the youngest sibling.
And we know how old Eli is.
This situation, I find it very nostalgic.
Where am I?
Why, inside Arsenal gear, of course.
This time, he had to take his pants off, though.
Actually, we're also inside the memory of Shadow Moses.
What?
What do you mean by that?
I'll take this back.
No.
You don't need this anymore, do you?
Dang it.
Oh, it's a lot.
Liquid.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
She'll get us out.
She doesn't want to look at her.
A foul wind is blowing.
We shall speak again.
Sorry.
It's Johnny.
Don't move.
Stay as you are.
Okay.
We're being monitored by a camera.
What are you up to?
I'm switching over to nano communication.
Okay.
Mr. X?
Ninja?
Correct.
It's me.
What?
That's supposed to be me.
I thought you were the leader of the Russian troops.
No.
That was just a smokescreen.
You said that about Olga, too?
This guy just...
I was sent to provide you support.
Support.
This guy says that about any lady.
Who sent you?
The colonel?
No.
The Patriots.
What?
I...
I deceived my troops.
Betrayed them.
Oh, my God.
But why?
My child is being held hostage by the Patriots.
Child.
It all started two years ago when I lost my father during the tank.
A tanker incident.
My men and I had nowhere to go, so we joined forces with an illegal Russian organization.
The Russian mafia?
Something like that.
Actually, I learned much later that it was a subordinate organization of the Patriots.
I was expecting at the time.
When I gave birth to my child, it turned out I was in a hospital run by the Patriots.
No.
In the morning, my child was gone.
Oh, my God.
My baby is being kept somewhere.
Somewhere in this country.
Have you ever met your child?
That's not fair.
Once a month, they send me a photo of my child via network.
I've never even held the child in my own arms.
Oh, girl.
I see.
Given your situation, nobody can blame you for what you did.
That's your opinion.
Everyone's just trauma.
Don't pick on her.
What about Snake?
I thought you were enemies.
He wasn't responsible for my father's death.
Oh.
Actually, we owe him our lives.
Two years ago, my father died.
So, they were responsible for getting us out of the sinking tanker alive.
That's me.
Oh, that did not happen.
That's from the trailer.
So, you were partners since the incident?
No.
I only found out the truth shortly before this.
Huh?
When I confronted him here.
She's dead.
You fought with Snake?
When?
Two years ago.
Well, it was around the time you were holding hands with that girl.
Oh.
Snake.
Holding hands with that girl.
Oh.
So, you joined hands with him to pay back a debt.
No.
Mutual gain.
Hmm.
My job was to assist you.
If Solidus gets away with Arsenal, your mission is a failure.
True.
The Patriots would judge that as failure on my part.
Oh.
And terminate my child.
Putting it simply, my child's life depends on your success.
Maybe.
So, you did it all for your child.
But why would the Patriots want to help me?
Maybe.
Are they hoping I'll take Solidus?
No.
You're just like me.
We're just pawns.
No.
We're not pawns.
Pawns for what purpose?
We're not pawns in the government.
Huh?
You'll figure it out sooner or later.
But I wonder if you'll handle it true.
Listen when someone's talking to you.
What do you mean?
Listen.
We haven't got time for this.
Solidus will commence his attack any minute.
I don't know if I've ever heard that one before.
He's got to be stopped.
What about the virus?
No results so far.
Make sure Olga doesn't see the picture they took.
Could change this.
I think the Patriots have tampered with the program.
Will it work?
I don't know.
Get me out of this thing.
Not yet.
That's not fair.
I'll release your restraints after I leave this room.
Hey!
Oh, okay.
Where's my gear?
Snake's got everything.
I couldn't bring it here.
Oh, my God.
And where do I find Snake?
It's chilly.
It's too cold.
Olga!
I've never heard that.
I don't think I have either.
I don't have a...
The passageway ahead leads to a hangar.
He'll be waiting there.
I still haven't gotten my favorite rose one, though.
I gave him a card key for the hangar.
It's the egotistical woman one.
Does Snake's plans destroy Arsenal gear?
No.
Even for Snake, it's impossible.
Oh, my God.
Here it comes.
Please, guys.
If there are people here who have never seen Metal Gear Solid 2 before, please, no spoil.
I still can't afford to be discovered.
Please, no spoil.
The line is, you're a real egotistical woman.
Yeah, I love that one.
Olga, you can't keep this up.
They're bound to find you.
Listen.
I'll free you in a little while.
Brace yourself.
Oh, my God.
I can't even move my head anymore.
She hit me.
Where'd she hit me at?
Hello?
Ah!
The stomach.
You can't change the camera view yet, I don't believe it.
You have to wait until after your first release.
I know.
No.
Oh my god.
You're really selfish, you know.
No.
Gun powder!
Yippee!
AK.
Jack.
You were like... you were like ten years old!
You didn't ask how many to kill.
If you didn't, you were the one they shot instead.
It's okay.
No one is blaming you.
I'm blaming you.
We were shown Hollywood action films every day.
The kind with macho guys and big guns.
They call it image training.
That's crazy.
He had to watch movies.
They built us from the ground up into killing machines.
We were fed once a day.
I can still taste the gun powder they mixed into the food.
Gun powder?
In the food?
Yeah!
Gun powder!
Our mother had to Halloween it, giving it hallucinogenic properties.
Woo!
It kept us drugged.
Controllable.
Oh my god.
That is so awful.
Rose's reaction there is like the most believable thing.
When the Civil War ended, those of us who survived were taken in by NGOs.
His cheeks are the bomb.
That gave me a new life in the States.
I can't complain.
But nothing's changed.
The only people who have no problem with my past have secrets and agendas of their own.
Terrible nightmares.
Every night.
I can never forget.
Jack.
I'm afraid of the night.
That's why I don't sleep next to you.
You should have told me.
Told you what?
That I'm a killer?
And always have been?
No.
What I hate more than anything else in the world is my own past.
I didn't want you or anyone to know about it.
Oh, God.
Now I know why I was chosen for this mission.
No one can take him on, take him down, except me.
I've been kept alive this long for this.
I knew as soon as I saw Solidus.
Jack, I love you the way you are now.
You have to believe me.
I didn't know anything about you, I admit that.
So dramatic.
Where you were born, how you grew up.
Pass the popcorn, please.
But I know that now.
And I know that what I feel for you can only get better.
And I'll share in your past if that's the price.
It doesn't work that way.
No one can share the burden of what I've done.
It's not one of those warm and fuzzy things couples share.
No.
I accept the good and the bad, Jack.
That's what you do for someone.
Someone you love.
I don't want to share my past with anyone.
I just want to forget about it.
Jack, I haven't told you, you know, about what I've done.
Uh oh, she got secrets.
The last two years with you, it's been more than I've ever hoped for.
Jack, Jack, oh Jack.
But I can't go any farther.
I'm breaking up with you.
I know you want to get married.
Oh, I...
But I can't.
Imagine getting broken up over Kodak.
I can't risk starting a family.
There's no way to erase my childhood.
It's all right, Jack.
Please, don't say any more.
We're free.
Took her long enough.
Gosh, oh my god.
Get back in.
Oh.
Thank you, thank you.
Bye.
So this is the cosplayer you saw at MGS con.
Minus the towel.
Yeah, exactly.
Light.
Wow.
Oh my.
Oh god.
Oh my god.
I really swear you could see it.
I swear you could see something when he lays down.
Oh my god.
Thank goodness.
We don't want to catch a cold now.
Beep, beep.
Which way does this go anyway?
It doesn't even have a number.
Double-cheeked on a Sunday afternoon.
Hallelujah.
Oh.
Oh my god.
A little...
Pause midflip.
Oh.
That was actually...
That was actually pretty good.
I remember this scene like it was yesterday.
Truly touching.
He's a Ken doll.
He's just a Ken doll.
There's nothing there.
Oh, god.
Here we go.
Colonel.
I'm naked.
I'm naked and cold and the clap of my glutes is alerting the guards!
I'm gonna need to get food soonish.
I'm starting to get hungry.
I'm naked.
I'm naked!
Rendezvous with that man.
Not while I'm naked, please!
Not while I'm naked!
Don't say it like that!
Jack, I guess you need to save.
I guess so.
Try getting an alert and going back?
I'm pretty sure I have.
Why is my clock keep changing between 2099 and 2000?
Hang in there.
Thanks!
Time to rendezvous with that man!
Oh gosh, this part you actually have to be sneaky.
What was the best way to go?
I think I remember.
Okay.
It's time.
Raiden, do you copy?
You must continue your mission.
I've lost all my gear.
I need to locate Snake.
He was never factored into the simulation.
Leave him out of this.
I can't do much naked.
Especially in this temperature.
That's cold!
That's true.
You won't be able to attack or enter the hanging mode either.
I think Snake has my gear.
Raiden, take out Solidus and his men.
You must recover Arsenal intact.
Colonel, are you under orders from the Patriots?
Your role, that is mission, is to infiltrate the structure and disarm the terrorists.
My role?
Why do you keep saying that?
Why not?
This is a type of role-playing game.
The point is that you play out your part.
And I expect you to turn in a perfect performance.
Colonel, I just remembered something.
What?
That I've never met you in person.
Not once.
Complete your mission according to the simulation.
Colonel, who are you?
What's a simulation?
No more questions.
We have Rosemary.
What?
What do you mean by that?
Over and out.
Raiden, out.
I like this area because...
All the little rays.
You can see them here.
The music here is so crazy.
Oh my gosh, you can see my breath.
The floor is so cool too.
Everything about this part is so cool.
Raiden, turn the game console off right now.
What did you say?
The mission is a failure.
Cut the power right now.
What's wrong with you?
Don't worry.
It's a game.
It's a game just like usual.
Great timing.
You'll ruin your eyes playing so close to the TV.
What?
What are you talking about?
Raiden, something happened to me last Thursday when I was driving home.
You make no sense.
I love this.
I had a couple of miles to go.
I looked up and saw a glowing orange object in the sky to the east.
It was moving very irregularly.
Suddenly, there was intense light all around me.
And when I came to, I was home.
What do you think happened to me?
Aliens.
Fine.
Forget it.
Oh, my God.
I love this so much.
Boo.
Destroy the final weapon.
Metal Gear.
Coachella.
Big Bus.
No.
Oh, my God.
Wait.
I can't...
Yeah.
He's right there.
Oh, gosh.
How do I get past this guy?
Hold on.
I'm waiting for him to leave.
I think they're my...
Oh, my God.
Sorry.
I took too long.
Honestly, though, you have played the game for a long time.
I have.
Don't you have anything else to do with your time out?
Rude.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
There's a box over here, actually, though.
Isn't there?
Yeah.
Nice.
Okay.
I remembered.
Yeah.
We finally got our zone in the Ender Box.
Hooray.
Okay.
We just wait for this guy to go past.
Oh.
Ah.
Can I...
Not right now.
Oh, my gosh.
I can't.
I can't hang.
Oh.
Shoot.
What's that?
Nothing.
Actually, there is something I have been meaning to tell you, but I just couldn't.
What's that supposed to mean?
I think you should know, though.
What's that?
On Saturday morning last week, I saw a guy leaving Rosemary's room.
How should I put it?
It was like they were intimate.
I'm sorry.
What's that supposed to mean?
Sorry to bring this up during the mission, but...
Yeah.
Hmm.
Just...
Exactly.
I can't...
Oh, wait.
I think I can go right here.
Oh, no!
Just a box.
Oh, shit.
Um...
Just a box.
I thought I was close enough to the edge.
Hmm.
No doubt.
Oh, shit.
Uh...
I lost my box.
And, um...
I lost everything.
Everybody?
I lost it.
This is it.
This is over.
It's over for me.
I don't remember how to get to the stairs now.
There's even cameras.
It's so over.
Can I go underneath here?
Hmm?
Who's there?
Nobody!
Where's the stairs?
Even my patience has its limits.
I just can't leave this thing up to you any longer.
I'll do the fighting.
You can just go home.
Okay.
Okay!
Sounds good to me, man!
You go ahead!
You do the fighting.
You do the cooking.
You do
the...
Who's there?
Hmm.
Exactly.
No one.
Oh, shoot.
Oh, shit.
Oh, I'm so... This is it.
This is it.
It's over for me!
I don't have a box!
An anemone or clematis plant's juice can cause a rash.
When prune them, it's a good idea to wear gloves.
Oh, shoot!
Bye!
Variety level 13.
The giant!
Granola!
G -Ginola!
The giant genome soldiers.
Look at them.
We are missions!
Yeah?
Granola.
I hear it's amazing when the famous purple stuffed worm in Flapjaw's space with the tuning fork does a raw blink on Harry Caray Rock.
I need scissors.
61.
When I met Paul Eiding, he wrote that on my...
He wrote that on my thing without me even asking.
I was so excited.
On my poster that I had him sign.
President Baker should be somewhere to the south of where you blasted through the wall.
There's some idle Easter eggs with these calls.
Oh, that's right!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I do remember.
I had to run an errand and just got back.
Oh, there she is!
I think I missed something.
Um...
I need scissors.
61.
I was a North American fall webworm in my past life.
Webworm.
That's what I do.
Oh, those were the good old days.
I webworm on the internet.
I'm a webworm.
Oh yeah, let's stay still.
Let's see if we get the codec again.
Your mission is to infiltrate the Fortress Gallowade, rescue the hostages, and neutralize Metal Gear before its assembly is complete.
This part is so isome.
This part is so isome, man.
You got a PSG-1?
You can use that against Sniper Wolf.
Sniper Wolf?
Hurry up and save Meryl.
What's going on?
Oh my god, it's so creepy crazy!
Actually, I'm...
I'm in really bad shape financially.
I pay money to my ex-wife as part of our divorce settlement, among other bills.
I just had no choice but to make you pay for lunch the other day.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay, Colonel.
It's okay.
Who programmed that?
Who put that into the system?
Honestly, though, you have played the game for a long time.
We got this one.
Don't you have anything else to do with your time?
No.
Your mission is to infiltrate the fortress Galuwade, rescue the hostages, and neutralize Metal Gear before its assembly is complete.
I think we've gotten all of them now, right?
Oh, I missed it.
Oh!
Even my patience has its limits.
Are you a real lalilulelo?
Yeah!
I'll do the fighting.
You can just go home.
I'm in really bad shape financially.
I keep super chatting VTubers playing Metal Gear.
It's okay.
I like this one.
Okay, I think we got all of them.
So awesome.
Okay.
We can start ignoring the Colonel now.
Beep beep.
Hello?
Colonel?
Oh!
Mayling!
Snake.
Remember what the Gaul said.
No!
She's so...
The graveyards are full of indispensable men.
Mayling!
Snake!
She's so cute!
You're all alone and surrounded by bad guys.
Try to be careful and avoid getting into a fight whenever you can.
I actually don't remember when he comes here.
Jack, it's me.
Oh!
Hi, Rose.
Rose!
Jack, I owe you an apology.
If it's about that conversation just now...
The airplane arms?
I know.
I'm the one who's sorry.
She's so cute.
No, it's something else.
What is it?
That day at Federal Hall two years ago...
Here it is.
It wasn't a coincidence.
I was ordered to keep an eye on you.
Keep an eye on me?
Yes.
By the Patriots.
You're a spy?
I suppose.
Yes.
It's an ugly word.
Are you still there?
Unfortunately.
Was sleeping with me a part of the job?
I fell in love with you.
How could anyone?
I can't excuse what I did.
I've reported every detail of your personal life to them these two years.
What you did, said, everything.
Must have been fun.
But some things I didn't tell anyone.
Like what I felt for you.
So that's why you were involved in this mission.
I should have known.
Why else would they toss an analyst into the mix at the last minute?
I'm sorry.
I know what I did was wrong.
I feel like I'm playing with dolls.
No matter where I go, I get used.
I reinvented myself to suit your tastes.
Hairstyle, clothes, the way I move, things I talked about.
You say you love the color of my hair, my eyes.
They're not even real.
You must have gone over my psych profile with a fine-tooth comb.
How do you change your eyes?
It was my job.
Great performance.
Had me completely fooled.
What I really wanted was for you to see the real me.
It hurt to play out this... this artificial romance.
It was worse to lie to myself than to you.
The more love you gave me, the more it hurt.
Because I knew the person you loved was just a character.
So it was artificial on my end, too.
It was just a game, not the real thing.
Oh, Jack.
I feel better knowing that.
What?
I was in love, or thought I was.
With someone who didn't exist.
I was trying to be someone I wasn't by loving what wasn't real.
I don't know who you really are.
The person I knew isn't real.
She's not the woman I'm talking to right now.
In a sense, the deception was my own, not theirs.
Jack, I thought I was acting because that was my job.
I thought I was acting.
But I did fall in love with you.
That wasn't an act.
I mean, you were acting.
You expect me to believe that?
You saw it.
You were acting.
That's okay.
You had your reasons, right?
Hey, I understand.
But I have nothing left to...
Jack.
What?
I'm...
I'm carrying...
I'm pregnant, Jack.
Rose!
My baby!
What's going on?
She's not a baby!
She's pregnant!
Oh, my God.
Amazing how you walk around like that.
Snake!
I've been waiting long.
He's so cool!
I love him!
Poor...
Where's my gear?
Right over there.
There he is.
Yeah!
That's more like it.
Everything you had when you were captured is still there.
Nice.
Oh.
Nano.
Ass shot.
They can't just do that, you know?
Brian coming to terms with his parasocial will.
Sorry about earlier.
I had to use you as bait to gain access to Arsenal.
It worked.
What?
Why didn't you tell me about Olga?
You never asked.
You didn't ask?
Not happy about that?
Get over it.
Any effects of the virus yet?
Still waiting on that.
Oh, my God.
Look at his bedding.
Look at his ear.
So, it was rigged by the Patriots?
Look at his nose.
His mouth.
Looks like it.
From what I can tell, Arsenal is headed for Manhattan.
No.
I don't know what Solidus is planning, but we'll have to deal with it one way or another.
Right.
There's also a troupe of production model Rays ahead.
How many units?
Twenty-five, according to Olga.
Hey, come on.
Twenty-five?
Yeah.
Can't say I've faced that many Metal Gears before.
But I think we can deal.
No way we can.
You're gonna be the one...
You're the one who's gonna be facing it, right?
Because we have no other choice.
Right, Snake?
You're the one who's gonna be facing them.
How?
I've stocked up on Stinger missiles.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
Olga left this for you.
Funny-er the twenty-er.
Funny-er the twenty-four.
Twenty-five.
What's the...
Oh.
Thanks, Olga.
Thanks.
Why?
Olga asked me to give it to you.
Besides, I'm not a big fan of blades.
Ask about the bandana, Ryden.
Ask about the bandana.
Jack is back, baby!
Move the right analog stick up and down to make a vertical slice, and left and right to slice parallel to the ground.
Move the stick in a circle to do a rotating cut.
Push it forward to lunge and strike.
You can guard with your blade if you have the L1 button pressed down.
You should be able to deflect a bullet or two.
Okay, hook!
Up, down, up, down, up!
He's gonna stand there or...
Oops, sorry, stay.
God, don't be so dramatic about it.
He watched anime, yeah.
No, no, no, hold on!
Don't turn and look at me, please!
I'm embarrassed.
Okay.
And then when I run, too...
Can I deflect bullets when I run, or is that...
Kill snake!
Oh my goodness.
Okay.
Oh, uh, wait.
It was, uh...
Oh, that's the jab.
Jab, jab, jab.
Wow, thank you!
This was the day Saucy Binto was born.
Thank you, Ilfried, thank you!
Also, Yanwei, thank you.
Rose acts weird and needy and possessive.
Rose is also trying to play the role of Jack's ideal girl.
I guess he's into deeply problematic women.
I guess so.
Oh, sorry.
Just wanna...
Oh my god.
Whoa, he's breathing in my...
We're so close, I can...
He's fogging up my glasses!
No way!
Wowee.
You look so cool, snake.
I love the floor in this area.
So awesome.
Oh, I guess that's it.
Hi!
You weeb.
Oh, that's...
Infinite ammo.
Wait up, snake.
I swore I'd thank you for the tech gift, dude.
I love that.
I love that line so much.
Infinite ammo.
Snake, have you ever enjoyed killing someone?
What are you talking about?
I'm not sure.
Me too.
Sometimes it's hard to tell the difference between reality and a game.
Diminished sense of reality, huh?
VR training will do that.
Do you guys mind if I get food before we continue?
No.
It was field training when I was a kid.
I lied, snake.
We only have a little bit left of the game.
I have more field experience than I can remember.
It's not VR that's doing this to me.
Raiden, we don't carry guns to take people down.
We're not here to help some politician either.
You can say that because you're a legend.
A hero.
I'm Jack the Ripper.
A dirty reminder of a terrible mistake.
Jack is back.
Legends don't mean a whole lot.
I was just a name to exploit.
Just like you.
People will remember only the good part.
The right part of what you've done.
Jack is back.
There's no right part in murder.
Not ever.
And we're not in this to make a name for ourselves.
And what are you and Otacon fighting for?
A future.
You can stop being part of a mistake.
Starting now.
Sorry, serious conversation.
What am I?
What am I supposed to do?
Just change.
Just be a better guy.
Have some of your ammo.
Find something to believe in.
And find it for yourself.
And when you do, pass it on to the future.
Believe in what?
The future.
That's your problem.
Come on.
Oh gosh.
They're gonna put us mid-fight, aren't they?
I'm just gonna have to pause it and go get food.
Oh.
Maybe?
Snake.
Riding.
Otacon.
You all right?
Yeah.
So we're all the hostages.
That's good news.
Yippee.
How's everything on your end?
All right for now.
But there is something.
It's quiet.
What?
The colonel's last transmission.
Oh.
It was strange.
Uh, transmissions.
How?
I don't know.
Just strange.
No idea.
Interference?
I don't know.
Find a new VTuber.
Where is this colonel?
I don't know.
I've never met the man, actually.
I'll dig around.
Thanks.
I owe you one.
Yeah.
If there's anything else, call me on the codec.
I might be able to help.
The frequency is 141.12.
141.12.
Potatoes ready on my desk.
Uh-oh.
Uh -oh.
Oh no.
I should become a ninja cyborg.
Um.
Yeah.
About that.
I'm gonna go get food real quick.
I'll be...
You guys can listen to this.
I'll turn it down a little bit.
I have some food ready.
So I'm just gonna grab a plate and I'm gonna...
Oh.
I have some food ready.
Eat for a second.
A little snack time for a second.
Sorry, I'm starting to get really hungry.
And I don't want to do the fights while I'm on an empty stomach.
And I gotta get some more water.
So I'll be right back.
I'll be right back.
Thanks guys!
We are back!
Your mission is to destroy the shagohan, eat some tasty animals like the purple stuffed worm.
Variety level 16.
Tasty!
Thanks, Colonel!
Oh, I want to fly.
Okay, here we go.
Sorry for the wait.
So sorry.
I'm back.
I'm back, I'm back, I'm back.
Bye bye spaghetti!
I'm gonna turn down the music just a little bit so we're not eating in battle music and stuff.
Yay, you were the gifted!
That's one, thank you!
I'm starting to get so hungry though.
Glad.
Good spot to... maybe not the best spot, but...
A decent... well, we only have this area?
We don't have so much left, honestly.
Just a few more battle sequences and...
That's it?
You deserve it, thank you!
Yeah!
Yeah, I think we'll be able to...
I think we'll be able to...
finish today... tonight.
Yeah, then movie time.
So true.
Though I'm worried about the Metal Gear fight.
Little worried about Metal Gear fight.
But I'll do my... my minto best.
Few more big fights and about an hour of Brain Rock cutscene.
Spaghet!
Wish I could eat this while they were doing the cutscene.
But, you know...
That's fine.
We're on normal difficulty.
So...
I don't exactly remember how many.
Minto best?
Yeah, she is.
I think it's a...
Mmm...
I think it was eight, right?
I thought it was eight.
Seven or eight, yeah.
I think it's eight of them.
So, for anybody curious...
Remember how they mentioned the 25 Metal Gears?
Well...
In the harder difficulties, you'd have to fight all 25.
But...
And I believe Kojima probably wanted that to be the case across the board.
But in the lesser ones, it's only...
It's only...
Uh...
Um...
It's only...
Uh...
Eight, I believe.
Mmm...
But the timing for it is pretty difficult for me.
So...
You do it on hard?
No!
Golly, no!
No, no, no.
You picked up the body armor.
I did!
I did get the body armor.
You're right.
And that's huge for that fight.
Leg then face.
Your reflexes have gotten so much better for this game.
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you!
We've been powering through.
Oh, it's only six?
No Pequod to help you.
I miss that guy so much.
Metal Gear Solid V, I wait for you.
Just for Pequod.
Do you ever wonder if Raiden was given BB cells?
Like the Genome Soldiers that Liquid talked about.
I don't think he was though.
Because their whole thing was...
Trying to raise a soldier like Big Boss?
Without it being him.
Like...
They wanted to see if...
If a person raised on a battlefield would turn out like Big Boss.
Is that spoilers?
We already know that he was raised as a child soldier.
A child soldier...
Exp boost-the-children.
My new kitten likes watching your streams.
Ignore the blue super- No, I won't ignore.
But..
yeah.
Install mods for MGS5.
No!
I plan on it, actually.
I'll be playing on the PC this time.
But I think.
Okay.
Don't judge me for some of these.
I don't know.
Because I've played through the game before, I might install some quality of life things.
Maybe like the ones where you don't have to wait for items to be developed and also...
Like the one where if you grab a soldier, he's already S++ tier.
Just stuff like that.
It's not cheating.
I already beat the game.
But also, if you guys have any interesting mods...
Remove the grind.
Yeah, that's basically...
The biggest issue with it, you know?
Like the gotcha.
Yeah, but don't you need... The only thing is to unlock certain things, you need a certain level, don't you?
With the soldiers, so it's kind of like...
Oh, well, to unlock...
I just need an S soldier.
A lot of deeply unserious mods.
Oh my god.
I want those.
Oh yeah, the music tape!
I wonder what song we should put as our... as P-Quad.
Sorry, I'm almost done with my food.
Oh yes, the mod that... Wait.
Yes, I've seen... I know about the mod that replaces D-Dog with Ocelot.
Or was it Khaj?
Get the mod that replaces D-Dog with Ocelot.
I've never seen it, so don't like tag me in it or anything, but I've heard about it.
People have told me to get it.
They were like, you should have that one.
I don't even know what Metal Gear is?
I hope you're enjoying the stream.
Um...
Planning on streaming the other MGS?
Yeah!
Between some games, I might take a break.
Just so I can tackle some other game series that I want to do.
Like maybe after 3 or 4?
Might take a small break.
Maybe after 4.
Because that kind of completes the timeline.
I think after 3, I'll immediately want to go into 4.
So probably after 4 is when I'll take a break.
No, my...
My breadstick got kind of hard.
Sorry Raiden, I must be in peak spaghetti condition.
Mint.
That's me!
Mentally.
Play Metal Gear Rising again?
Of course!
That's the one I have to play the most.
Because...
Now I'll understand it.
For context, I played Metal Gear Rising first.
And uh...
I was like, what's going on?
Who are these people?
Now, I'll understand who these people are.
Kind of.
Mostly.
Most of them.
Some of them.
Not very many...
Not very many people that are reoccurring from the original series.
Oh my god, you guys.
I got to hear Rules of Nature live at MGSCon.
And Sam's Theme.
What's it called?
Oh gosh, I can't remember.
I just remembered.
There will be blood!
Blood!
Shed!
It was so awesome!
I was headbanging.
I was like...
It was so awesome.
The only thing I know for real.
Yeah!
Okay.
I'm so sorry, you guys.
I'm so sorry.
I'm taking a long time to eat.
Jason Charles Miller looks like a video game character.
He looks so awesome.
He looks like my uncle.
When my uncle was in a biker game.
They made us watch VTubers.
The kinds with maids and karaoke.
I still remember the taste of mint they mixed into the food.
Yes.
Okay.
Nom nom.
It's cute hearing the plate and the stuff talking.
Stop!
Oh gosh.
My desk is covered in postcards.
So I don't have a place to put my plate.
I don't think a cat followed me in.
So I'm just going to put it on the ground.
Okay.
Memories broken.
The truth goes unspoken.
I can't even remember.
I can't even remember my game.
Okay.
She lives like this.
I have so many postcards.
So many.
I have like...
Almost 5,000 postcards to sign.
And then I have the last months or the...
Like I've ordered almost all of them.
Except one month.
So...
Is that for one month?
No, no, no.
That's for five months.
Well, it would have been less.
It would have been just 4,000.
But Matara and I...
This is for the podcast Patreon, by the way.
For anyone wondering.
One of the tiers is we send an autographed...
A hand signed postcard.
And...
Is this the original PS2 version?
Yes.
This is the original PS2 version.
Okay.
So...
We have been really bad about sending them out.
Because it's hard for us to meet up and sign them.
So...
I've been signing some.
And then I'm gonna give them to Matara at Otakutan.
And then I'm gonna...
Sign some more.
And bring them with me to Japan.
And then...
Probably mail her the rest of them.
But...
I'm...
What was I saying?
Oh, yeah.
We decided...
The first batch of postcards...
Of course they got sent.
And they were like...
Had this horrible mark on it.
This...
Scuff mark on it.
So we decided that we wanted to...
Reprint them and re...
Or...
Resend them out.
So...
So that's why it ended up being...
Another like...
A thousand of...
Of them.
Too scared to say...
Skin marks.
Aye!
Yeah.
Okay.
Are we ready?
L1 block.
R...
R3...
Stabby stab.
Circle...
Circle stab.
Left left.
Left right.
Sideway stab.
Up down.
Uppy stab.
Okay.
Colonel!
Training will have to be postponed if we are invaded by UFOs.
He's still freaky.
What if we call Otacon and now we have his thing?
There's a door at the north end of that corridor.
Okay.
Solidus should be somewhere on the other side.
Stay with Snake and keep north.
Okay.
Alright, Snake.
Are you here, Snake?
This guy and his UFOs.
There's a door at the north end of this corridor.
Yeah.
The enemy is on the other side.
We'll rush it.
Okay.
Here we go.
Block.
I'm blocked.
Oh, wait.
My gun.
Not gun.
We're blade time.
Blade mode.
Oh, shoot.
Stop.
Oh, sorry.
Oh my gosh.
Wait.
My Russians.
Oh my gosh.
Hi.
Thanks, Snake.
Run
like this then?
Okay.
So I do have to run like that.
I thought it was just running normal.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm okay.
I'm okay.
Oh my God.
All the blood.
Oh, Snake.
Watch out.
Watch out, Snake.
Oh my God.
I'm going.
I got this.
This is the end.
Is there any more...
Oh.
Good job, Snake.
I'm just going to regain my life real quick.
Are you okay, Snake?
Okay.
I'm coming.
I'm coming, Snake.
Don't push yourself.
Stop
me.
Stop.
God.
This is so...
Ah.
Oh.
Okay.
Good job.
There's an invisible wall.
Is there anything?
Oh, wait.
We can see them here.
Metal gear.
Look at them.
Look at all the Metal Gear Rays.
Metal Gear Rays.
So much blood.
It's not my blood though.
Look at them.
Ah.
Little baby.
Oh my God.
Metal Gear Ray, Metal Gear Ray, Metal Gear Ray.
All right, let's do it all over again.
Snake, do you have any rations or... Otacon, you got any more rations?
Anybody?
Otacon, do your job.
There's a door at the north end of that corridor.
Yeah.
Solidus should be...
Okay, I already did that, okay.
Oh, oh, oh, I didn't mean to call him again, my bad.
There's a... Okay, there we go.
Okay.
Hello?
Oh.
Where?
Here?
The music's so creepy.
Huh?
Check his fingers!
How many fingers does he have?
He has eleven.
He's starting to affect GW, which will explain the Colonel's behavior.
Wow.
It was all an illusion?
Everything I've done so far?
Oh, Brydon.
Ryden, Snake, what's happening around here?
He sounds like he's gonna cry.
I don't know.
What I do know is that you're standing right here in front of me.
Not an illusion.
Flesh and blood.
Oh, Brydon.
It's your call.
You can drop this if you want.
No, I can't do that.
Let's go.
Be strong, be strong.
See if the hair blends into his shirt collar.
Yeah, yeah.
We're in the colon.
Hello?
Brydon, they've got Rose.
What?
Rose is being held in the holds.
It's a trap.
Help!
Rose!
Why are you still believing him?
But Snake, it's a trap.
Since the Colonel doesn't exist, there's no way he can take Rose hostage.
Yeah, you're right.
I am right.
Okay.
Does Rose exist?
Don't be weird.
What if I've never really met her?
What?
If the Colonel is something that I partly dreamt up, then everything I remember about her could be...
Don't jump to conclusions.
Wouldn't it be a crazy twist if Snake and Otacon were the real gaslighters?
Is this what Olga was talking about?
Nice.
Don't watch where you're pointing that thing.
Here we go.
Oh.
Oh, wait.
I just remembered something.
Here we go.
Dropping like monkeys.
Maybe I... You know what?
I'm just gonna... I don't know why I'm using my gun.
Oh my gosh.
I saw this in the...
I'm just gonna use my gun.
Oh.
Yeah, I can use it on some of them.
Anyway,
so I started blasting.
Yeah.
Take him out.
We get him eventually.
Yeah.
Out of the way, baby.
The sword is overrated.
The sword is overrated, everyone.
Oh, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Oh, God.
Oh my God.
Fish and mailed.
Uh-oh.
We're almost out.
Ouchie ouch.
Time to change to this guy.
You got him.
Oh my God.
I need to heal, but...
Again?
You can't do this to me twice.
Oh my gosh.
My little bandage.
I can't see.
Kojima, please.
Is that bandage?
Bandage.
Oh, I never got a cold.
Fish and mailed.
Yeah.
That's right.
Oh.
That's you, Snake.
Oh my gosh.
Dang.
Snake is so fast.
Oh.
Thank you.
Can you give me a ration?
Give me health, please.
Oh my God.
Ouch.
What are you giving me?
More ammo.
Okay.
Snake is... Oh.
I got it.
Body armor?
Oh, you're right.
Just eat the bullets.
Fortune!
She's been... She's... She's...
It's been a long wait, Solid Snake.
She's seen better days.
What?
Two years ago, you killed my father.
That was the beginning of hell for us.
Everyone I love has been taken from me one by one.
And no matter how hard I try, I can't follow them.
An endless nightmare.
The only thing we live for is to see it end.
Our wait is almost over.
You can't be serious about firing the nuke.
Since no one can kill me, I may as well kill everyone I can.
Damn.
I'm starting.
You suck.
Looks like I'm today's pick.
You go on ahead.
Wait!
Isn't two better than one?
Ow, the edge.
Snake!
No!
You want eternal rest?
I've got it right here.
Say hello to my eternal rest.
What are you gonna do?
Bullets can't get near her.
I'll think of something.
There's no such thing as a witch.
You think you can kill me?
She's been... why are you even crying?
I don't know what your group's been through.
But let's get one thing clear.
I didn't kill your father.
Do you think anyone believes your lies?
Raiden!
Get out of here!
Why don't you tell her who it was?
You literally saw it.
Oh my god.
Snake, don't die.
What a thrill.
I'm going to go fight the hot girl alone.
Now go!
Here we are, everybody.
Arsenal Gear Rectum.
Jack, I've been watching how you fight.
It says it on the floor!
It looks like you've remembered the way you used to kill the angels.
That's what it's really called!
Or is it one of the S3 plan's proud achievements?
What are you talking about?
It came as a complete surprise when Ocelot discovered the S3 data from GW.
Not a bad idea, though.
Using fire to fight fire.
Creating the perfect assassin to retire.
Solid Snake's brother.
S3 stands for Solid Snake Simulation.
It's a development program to artificially reproduce Solid Snake.
The perfect warrior.
The result is a Foxhound commando.
When Foxhound no longer exists, a simulated Solid Snake shaped by VR regimen.
Sound like someone you know, Jack?
No, Gear Rectum.
I'm sorry to see you reduced to one of the Patriots' puppets.
But I've made use of you.
And their plan, too.
Solid Snake's sudden appearance.
Your arrival.
It was obvious the Patriots were among my ranks.
I had to smoke out the agent before the mission entered the final phase.
You came in handy.
Sorry, I doubt you.
As bait.
Jack.
Yeah?
Those days during the Civil War were as real as they come.
Every day was absolute.
Split between life and death.
Yeah.
You ran from it.
And now you've been led back to war by something less than real.
Look at the way he rides.
Sorry.
Solidus!
No more games, Jack.
At least you know.
There's no reason to keep you alive now.
No!
Papa!
Please, Papa!
I've given you a worthy opponent, at least.
But now, you should die as the little Jacky-boy I once knew.
Jacky-boy.
Come on.
Come on, Raiden.
You have so many other better weapons.
Oh shit.
Okay.
Um, hold on.
I'm gonna use this ration.
Body armor.
What is BDU?
Oh, that's the uniform.
That's the Gerlukovich.
Okay.
Then, we're gonna grab a...
Stinger Missile!
And we're gonna...
Okay, remember how to do this fight.
Ouch!
Remember how to do this fight.
Right.
Okay, I remember.
We'll just focus on this guy real quick.
No, I need to get him before...
Oh shoot, I missed my chance.
Oh shoot.
Ouch!
Ouchie ouch.
Get up.
Get up, Raiden, please.
Oh my gosh, I keep missing my chances.
I know I have to hit him in the mouth, but I have to hit him.
Can I chaff in this part?
Does chaffing work?
Can't remember.
Oh shit.
Oh, I don't think I hit him.
No!
Oh my god.
It does help.
There we go.
Woohoo!
Holy moly.
Can't get too close.
Stop sending missiles at me.
There we go.
Nice.
So...
I don't
remember this part.
Wait, I don't remember this phase!
I don't remember this phase!
Oh shoot!
I don't...
Hold on.
I made a mistake.
Oh wait.
No, I should have gone to Otacon.
Otacon.
Oh, sorry.
Otacon, help me.
Raiden, aim for Ray's head section with the stinger missiles.
That's it?
Call the colonel.
Colonel!
The
mass production Metal Gear is unmanned.
It's probably under the control of GW, the Arsenal Gear AI.
A chaff attack should cause electronic interference.
Confuse Ray for a moment.
Okay.
Use the opportunity to fire a stinger into him.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Okay.
Hoi yui hoi yui.
Aaaaah!
I had...
I'm so mad because I had the...
Guys, I don't think this is the run.
I'm just saying.
I don't think this is the run.
Byeee.
Bye.
Yeah, he's leaving!
That's so unfair.
That's so unfair, man.
Oh gosh.
Oh my god, please!
I just stood up!
This is so unfair!
You son of a bitch!
That was so mean!
I just stood up!
Where was my iframes?
Fishing my own.
If only.
Alright.
Chalk.
Ration.
Body armor.
Chalk.
Oh, that's a magazine!
Oh my god.
What the... Oh my god.
What are you doing?
That was really embarrassing.
Okay.
I
think the chaffs last a little longer.
Oh, okay.
Oh shoot.
I just realized.
I did not...
I didn't... I didn't... I didn't...
Oh!
It still works!
Yeah!
Let's go!
Nice!
Will
it work?
Nice!
Okay, bye!
So unfair!
I have no more bandages either.
Oh gosh.
This thing is such a pain in the butt.
Oh my god.
I need the chaff again.
Whoa!
My vision!
Chaff!
Okay.
Now is the time to strengthen myself.
Eeeeee!
Hold on.
I think I need to get that.
Oh!
Oh gosh.
Okay.
Chaff again.
Chaff!
Those are stupid.
Silly.
And... take him out!
Nice!
Okay.
I'm gonna grab this.
Thank you.
Bye bye.
Next!
Next please!
Oh!
Oh my god.
No!
That might waste!
You're such a jerk!
Oh!
I don't think that worked.
It did!
Nice!
Okay.
And chaff.
Sting up!
Oh!
I think I missed.
Never mind.
Chaff!
Soon!
Soonish chaff.
Oh!
Chaff now.
I think I can get like two in while...
Okay.
There we go.
Sting up!
You're close.
You're really close.
Run away.
You're too close.
Oh!
So unfair.
How am I supposed to know which one comes out?
Beep!
Oh!
Shit!
There we go.
Not the great timing.
Not the best timing.
But you know.
Oh!
That's the wrong guy.
Can you give me more chaffs?
Oh!
Shit!
Nice dodge.
Nice dodge!
Okay.
Right where it hurts.
And right in the kisser.
Nice!
Oh!
He's like immune for a second.
Okay.
I think he's better.
There we go.
Okay.
Right in the kisser!
Oh!
Gosh!
Once I'm out of chaffs, what do I do?
Oh!
Whoops!
I didn't mean to hit that guy.
Oh!
Shoot!
Run!
Nice hit.
And...
Kiss him!
Oh!
Chaffs!
Once I'm out of chaffs, what do I do?
Wait!
Oh!
He's not done.
Oh my god!
I came running in thinking he was still over.
Oh my gosh!
That's so...
Right there!
Now he's done.
Once I'm out of chaffs, what do I do?
Ouchie!
Okay.
That's nice, I guess.
Body armor.
Oh gosh!
Oh shit!
I was trying to... I pressed X.
I swear I did.
Oh gosh!
Okay.
Two more chaffs.
Oh!
There we go.
Stinger missile...
Okay.
I have a lot.
Ray... Did I say Rose on accident?
My bad.
Okay.
Get him.
Oh gosh though.
For real.
Once I'm out of chaffs, what do I do?
This has been my whole thing!
I'm so bound!
App
is unnecessary but it makes it way easier!
It makes it way easier!
To avoid the beep beep beep ones, you know?
Oh, I just shot that into the ether.
There we go.
Ouch!
Oh my god!
Sorry, I've been staring at the computer screen so much.
My contacts are drying out.
Get up, Raiden!
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
This is it for it.
It's over.
It's so over.
It's so jover.
Oh shit.
No!
Can't
even aim!
Oh my gosh, wait, we're on Rose!
Oh god.
Everybody's shooting at me!
Calm down!
Oh!
Ouch!
Oh gosh.
But we got him.
We got him.
Oh, hello?
Hello?
Oh, how many more?
How many more?
That was cruel.
That was so cruel!
How many more do I have?
Please!
Envoy suffering!
Just go quick.
Back to Jack B.
Quick!
Jack B.
I have one ration.
Oh, jeez.
God.
It's so over.
No.
We were doing great boss only because I had the trap grenades!
Now I don't have the trap grenades anymore!
Oh gosh, you saved just like a few...
Oh my god.
I pressed X, but not soon enough, I guess.
What's the point of... What's the point of even running?
What's the point of even running?
What's the point?
Oh my god.
Okay.
Okay, please.
I'm bleeding out!
This is it, you guys.
I don't want to have to do all of it over.
Oh shit.
Raiden, come in.
Raiden?
How many did I get through?
Like...
Three or four?
I think three or four of them I got through.
Oh gosh.
Oh.
Four.
You were on the last one?
No, I wasn't.
Oh god.
Five out of six.
Okay.
One thing I know now is they always come in from the right side.
So I need to not...
A baby.
Actually, I don't know.
I feel like if I'm on the left side, they're going to hop on top of me right there.
Oh, my tummy hurts.
Okay.
Why didn't I pick up more chaff grenades?
Can you get more chaff?
Nope.
If you get the second stinger shot a little faster, you avoid the missiles.
I think if...
Well, maybe I should start shooting the guys in the back too because they also...
I don't know.
I would have to be very strategic about it because they also...
Like, I want to avoid their missiles as well.
They're the...
The beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep missiles are the ones that are really hard to avoid.
Like, they're the ones that make it difficult, I think.
Well, for me at least.
I don't know.
You were doing good until the ray utilized jumpscare tactics.
Armor.
Oh, shoot.
Oh, shoot, please.
Oh, my God.
I'm forgetting controls.
Why am I forgetting controls?
Worst time to forget controls.
Oh.
It's these.
This one here.
Travel?
I got these.
Oh, these during the play fails?
I didn't know there were those in game plan...
Oh, sorry, I forget trilogies.
Ar duo?Ar duo.
Ar duo?
Ar all this?
Ar duo.
Right.
Hey, it's not gusta, I think I got it right.
I got it wrong.
Ar duo.
They don't stop coming!
2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13...
They don't stop...
See?
This is why I'm just like... I can't get a shot in.
Raiden!
Maybe if I do get closer...
But then they all start blasting at me.
Are you gonna come up?
Are you coming up now?
Are you hopping up?
No?
Okay.
You're not hopping up.
Look at them!
Look at them staring at me!
Stop looking at me, you!
Stop watching!
Oh my god.
Even dodging it does nothing.
Raiden, get up!
Get up Raiden!
What the... Why did you duck?
Why did you duck?
Why did you do that?
Ray down.
Oh my god.
No, wait!
Wrong!
Here's the guy that's coming next though, right?
You're coming.
Yeah.
You're hopping up next.
I know.
I know your game now.
Oh.
Wait.
I missed it somehow.
Next guy comes walking on in.
Oh.
I see him.
Um...
Raiden, come in.
Raiden?
What the hell was that?
Oh.
He's so fast when he's here.
You're not coming up yet.
No, no, no.
No,
no, no.
No, no, no.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now he's coming up.
Oh my god.
Where are my rations?
Raiden, please.
This is so funny.
Why don't I get invincible?
Just kill me.
What?
I was standing right there.
Raiden, come in.
Raiden?
Oh.
Ouch.
Oh shoot.
Oh shit.
I forgot to do my rations.
Oh.
My body armor.
Oh my god.
Please, Raiden.
Move.
Keep going, Raiden.
Just get out of here.
Oh no.
Okay.
Oh.
I missed my chance.
And I missed my chance.
I also... I also just...
Oh.
Guys.
Oh god.
I...
I don't believe.
I don't...
Why is your aim... Why do you...
Oh my god.
Run, run, run.
Run, Raiden.
Oh, thank god.
That's one down.
Come on up.
Even with body armor...
Raiden.
Even with body armor, they hit so hard.
Oh my god.
Stop shooting at me.
Okay.
Oh.
Shoot.
Here it goes.
Raiden.
Get up.
Please.
Okay.
Now it's time to change.
Jeff.
Where's my...
Guys.
I'm not...
I'm not feeling so good.
Guys.
While I wait, I should really take out like some other...
Should really do some other things.
Oh.
He's leaving.
Shoot.
Oh shoot.
I missed my opportunity.
I didn't notice.
I
didn't notice that he was down.
I missed my window of opportunity.
Oh my god.
Both of you guys.
Oh.
Ouch.
Why is...
Why am I...
What's the point of dodging?
If it's...
If...
Even when I'm in midair.
Nothing happens.
What's the point of dodging?
Don't fall off.
Don't fall off, Raiden.
And you.
Take him out.
I'm just getting their legs so that they...
Well.
Hopefully.
I just realized also...
I need a Jeff.
Jeff.
Did I...
No.
I didn't.
There we go.
Okay.
Oh gosh.
What's the point of dodging?
Because if they're like...
You know, if they're...
Down...
Then, they're less likely...
Even though I'm not hitting them.
They're less likely to shoot out.
You know?
Oh...
Well that was...
Woah.
Why do you have so much ammo?
Oh okay.
Here.
Okay.
Little waist.
It's fine though.
It's fine.
Oh my god.
What do you want?
Shit.
Oh, I still got it.
My ration!
So three... oh shit.
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run!
Run, run!
There's another ration over here.
I wonder if I can get it.
Wait.
Oh.
No, that's not a ration.
Stinger, rocket, bow.
There's something over here.
Oh, more bullets.
No chop.
Shit.
I've lost it.
I've lost everything.
I've lost all control.
I give up.
I don't want to play anymore.
Why don't you run?
I don't want to play.
I don't want to play anymore.
Oh god.
That was so close.
Holy shit.
Oh my god.
Get the ration.
No!
I'm sick of this game.
This game sucks.
Oh.
Why did I?
Why?
Oh.
I got him still.
Nice.
Take him out at least.
Come on.
Come on out.
Number four!
What's the point?
Okay.
Stinger!
Why am I doing this?
It's all just some simulation.
It's just a simulation!
Oh my god.
They gave me another... They gave me another ration though.
Please.
No!
I missed it.
I messed up.
Run him in between his legs.
Yeah.
Run him between his legs.
I'm gonna use it now.
Where's my... Where's my... Where's my body armor?
Why are we here?
Just to suffer!
Stinger!
Okay.
Nice.
And the kisser!
Boop!
Ah, boop, boop, boop, boop.
Ah, I hope I hit!
I did!
Yippee!
Okay.
Your turn!
Yep!
And the kisser!
Oh my
god.
Raiden!
Raiden, please.
I hate... I hate that mechanic more than anything, I think.
Oh shit!
Just stay on the chat.
Ok.
There we go.
Tactical.
Okay.
Oh, thank you.
Which one's next?
Oh, I think I went to trap the grenade too early.
But that's okay.
Stinger.
Oh, uh... Stinger.
Oh.
Stinger.
Get
the...
get you.
Get you.
No!
Wrong way!
There we go.
Oh.
I got him twice I think.
Whatever.
You guys, I think my sanity is kinda low.
Beep.
Stinger!
I hardly even know it.
And the kisser!
Yum.
Ouchie.
Ouch.
Come on.
Maybe two more.
Oh shit.
I actually don't know anymore.
CHAAAALF!
Okay, more.
I thought that was the last one.
Not gonna lie.
I thought the other one was the last one.
I'm out of chaps.
Of course I am!
Of course I'm out of chaps!
Why wouldn't I be out of chaps?
That would be ridiculous otherwise!
Okay.
Recover!
There we go!
Nice!
Why do you get invincibility and I get nothing jack?
Poopy!
I know I don't need chaps!
But I like to have them!
They make it really easy!
They make it so much easier!
I'm so sweaty!
This game makes me go bonkers!
Not that game.
This fight makes me go bonkers for real!
Feels like I'm just in hell.
You know, just never ending hell.
The same thing.
Over and over again.
Olga!
What about now?
You did amazing!
Well done!
Thank you!
This is suicide!
Fuck you!
Thanks for the thing you did!
You are nanomachines.
They're transmitting your vital signs to the Patriots.
My hands are shaking so much.
If you die, my child dies.
Sorry.
Sorry I got a little extra during that fight, you guys.
I'm okay.
So that's why you sold your troops out to me.
So many dead.
They all died trusting you.
Were they your comrades?
No, they're not just comrades.
I'm okay.
I have to like talk myself through those kinds of fights sometimes, you know?
I have to be like, okay!
Unequip!
Equip!
I have to like talk myself.
I have to be like, jump high!
It's how I focus.
See you in hell!
Oh god!
Don't do it.
Don't do it!
Live!
I think we could have done a second take on that one.
Oh god.
Her death is so...
Feels so icky.
Enjoy the show, Jack.
Let's pick up where we left off.
Something's wrong with them.
What's going on?
What's wrong with it?
It's AI.
GW, it's out of control.
What?
Ooh, the way they shake is so creepy.
Ew!
So creepy.
I love it.
Oh god.
They're possessed.
A ghost in the machine.
GW.
Metal ray freaky.
I'm reading an abnormal impulse cascade throughout the neural network.
I want some chocolate.
What happened?
Maybe some kind of virus.
The Patriots?
I don't know.
Ocelot, what have you been up to?
It's too late.
Arsenal's system control is going haywire.
GW equals ghost wife?
The virus.
No!
Stupid machines.
Come on.
Oh my god.
He's turning superhero.
GW means goat?
George Washington?
No, no, no.
Ghost wife.
Ghost woman.
That's mean.
Yes!
Solidus!
Why does his gun work on it?
But not mine.
Actually, I don't know.
Does the gun work on it?
I imagine not.
Otacon told me to use the stinger missiles.
Damn the Patriots.
Solidus even having his little snake hair tuft is just so amazing.
You still have some use.
I've captured Snake.
What?
Snake!
Snake?
Snake, I just had to fight off like six Metal Gears.
Bring him in.
All by myself?
I might be better than you at this point.
You had a hindy.
I had a Harrier.
And if I...
Snake spilled his spaghetti.
You lack his charisma.
You know what?
You're so right.
The moon.
The moon is beautiful.
Snake!
I'll squeeze the answers out of you instead, my son.
Oh, oh!
Wait,
why isn't it...
Oh, oh, oh, okay.
Oh my god.
If you stop...
Okay, I was like, why is it still going down?
Oh my god.
Solidus!
Okay.
What do you hope to hear?
He's solid, but handcuffed by fortune.
It's not him I want the answers from.
I'm gonna look at Snake for...
Oh, I was gonna say for...
For moral support.
Ah!
Oh, I'm handcuffed.
What do you mean?
That's not your business.
Oh, really?
It so happens I have some business of my own to attend to.
I like that fortune's the only...
The only dead cell left.
You were going to screw me over, weren't you?
You talked, Ocelot.
Not exactly.
I was the one who used Ocelot to suggest the idea to you in the first place.
Whoa!
What?
I was planning to give you Ocelot to begin with.
Ah, okay.
That is fine.
I'm no philanthropist.
Ocelot is far from impregnable.
It needs other Metalgears as guards.
A huge payload of warheads.
Solidus fighting Ray like that got inspired.
With just a large attack force without support, Arsenal is nothing more than a gigantic coffin.
Seizing Arsenal gear was never the real objective.
What?
What was your objective then?
Why does everybody just create things?
A list of names.
Of the Patriots!
Oh!
The Patriots!
They were planning to extend their control to digital information flow with GW and Arsenal.
That means the information they want to filter out is contained in GW.
Including that list of the highest 12 members of the Patriots' Wiseman's Committee.
I kinda wanna go get my cake.
And once you knew who they were, you would cross out their names one by one.
While we, with our useless arsenal, drew their fire.
I gotta finish it sooner or I'll go bad I think.
You were using us all along.
Were you any different?
But your plans hit a snag with GW destroyed, hasn't it?
Everybody...
Everybody double crosses, everybody triple crosses, everybody is just in it for themselves.
No, there is another way.
Really?
But we have our own plans to carry out.
I love fortunes.
We'll take the arsenal since you don't care for it anyway.
The purified hydrogen bomb is ready to go.
A nuclear strike won't stop them.
It will damage their power source.
How is it possible to get so...
So...
Attached to characters.
In just a single video game.
Even Batman.
You see him once.
And I love him so much.
Oh boy.
Good riding.
What exactly do you find so funny?
Charades usually are humorous.
I played you.
He's pointing at everybody.
Played you.
But we're running a little short on time.
What are you talking about?
I played you.
Everything you've done here has been scripted.
A little exercise set up by us.
Oh my god.
Exercise.
The S3 plan was conceived as a means to produce soldiers on par with Solid Snake.
Yeah.
That's what I told you.
Otacon and Fortune fell in love.
But the VR training the boy was put through is not the meat of the project.
Otacon's is too strong I think.
You think this little terrorist incident is your own doing, Solidus?
This is the S3 training, Colonel.
He looks so mad.
An orchestrated recreation of Shao Kahn.
Shadow Moses.
What?
Ames and the President's deaths.
You thought before was the recreation?
No, no, no.
The computer virus that mimics Fox Die.
This whole game has been the recreation of Shadow Moses.
Ames' own nano-machines were used to shut down his pacemaker.
Ah ha ha!
I arranged it.
Ain't no way.
Thanks, Peter.
As for the President, although Johnson realized what was going on, he played out his allotted part.
As for the computer virus, it's a digital counterpart of Fox Die.
It was also designed to eliminate every scrap of information regarding the Patriots from GW.
Your plan was invalidated.
Those birds.
Even before execution, so was...
Yeah, birds were paid actors, too.
Fat Man was a different story.
He's one of our own people.
A sort of examiner we hired to test the boy's progress before letting him tackle the exercise proper.
We had to arrange for Stillman's presence to coax the maniac into agreeing.
If the boy had allowed the Big Shell to be destroyed, this exercise would have ended there.
Fat Man just being his own thing is just so fitting for him.
The project has no room for failures.
Fat Man is just his own guy.
What do you mean?
Given the right situation, the right story, anyone can be shaped into Snake.
Even me!
Even rookies can fight like men of experience.
I can become like Snake.
An instant creation of genius.
So it is not played like a damn fiddle.
A single journal will provide more than enough data to formulate such a program.
You, Dead Cell, Olga, you're all nothing but pawns...
Pawns!
...placed to create the perfect simulation.
Also, I've never met someone that he couldn't double-cry.
Solidus, you and the boy were selected because your relationship resembles the one between Snake and Big Boss.
Pawns!
Fortune, you and the rest of Dead Cell stand in for the Foxhound's victory.
And you are part of the team which Snake took on in Shadow Moses.
You're the most impressive collect of freaks outside Foxhound.
They never met freaky phantom.
We have gone to a lot of trouble to set you up against the boy.
That story about purified hydrogon bonds...
The boy.
Just the tip of the iceberg.
I'm a freak too!
...when I sunk that tanker along with your old man two years ago.
...throwing your husband in the brig was a part of it too.
You were told that the eradication of Dead Cell six months ago was an act of the Patriots.
We provoked and encouraged your hatred.
Never go against a woman scorned.
And you opted for vengeance, just as we planned.
Just as we planned.
The way he says that is so funny.
Except for the appearance of the real Solid Snake.
He looks like he's like, oopsie.
Now, who sent for you?
All our misfortune was...
just a part of their project?
But you can't hit her.
How could...
You're no Lady Luck.
You have nothing that we didn't give you.
No, fortune!
What?
Do you know why no bullet could hit you?
It wasn't magic.
Or some new age mumbo jumbo.
It certainly wasn't your psychic talents.
It was all staged by the Patriots.
The Patriots?
What can they not do?
You were being shielded by the electromagnetic weapons...
and technology that the Patriots developed.
Oh my god.
Your dead cell comrades loved your father and husband.
We needed a pathetic wretch like you...
to keep them focused.
You've been our puppet all along.
Just like Olga.
Oh my god.
No!
The Patriots are just...
The Patriots this, the Patriots that.
You were hamming it up as the tragic heroine.
Thanks to the script that the Patriots wrote...
for you.
Well what about free will exists?
Your self-indulgence...
absorbed in your own misfortune.
You couldn't get enough of the drama.
Bro, he's so mean.
I could have died whenever I wanted to.
Yeah.
I guess so.
Thought I got her in the heart.
Oh my god.
He's Lady Luck.
It missed.
Thanks Raiden.
Now I remember.
Your heart's on the right.
A blast of metal, my dear.
But your luck's run out.
This is the little gizmo.
There's no such thing as miracles or the supernatural.
Only cutting-edge technology.
Wait, then how did...
Oh!
Oh my god.
My ears.
She didn't have that on.
Did she?
I can't prevent me from ascending.
What the heck then?
Oh no!
The Patriots!
Happy 4th of July!
Time to fight!
25 more raids!
Yippee!
Here's the real boss fight.
Oh my god.
Remember the Alamo.
Now that I have enough data, all I have to do is retrieve Arsenal and clean up the refuse from the exercise.
Look out.
Look at his tail.
Just try.
Raiden's just so cute.
Yeah!
Oh!
Nice!
Good job.
Ah!
Rules of nature!
That's how we learned it!
Wow!
I love Solidus's outfit.
So awesome...
Oh!
Fortune!
She stands!
She's still standing.
Okay!
Oh, my God.
Ray-sized arsenals or one arsenal-sized room.
She's so awesome.
She is Lady Luck.
I
love her so much.
She's so awesome.
We're done.
My name is Helena Dolph Jackson.
The daughter of a proud and noble soldier.
I can see my family... again.
So awesome.
Damn!
Try this instead.
Try this on for size.
Uh-oh.
Oh, that pesky hand of his.
This game just never stops delivering.
It's one thing after another.
It truly is.
Brothers!
Liquid.
I've been waiting for this.
It can't be.
Liquid.
Brothers.
I've been inside this arm all along waiting for the right time to awaken.
Oh, I love this game so much.
You were inside Ocelot?
Yes.
A sleeper in the arm of a Patriot spy.
It was you two years ago?
Exactly.
I was controlling him.
I guess we know who tops.
Imagine doing an alpha strike on a 1HP in between.
It was like all your doing roles.
Snake, it was I that leaked information about Arsenal to your partner and got you out here.
What?
You're the only one that can free me.
After all...
After all?
Dramatic pause.
Dramatic pause?
I'm off to bury the Patriots for good.
You're drowning in time, brother.
You know who they are.
How?
Why do you think I chose Ocelot as my host?
That guy's crazy.
Before I go, I have a family matter to settle with both of you.
There's room for only one snake and one big boss.
Snake.
Did you get that?
Okay...
Don't let me run!
Just be carefull.
Shake it away!
Where are you going?!
I'm going to kill you.
You
Deep inside my head.
Whee!
McQueen, stop this thing!
Snake was on something this dark.
Oh no!
Oh my god!
We're gonna crash right into the city!
Arsenal!
Oh my gosh!
False alarm!
Like a glove.
That was so clean.
Now we're here!
Are you guys ready for even more info dump?
Let's go!
I have to go to this place.
I'm so happy we're at the end.
Oh my gosh, I love the ending of this game so much.
Hit me with it.
Federal hall?
Yes!
Federal hall!
What are you laughing at?
Do you know what day it is today?
April 30th?
Actually...
July 20th?
That's right.
George Washington took office as the first president of the United States of America 200 years ago.
Today.
Wow!
And it happened right here.
We were going to declare another independence.
The dawn of a new nation.
Here.
The end of the Patriots' secret rule.
Liberation of this country.
This was where it was supposed to begin.
This is where freedom could have been born.
Yep.
Born.
All you want is power at any cost.
Jack.
Sorry, I was checking a text.
It's not power I want.
What I wanted to take back from the Patriots are things like freedom, civil rights, opportunities.
The founding principles of this country.
Everything that's about to be wiped out by their digital censorship.
Jack, listen to me.
We're all born with an expiration date.
No one lasts forever.
Life is nothing but a grace period for turning the best of our genetic material into the next generation.
The data of life is transferred from parent to child.
What is that, water?
That's how it works.
But we have no heirs, no legacy.
We brothers are called Les Enfants Terribles.
Terrible.
Cloned from our father with the ability to reproduce conveniently engineered out.
Oof.
What is our legacy if we cannot pass the torch?
Your legacy is...
Proof of our existence.
A mark of some sort.
Is what you do with your time here.
You don't need to have children.
It's okay.
When the torch is passed on from parent to child, it extends beyond DNA.
Information is imparted as well.
Spade or neuter your snakes.
They have... wait...
Did they also take Ryden's people?
By history.
He was a Kandar.
The Patriots are trying to protect their power, their own interests, by controlling the digital flow of information.
I want my memory, my existence to remain.
Unlike an intron of history, I will be remembered as an Exon.
That will be my legacy.
My mark in history.
Okay, crazy pants.
But the Patriots will deny us even that.
I will triumph over the Patriots.
Yeah, he did get Rose pregnant.
And liberate us all.
Pregante.
And we will become...
The Sons of Liberty!
Yeah!
Tidal drop, baby!
Ryden, are you receiving?
We're still here.
I don't want to talk to you, creepy colonel.
The AI was destroyed.
Only GWs.
Who are you?
To begin with, we're not what you'd call human.
Over the past 200 years, a kind of consciousness formed layer by layer in the crucible of the White House.
It's not unlike the way life started in the oceans 4 billion years ago.
The White House was our primordial soup.
Primordial soup!
Good soup.
We are the very discipline and morality that Americans invoke so often.
How can anyone hope to eliminate us?
As long as this nation exists, so will we.
Cut the crap!
If you're immortal, why would you take away individual freedoms and censor the net?
The net?
Jack, don't be so despicable.
Don't you know that our plans have your interests, not ours, in mind?
What?
Jack, listen carefully.
Like a good boy.
Rose?
The mapping of the human genome was completed early this century.
As a result, the evolutionary log of the human race lay open to us.
We started with genetic engineering, and in the end, we succeeded in digitizing life itself.
Despicable.
But there are things not covered by genetic information.
What do you mean?
Human memories, ideas, culture, history.
Genes don't contain any record of human history.
They don't.
Is it something that should not be passed on?
Should that information be left at the mercy of nature?
We've always kept records of our lives.
Through words, pictures, symbols, from tablets to books.
But not all the information was inherited by later generations.
A small percentage of the whole was selected and processed, then passed on.
They're gonna see my books.
Not unlike genes, really.
That's what history is, Jack.
But in the current digitized world...
They're gonna see all my books.
The trivial information is accumulating every second.
Preserved in all its triteness.
Never fading.
Always accessible.
Rumors about petty issues, misinterpretations, slander.
Slander?
Wait, what about libel?
Preserved in an unfiltered state, growing at an alarming rate.
It will only slow down social progress.
Reduce the rate of evolution.
Right.
You seem to think that our plan is one of censorship.
Are you telling me it's not?
You're being silly.
Silly.
What we propose to do is not to control content, but to create context.
Create context?
The digital society furthers human flaws and selectively rewards development of convenient half-truths.
Just look at the strange juxtapositions of morality around you.
The music is crazy.
Billions spent on new weapons in order to humanely murder other humans.
Rights of criminals are given more respect than the privacy of their victims.
Although there are people suffering in poverty, huge donations are made to protect endangered species.
Everyone grows up being told the same thing.
Be nice to other people.
But beat out the competition.
You're special.
Believe in yourself and you will succeed.
But it's obvious from the start that only a few can succeed.
You exercise your right to freedom, and this is the result.
All rhetoric to avoid conflict and protect each other from harm.
The untested truths, spun by different interests, continue to churn and accumulate in the sandbox of political correctness and value systems.
Everyone withdraws into their own small gated community afraid of a larger forum.
They stay inside their little ponds, leaking whatever truth suits them into the growing cesspool of society at large.
Cesspool of society.
The different cardinal truths neither clash nor mesh.
No one is invalidated.
But nobody is right.
Not even natural selection can take place here.
The world is being engulfed in truth.
And this is the way the world ends.
Not with a bang, but a whimper.
We're trying to stop that from happening.
It's our responsibility as rulers.
Just as in genetics, unnecessary information and memory must be filtered out to stimulate the evolution of the species.
This game is too crazy.
And you think you're qualified to decide what's necessary?
They're aware of Twitter.
The patriots go on Twitter.com.
Who else could wade through the sea of garbage you people produce, retrieve valuable truths, and even interpret their meaning for later generations?
That's what it means to create context.
I'll decide for myself what to believe and what to pass on.
But is that even your own idea?
Or something Snake told you?
That's the proof of your incompetence right there.
You lack the qualifications to exercise your power.
He gave up so quickly.
Does something like a self exist inside of you?
That which you call self serves as nothing more than a mask to cover your own being.
The sigh.
He just gave up.
Come on, Ryan.
In this era of ready-made truths, self is just something used to preserve those positive emotions that you occasionally feel.
Another possibility is that self is a concept you conveniently borrowed under the logic that would endow you with some sense of strength.
That's crap.
Is it?
Would you prefer that someone else tell you?
All right, then.
Explain it to him.
Jack, you're simply the best.
And you got there all by yourself.
What happened?
Do you feel lost?
Why not try a bit of soul-searching?
Maybe.
Don't think you'll find anything, though.
Ironically, that all those self is something that you yourself fashion.
Every time something goes wrong, you turn around and place the blame on something else.
It's not my fault.
It's not your fault.
In denial, you simply resort to looking for another, more convenient truth in order to make yourself feel better.
Leaving behind in an instant the so-called truth you once embraced.
Should someone like that be able to decide what is truth?
Should someone like you even have the right to decide?
You've done nothing but abuse your freedom.
You don't deserve to be free.
We're not the ones smothering the world.
You are.
It's on you, Raiden.
The individual is supposed to be weak, but far from powerless.
A single person has the potential to ruin the world.
And the age of digitized communication has given even more power to the individual.
Too much power for an immature species.
Building a legacy involves figuring out what is wanted and what needs to be done.
All this you used to struggle with.
Now, we think for you.
You know what?
Sounds kinda nice.
You want to control human thought?
Human behavior?
Of course.
Anything can be quantified nowadays.
That's what this exercise was designed to prove.
You fell in love with me just as you were meant to, after all.
Isn't that right, Jack?
Ocelot was not told the whole truth, to say the least.
We are an entire nation.
Of what interest would a single soldier, no matter how able, be to us?
The S3 plan does not stand for Solid Snake Simulation.
What it does stand for is Selection for Societal Sanity.
My sanity is gone!
The S3 is a system for controlling human will and consciousness.
What AI Summarizer says for the stream is, I agree.
What just happened?
Soldiers are trained in the image of Solid Snake.
Well, that scared me for a second.
It is a method, a protocol that created a circumstance that made you what you are.
So you see, we're the S3.
Not you.
The game is screwing with you, for real.
That was getting too meta, too meta!
That's crazy.
You heard what President Johnson said.
The Arsenal's GW system is the key to their supremacy.
The objective of this exercise was to establish such a method.
The difference between submission and rebellion.
We used Shadow Moses as a paradigm for the exercise.
I wonder if you would have preferred a fantasy setting.
Ooh, with elf girls.
We chose that back thought because of its extreme circumstances.
Sorry, the hack.
It was an optimal test for S3's crisis management capacity.
If the model could trigger, control, and solve this, it would be ready for any contingency.
Snake is so awesome.
And now we have our proof.
I did all that.
Fantasy Metal Gear would just literally be Bloodborne.
Right.
There are also reasons behind your selection.
Solidus raised plenty of other child soldiers.
Or Lake Elden Ring.
You know why we chose you over them?
Hmm.
It was because you were the only one who refused to acknowledge the past.
All the others remember what they were and pay for it daily.
But you turn your back on everything you don't like.
You do whatever you like.
See only the things you like.
And for yourself alone.
What's wrong with that?
If I don't like it, why do I have to deal with it?
You refused to see me for what I was.
I lied to you.
But I wanted to be caught.
You pretended to be understanding.
To be a gentleman.
You never made a conscious attempt to reach out to me.
The only time you did was when I gave you no choice but to do so.
I was just trying not to.
What?
Trying not to hurt me?
Dear, the one you were trying not to hurt was yourself.
Avoiding the truth under the guise of kindness is all that you did.
It occurred to you to do nothing but look out for yourself.
Even if you claimed that it was for my sake, that feeling was nowhere to be seen.
In the end, everything was for your sake.
I was never part of the picture.
Raiden, are you okay?
Exactly right.
Why is the AI laughing?
It's creepy.
You are a perfect representative of the masses we need to protect.
Why is the AI laughing?
Why does it have emotions like that?
You accepted the fiction we've provided, obeyed our orders, and did everything you were told to.
The exercise is a resounding success.
The snake actually over there in the oil rig?
Did you not tell me the GW was still incomplete?
But not anymore, thanks to you.
Your persona, experiences, triumphs, and defeats are nothing but byproducts.
The real objective was ensuring that we could generate and manipulate them.
It's taken a lot of time and money, but it was well worth it considering the results.
I think that's enough talk.
It's time for the final exercise.
Raiden, take Solidus down.
Think again.
I'm through doing what I'm told.
Oh really?
Aren't you forgetting something?
If you die, my child dies.
Determination of vital signals from your nanomachines means the death of Olga's child.
Not to mention the death of Rose.
She's wired the same way.
What?
Rose, does she actually exist?
Of course I do, Jack.
You have to believe me.
Belive me?
Before you are dying to the death.
Solidus at least wants you dead.
We will collect the necessary data for this last fight.
Believe me.
Then we'll consider the exercise closed.
So, Jack the Ripper.
Jack the Ripper.
Will it be Solidus, the Patriot's creation?
Or you, Solidus' creation?
Our beloved monsters, enjoy yourselves.
Oh god!
Chills!
The last line is just so...
Oh my god!
Jack, my son.
My clone brothers and I are called monsters.
Replicates of evil genes.
Our beloved monsters.
You are one of a kind, but still a monster.
Shaped by a dark and secret history.
We need to decide which monstrosity will have the privilege of survival.
By the way, Jack.
This part is so funny.
I was the one who killed your parents.
Why you...
By the way, man.
I claimed you for my own and raised you as a soldier in the army of the devil.
I am your foster father and your worst enemy.
The timing is crazy.
Because I needed to know whether we were really someone else's creation.
We're repeating history, Jack.
Liquid and Solid hunted down Big Boss.
Trying to sever the tie that bound them to him.
Unless you kill me and face your past, Jack.
Big Boss.
You will never escape.
You'll stay in the endless loop.
Your own double helix.
Little baby.
Looks just like Paws.
It's time we were both free.
My hands!
I'm free!
Here we go, everybody.
Final boss fight.
Let's do this.
No guns.
I have other reasons for wanting you.
Actually, I don't remember.
I don't think I can use guns in this game.
The clues to the Patriots inside GW have been erased.
But there are other traces.
Inside you.
What?
The information is being carried by the nanomachines in your cerebral cortex.
And throughout the neural network, they fool you.
I forgot about...
What the...
That's crazy.
Why do you get two swords?
Here we go.
Brace yourself.
I don't remember how to fight.
What?
Oh.
Oh, shoot!
Oh!
Oh my God!
Okay, I have a body armor.
What else do I have?
Nothing.
Okay.
I have my dog tags.
And one ration.
And I can become a Grulukovich soldier.
Why did they give me that, of all things?
That's how I fight.
That's right.
I remembered.
I remember.
Here we are now.
Stabby Stab!
I'm on fire!
There's an additional ration?
Oh there is?
On the edge?
Oh I see it!
Ouch!
What's wrong with you?
Oh my god!
I don't remember how... I think I beat this last time in one try.
I don't remember how the hell I did that.
Come on!
Get up!
Probably by hitting him.
Probably.
Oh shoot!
What's wrong with you?
Oh my god!
Why can't I hit him?
I'm dumb.
That's why.
I'm dumb dad!
You gave me gunpowder!
Why can't I get a hit in ever?
Oh my god.
Or I can block like that.
Nice.
Oh!
Is that the best you can do?
Oh my god.
It's so janky.
This sword is so janky.
Oh my god!
Sweep!
I'm trying to get his right side since that's where he has the...
The eye.
Oh!
You have to keep it tight.
I'm trying!
It's fun to hear him laughing though.
What can I say?
I'm not a weeb like everybody else.
I think I got the most hits by...
Oh shit!
Forgot to do L1.
Oh nice!
Oh!
Oh shoot!
There we go!
Yahoo!
No!
What the hell?
Oh!
That's right!
I can hold...
I can hold L1, right?
Oh my god.
I just end up turning around.
It's so funny.
Shoot!
Oh shoot!
I missed my chance again.
Oh!
I got him!
Yeah!
I'm the one who's hitting you though.
Woo!
Hey!
The sword is...
Oh my god!
Oh!
Ah!
Never mind.
L1 doesn't do anything there, you guys.
I lied.
L1 doesn't do anything there!
L1 doesn't do anything!
After this, you'll be ready for Dark Souls.
Oh my god.
No, no, no.
How did I beat this first try before?
I was built different back in the past.
Oh!
Ouch!
Oh my god.
I'm on fire again.
I think I just gotta...
Oh my gosh!
I think I just gotta avoid them.
I think you have more rations.
That might be the case.
Okay.
Oh.
It wasn't interesting before?
Oh!
Yeah!
I'm working on it!
Why are you calling me?
Why aren't you zoomed in?
He had that grandpa angle.
When grandpa facetimes you.
T-that's not right.
T -that's not right.
Why are you guys so quiet?
...
You looked so defeated.
Don't cry.
Oh I see a tear.
Oh don't cry Raiden.
Don't cry.
I'm working on it!
Now I'm out of the groove!
Oh my god.
I was holding L1 though!
I was holding L1.
Oh my god.
Oh no.
Hold on.
Guys!
Oh my god.
I don't think this is it.
I don't have any more health.
I didn't see... unless they give you more rations.
Do they give you more rations in...
Ha Raiden!
Call Otacon?
Okay.
Let's call him now.
What does he got to say?
Raiden, you don't have a lot going for you with just your bare hands.
You have your own blade.
Use it.
Okay.
What an asshole.
You know what Otacon?
Wow.
Raiden, take Solonus down.
Think about Ogre's child and your rosemary.
You must win.
Nice angle grandpa.
Okay.
Oh shoot.
What the...
What's wrong with you?
Wait!
I was... I couldn't move!
Oh my god.
What the hell?
There we go.
Oh my god.
I'm like pressing X and he's lying down.
What are you doing?
Oh my god.
These things again.
You guys, I think I'm in trouble.
I need more rations.
I don't have enough.
I'm not good at sword fight, you guys.
This is so janky.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Thank you.
How can you still do fire also?
Oh my god.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay.
That was weird.
Sorry, my... It wasn't attacking anymore.
Oh my god.
Stop.
Thank goodness you improved your group strength.
Does that really make a difference?
Oh my god.
I'm gonna fucking lose my brain cells with this guy.
Maybe stab more.
Just remember the basics of CQC.
Yeah, totally applicable in this fight.
Totally applicable.
L1 doesn't do shit this fucking game.
I swear to god.
I
didn't...
I didn't... When I press X, I really need you to... I really need you to cartwheel away.
Okay, buddy.
I really need you to do it, please.
I just really need you... Oh god.
Oh my god.
God.
Oh, oops.
There we go.
Can you get off, please?
He sounds like an actual snake when he goes...
I hate the sword.
Oh my god.
Nooo.
Sometimes you stab and sometimes you don't.
Raiden.
Raiden, why?
Oh god.
Raiden.
Yeah.
Can you give me another ration, please?
Something.
Oh my god.
So, I have a question.
If I do left on the joystick, am I...
Shut up, Colonel.
Am I swinging to the left or am I swinging to the right?
Hold on.
Because people are like, go towards... See, I'm... I can't tell.
That was... The first one was... What?
Okay, hold on.
Okay, so if I go right, I swing from the right.
Okay.
There we go.
Like that.
Okay, okay.
But it doesn't really do much.
And also, sometimes it inputs as ups up and I don't know why.
I don't want to watch all of them.
Nice.
Oh!
I don't want to watch all of them.
Okay.
If you ask me to, I would...
I got nowhere else to go.
It was either that or the...
Why do you have missiles?
Why can't you... Why do you have missiles?
Hold on.
I'll start over.
Yeah, I'm not really going to...
I hate Colonel.
He's pissing me off.
Oh my god.
Why sometimes I can do it from the right and it seriously inputs as...
What's wrong with my controller?
What's wrong with this game?
Why?
Why if I swipe right, it says I'm doing up?
Oh my god.
I can't.
Come here.
Oh my god.
I'm so tired, you guys.
I'm so tired.
Point
of standing up.
Oh, you were doing... You were doing less damage to me as I was laying on the ground like a fucking potato than me actually moving.
Are you going to launch missiles at me?
No?
Side.
Why have I done like no damage to you, man?
This is so stinky.
Left side.
Right side.
That's me at you.
Okay.
All right.
I don't know how... How did I do this first time last time?
That must have been... That must have been an absolute like... Oh my god.
Nirvana or something.
I don't like doing the pierce because it takes too long to recover from it.
Is that the best way?
R2.
Wait, there's R2?
Oh my god.
Oh shit.
I'm dying.
Oh my god.
What's wrong with you?
Why does he have such a big health bar too?
So unfair.
Oh my god.
Please.
Every time I try to grab your ass.
That move is so OP.
You already have my oxygen.
Why do I have to also...
Be careful.
Or do I also have to be slammed on the ground?
Oh my god.
I can't see when I'm... I'm stabbing him but like I'm getting the angle wrong obviously.
But I'm like...
How?
How am I supposed to...
The camera angle is just so funky.
Oh my god.
Why do you turn around?
I'm not even moving.
I almost ran into that.
This is so messed up.
This is so messed up, Solidus.
I wasn't worried about this fight but now I am.
Oh my god.
Can we not have the camera angle change while I'm running?
And while he decides to...
Do that.
But
like I've tried blocking stuff and it wasn't working.
So I don't know.
Take this.
Okay.
I
really...
No.
You guys...
I don't need you guys to be like...
Do this.
You know?
It's okay though.
Oh my god.
Oh.
Okay.
Yippee.
Why are you still going?
I'm dead.
This
is so stupid.
So when he goes above I wonder if I can block that or it's just too...
I'm on fire.
Oh no.
How am I alive?
We're alive!
PJ, thanks for the gift.
Why do you sometimes do more than one?
Sometimes you don't.
Oh my god.
I can't read them at all.
What?
In one hit?
It's so strong.
I just got to do a little frustration cry.
I was like, I'm not worried at all about this fight.
I did it in one shot before.
I think I'm just tired.
Since I've had a long week.
Sorry.
Need food?
No, I'm good.
I already ate.
I ate earlier.
Liquid had some sense of honor and fair play to face off compared to Solidus.
Right!
Well, kind of.
I mean, Liquid still went into the Metal Gear against a singular man.
But...
It was more even in the car fight.
One singular man.
I'm gonna go get some water.
I'll be right back.
Okie dokie.
I got some honey water.
I don't want to drink tea because it's kind of late.
Yummy.
Yummy, yummy.
Okie dokie.
I'll try to block more.
And...
I'll try to beat him.
Skill issue something something.
Get behind him.
Yeah, I've been trying.
He's a slippery snake.
Ok.
Oh my god.
Great start, Raiden.
See, like that?
When I try to...
Ok, when he does...
When he revs up for that...
See, I was holding L1 there.
I was holding L1.
I promise.
Oh, it does work.
That works.
Ok, let's see what he can block.
Ok.
Oh, what the?
What the lag?
Ok.
Oh shoot, I turned!
I turned!
Wait, where's the ration?
There it is.
The angle of the block has to be...
extremely specific then.
Oh, come on.
I'm blocking!
Oh,
that didn't work.
I'm on fire.
No, I'm not.
I'm block...
Oh!
Ok, so I cannot...
block the over...
overhead one.
That's good to know.
Oh!
Wow.
I'm blocking.
Oh!
Sorry, I just realized which one it was.
I'm blocking!
Yeah, yeah.
What's that?
Yeah, you scared of my...
Don't laugh at me.
Don't laugh at me, Solidus.
I'm blocking!
What the?
Why did you block back?
I'm on fire.
I'm blocking!
Oh!
I'll never learn my lesson.
Yeah, you afraid of my sword?
Why do you look so tiny in that thing?
Why is he look...
Is he really that small?
Is Raiden really that tall?
I can't...
I can't tell.
Oh my god.
Ok, if it's the other side...
he's gonna sweep me.
But if it's the left side...
he's gonna...
Oh!
Like that!
See?
Ok, ok, ok.
I'm just testing...
how to get used to...
Ok, ok.
Ok.
I'm blocking!
Hang in there, Minto.
Thank you.
Oh!
I guess I should probably like...
Yeah!
Triple...
Oh, I can't see myself.
Oh my god.
Can't block those!
What's wrong with you?
Solidus is 5'11 according to Google.
What?
He's not tall?
But he look...
How tall is Raiden then?
I'm blocking.
And you're blocking too.
And I'm blocking.
And you're blocking.
I've got you in a corner.
Oh shoot!
You swept me!
You side swept me!
And I'm blocking.
And you're blocking.
Not fair!
I'm blocking.
And you're blocking!
Oh!
And I'm blocking!
And you're blocking!
Oh my God!
Oh!
I'm blocking!
And you're blocking!
And I'm blocking!
And then you block!
And then...
I probably shouldn't stand so close to the guy.
I'm blocking and then you're blocking.
How could you even triangle it?
Like how can you...
Maybe if I...
Oh, shoot.
I'm blocking.
Oh, no.
I never learned my lesson.
It's so unfair.
There we are.
I'm just chipping away.
And I block and you block.
And I block.
I'm blocking.
Yeah.
What?
Oh!
Oh, nice.
I'm blocking and you're blocking.
I'm blocking.
Yeah, maybe we could do that the entire rest of the...
Oh, shoot.
Oh, you missed.
And I'm...
Shit, I missed too.
Oh.
God,
I can't...
I can't see.
Oh, God.
Oh, how did I make it?
How did I live?
Oh.
I'm blocking and you're blocking.
Nice.
Do
I have any rations left?
No.
The game says get good.
Get good, lady.
One more.
Nice.
I'm blocking.
You're running away.
Yup.
Oh, we're standing here.
Get him.
Oh.
Wait.
Phase two?
Phase two.
Oh.
I realize that I don't like to play with swords.
Where was I?
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Uh-oh.
No, no.
Please, Solidus.
I don't have any more.
I don't have any more rations.
I'm going to bleed out, Solidus.
Solidus, I'm going to bleed out.
I'm going to bleed out.
Solidus?
Solidus, I'm going to bleed out.
I'm going to bleed out, Solidus.
Oh, God.
I'm going to bleed out.
Solidus, I'm going to bleed out.
I'm going to bleed out, Solidus.
Ouch.
Oh, God.
Solidus, I'm going to bleed out.
I'm going to bleed out, Solidus.
Ouch.
Oh, God.
1 HP and a dream!
Yeah!
I would like to thank Honeywater.
You are lost.
Thank you, Urban.
Thank you!
Okay, someone should really get right in some bandages.
You got animated.
It's only when we're backed into our toughest corners.
What does he say there?
I think he says, it's the crazy frog.
Honeywater.
Bleeds out mid cutscene.
07.
Oh, so good!
You know how to make a boss battle exciting.
Yeah, totally was on purpose.
David, thank you for the vibe gifted.
Thank you.
I want to go there and I want to lay where Solidus died.
Great job, boss.
Thank you, Andrangus.
Thank you!
Yay, we beat it today, you guys!
Yippee!
Oh, man.
Struggles.
Struggled quite a bit in the last two moments, but that's okay.
Last two fights, rather.
Yippee!
Coding boomers.
Who am I, really?
No one quite knows who or what they are.
Snake!
This ending is so trippy.
The memories you have and the rules you were assigned are burdens you had to carry.
It doesn't matter if they were real or not.
That's never the point.
It is real.
There's no such thing in the world as absolute reality.
Most of what they call real is actually fiction.
What you think you see is only as real as your brain tells you it is.
Then, what am I supposed to believe in?
Whatever you want to.
What am I going to leave behind when I'm through?
Believe in whatever you want to believe in.
You can tell other people about having faith.
What we had faith in.
New York.
What we found important enough to fight for.
It's not whether you were right or wrong, but how much faith you were willing to have.
That decides the future.
The Patriots are a kind of ongoing fiction, too.
Come to think of it.
Make the victory all more rewarding.
Congrats, Pinto.
Thank you.
Don't obsess over words so much.
Find the meaning behind the words, then decide.
It didn't feel like I was going to win because I kept saying, I'm going to bleed out, Solidus.
Decide for myself, and whatever you choose will be you.
I don't know if I can.
I know you didn't have much in terms of choices this time.
But everything you felt, thought about during this mission is yours.
And what you decide to do with them is your choice.
So what did Raiden do?
What did he do in between being a child soldier and this?
Give a recap of what happened?
Sure.
I could try.
It's a little funky, you know?
By the way, what is that?
Bull!
My dog tag!
Thank you.
I'm going to...
Ah!
Vito!
That's my birthday!
Yeah, it's me.
What?
Raiden!
I'll pick my own name and my own life.
I'll find something more fascinating.
I'll pick my own name continues being Raiden.
They taught me some good things, too.
I'm getting freaked out seeing my name in the tags after forever.
I've inherited freedom from all those who fought for it.
We all have the freedom to spread the word.
Even me.
Snake, what about Olga's child?
Don't worry.
I'll find it.
Count on it.
As long as you keep yourself alive, he's safe.
Do you know where Liquid went?
I put a transmitter on his reg.
I don't think Snake knew the gender of the kid, right?
But I have a feeling they gave Ocelot a bogus location to begin with.
You know.
Cheer up.
We have a better lead.
This contains the list of all the Patriots.
But Ocelot took it.
The one we gave you wasn't the real thing.
I'm just going to hold it up in public, you know?
This virus is coded to destroy only a specific part of GW.
Namely, the information about the Patriots' identity.
Which means that there's a parameter coded in here that defines what that information is.
I get it.
Analyze the code and you can probably find out where they operate.
Count me in.
No.
You have things to do first.
You have a lady to please.
And people you need to talk to.
And a lady... to talk to.
Okay, everybody just go about your business.
Don't worry about the dead president behind the statue.
Rose!
We're just going to...
She's like, howdy!
You've got furniture to buy.
Rose!
His skull suit in this part looks so... it looks so much like the sneaking suit in 3.
Herbert!
What's wrong?
A lot of things, actually.
She isn't an AI.
No, she's real.
Who am I, really?
I wouldn't know.
Happy boots?
But we're going to find out together, aren't we?
It's better for your circulation.
Smoosher.
See me for what I am, okay?
A dummy...
I know.
What are you?
An idiot sandwich.
Oh my god, the baby.
There's still more cutscenes and then when the credits play.
Do you remember this place?
Oh god.
Of course.
This is where we first met.
I remember now.
Today is the day I met you.
That's it.
How could you forget?
Happy April 30th, everybody.
Oh,
happy birthday to my favorite idiot guy.
My favorite idiot couple.
I mean, you're having a baby.
You passed along...
You're passing along plenty.
Are you talking about the baby?
Yeah.
But genes aren't the only thing you pass on.
There are too many things that aren't written into our DNA.
Rose, I...
It's up to us to teach them to our children.
I made history.
I killed a president.
An ex-president.
What kind of things?
About the environment.
Our ideas.
Our culture.
Poetry.
Compassion.
Sorrow.
Joy.
Oh, sorrow and joy.
We'll tell them everything together.
Is that a...proposal?
This is for your ears only.
Yay!
Rizden.
Oh my gosh.
Don't worry.
There's still more to go.
There's still more talking.
Oh wait, it's after the credits.
Just kidding.
Um...
Yippee!
What am I made of?
Am I full of sorrow?
Am I hurt and pain?
Or am I filled with love?
Yay!
Kojima and Tomokazu Fukushima!
Yeah!
Tomokazu Fukushima!
Fukushima-san!
Thank you for...
Thank you for guiding Kojima.
Thank you.
Love watching your playthroughs every time.
Thank you!
Bye.
Okay, after the credits.
After we get back to the main...
The main menu, I'll explain for people who are like, I don't know what's happening.
I'm so confused.
Killed the ex-president and was assaulted by the current president.
Who can top that?
M was there for the current president's death too!
What a grim Reaper.
Thanks for playing one of the best games.
The best Metal Gear games I have loved.
I wonder where that Plissken fellow went.
I miss him too.
Yeah, me too.
Out of the MGS game songs, where would you rate this one?
Better than the best is yet to come?
They each make me feel something different, you know?
I love this one because I just really love jazz.
But it also just makes me... I don't know.
Each game's theme song makes me feel something different.
This song and the feels... I know.
But I really do love this one a lot.
I
put it above Heaven's Divide, but not Calling to the Night.
I really do like Calling to the Night.
A lot, a lot.
I think, like, 1 and 2's themes...
I don't want to say themes.
Like, they're songs.
Really make me feel, like, this nostalgia.
Are free.
Little sounds of laughter.
A warm hug.
A smile.
A kiss.
From you to me.
I've fallen tiny.
Again, they all make me feel something different.
I cry and I cry.
Lost.
Me, Bob.
This day.
For a while.
Chris Zimmerman!
Yeah!
Voice-over director Chris Zimmerman!
She is such a genius at directing.
My god.
Say goodbye to yesterday, my friend.
Yippee!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Chris the goat.
And her husband is awesome.
I miss a lot.
Yeah, yeah.
Patrick Zimmerman.
Revolver.
Power couple.
Oh, ex-husband!
So, I'm so sorry.
My bad.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Anyway.
Yesterday.
Double-crossed again.
No, no, no.
Planning, game design, Hideo Kojima!
Yoji Shinkawa!
Yeah!
Tomokazu Fukushima!
Look at all those people in the script.
Crazy.
Crazy, crazy.
And what a crazy script it is.
What a crazy script!
It is.
So crazy.
Nakagawa Shoko?
Not like Shokotan, right?
No.
Right?
Skateboarding theme!
Yeah!
Wait.
It...
Wait, is it actually Shokotan?
No.
Wait.
I don't think so.
What year?
Ghost Babble.
Wait, I don't remember seeing a Ghost Babble poster.
Oh wait.
Was it in the...
The...
Yeah, she would have been really young.
Yeah.
Cause she's in like her mid-thirties now, I believe.
This game came out what?
2001?
Yeah.
I don't know.
I think she would have been too young.
That's a funny...
Funny, uh...
Coinkydinkto.
Congrats Minto!
Seven hours of grinding through some struggles you pushed your way through frustration and finished it today!
Yippee!
Thanks for another awesome MGM stream!
Thank you!
Okay.
Let's finish it up.
Ah, this song is so good.
Rose is real and Raiden had a girlfriend.
That's the most unbelievable part.
I mean, he's a good looking guy.
He's just gotta work on his personality.
Memes!
These are the things I will pass on.
That's what I live for.
We need to pass the torch and let our children read our messy and sad history by its light.
We have all the magic of the digital age to do that with.
The human race will probably come to an end sometime and new species may rule over this planet.
The Earth may not be forever, but we still have the responsibility to leave what traces of life we can.
Building the future and keeping the past alive are one and the same thing.
He's so awesome.
He's so wise.
Snake.
Solid snake.
The squirrels will rule.
Is this implying the squirrels will inherit the Earth?
One second.
Snake, you there?
It's me.
I've finished going over that disk.
Did you find the Patriot's List?
Of course.
It contains the personal data of 12 people.
There was a name on it.
Snake, it was one of our biggest contributors.
What's going on around here?
I don't know.
Anyway, where are they?
Well, we were right about them being on Manhattan, but...
But what?
They're already dead.
All 12 of them.
What?
When did it happen?
Well, about a hundred years ago.
What the hell?
Oh my god.
Wow, I saved and continued the same amount of times.
I killed 72 persons!
But I only alerted 16 times.
It's not so bad.
I've already done that a lot of times.
Suwako, wait, you could call an emergency man.
Bye, beaut.
When would they leave this mothership?
By the time I just left this place, they'd left.
I don't trust you.
I know what's going on down there.
Bye, beaut.
legislative order.
No one wants to know what's going to happen at the computing lab.
Nice.
What did I get?
Yay!
I got the camera!
Yube!
Yay!
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
And now the screen changes to Raidu.
God, this music, this title music is so...
It sets the tone of the game so well.
Oh my god.
I love MGS2!
MGS2 so much!
I'm going to press the start button though so we don't loop through the...
Oh my gosh, Raid!
I never noticed him there.
Unless he wasn't there before.
I don't know.
Such a good game.
So good.
Freaky Elephant sounds like an MGSV codename for a random guy you recruit.
Truly.
So yeah.
The end of the game is pretty wacky, huh?
There were some people maybe who...
Sorry it took so long.
The ending cutscenes are so, so long.
Some people who are just like watching for the first time and are just like, I'm so confused.
So basically...
From what we learned in this game...
Solidus had this thing called the S3 plan.
In which he was training child soldiers...
To try and become...
Like...
Solid...
To become...
Like a solid snake.
Right?
They want to see if people can become...
Like...
Oh.
Wait, what?
Yeah, mini snakes.
They all wanted little...
Or the Patriots.
Sorry.
Well, solid...
Okay, hold on.
Sorry, my brain is so mush right now.
Okay, so...
Hold on.
Because there were multiple S3 plans, you know?
There were multiple S3 plans.
Everybody had their own, basically.
Everybody had their own S3 plan, you guys.
Because they already...
They all talked about it.
Ocelot had one.
Solidus had one.
And the Patriots had one.
So...
That's why it's kind of weird.
And...
Do you have one?
Hmm...
What would my S3 plan be?
Does Olga's baby have one?
Yeah.
Olga's baby had one.
I think everybody should have an S3 plan.
Everybody, start feeding your children gunpowder.
Okay?
Super sexy snakes.
Yeah, basically.
But anyway, Solidus was raising his little girl.
And he wanted his child soldiers to become...
You know?
Powerful?
And if they could become...
You know, if they're raised in a certain condition, if they can become...
Like...
Snake?
And...
Then Ocelot was just like, Actually, I double-crossed you.
Solidus' thing was just like...
Yeah...
Yeah.
Raised in certain conditions...
And Ocelot was like, actually, I double-crossed you.
This whole video game was my S3 plan.
And actually, the whole big shell was the S3 plan, because it was exactly like Shadow Moses!
And then the Patriots' S3 plan is just like... what?
It's the sanity thing.
I don't even know how to describe it.
Where does the White House soup come in?
The primordial soup.
Yeah, nature versus nurture, then mind control.
Their sanity plan.
But we find out that basically...
Colonel the whole time was part of this program called GW, which is part of the Patriots.
And...
is this AI that... the Patriots are like this overseeing AI or group of people that...
that are able to control everything, I guess, in the world.
And what they really want is, because the digital age is rising, they want to control digital media.
Before they were able to control stuff, but now that digital stuff is becoming more prominent, they were like, we must control the digital media as well!
So...
I don't think Mint knows what she's saying.
What?
What are you talking about?
I know what I'm talking about!
They want to moderate Twitter.
Yes, they want to moderate Twitter.
And...
So Raiden, from just being a little baby, he was always basically just...
He never was able to make his own decisions.
And he thought that falling in love with Rose was his own decision.
And no, she was a plant!
And she does actually exist.
But...
The Rose at the very end, when she's like talking, going back and forth with the Colonel, that's AI Rose.
She's not real.
But up until then, she's real, you know?
But he can do flips!
Wasn't Rose AI the whole time?
No, I don't think so.
I thought she was only AI at the very end.
I mean...
If so...
They trained that AI so well.
They made that AI insufferable.
Yeah, real Rose is cut off after she says she's pregnant.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
She's real up until that point.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And so...
Yeah.
That's basically it.
That's really it.
Solidus was just like, no!
I want to...
I want to be remembered!
So he didn't want to be erased by the Patriots.
Essentially, I guess.
I don't know.
And so...
He was like, down with the Patriots!
And...
Am I real?
Does GW win?
I mean...
At the end of this?
Kind of, yeah.
GW does kind of win at the end of this.
The Patriots got what they wanted because they wanted Solidus dead.
And they got it.
But they had the virus in them.
So...
You know.
They had the virus...
The virus was kind of like, seeping through them.
So...
Yeah.
But there's other Patriots.
So...
They proved the S3 plan could work.
I know.
We're all just...
We're all just pawns.
And the Patriots was planned.
So if anything bad...
Bad ever happens to you...
Don't blame yourself.
Blame the Patriots.
For it's their fault.
I don't understand but pog.
What?
How?
I don't know how much easily...
How much more easily I can explain it to be honest.
Why did they say that the Patriots died a hundred years ago though?
Well...
We'll have to play the other games to find out.
It's a mystery.
This is why we need the MJS podcast?
No.
Explain in the form of a caffeinated karaoke stream.
I need...
Actually I don't need any caffeine right now.
I'm ready.
I'm like...
My eyes are droopy.
Patriots are basically the physical embodiment of the memes.
That's what they meant by...
They are American culture.
They're the memes.
Was the Colonel at any point part of the Patriots?
Like...
The Colonel...
The Colonel in this game?
The Colonel in this game the entire time was GW.
Are you playing MJS 3 on PS2?
Yeah.
Oh yes.
I am actually.
I will be playing...
Subsistence.
You're...
So...
We'll get that hidden cutscene that happens in MJS 3.
The game within a game.
Thank you.
Bye.
Something I really love about this game is how the theme of censorship and controlling information is exactly what they did with Raiden and hiding his existence from all commercials and from...
Whoa!
Yeah!
You're right!
So meta.
Patriots stressed out and overworked by Oshii.
Unforgivable.
But yeah, I'll be playing...
I'll be playing the PS2 version.
It's funny because I was just like, oh, if I'm going to be gone in Japan for a whole month and I won't have like my PS2 or anything like that.
What if I played the 3DS version?
But...
The 3DS version of Metal Gear Solid 3.
But I was like, I don't think I want to put myself through...
the torture probably.
Even though Patriot's AI speech is relevant today, I'd say Snake's final speeches are also very important to learn and use in our lives.
So true!
Snake is so wise.
He's so awesome.
I love Snake.
Oh my PS2 clock battery!
Oh, you're right!
I don't think it's dead.
I think I'll...
I'm just gonna probably put it...
on like a random date and see what happens.
I think it's getting mixed up because it's going back and forth between 1999 and 2000.
It's kind of weird.
Snake is very philosophical.
I know!
Solid Snake is like really...
He's such a good person.
I love that guy.
I'm so tired.
I wish I was tired.
Yay!
We did it!
Yippee!
Metal Gear Solid 2!
I was wondering if I'd be able to do it today, but I was like, I don't know.
There's really not that much left of the game after...
from where we were at, you know?
So...
This weekend is Otakuthon.
So I will be there.
So...
A bit of...
A bit of a shorter streaming week.
I'm so sorry.
My streams are all...
Everything is so whack lately.
And then as soon as I get back from Otakuthon, I am going straight to Japan.
So it's kind of...
But I will be bringing all my stuff.
And I will be streaming in Japan.
And I have checked...
I've double...
Triple-checked my hotels.
I will be able to stream there.
So...
Yes, yes, yes.
It's going to be my first con ever.
Oh my gosh!
So exciting!
Thank you!
Thanks for going.
Congrats with you with finishing one of my favorite MGS games.
I can still remember screaming like a monkey when Raiden got the sword.
I wish the sword never happened.
So...
It's so icky.
It's the hottest summer in recent years in Japan.
Good luck.
Ugh.
It's okay.
I'll deal.
I actually don't know if I'll be going out that much so...
It's okay though.
Thank you!
I'm happy to see one of my all-time favorite games completed.
The sword is cool, controlling it...
Yeah.
I love hack and slash.
Once I just started blocking, though, it was great!
I would block, and then he would block, and then I would block, and then he would block, and then I would block, and then he would block...
Until MGS4 came out, my friends had a theory that everything after Raiden got knocked out was a fever dream.
It held for seven years.
That would then be such a stinky ending, though, right?
It was all just a dream.
No, that's the biggest cop-out.
This is the part where I plug the MGS2 analysis driving off the map.
It really made me appreciate the game's design choices, and the writer later got to work on MGS4 among some other Metal Gears.
Oh!
Thank you, I'll look into it.
A VR simulation.
What if we're all just... this is the Matrix.
Kojima watched the Matrix and was like, Hmm, yeah.
How about like that?
Oh, man.
I think we can canonize I'm bleeding out solidus as a code word.
A code word for what?
Raiden didn't avoid drowning and died when trying to enter the Big Shell!
Oh my gosh, that's a real...
That's some real...
Conspiracy theory.
I'm bleeding out solidus.
I'm bleeding out for perseverance.
Anytime you guys are feeling like you're...
You're about to...
You don't think you can make it...
I'm bleeding out solidus.
Hoo-ha!
So...
For this is the run.
Watching you play this game after having played it myself just barely February this year made me go like...
Oh, from like...
From... wait.
Like to love?
Because of all the stuff you freak out about.
It's so easy to freak out about this game.
It's so great.
Oh!
I wish we could have gotten more Jack and Rose drama.
So blows my mind how much Kojima predicted regarding AI.
I know, right?
Censorship.
So on in the finale.
Yeah.
I mean...
Yeah, it's pretty crazy.
I guess...
Back then...
With the internet being so new, you could probably look at it and be like...
Well, what if this happens?
You know, like...
What if...
What if people start using...
The internet in this way?
Freaky.
What rank did Mito get?
I got...
I got elephant.
As I...
As expected.
I got elephant.
But I only had 16 alerts.
I think that's not so bad.
Patriots, thank you for your service in perfecting the sword blocking simulation.
Thanks, Avril.
Okay.
Well, guys, it's been eight and a half hours.
Thank you for this fun little endurance stream.
I'm gonna go now and sign more postcards.
I'm gonna go sign more postcards and I will catch you later.
See you guys.
I will probably make a schedule for this week.
I will try to make one as...
I will try to make a schedule while I'm gone as well.
Maybe not with specific games, but at least with like times and things like that.
So...
So that we can have some semblance of normalcy.
I think next week might have to be mostly no streams.
Mostly.
I will try once I'm in Japan and stuff.
But there's also VEXPO.
So...
And the concert with Doki.
It's...
It'll be more outside events than streams, I believe.
Yeah, I will be attending the conventions from Japan.
So...
You might get a really sleepy meantime.
Nah...
I'm so hyped.
I'm super excited.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But...
Once...
Once things calm down...
Like I said...
August is...
Pretty really crazy.
But starting September...
Things seem to slow down a bit.
I have a few more events.
That I have planned.
Um...
Some outside of the USA.
And um...
Uh...
But...
I shouldn't be traveling for them.
So I should still be able to like...
Be around them.
And such...
Hmm...
Sorry that...
I overbooked myself.
My math teacher always said...
In order to catch an elephant...
You gotta dig a hole.
Fill it with wood.
Wait...
A hole, what?
Burn the wood and put peanuts around the hole.
Then when the elephant goes to pick up a peanut...
You kick it in the...
In the ash hole.
Does this work?
What is this...
What is this joke?
Just hope you get enough rest.
Yeah, yeah.
I will.
Will the podcast MGS episode happen after the series is done for Bug Mom?
Well, I don't think she's gonna finish it in time.
She...
She's...
She hasn't even touched it.
So...
I don't...
I don't know.
But...
It'll still happen.
Yeah.
I think we're just gonna talk about...
Kind of...
I think I'm mostly gonna like...
Kind of remind her what she's been through so far.
And maybe her theories on...
About future games.
I'm gonna make...
I mean it'll be...
Spoilers for just MGS 1 and 2.
And then the beginning of 3.
Since that's all she's played.
So...
Yeah.
I'll have to censor myself...
A lot.
But we'll hear what her theories are.
And...
Things like that.
So...
Talk about the culture and the experience.
Yeah.
Talk about like...
You know.
What she's looking forward to.
And...
Things like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okie dokie.
Alrighty guys.
I'm gonna go.
Thank you guys.
Love to hear your MGS con review.
Yes!
Of course.
I'm gonna go.
Otsuminto everybody!
Thank you so much for...
For...
Cheering me on!
And pushing me...
To finish...
Through...
And everything.
I really appreciate it.
I'll see you guys tomorrow if I see you.
And if not...
I'll catch you when I catch you.
And...
Yeah!
Otsuminto!
Thank you!
Get some rest.
Thank you so much for watching.
I really, really, really appreciate it!
And I'll see you guys...
Next time!
Itterashai!
Bye bye!