I can't do it anymore.
I can't listen to this song anymore.
I can't do this anymore.
Please.
Oh my god.
It's just been beep beep beep.
Beep...
Beep beep beep beep...
I can't do it anymore!
Ok, have you guys enjoyed the title screen enough?
Ok...
Yay!
Hello Everybody!
Hi!
Peace and quiet.
I had to turn the sound down so low.
Genuine tip for feeling sick.
Rub a little rubbing alcohol around your nostrils.
Also face bump your cat.
Guaranteed treatment for any illness.
No, I don't know.
I ate and then I was like...
I don't know.
My head started hurting.
Weird.
But speaking of my cat.
Yesterday I took him to the vet.
And he got poked.
And he got prodded.
And he...
Do you guys like the new emotes?
You guys are just spamming it.
I'm glad that you guys like it.
They're so good.
I'm glad you guys like it.
I'm glad.
Yes.
Dear Moodment, please consider playing Strong Bad's cool game for attractive people.
This summer, you fit the demographic.
Crapfully yours.
Let me tell a story about my cat.
And then we'll talk more about Strong Bad.
I took him to the vet yesterday.
And I got him a bunch of tests done.
Not really a bunch.
Just like an overall...
Well, it was like a big test for senior cats.
Last time I mentioned him.
I was like, I smelled his little head.
And it smelled sweet.
And I was scared because cats smelling sweet is sometimes a sign of diabetes.
So I was like, oh no.
And I took him.
And they were like, wow, he's down two pounds.
Which they were a little concerned about.
But I have him on a diet.
Because last time, the time before I took him, they were like, he needs to lose weight.
So...
You know, he's down a little bit.
Um...
It's scary when pets lose weight.
Yeah, but they...
Um...
The doctor checked him yesterday and was just like...
I don't know.
I don't see anything wrong with it.
Or rather, I don't hear anything.
I don't notice anything.
So we'll send the tests in.
And we'll give you the results tomorrow.
I also had to reach into his litter box.
And take some poop.
So...
It was a really shitty day.
No, I'm just kidding.
Um...
Get it?
That's what happens when you...
When you...
When you have a pet.
Literally.
But...
When I went and got his lab results...
The doctor there...
She was like, oh my gosh.
Your cat is like...
First of all, every time I take him to the vet...
The vet...
And the technicians and everyone...
Everyone is like...
He is so good.
He's like the best cat I've ever worked with.
He just stands there and lets you do anything.
He doesn't fight.
He is so good.
He doesn't bite.
He doesn't scratch.
He's so sweet.
And I was like, yeah, I know.
Everybody tells me that.
He's my good boy.
But...
He's pregnant.
Close.
Oh my gosh.
So close.
Today...
The doctor was like...
We were oohing and aahing at your cat's results.
He is like...
The pinnacle of healthy...
For a cat his age.
He is so healthy.
Like...
There was nothing with diabetes.
Not even a worry.
Like...
He is...
My vet called my cat...
An unholy terror.
Yeah.
So they were like...
Nothing.
His heart is good.
His kidneys are good.
Everything is good.
We just have to look at his poop and make sure there is nothing wrong there.
But...
He passed.
Yeah.
He is healthy.
Yippee.
So I felt...
I felt so much relief after that.
Especially because she was so enthusiastic about it.
She was like...
He is so healthy.
And I was like...
He is a bit of a butthole.
But that's okay.
Diagnosis stinky.
True.
Did he pass gas?
You know...
He has been farting a lot recently.
It's...
You know...
He is just...
Ghost cats are a little gassier than others.
I suppose.
But...
Thank you.
Can we get a butaro...
A butaro emo.
I will think about making one.
Maybe.
Yeah.
But yeah.
Anyway.
Sorry.
That's just a side...
I know I am talking in absolute silence right now.
I just couldn't keep the gaming...
That opening music.
on any longer.
Hope you feel better Min.
Thank you.
Based on the title though.
Which of these should I watch next?
Outlaws, To the Ends of the Earth, Super Dark Times, The Mimic.
I think The Mimic sounds interesting.
Or To the Ends of the Earth.
But I like The Mimic.
So...
Thank you.
Your cat won it.
Cat.
Here is cat money for the cat.
Thank you.
You know Yoko.
Your donuts makes so much more sense than they used to.
Dear Min Min.
How do you type with your sleeves over your hands?
Your super chatter.
Charo666 Well Charo.
This is how I type.
And then I punch the screen.
Super awesome punching.
Ba ba ba ba ba ba.
That's my...
That's my impression of Strong Min.
Deleted.
Strong Min.
Andragos thanks for the 10 gifted.
And KM thank you so much for the ping.
Oh wait.
You asked this.
Dear Strong Min.
How do you type with those big dorking sleeves over your hands?
Thankfully yours bent over.
Deleted.
Teen girl squad.
Cheerleader.
What's her face?
How do I make a voice that sounds like Strong Bad trying to talk like a teenage girl.
So as a kid I watched so much Homestar Runner.
Oh my goodness.
I watched way so much Homestar Runner.
And I played this game quite a bit.
I don't remember at all how to beat it but I would like to try and get like I think with 150 points I would like to try and get every every little drop out of this game that we can get.
Thank you for the memberships.
Thank you.
Kenki Thank you.
Glad to hear he's alright.
I wanted to let you know that Streamer Life Simulator is free on Fanatical right now in case you needed any more games.
Streamer Life Simulator?
I mean I'm afterlife.
Like I'm dead so if I do a life sim it is it is I mean so if I um I don't get it.
Come on.
Wait I wait that's another reference isn't it?
I remember but I don't remember at the same time.
Your impression of Strong Bad doing a teen girl voice is so good.
And you keep it up so well.
Dear Strongman, I love you.
I think I once wrote into Strong Bad emails.
I think I once did.
But it never got chosen.
I'm so sad.
I wonder if he still accepts them.
Oh my gosh.
Thank you for the pink.
Strong Bad has the cheat.
Strong Maid has the chat.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
I'm a super chat from the 60s.
Here's a few things I remember from Strong Bad emails.
I remember the one when he makes an anime about himself.
He gives him the awesome blue hair.
I remember the The system is down.
The system is down.
Stinko man.
Oh my gosh.
Legitimate business.
Yes.
He has the rave when he makes the song.
Dear Strong Bad.
What would you look like as a Japanese cartoon?
And what would it be about?
Well.
If I was a Japanese cartoon.
I would be super boobylicious.
With a bubble butt.
And I remember the song about the cheat.
The cheat.
Strong?
What's strong?
Armstrong?
No.
Stop.
Please.
Metal Gear and Home Star Runner.
How can one ghost be so cultured?
Stop.
Toons.
Games.
Email.
Why is this so ingrained in my brain?
Oh my gosh.
Downloads.
Why is it so ingrained into my brain?
Characters.
Oh no.
Mint, you've always made my day better in life.
Without you it was ghastly, but now that you're back I feel like I'm in mint condition.
Love ya.
Thanks.
Limousine or sloshy?
I
don't remember.
The original brain rot.
Oh my gosh.
It was so much fun.
Actually, I think I tried to get my friends into Home Star Runner, but I got into Home Star Runner from another friend when I was a kid.
He and I would do the emails and try to find all the little hidden clickies in it, so that was a lot of fun.
I heard my name.
Well if it isn't Saucy Maid but oh my gosh it's an actual Armstrong.
Hello, Senator.
Oh shoot.
I just realized something.
But it should be okay until after stream.
I am constantly quoting Strong Bad anytime I see a protagonist with blue hair.
But yeah, so Home Star Runner was a huge part of my ghastly childhood.
And so was Peasant's Quest.
So we're gonna play it.
Here's how things work round here.
Tips for not morons.
Beginners.
Look around by typing stuff like look tree or just plain look.
Talk to folks by typing stuff like talk man.
Take items by typing get item.
Use items by typing use item.
You can also give item, throw item or some other action words.
Type in to see your inventory.
Type save to save your game and load to load one.
What?
You can save and load games?
To save games your browser must have cookies enabled.
Press plus and minus to speed up or slow down your character.
Okay.
Wait.
Hold on.
Can I turn off the music?
No.
No, I'm not even reading it.
Hold on.
No, I can't do this anymore.
Please.
No.
I can't do this anymore.
Please.
Maybe...
Hold on.
I will...
You can start playing in a second.
Here.
Maybe it doesn't play the whole game, right?
Go for it.
Oh!
Yes!
Okay, I'm gonna restart that.
I'm gonna restart that so we can...
I'll read it to you guys.
Never felt so young until now.
Tongue looks like a thong?
Oh, my God.
Now that you say that, it really does kind of look like a thong.
No, I didn't want it to be that...
I didn't want it to be that sexy.
Okay, here we go.
Beep.
Okay, okay, okay.
Alright, let me read now this.
Hayden, thank you so much for the 10 gifts.
Thank you!
You are rather dashing.
Oh, thank you.
A humble peasant living in the peasant kingdom of peasantry.
You return home from a vacation on Scalding Lake only to find that Trogdor, the Burninator,
That's a nice looking lake.
You can start playing in a second here.
Oh, my thatched roof cottages.
Thatched roof cottages!
Hello, sir.
Oh, talk.
You explain your situation to the knight.
That Trogdor burninated your cottage, and you have sworn revenge.
You ask for passage to the mountain to settle your score.
Hang on there, Trogdorkilla, says the knight.
I can only allow actual peasants up the mountain pass to face Trogdor, and you clearly are not one.
Look, dragon heart.
Fine, thanks for the tiny gift, and thank you.
You don't stink like a peasant.
You don't dress like a peasant.
Actually, I feel like I do dress like a peasant.
And you are definitely not on fire like a peasant.
Once those three things come back, and maybe we can talk.
Be sure to look around lots.
Talk to everyone you see and ask about stuff.
Type help if you get confused in inventory to see your worldly stuff.
Load your game, duh.
Oh my gosh.
If I just walk, I don't stop.
Look at me, I'm so dashing.
Do I need to put on some BGM for this game?
Actually, I don't know why I thought there might be BGM, but...
Here I go.
I'm walking here.
I can't stop walking.
Actually, is there...
Oh, there is a way to stop.
I'm going in.
I'm going down.
Man!
Look.
Why, it's half a lake.
With a fisherman in it.
And he's fishing.
Yell.
Oh.
Talk.
You holler at the old man about Trogdor, but he just grumbles about the fish not biting.
Must be the wrong...
I must be using the wrong bait.
He says...
Oh, sorry.
Must be using the wrong bait.
He says suggestively.
Can I fish?
Fish.
Swim.
Damn.
How do you say that suggestively?
Okay, I'm going to put on a little bit of BGM real quick.
Because it's kind of quiet.
Unless you guys don't have...
It's basically a podcast at this point.
Or I can sing the song again.
But...
Oh, the press and minus.
Thank you.
Oh.
Oh, we're so fast.
Nice.
Where's my music?
Oh, here we go.
What do you guys want to listen to?
Let's listen to some cool...
Some chill music.
Cool.
This isn't really fit the vibe.
But just pretend it's like after school.
And you're on your like Windows 98.
Actually, I don't know when this game came out.
I don't know if it's older or newer.
But...
And you're playing.
And it's old.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, yeah.
We're speedy now.
Wait.
Is this my house?
Eat.
Take berries.
You probably wish you could get that.
Oh, dang.
Okay.
What's here?
Knock?
It's open.
Oh, all right.
Says a female voice from inside.
It's not open.
But you get her drift.
Open.
You open her up and head on in.
Yeah.
Oh, she's got a baby.
Talk.
Hello.
I'm...
You start.
But the lady cuts you off.
Okay.
Here's why I let you in here.
She explains.
My husband got squished by Trogdor.
And to make matters worse, the insurance riches I got were just stolen by the jonka.
Go steal them back for us and I'll give you something great.
ViviCore, thanks for the gift.
I never thought I'd see you play Baldur's Gate 3.
You're welcome.
I'll give you a gift.
Yeah, I think we're gonna go see Asterion.
Take...
No.
Talk.
Oh, okay.
It's a take.
Grab.
Look.
What a depressing little cottage.
It reeks of single parent.
I mean...
Oh my gosh.
They said he is rather dorky.
Or dashing.
But they never said he is rather classy.
Dang.
Oh my gosh.
A lady rocks her baby in a chair.
A mostly empty shelf sits against one wall.
Mm-hmm.
Sav...
Rather savage.
For real.
Um...
What's this?
Can I sleep?
That's probably how the first baby got here.
Forget it.
What do you mean, by the way?
Look at that.
I...
I mean...
Yeah.
Oh my gosh.
Um...
Take...
What can I say again?
Um...
Look to...
Oh, where?
Where am I?
Where?
You're hanging out in the...
In baby lady cottage.
Can I take baby?
Take baby.
You wanna be part of this family?
Go get it.
Go get us those riches!
She shrieks.
Dang.
What is this, though?
Take...
Take feed?
Oh, you used to eat this stuff like crazy when you were a kid and your parents weren't watching.
Which was all too often.
You grab several large handfuls.
Oh, we got a point!
We got a point!
We have a chicken feed!
All right!
Nice.
Wait.
Can I take...
Okay.
Take pillow.
You don't have anywhere to use it.
Okay.
And it is rather bulky so you leave it.
The baby lady calls after you.
Why don't you...
Calling her the baby lady instead of like...
Mom?
The mom calls after you?
No.
The baby lady.
Well, actually we don't know if she's the mom.
We have no idea.
Hey!
You're on some quest, right?
Well, the little squirt here lost something of mine in the yard the other day.
It's yours if you can find it.
Okay, let's look in the bush then.
Check bush.
Look bush.
You suspect they might be crunch berry bushes.
Take berry.
Okay.
Look bush?
Search bush?
Oh!
You reach into the bush to snag you some berries but they all just squish in your hand.
Okay, here we go.
Search, search.
I really liked the last podcast episode and did that personality quiz and I ended up with the same result as you.
Great minds think alike.
Right?
Search bush.
Nothing in this bush but squished berries either.
Let's check this one.
You guys are so smart at saying search.
Search bush.
Too bad you don't want any squished berries.
Because hey, jackpot.
Maybe I shouldn't be so aggressive.
Search bush.
You reach into the bush to snag you some berries but instead find a super trinket.
Get ye flask.
These things are awesome.
You have a sneaking suspicion that someone in this game will need this thing.
We're at three points already.
Feed.
Oh.
Huh?
You cannot get ye flask.
You can't get ye flask.
But you can't get ye flask.
What do you guys mean?
You can't get ye flask.
What?
Oh, what's our shirt look like?
I bet it's like a boy band or something.
Oh, it's so cute.
This has got to be your favorite t-shirt ever.
Oh, the times you had at Scalding Lake.
Canoeing, fishing, stoning heathens.
What a blast!
What is this thing?
This super trinket is weird.
It looks like it could either kill you or make you the hit of your Christmas party.
Whoa, gold nuggets!
Oh wait, this is just chicken feed.
Crap.
This game is so dumb.
This game is so silly.
Silly.
Sorry.
What was that?
What in the world was that?
I tried getting ye flask.
I could not get ye flask.
I tried and I tried and I tried and you wanna know what happened?
That's right.
I became ghost.
What is the flask?
I'm sorry if you could see my mouse.
Okay.
We'll go this way instead.
Look.
Rushing River.
Black and white.
Yellow tree.
Huh?
What?
Rushing River?
For the river.
Okay.
Dang.
I miss Oregon Trail.
Backed with?
Between?
Everyone's giving me...
Everyone's giving me different answers.
Pee in the river.
Pee in river.
Doesn't understand your strange request.
Wait.
If I go over, is it gonna be that guy again?
Oh.
Look.
There's a really generic well here.
Oh.
And a picture.
Apparently, it's Autumn on this screen.
Well, well, well.
I gotta go for now, men.
But I hope you have a wonderful day and a wonderful stream.
Take care.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Use.
You don't need to use that now.
Crank.
That.
Soldier boy.
Dang.
Okay.
Don't go that way either.
Wait.
Wasn't it up though?
What if I look at...
Oh.
Hold on.
Look!
It's the Carrack, you moron!
Get out of here!
Um.
This is a really creepy screen.
Why does it look like this?
Crank that hog.
Um.
Look.
Nothing special.
Nothing special here except for that weird wavy tree!
Who is that?
Look!
Man!
Talk!
You startle him and he disappears!
Oh god!
Oh my gosh!
What a suspicious...
What a suspicious man!
I remember this part!
I remember this because look!
Move rock.
That!
I remember that.
You slide the stone over to reveal a little hole.
If only you could cut off your arms, legs and head, you might be able to squeeze through.
Yippee!
I remember that one.
I don't remember much of anything else though.
Knock?
You can knock until your knuckles bleed.
Nobody's home.
I'm a ghost.
I can fit through.
You know who could fit through?
The baby.
Oh.
Talk.
Your attempts at conversation are met with horse grunts and tail flaps.
Which is better than you do then...
Which is better than you do...
Which is better than you do a conversation with most people.
Ride.
Pet horse.
That's sweet.
Poor game.
Gary tries in vain to bite your arm off.
Thank you for the dough.
No!
That's a horse?
What is this?
Oh wait, look.
There's a rotten old horse!
It's a horse!
He doesn't look so good though.
Take Gary.
Oh my goodness.
He's probably wishing.
Eat flies?
Oh, there's the flies.
Eat flies.
How hungry.
He looks pretty.
You're hanging out in poor Gary's glen.
Why is he...
Someone take care of Gary so he's not so poor anymore.
Please, don't get kicked.
What's in here?
Search hat.
Sorry.
Sometimes my fingers work in really mysterious ways, you guys.
Sometimes
my fingers work in really, really mysterious ways and I don't know why.
That's after streaming.
Dang it.
You'll probably see me making crazy mistakes all the time.
This whole stream.
Did you find the rainbow?
Did you find anything?
Just some...
Just some edible glitter.
It's your sleeves.
Exactly.
Also the G and the H are right next to each other.
Okay.
You search and search through the haystack.
Nope.
No needles.
Someone had a good idea.
Take hay.
What do you think you are?
Some kind of thigh dungeon man?
You don't need any hay.
Okay.
What about for the horse?
Can I climb this tree?
Climb tree.
But then all your hands will get all sappy.
Oh.
What's this?
Read...
Note.
It says sacred...
Oh.
Scared of Carrick.
Go away.
J.
Okay.
Where am I?
Where?
You're hanging out in Janka...
Oh.
This is where Janka is.
We need to talk to him.
Knock.
A gravely voice inside yells, just us chickens.
Oh.
Okay.
We're back here.
Love the podcast on Thursday.
Love to hear more about your music taste.
My music...
Oh, maybe we could do a music episode.
That'd be fun.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh.
Look.
You have chicken feed.
Wait.
What do you mean the chicken feed?
For us chickens?
There's a dried out mud puddle.
It's all caked up.
And cracked like the kind...
Like the kind that rock stars are always standing on.
What?
I don't...
I don't get it.
Okay.
Here.
What do I do with this chicken feed?
Throw chicken feed.
Use chicken feed.
You don't need to use that now.
Hmm.
My house!
The remains of your thatched roof cottage lie burninated before you.
You swear revenge against Trogdor.
You're hanging out in your burninated cottage.
Mint, if this is how you wanted to come out to us, this is really complicated.
Stop!
One of my manga shelves broke down yesterday and a lot of the manga on that one had black covers so the damage is really noticeable pain.
No!
Oh my gosh.
I'm so scared of that day.
That like my shelf just decides to...
To break.
I hope never.
I have so many doujin.
Oh.
Can I take the berries here?
Take berries.
No!
Man!
Geez!
Why not?
There's definitely half a lake here with a sandy shore.
There's some rocks here though.
Take rocks.
You grab a handful of fairly substantial pebbles.
You make sure to get an even mix of sedentary igneous and surreptitious rocks.
Yeah!
Wait!
Oh!
I know what to do with the chicken feed!
I just...
The guy fishing!
The guy fishing said that nothing was biting.
If we throw the chicken feed here...
Right?
Throw chicken feed.
You toss the feed into the lake.
You shed a tear for each one.
Goodbye, Monty.
Oh!
Goodbye, Delga.
Rasputin.
Farewell, Combaldon.
That's so forth.
Ho ho!
Wow!
That crotchety old man just caught a pantload of fish.
Now I can get back to running the inn, he says and rows to shore and hauls his boat out and cleans guts and filets all the fish and a bunch of other stuff.
We didn't animate.
Yippee!
Oh my gosh!
We're making awesome time.
Oh!
The inn was right here the whole time.
There's a giant inn here.
Takes up, like, the entire screen.
I'm knocking.
Just open it, man!
Open.
Open the door and step inside the inn.
Oh!
He's back!
I'm going in here, too, then.
Open.
Look.
What a dump!
Only one bed and no mini bar?
The innkeeper stands behind a desk and there's a door that's closed.
Open door.
That's the pantry, says the innkeeper.
Employees only.
It's wild how much Skyrim ripped off this game.
I...
Right?
Like, this game is so innovative.
To every... to every game follow...
Like, every game following it has just taken everything from it.
Peasants quest walks so Baldur's Gate 3 could run.
Could we get a job here?
I don't know.
Sleep?
You probably ought to talk to that stinky old guy over there about that.
Okay.
Hello, sir.
I would like to inquire about a job.
If you're interested in staying the night, just type, get a room.
Get a room!
I only serve peasants here, fancy pants, barks the old guy.
Where's your robe?
Why are they so mean to me?
Oh.
What is this?
A single...
A signal lantern.
And of some kind hangs from a severely burninated tree.
Where am I?
I'm at the burninated tree.
Okay.
Nice.
There's a beautiful, magical waterfall cascading down the cliffside.
I'm gonna swim.
That waterfall would probably turn you into one of those weight gain protein smoothies.
So sad.
Burninated?
Oh yeah.
That's what Trogdor does.
He burninates the countryside.
He burninates all the people.
He's burninating all the thatch roof cottages.
Okay, so I need to figure out a way to kill this guy.
Oh, not here.
Where is he?
Is he down one?
Oh!
Hello.
Oh hi.
I'm Mendelev, says the archer.
I used to run a shooting range here with my brother, Dongolev.
But we don't talk so much anymore.
I haven't seen him in a dronka's age.
Have you ever run into him?
Tell him I said, Haldo.
You mean hello?
You ask?
Um, no.
Shut up.
I said Haldo and I met Haldo.
Tell him I said, Haldo.
Dang.
Can I play?
Play game.
The gallery's not open and you got no bow or arrows, Cupid.
Haldo, everybody.
And I said what I said.
Not much to see.
River's got a rock in it.
Take rock.
For what?
Now you're just making up puzzles to solve.
Sorry.
Wait, if I go back here...
And I go up...
Okay, we're here.
This map makes no sense.
Haldo, everybody.
Does this lead to dronka?
No, it leads to mud.
Then this leads to jonka.
No, it leads to hay.
Can you swim here?
I don't know.
I still use Haldo to say hello to my friends.
So crazy.
This game is too influential.
Wait, how do I get him out?
Wait.
Maybe the super trinket.
Or...
Can I throw the pebbles at...
Maybe the...
Maybe I can stone...
That guy to death.
Whatever his name is.
Talk to jonka?
Okay.
Rock and stone.
I thought I tried to talk to him.
Did I not?
Talk.
Talk to...
How do I spell his name?
So glad to see my favorite ghost playing such a great game.
Thanks, Black Knight.
Thank you for the pink.
Thank you.
Wait, how do I...
Talk to...
How do I spell his name?
Oh, there we go.
It's sad when you have to make up people to talk to.
Man.
Person in my chat yelling in all caps.
Dr. jonka.
You're wrong.
Is this it?
Okay.
Okay, hold on.
Throw pebbles.
Stone him.
Death him.
Kill.
Will I die here if I...
Where am I?
Oh, there I am.
I will die?
Slash kill.
Ha ha ha.
Hmm.
I think the guy, he'll want this.
Okay.
Is there anywhere...
Map?
Is there a map?
We are neither confirming nor denying the presence of a map in this game, but irregardless, you don't have one.
Save?
Okay.
Oh.
Oh, it does autosave, you guys.
I think we're okay.
Okay.
But I'll save anyway.
Okay, go away.
Thank you.
What have we...
This one?
Use.
What else can I type here?
Earward...
This...
Regardless.
Okay.
Dock deck.
Welcome to membership.
Thank you.
Turn crank?
Hmm.
It won't budge.
Maybe if there was something heavy in that bucket.
Take bucket?
You can't.
It's tied to a rope and you're terrible with nuts.
Jump in?
Jump.
Dang.
Ha ha ha.
Can you imagine?
Like there's this area here.
Great game choice.
Love home.
Home star runner stuff.
Do you think Strong Bad is a Vtuber?
I think so.
He just used email instead of chat.
Wasn't there a Strong Bad Vtuber that was made though?
Like actually?
Or am I going crazy?
What's above the inn?
Ah.
Wait.
What's up here then?
Ah.
Now we're on the other side.
Oh.
The world is so small and confusing.
Burger buns.
Welcome to membership.
Thank you.
Hmm.
Try and make friends or buy Karak a cold one.
I don't think I even have a place.
Where can I even buy a cold one?
The inn is useless.
Okay.
I need a robe.
Hmm.
We need to...
I think.
Okay.
We need to figure out how we're going to kill this guy.
The Karak.
Did you just prove this world is round?
And small?
So very small.
Call me Galileo.
Magnifico.
Did you try to seduce him?
Seduce him.
Kiss... kiss Archer.
Can I take this?
Take arrow.
They have range printed on them, so it would be kind of embarrassing to have to shoot around with them.
Also, that guy over there is giving you the evil eye.
Hexadise, welcome to the membership.
Thank you.
See, I think the bucket is used for this, right?
We'll get the bucket full of water.
And maybe that's what we need to do, but it won't...
It won't move.
Yeah, we can't get it out.
Use the pebbles.
In the bucket?
I think you're a genius.
Where is it?
What?
Here?
I'm trapped?
Okay.
Game is very specific.
Oh, here we go, here we go, here we go.
Use pebbles.
I'm not supposed to use them for death?
For stoning?
I'm supposed to use them for... for life!
What do you propose to do with them?
Discuss.
Oh.
Put pebbles in bucket.
You plunk all your pebbles into the bucket!
The weight causes it to descend to the bottom of the well with a quickness.
Crank.
Level.
Get to... bucket.
Um...
Raise bucket.
Oh, here we go!
What is that?
The crank seems to have loosened and you haul the bucket back up.
What's this?
Why is there a monster mascus in there?
No doubt left over from some pagan ritual.
Silly pagans.
You grab up the scary monster mascus.
Man, this thing could scare a horse!
Wear mask.
Not on this screen.
You've got to im-im-im-image...
Wait, you've got your...
You've got your image to think about.
Oh, actually you might want to start deliberating on that right now.
To the horse!
To old Gary.
Stinky Gary.
Gary's gonna be really sad about this though, I think.
Sorry.
I can't read you guys, okay?
It's very hard.
With ghost eyes, okay?
I died with poor vision, okay?
Wear mask.
You slip on the hideous monster mas- Oh, wait!
I wanted to see the description of it first.
Oh!
You scared the crap out of poor Gary.
He broke on through to the other side.
Oh my god, it's terrifying.
Man, those pagans sure can make a freaky looking mask when they want to.
It's like those theater masks.
Uncle... evil uncle or something.
Yeah, basically.
I don't know, when I was... this did not happen to me.
But it happened to my sister.
Um... hold on.
My...
Oh!
It's brother!
Wait, can I...
Um, my grandpa went to go pick up my sister.
And...
It was when she was in kindergarten.
And he decided to wear a scary mask.
And barge into the kindergarten.
Going...
And...
He got banned from doing that.
He...
Wasn't allowed to...
Um...
Pick up my sister anymore.
Save...
Save.
What if...
Oh!
Hopefully this guy will have some sense and not shoot you.
That guy has no sense.
He shot you.
Dumb, dumb, dumb.
Nice one, William Tell.
You dead.
Thanks for playing.
Yippee!
Okay.
That was fun.
That was a...
That was a good little...
Okay.
Now we say, Now we say, Now we say, Now we say, Now we say, Please help us top-up our store.
Thank you,
That's it.
One up.
We have reached four, Take us to the arcade!
Oh...
We are leaving The series of We're getting somewhere, you guys!
Now we go back to the archer.
I want to see how they're doing.
Our favorite brothers, look at them!
They're so happy.
Talk.
Haldo, says the brothers, test your skill.
Give us the right super item from your inventory...
and you can give it as many tries as you need.
We have a super item!
Give...
Trinket.
That'll work, says Mendeleev.
Just hit three bullseyes...
and you win the super time fun bow TM!
The arrow keys aim left and right on the space bar operates the bow.
You'll need to press it a couple of times to get a nice shot off.
But we don't give lessons, so you're on your own.
Okay.
I think we'll get it first try.
Oh.
I knew how it worked.
Close!
Oh my gosh, wait, there's wind too.
So we need to go over this way, right?
Like as...
Huh?
Ah!
Did you guys see that?
That...
That was professional gaming?
Professional gaming?
I mean, I told you so.
I told you guys.
I told you guys I would get it first try.
Pro gamer.
I know.
I told you.
I told...
You said you weren't an FPS player.
I just...
You know...
I learned from the best.
Me.
Obviously.
Nice shooting.
Three hits, says Mendeleev.
Here's your prize.
You got the super time fun bow.
T.M.
We don't sell ammo.
So you'll have to find your own arrows for it.
Now we can go kill that guy.
Wait, right?
Wait.
Oh, we see it.
We have an arrow.
Boy, you sure know how to pick them.
This arrow is kind of pointy even.
This is a pretty fancy bow.
You're surprised those shady archers give away such decent prizes.
You have expected goldfish in a bag.
Let's go.
Steel arrows.
Wait, you can do that?
Hold on.
I got to save real quick.
I can't stop coughing today.
I'm so sorry.
Dead eye ghost girl.
Who's the big boss now?
Me.
What do you mean?
Steel arrow.
Oh.
Yeah.
No.
They're still watching me.
Dang.
Pollen?
I think it is pollen.
I think I have a bad allergy.
Yeah.
Coughing Tascaru.
Now.
Hi, Tech.
Welcome to membership.
Thank you.
Let's take some arrows here, I guess.
Do I need them?
Do I need any more?
I think I can one-shot him.
Take arrow.
You're pretty much all set on the arrow front.
They are kind of cool, though.
Okay.
We're confident, you guys.
Have confidence.
We're going to kill this guy.
We're going to kill him dead.
Kill.
Shoot arrow.
Here goes nothing, Kid Icarus.
What?
Arrow.
Nice shot.
You smote the Carrick.
He lay there, stinking.
Just like my cat.
Oh.
A light rain heralds the washing free of the Carrick's grip on the land.
You're feeling pretty good, though.
So the artless symbolism doesn't bug you.
I'm going to take my arrow back.
Take arrow.
Ew.
No way.
That thing is going to die.
It's got some serious Carrick brand cooties on it now.
Not the cooties.
Terrible day for rain.
Cry for Carrick.
What's his name?
Carrick.
Look.
There are large hoof prints in the grass here.
There's a large Carrick shaped mound on the grass.
Cry for Carrick.
It's got some serious Carrick brand cooties on it now.
You can call it that one.
This eye has no empathy.
Take his belt.
Strip.
Everything.
Steal.
Rob him.
Loot him.
Take everything he's got.
Rob him for all he's worth.
Steal his fortune.
Richard.
Search?
Search Carrick.
I think we have exhausted everything.
Oh!
Oh my gosh, this is literally the Bigfoot over here.
I look like Bigfoot right now.
Type cheat?
What happens if I type that?
Cheat.
Meh.
I look like Bigfoot over here.
Okay, this guy should now be... Oh yes, there he is!
Talk.
The Carrick is dead, he cries and hops around some more.
You wonder how someone this primitive could have made that much dough.
Hello?
Talk?
Take gold.
The Janka will see you and rip out your jugular with his teeth or something equally horrible.
Steal.
Treasure.
Wait.
Let's just go get another arrow.
We can solve all of our problems.
Oh!
Take arrow.
You grab yet another arrow from the tree hoping to get some bonus points.
Okay.
Let's go kill him.
Let's go kill the Janka.
Yeah!
We're gonna go kill him.
Shoot.
Shoot Janka.
Shoot bow.
Fire.
Kill.
Kill Janka.
No way!
Jankas are born scrappers!
He may be little but he'll crawl ya.
Shoot arrow.
The game is not letting me choose violence.
So we need to distract him somehow.
What do I have?
The monster mask.
Maybe he'll be afraid of me.
Wear mask.
Tell him a joke.
Hmm.
Hmmmmm...
No violence?
What else can we...
do?
Um, wait!
I'm kind of stinky now, right?
So maybe the...
The innkeeper will let us...
Let us in?
Welcome to membership!
Thank you!
A bribe.
Do I have anything?
My t-shirt?
He wants my t-shirt, maybe?
Here we go.
To the end.
We're gonna say...
Open.
Get a room!
I only serve peasants here, fancy pants.
Where's your robe?
Can't you see that I'm quite peasant-ly looking?
How am I not a real peasant, I wonder?
Hyper dude man, welcome to the membership, thank you.
Master 117, welcome to membership, thank you.
Baby lady.
We haven't seen her in a while.
No, she says the same thing.
This place is dead anyway.
Dang!
Is there a mewing commet?
Is that actual mewing emote?
What?
Oh my god, not the Lorax.
He speaks for the trees.
Welcome to the peasantship.
Also,
the hay.
I'm trying to think of what else.
Okay, so we...
Killed him.
We scared Gary.
There's the hay.
Search hay.
No needles.
There's nothing else because we got the farn- or the fissure.
Roll in hay.
No.
Eat...
I did it again.
It means eat happy, you guys.
Eat happy.
By the way, what are you playing this on?
Is it a recent re-release?
I'm on the homestarunner.com website.
Actually, find needle.
No.
I saw some people say jump in hay.
You've not known much better than a roll in the hay alone.
What?
Wait, that was right?
You leap in the hay like a two-year-old boy.
Uh-oh.
The hay sticks to your muddy body.
You're a walking hay bale.
Just like that one guy from that one show.
Oh my god.
I'm just hay.
Oh, the winds are heavy and all but a couple of key screens.
Looks like you're no longer in...
Stealth mode.
Okay.
We gotta go into stealth mode.
Jump in hay.
Oh, yeah.
He looks so excited to get in there, you know?
Hey, nice disguise.
The jonka doesn't seem to notice you.
Steel.
Gold.
I wanted to say that I've been enjoying all your streams since you came back.
I can't wait to watch more.
Also, since you started streaming again, you've become one of my favorite YouTubers to watch.
Oh my gosh.
What?
No way.
Little old me.
Thank you so much.
Mr. Mike Tyson's butt.
Oh, oh.
A stiff breeze blew all the hay and surprisingly the mud off of you.
You take my riches, growls the jonka.
Run?
Go run?
Uh...
Run.
Just answer him.
Oh, yes or no.
You fool.
Oh.
No.
Okay.
Let me know if you see riches anywhere.
Huh?
Just a hay.
He grunts and goes back to his hopping.
You smooth talker, you.
All right, let's go to the baby lady.
Fooled.
Oh, no.
Our mud is gone.
That was so easy.
We're going to be a peasant in no time, you guys.
Except we've done 41 things and we don't even stink.
We don't even anything.
How are we supposed to become a peasant?
Okay, lady.
Uh...
Oh.
These riches though.
Riches, dude.
Riches.
That peasant lady totally has to share some of this with you, right?
At least that shiny clawed scepter thing.
She will.
She's a good lady.
She's a good mom.
She's been raising her baby all by herself.
She's a good lady.
She's nice.
She's going to...
She's going...
She's...
She's a good lady.
Give riches.
My riches!
She screams and snatches up every last gold coin.
Thanks, sucker.
Here you go.
She shoves the baby into your hands.
And bolts out the door.
Huh?
You later learn that she does this all the time.
And is wanted throughout the countryside.
Those riches probably were the Junkas.
And who knows whose baby that is.
Well, it's yours now.
I got scammed.
Is there a baby in my inventory now?
Baby.
Oh.
It's a beautiful blue-eyed baby.
Aw, peasant babies are adorable.
No wonder they fetch such a pretty penny on the black market.
Now we're going to throw this baby.
Oh, it's kind of creepy.
The rocking chair is still rocking.
There is...
It reeks of single parrot.
It's such a...
Savage lion.
Mint is cute.
Stop.
Stop it.
There's one of those self-rocking chairs.
A mostly empty-shelf sit...
Okay.
Oh, it's a self-rocking chair.
She was even too...
Thanks for the super chat.
Wait, why can't I move?
Oh, there we go.
I'm gonna go to the lake and throw the baby into the lake for the gods.
Oh, here we go.
Throw baby!
You already fed the fish.
Let's get moving here, people.
The fish on the other side!
Throw that baby!
Throw baby!
Maybe try again from the center of the lake.
Looks deeper there.
Throw that baby!
Where is the center?
Throw baby!
Maybe try someplace else.
Throw that baby!
I accidentally clipped into the table for a second.
Throw baby!
Where else can we throw the baby?
The waterfall!
Oh my gosh, the waterfall!
Throw that baby!
Down the well!
Throw baby!
Throw it where?
Throw baby down well!
Dang.
Put baby in bucket.
You're not that keen a shot.
Try standing a little closer.
I'm as close as it can be.
Baby in bucket.
Dang.
Throw that baby!
Wait, how do I get to the center of the lake?
I forgot about this guy!
I'll give him the baby.
She threw that baby!
Actually, I have to or else I'm going to be a liar.
Where is he?
Did he go home?
Throw baby.
Give baby.
Talk.
How do we not startle him?
Is this guy okay?
I kind of feel bad now.
The Carrick is dead!
Oh yeah, that's right.
Can I go into his house?
Knock.
Open.
No.
Dang.
Wave.
Give him a big hearty wave.
Okay, what do we have?
Arrow.
Baby.
Bow.
Mask.
We got to use the baby.
We got to throw the baby somewhere.
I think it's the waterfall.
Throw that baby.
Give baby.
You think he wants the baby?
No.
How close are you to getting your own thatched roof cottage?
I don't think I want one.
Because if I get one, Trogdor is going to come and burninate it.
That would be really unfortunate.
And I have to go on my own quest.
I'd also have to become a peasant.
I'm already a maid.
Can I get any lower than this?
Like, come on.
I'm already a servant, essentially.
Give baby.
Don't need nothing from no filthy peasantses.
I'm not...
He said I'm a peasant.
For real.
You are, but you get paid.
I forgot about this room.
Wait a second.
Is this where you...
Use baby.
Deploying queue, baby.
No, baby, come back.
Baby, come back.
No, my baby.
My baby.
Way to go, baby.
It got the cottage door open and headed off to a new life.
Baby!
He becomes valedictorian of his graduating class.
Goes to scalding lake state.
Gets a degree in advanced peasantry.
And lands a job at thatch pro.
Building better cottages.
For a better tomorrow.
My baby.
You grow apart.
And the letters from him become fewer and fewer.
He develops a severe mead problem.
And blames you for never being there.
Wait.
Did I read...
Is that mead or med?
Like head or reed?
What is...
What is mead?
What is that?
Oh, I got more points.
Oh, it's alcohol.
Like reed.
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
So, what is mead?
He gets a alcohol addiction?
Oh my gosh, my baby.
You went to...
You went to scalding lake...
state.
The pressure was too hard on you?
Normal plant.
Welcome to membership.
Thank you.
An alcohol made from honey?
Honey wine?
Wait, is it good?
Mead is a type of alcohol made with fermented honey.
How can you ferment honey?
Open.
A search drawer.
Search?
Look.
This place could use some serious sprucing of the up variety.
There's a dresser over there and a broom kind of silhouetted all mysterious like.
Open...
Oh, no.
Search dresser.
Uh...
Huh?
I'm in mysterious cottage.
What can I say?
Open dresser.
Oh, there we go.
There's a vintage peasant robe in there.
Just like grandpa used to wear.
Wear robe.
You don't have anything but your scalding lake t-shirt and pants.
Forgot to mention the pants.
Take robe.
Yeah, get that robe.
Wear robe?
You slip into the vintage robe.
It smells like grandpa's...
Ew.
Grandpa's lap?
No, you're looking like a serious peasant.
Mint's got...
Oh, sorry.
I didn't mean to kick my mic.
Mint's got that baby fever.
Hmm...
I want my...
I want...
I want baby back.
You guys, we're a peasant!
We're a peasant!
Let's go to the inn.
We have to catch ourselves on fire here, I'm assuming, right?
I'm sure I'll remember to collect the fee come morning.
Good night, everybody.
Night falls like a bad PowerPoint presentation.
Allie, welcome to membership.
Thank you.
Whoa, it's night.
What an uncomfortable bed.
You sleep for maybe 20 minutes before the extreme pain in your spine forces you to get up.
He left the pantry.
What can we take?
Take candle.
Seems like you should be able to do that, doesn't it?
Sorry, no dice.
A small hint of brilliance.
Mint is a ghost, but she can wear clothes, right?
She can still be a peasant because it's not her on fire, but the robe.
Yeah!
So true.
The brilliance is magnificent.
Still dark out, the grimy old innkeeper is gone and he's left the pantry open.
Search pantry.
Look pantry.
Shelves and shelves of something called old band rub.
I want my baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby back.
Chilis, baby back ribs.
What is this?
Yes.
Old man rub.
The only thing of interest is a big black pot of horse grease up on the top shelf.
Take horse grease.
You reach way up to the top shelf.
Oh, great.
Now you can't see a thing and your head is covered in highly flammable horse grease.
You better get out of here before that disgusting old man comes back.
Oh.
Oh, no.
Oh, my keys are all messed up.
Wait.
Okay.
This way?
This way.
Oh.
Whew.
That was close.
Phew.
That cause me hell.
All right.
Thank you for the reallyreally big arigato cheese.
Thank you.
Oh, my gosh.
Thank you so much.
I really appreciate it.
Arigatoarigatochew.
This is supposed to be like the  vermicelli with garbage.
I don't know... for that.
Thank you.
Oh my gosh, we're gonna catch on fire like... soon.
Soon, soon.
Wait, can I take that candle now?
Or...
Open.
Take candle.
Candle.
Light candle?
Eat candle.
Save.
Okay, you guys are so...
So big about me saving.
Rolling for two.
Oh, it's on, it's on, it's on!
Okay, here we go.
Wow, the horse grease on your robe caught fire!
You're a four-wheel peasant now!
Wait, but I'm still not stinky enough, right?
Or am I?
I mean, it said it smelled like my grandpa, so...
Man, screens sure get light fast around here.
Yeah, I'm just having your normal...
Peasant day.
I'm on fire.
I'm...
You know, do what... There's a lot of stuff that I don't have.
This...
There's a lot of stuff.
Hmm.
Hmm...
What else am I missing besides the guy behind the tree?
He looked naked.
Talk.
Go away, said Dongolev.
We're arguing about who's hotter, as Mendeleev.
Okay, I can settle this.
Well, I can see that Dongleve has a very pronounced chin.
That's already the signs of a Chad.
And he also speaks with confidence.
Where Mendeleev is, you know, he's just kind of Eeyore.
He's like, I'm so king.
I'm sad.
Mendeleev is hotter for sure.
What?
What are your credentials?
Peasant day.
Peasant time.
Stop.
Not the lane reference.
And you don't seem to understand.
I have a confidence.
Whoa.
I'm walking on top.
I'm walking in my heart.
Whoa.
That's true.
Sorry, my thatched roof cottage.
Whoa.
What am I missing?
Talk.
We're on fire.
Set on fire.
I can say anything set on fire.
I can light anything on fire now.
You guys.
Ugh.
Another level.
Hmm.
Is there anything I can take?
Look.
Large hoof print.
No Carrick mound.
Hmm.
Take shoes.
Take.
What is this?
Is this a pants?
Take pants.
Take.
He doesn't have a shirt on.
Oh, it's a belt?
Oh!
You strapped the Carrick's belt buckle around your waist.
Oh, boy.
You sure stink now.
Oh, my gosh.
We smell?
Oh, we got the Carrick belt.
Phew.
This thing stinks like...
Oh, get out.
Why couldn't the Carrick have kidnapped a hot wench or something that you could have saved?
So true.
Give me the hot wench.
I'm a peasant.
And I'm gonna go kill Trogdor.
And I'm gonna get a hot wench.
For me.
Myself only.
I'm a peasant.
But there's still so much that I don't have.
Before we go face him.
Face Trogdor.
And also...
Okay.
Hold on.
I have an idea.
Because I do...
Now that I have the robe on, maybe I can give the shirt to that guy.
Approve.
It's a proper peasant robe.
It smells freshly washed and has the initials NN sewn onto the tag.
NN.
Is there anyone in Homestar that has those initials?
Homestar.
Oh, wait.
Look.
Hey, come on out, buddy.
Oh.
No, no, no, no, no.
Talk.
How do I make him not disappear?
I was once possibly, maybe, perhaps a chicken nugget.
Thank you.
Nice bowtie profile pic.
Oh, give shirt instead.
Okay.
What's wrong with NN?
Give shirt.
You don't need to give that now.
Give robe.
Give shirt.
Throw shirt.
Gift shirt.
Hide behind the tree.
Give shirt.
Drop shirt.
Talk.
Maybe I'm missing something.
Does he need pants also?
I don't know.
Let's go back to the inn because it's daytime now.
Let's go back.
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
Beedee, beedee, beedee, beedee.
Open.
Hello, mister.
If you're interested in staying the night, just say, get a room.
Get.
Eh, eh?
Eh?
It might have crashed.
It popped right back up as I refreshed.
No way.
Oh my goodness.
Skip.
Load.
We have to go back just a little bit.
Oh wait.
Actually...
Load.
Oh here we go.
That's better.
The auto-save is better.
Sorry guys.
So sorry for the inconvenience.
Also this screen has nothing.
We could have thrown the baby in here.
Here too.
No, we went to college.
Do you have the belt?
Yes.
Yes, I do.
Oh, open.
I don't know why I typed inventory.
Ord of peasant health says I can't serve any folk that's on fire.
Nothing personal.
Well, I mean, I don't like you much anyway.
Because I'm on fire?
You're discriminating against me?
It's a pre-existing condition.
You can't do this to me.
Please, I needed to sleep.
So it's very personal.
Yeah.
Can I swim now?
I don't know how to give that guy the shirt.
Hmm.
Let's go talk to the knight here, too.
The one that's gatekeeping us.
But I don't exactly want to go.
We only have a score of 92.
Talk.
Looking good, Mr. Peasant.
Good luck with old beefy arm up there.
This is it.
You can finally get revenge on Trogdor.
Nice work so far, stupid.
Okay.
But we have to get that guy.
Now, welcome to membership.
Thank you.
How can we give it to him?
How can we?
I'm gonna give it to him.
I love that they call you stupid all the time.
Hi,
Mint.
This is Trevor from Hampton, Maine.
I was wondering if you could teach me to be as awesome as you.
Ah!
Sorry.
You scared me.
I am a vampire.
And...
Huh?
And what?
Melon, welcome to membership.
Thank you.
What do I do?
What do I...
Maybe I hide behind...
Hide behind tree.
I'm just gonna say hide.
Hide.
Um...
Eeh?
Can you whisper?
Whisper.
Um...
Check my inventory.
I feel like the hay would have been a good thing here.
Um...
Hmm.
Take off shirt.
No.
This guy needs my shirt!
His nipples are so prominent!
Look at them!
I thought they were eyeballs at first!
Maybe this is not a human.
Maybe this is actually a creature.
These are his eyes.
And this is like a cyst or something.
You know...
What do you mean another nipple hater?
I'm not hating.
I'm just saying.
Wear mask.
No.
I can't tell what to do here.
What to do here?
He's gone!
I scared him away.
What?
There are large hoof prints in the grass here.
Looks like someone left their spare bones here.
Take bones.
No!
I want the bones!
What?
Does anyone actually have a good idea?
I was going to say an actual good idea.
Does anyone, if you remember the game, want to give a hint?
I can't remember.
Talk tree?
Talk tree.
Trees can't talk, but a breeze picks up and you swear the leaves whisper in the words, Naked Ned!
Naked Ned.
Hey, Ned.
Holdo.
Oh.
That's totally not Dongolev.
And end.
The trees are on something.
Naked Ned.
Did you get along with the baby?
Oh no!
Really?
Wait, like points?
That's so sad.
You have his robe.
I know, but...
Take off robe.
Give robe.
I have your robe.
Try talking to him.
I'll show you what happens.
You startle him and he disappears.
Hmm...
Wavy... Oh!
Talk to Naked Ned.
Never speak of this meeting, says the nudie, and he disappears.
Oh, talk Naked Ned gives a different name?
Shirt doesn't do anything.
Game facts.
What the...
Okay, we'll do talk Naked Ned instead of talk to...
Okay, talk...
Naked Ned.
Nope.
Same thing.
Ah!
What the...
Hmm...
Maybe I missed something.
He give...
Gave us hints for the robe.
Use...
Useless.
Oh!
Baby had two other tasks.
Ohh...
Oh...
Baby had other tasks.
Wait, where were they?
Guess we gotta go beat Trogdor now then.
Oh.
Here I come.
Here I go.
Please insert floppy disk 2 into dragon.
Can I be impressed?
Enter!
There we go!
Let's go!
You'd best avoid thems.
Okay.
Goodness gracious!
You cannot go up and also...
You have to like...
You cannot go up and sideways at the same time.
Okay.
We're just gonna go this way.
Alright.
I'm gonna go scoot over a little maybe.
Here we go everybody!
We're gonna...
We're gonna go beat Trogdor!
Oh!
Nice job climbing the cliff.
You have a real way with those arrow keys.
What a thrill!
Oh!
You do keep getting more points.
Oh my gosh.
What's this?
Oh!
Foolish peasant!
How dare you enter this fairly sacred chamber!
You explained that you are here to smoke Trogdor.
And if he doesn't get out of your way...
Him too!
I love Coach Z.
Great job!
You cannot vanquish Trogdor.
Only the three keepers of Trogdor hold the tools with which to destroy the Burninator.
The Trog shield, the Trog helmet, and the Trog sword.
And the only way we'll give them up is if you answer the three Trog trivia questions correctly.
Oh!
Right here goes What does Mendeleev have you tell Dongalev?
Hello everybody.
I mean not hello.
Everybody.
Let's all say it together.
America!
Happy!
No I'm just kidding.
It's A.
Oh crap.
You're right.
Here take this stupid Trog shield.
America!
Hold peasant.
You must answer the second dreaded Trog trivia question.
Listen careful now.
What was the innkeeper's pantry full of?
I remember.
Not Epson printers.
Old man rub.
That's right.
Oh.
This sucks.
Because I have to give you this Trog helmet.
Dang.
And last.
Oh.
But not least.
I thought they were all going to be color coded like their fancy dangles hair.
Old man rub.
Think you're pretty hot stuff eh?
Let's see you answer the deadly and pretty impossible third Trog trivia question.
Riddle me this.
Which way does the river that runs through peasantry flow?
North east to south west?
West?
Uh...
I think... wait.
I'm thinking of the...
No.
What's the word?
I'm thinking of the waterfall.
Wait.
C you think?
I think it's C right?
Yeah.
Maybe I am right.
Pick number C my lord.
Pick number C mint.
Okay.
Let's try C.
Oh.
Uh oh.
You got it right.
Trogdor is going to kill me.
Okay.
You can have the Trog sword.
Just promise not to kill any Trogdors with it.
Okay?
You just stare at the keeper blankly.
Okay.
Fine.
You can have the dumb thing anyway.
Trogdor is through the beaded curtain over there.
The fabled Trog sword is yours.
Now you have the means to strike down Trogdor.
Good luck peasant.
Yeah.
Look at me.
We are still missing three things.
Oh four.
Four things.
How curious.
Let's check out the Trog helmet.
The Trog helmet is not screwing around.
It's a serious helmet.
It also protects against harmful UV.
Are you team Yukari sensei?
Or team Nyamo?
We need to know.
As a kid I was always more team Yukari sensei.
Behold the Trog shield.
No seriously.
Behold it.
There is no way Trogdor's fire breath can penetrate this thing.
Yeah.
The Trog sword is for real.
Hands down the coolest item in this whole game.
You can't wait to lop off that beefy arm of Trogdor's with this guy.
Oh my gosh.
Oh my gosh you guys.
We are going to go do it.
We are going to defeat Trogdor.
This is it.
Actually I don't remember what the...
Is there a mini game?
I actually don't remember what happens.
So let's go.
My ears.
The beaded curtain slams shut behind you.
There is no turning back now.
Save.
Oh.
No turning back now you guys.
Oh save.
Maybe I should have had like a thing before I did the baby.
Oh my gosh we are so small.
Throw sword.
This is it.
You hurl the Trogsword with all your might at the sleeping Burninator.
Oh.
Wow.
It's beefy.
It looks like a cigarette.
You shouldn't be smoking Trogdor.
Now you've done it.
Trogdor is awake and the Trogsword doesn't seem to be doing a whole lot.
Oh no.
Your legs lock in fear.
Your eyes glaze over and you wish for some depeasant depeasant adult undergarments.
But you think you hear Trogdor whimpering.
Aw crap.
That's you whimpering.
At least your voice still works I guess.
Uh.
Talk.
You scream that your name is rather dashing.
And that Trogdor burned and ate your cottage and you're here for revenge.
Submortal.
I really appreciate you making the effort to come all the way up here and vanquish me.
But I'm kind of indestructible.
Mortis!
Um.
I will say that again for anyone who did not understand.
Sup mortal.
Booms Trogdor.
I really appreciate you making all the effort to come all the way up here and vanquish me and all.
But I'm kind of indestructible.
Yeah.
I can't be cute.
I'm surprised no party mentioned that to you.
This is terrifying.
You've got it farther than anybody else ever has.
I bet they'll make a statue or something in the corner of you somewhere.
Rain of spiders!
Yeah.
I can't be killed.
I'm surprised nobody mentioned that to you.
I'll admit though.
You've gotten farther than anybody else has.
I bet they'll make a statue or something in honor of you somewheres.
Rain of Trogdors.
I can honestly say it'll be a pleasure and an honor to burninate you, rather dashing.
That sure was nice of him.
And I've been burninated.
Congratulations.
You've won!
No one can kill Trogdor, but you came closer than anybody ever.
Way to go!
No!
I wanted to 100% it.
He's eating him.
Then he's gonna eat me.
Oh!
Oh my gosh, it's our statue!
Nice work on winning and everything.
Oh!
Scalding Lake!
134 out of 150 is so...
Okay, that's it.
Ah, so frustrating though.
Ah, it's so frustrating not to get 150.
The end.
Yippee!
What a game.
Look how rather dashing we are.
Yeah, here is this statue as an honor of rather dashing.
I expected him to have a bit more of like a Farquaad kind of haircut from his little sprite, you know?
He seemed to have like a bit of a... a bit of a bob.
A bob.
Yeah.
Hmm.
How can AAA games compare?
I think I found my new brain rot.
I think I found my new brain rot with this.
Um...
I'm kind of a fan.
Is this an old game or a new game made retro style?
It's pretty old.
It's...
It's not like as old as it seems though.
It's... it's...
It's like mid-2000s game.
Right?
Circa 2004.
That's what I meant.
Like mid-2010.
Right.
Wait.
2000 to 2010.
So 2004 is almost in the middle.
So 20 years.
Yeah.
20...
20 years old.
This game is.
But it seems like it's supposed to be like 40 years old.
You know?
Hmm.
It's an old parody of an even older genre.
Exactly.
Oh my gosh.
Traktor!
Thank you for the trip down memory lane.
Thank you!
Hmm.
Yeah.
Sorry.
When I say not too old, I mean compared to the style of game that it's emulating.
Or that it's parodying.
You know what I mean?
It's not from the 80s or 90s or anything.
So.
Your head explode.
Yeah.
That was so fun.
What a trip down memory lane.
I... I almost want to speed run it to try and get the baby extra stuff but I'm kind of tired.
I'll be honest.
Today and yesterday were some couple of busy days with me haunting all over the place.
Yeah.
Spiderman!
Oh.
Sorry.
I wish you were spiders, man.
Welcome to membership.
Thank you.
Burninating the countryside.
Burninating the people.
Look, you guys.
Metal Gear Solid is older than this.
I think Zumbini's is also older than this.
So...
Cap fourth leg is like a house without a bonnet.
Has to find the bill key to pen blue door.
Oh my gosh.
That's the yokel felon king I know and remember.
It's crazy.
They copied how back then they just copied how old DOS games and nowadays we get styles copying the PS1 wobble.
What a time we live in.
I know, right?
So funny.
Though, there are some games that copy styles like this too sometimes.
Um...
You know, indie game Dave the Diver.
No, I'm just kidding.
What was... like...
Mortis.
What is... Faith!
Faith is pretty...
You know?
Uh...
I don't...
I don't think it's a very...
I can't think of anything else though.
I don't know.
Undertale?
Not really though.
It's just like a pixel game.
Right?
Movie time?
What do you mean movie time?
What's the movie time?
How do I get out of this?
Help.
Quit.
Done.
Thanks for bringing clarity to me for a rep... to me for a reference that I never...
got to experience but only heard about it second hand.
Also cute.
Maid Ghost is cute.
Thanks Black Knight!
I'm glad that...
There's a Peasant's Quest movie?
Wait, actually?
Hold on, I'm looking it up.
Peasant's Quest movie.
Also don't google Peasant's Quest because there's apparently another game called Peasant's Quest that does not...
It uh...
It...
It does not look friendly.
Hold on.
Oh movie trailer.
It began.
Oh!
I think we can watch this.
It's... hold on.
Give me a second.
How can I do this real quick?
I'm gonna hide the Peasant's Quest.
I'm gonna do this.
Wait, can I put it here?
Oh no I can't.
Here we go.
Peasant's Quest.
And then I can scoot it over.
Like that.
Okay.
We're watching... we're gonna watch ye olde YouTube.
We're watching ye olde YouTube everybody.
Oh it's a little cut off.
Hold on.
Turn it down some too.
I hope I don't get copyright struck like before.
There we go.
Okay.
Um...
It began as the best selling video computer TV game of all time.
Not really.
But still.
Still.
A simple peasant wearing short pants.
I was him.
Quested his way into the heart of a nation.
Now for his greatest adventure yet, he will quest into theaters.
Oh see that's what I imagined him to look like.
Where's my cottage?
Oh no.
I got...
Oh my god.
Oh.
Woah.
Who is he fighting?
I don't remember that part.
Is that with the baby?
Who is that?
This is from 14 years ago you guys.
Oh he's got a scalding leg.
I like this couch.
From the sort of people who brought you Trogdor and Litigation Jackson.
Is that a real horse?
Easy now Gary.
I'm just going to wear masks.
Is that a real horse?
Show me your real man, rather dashing.
Throw baby.
Throw baby!
How do?
I'm Mendeleff.
I'm Dongleff.
Rather dashing.
More like rather homely.
Woah.
Hot dog.
A Trogventure for the whole Trog family.
They said they don't do lessons.
They just hate me I guess.
Oh I love Blue for Night.
I'm just so mad at Trogdor.
Access to Trogdor is strictly for peasants.
He just goes around burning things.
He doesn't even care.
Why is it wiggling down here?
You don't smell like a peasant.
Ah!
Oh my god!
I killed that guy!
Yeah!
Good thing we didn't watch this.
It's spoilers.
I don't remember this part.
Maybe I should have attacked him.
Oh my god.
Oh!
What is that?
A quest for a peasant.
Oh!
My eyes!
In the moon?
And the Trogdor comes.
In the night.
Not tonight he doesn't come.
Trogdor.
Yeah!
Peasant's quest.
I think I get it more now.
I think.
Thank you.
The maid is grounded.
Strong bed?
There was so much love in that video.
I think the people that made Homestar probably had a lot of fun.
You know?
They seemed like they just were goofy people.
All around goofy people.
You know what I mean?
Oh.
You can see I'm on the Homestar website.
That's it.
That's it everybody.
I really wanted to 100% it but oh well.
I'm glad we watched the video.
I'm going to go to the bathroom real quick.
I'm going to go to the little ghosty's room.
So you guys also get some something to drink and stretch or go to the bathroom.
I'll be right back.
I'll put on music at least.
I will be right back.
I'm
back baby.
I'm back baby.
I'm from the dead.
Give me one second.
We'll move to my maid cafe.
And uh...
Yeah.
We can talk.
Welcome back.
I'm back.
I went and I saw my cat and he was laying on his back and looked really cute.
So I went on his tummy.
And then I kind of kissed him and I said Who's a healthy boy?
Who's a healthy boy?
Him.
He's a healthy boy.
Have I ever mentioned you have a pen chant for a pleasantly peasant quest for a pheasant?
A what?
I didn't understand a single word you said.
I've been busy at work so a little late.
No worries.
Glad to hear your kitty's healthy.
How old is the little guy?
My kitty is 17.
You would never guess looking at him but he is definitely stinky.
My cat's about like 13 so...
Definitely not 17 of stink.
17 age of stink.
Penchant.
Oh!
A penchant!
Penchant?
Like that?
I was thinking like a chant.
Like water game.
Oops.
That's what idle brain does to you I suppose.
Thank you guys for all the donos while I was going potty.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Penchant.
A penchant.
I was just like...
Let's see.
I'm going to make a penchant right now.
Ball.
Pen.
Quill.
Fibo.
Wipa.
Inky.
Inky, inky, inky.
What's um...
What's like the different sizes of a...
You know.
Um...
Pen size.
Like millimeter.
You know.
Fine, medium, bold.
Yeah we can do that.
Um...
Fine, point.
Quick drying.
Clap.
Um...
Rubber grip.
Okay, let's try it real quick.
Wait, maybe I should change the Fibo Wipa part though, right?
Ball.
Pen.
Quill.
Fibo Wipa.
Inky, inky, inky, inky, inky.
Fine, medium, bold.
Fine, point.
Quick drying.
Rubber grip.
0.7 millimeter.
Inky, inky, inky, inky.
It kinda works.
I think I tripped over my words a little bit towards the end though.
Inky, inky, inky, inky.
Fine, point.
Quick drying.
Rubber grip.
Inky, inky, inky, inky.
0.5.
0.7.
Rubber grip hits hard.
It's a first draft.
I think it's perfect the way it is.
It's okay, but it's not your best work, boss.
Wow, we have some real criticizers in the chat.
It's okay, I get it.
I get it.
What if I go to Homestar Runner today?
Their website?
Wait, the main website is like...
Oh, come on in.
Wait, can I actually... What is Ruffle?
Oh, at the bottom it says, what's this big play button, you ask?
Well, Flash is all kinds of dead.
But the amazing Ruffle project helps our cartoons live on.
Not every cartoon and game works perfectly just yet, so be patient and expect some jankiness here and there while we keep working.
That's so cute!
Tough crowd.
For real.
It's not easy making chance up.
We've got a good knack for it.
Thanks!
Wait.
Hold on real quick.
I want to make sure I say the right thing.
Hold on.
One second.
Will you ever be playing the dangerous point and click game also on the Homestar Runner website?
I don't know.
I don't remember playing.
This one I played because I played it a lot as a kid too.
Um...
But...
I don't really remember uh...
the other ones.
So...
I don't know if they work either.
Like they said, not all their games work.
My heart felt that chat.
Did you beat it back then?
I don't remember beating it because I didn't... I feel like...
I feel like Trogdor's voice would have traumatized me as a kid.
And...
I don't remember that.
I don't remember that at all.
But I probably would have remembered that.
Right?
I...
I don't know.
I'm so sleepy.
You guys...
Yesterday I worked...
I did a ton.
Essentially I like had a...
I made a... what's the word?
I made like a big calendar for Matara and I to work on future podcast episodes and scheduling them out.
And scheduling some trips.
And scheduling some other events.
And scheduling things like that.
And...
So I worked on a bunch of that.
I worked on messaging some people for commissions on things.
And...
Oh nice!
I was so organized.
She loves to schedule.
Yeah.
We have things we're cooking.
I'm so glad you're indie.
I mean...
I guess it is...
I guess there is more freedom with it, right?
Did you message Hena?
I messaged her!
I said...
I said to her...
I first...
She sent me a waving emoji.
And I sent a waving emoji.
And she said, Hi people...
People shy.
And I said, Hi I'm a big fan of you.
LOL LOL LOL LOL
I said I'm a big fan of you.
LOL
Is it people shy?
I don't know actually what's a people.
I don't know which ones they are.
Hold on.
People shy.
Yeah!
She sent a people shy.
LOL This one.
Hold on.
It's literally me.
Me people shy.
Yep.
Gotta hit her with the...
LOL I don't know.
Can I stick out my tongue to her?
Would that be considered weird?
I don't know.
What if I...
What if I just always talk with my tongue out?
What if I always talk with my tongue out?
And I...
Wait what cant I stream like this all time?
What do you think...
But if you keep watching it's like...
If I stream like this....
If I stream like this...
You guys will have to grab my tongue and turn it on the table...
Grab my tongue and turn it on the table...
Intimidation.
Sticking out your tongue for the...
No!
No, they're not pants!
It's not pants!
It's my tongue!
Wish I got to experience the early internet some more.
No!
I think the early internet...
I don't even know.
There's definitely some weird stuff.
I mean, there's always weird stuff, right?
Homestar Runner was very pure, which is the best part about it.
People... Oh, Pepe and his son...
People is Pepe's son?
Do you guys know that?
Like, Pepe is so popular in Japan.
There's a whole section in Village Vanguard for...
For Pe... Pe... Pe...
Pe... Pe... Pe...
For him.
Look, they sell a bunch of merch.
Hold on.
It's like this.
I got a picture.
Like this.
Pepe the frog.
What is Pepe the frog?
Who is Pepe the frog?
Thank you, thank you.
Demonic Garmals, thank you so much for the 50!
Thank you!
Thank you so, so much!
Shoush!
Hey, Mint, it's my birthday today!
I just wanted to send some love and appreciation to the silliest, goofiest...
Wait, hold on.
Let me get this out of my face.
Ghost!
If it's not too much to ask for, could I get a...
Birthday...
Birthday tongue?
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday dear Shoush.
Happy birthday!
Yay!
Happy birthday.
I'm assuming that's what you meant.
I sure... I sure hope so.
I sure hope so.
Now lick the candles.
Ooh!
This was fun, guys!
Sorry, that...
I feel like...
This week I don't have so much planned.
It's only like my second week back, but...
Um.
And I'm already just like...
I'm...
I'm tired, no.
But you know, I'm all ready.
Since I kinda kinda came back, the...
Um.
The day after I came back was...
When we announced the...
So, since then, there was a lot of stuff that I needed to take care of and I was like, okay, I should probably take care of some of this stuff before I get too deep into things a little bit... a little.
Yeah, but it's okay.
Like, just some like... housekeeping, you know?
Housekeeping!
You kinda dropped on us from heaven.
I know!
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
But I'm still planning lots of stuff.
And... yeah.
We can have fun with the podcast happening too!
Yippee!
It's only been two weeks.
I know, right?
It feels like so much longer for even me.
But I was like looking... I was like, okay, alright, time to make my schedule yesterday.
And then when I was posting it, the post that I made before was like, first schedule!
And I was like... first schedule?
What do you mean?
I'm only making my second schedule.
Professional maid housekeeping.
Yeah.
Yeah!
Podcast is super fun.
I've been loving every episode.
I think...
Um... we... well, last night when I was doing the planning, I think I decided...
Or rather, I decided maybe...
A good day to end the podcast?
Um... but...
I still need to talk about it with Matara.
Mmm...
Which is already so sad to think.
I don't want to think about it.
Because...
Yeah...
Even though... well, the podcast for me also...
It feels different than...
How do I say?
Like, for me, like obviously it's different than normal streaming, but like...
It's weird because when I stream... I don't know.
I feel like maybe half of my brain is turned off.
When I stream...
But with the podcast, I feel like my brain has to be like...
Totally on.
Hear me out.
What if you don't end it?
No...
We gotta end... it's... you know...
It's a summer podcast, you guys.
It's a summer podcast.
But that's okay.
You'll have...
You'll have... um...
You'll have lots of... lots and lots of more episodes, so...
Um... stream nerf.
But yeah, since my brain is like on...
For... like 100% or at least what it feels like.
It's supposed to be 100%.
Um... during it, like it...
It actually does kind of like wear me out a little bit more.
Which I didn't expect.
I was like, oh my gosh.
It's just talking for like a couple hours.
Like no biggie.
But...
Maybe I'm just... because you know...
Uh... it's been so long since I've streamed.
I...
Have no stamina anymore.
I have no stamina anymore.
Will you still collab with... in the future with Matara?
Yeah, yeah.
Of course.
So...
Podcast turns into collab.
Y'all are very... on very high grade yap mode.
It's gotta end someday so that we get the fall and winter Matara.
Mentora podcast!
No!
But... but I think...
Because I'm just like, oh my gosh.
This is like kind of wearing me out.
Maybe also because like Matara is such an extrovert.
And for me...
Like... when I talk to you guys...
Like I still can feel like I'm an introvert.
Because I just see you guys' texts.
But with her I have to have an actual conversation.
So...
My battery just goes...
So quickly.
It's something that I've like...
Kind of been like...
Self-aware of with the podcast.
I'm like, oh my gosh.
By the end I start to like...
I feel like I start to get kind of...
Tired.
I need to...
I need to work on that for future episodes.
So like...
I wanna say lately I've been...
Trying...
Collecting more...
Ace Combat Merch.
Although the shipping is kind of expensive.
Because they're mostly in Japan.
Shipping from Japan is so expensive.
But good luck now.
Good luck.
Podcast in winter because it's summer down south.
That's true.
Yeah.
But it's not that I...
I'm still definitely of course having fun with it.
It's just...
A different experience for me.
Something that I didn't expect.
Because I thought it would be so easy.
But...
Not that I'm complaining or anything.
Oh my gosh.
Being a content creator...
Is so...
Difficult.
You're just...
You...
You peasant.
You just never understand.
Now go...
Go and destroy Trogdor.
Yeah.
Special Aussie episode.
Socially battery depleted.
My battery.
Maybe that's what's making me so tired all the time.
No.
I had a bad dream last night.
Oh my gosh.
Oh.
I think it's because I fell asleep listening to...
Listening to like one of those ghost hunting YouTube channels or whatever.
There's this one that I...
There's like...
I love the ones that are so dramatic.
About everything.
Because it just is so funny.
Where...
First of all, it's just like...
Oh my gosh.
You're doing that to a ghost?
Like...
A ghost is never gonna respond to that.
You know?
But...
You know.
As a ghost.
Of course.
I would know.
But yeah.
They're always so goofy.
They're just like...
It's...
Yeah.
I don't know.
What's the one that I've...
What is their name?
They had a TV show.
I saw a Metal Gear Facts to Fall Asleep 2 video.
I was going to try tonight.
You should.
I'm a person...
I...
For the past couple of nights...
I haven't been able to sleep well.
I was trying to...
Fall asleep to like head scratching ASMR.
But it just wasn't working.
I fall asleep so much better to...
Just mundane person talking videos.
With Shane and Ryan?
No.
I love them.
I love Shane and Ryan.
Ghost Adventures?
No.
It's a...
It's a YouTube channel.
Project Fear.
I remembered it.
They are...
If you want some like...
Trash TV-esque ghost hunting YouTube content...
They are...
It's one of those like...
Like every video they'll be like...
This is the craziest night we have ever had.
History channels are my sleep channels.
Do you dream of aliens?
Do you dream of getting probed?
Wow.
Have you tried rambling videos?
What's a ramble?
What do you mean?
Just people rambling about stuff?
Are you a Shaniac or a Bugara?
I'm a Shaniac.
All the way.
Even though...
Even though I'm a ghost and I appreciate that...
That...
Oh gosh.
What's...
That Ryan believes in ghosts and Shane doesn't believe in me and that's okay.
You know?
It's not like...
If someone...
You know?
If someone doesn't believe in me, it's not like I'm gonna die again, you know?
Or cease to exist.
I'm not like other...
You know?
I'm not like other creatures where like if someone doesn't believe in you, like they like fade out of existence, you know what I mean?
But...
So for me, it doesn't matter if...
If Shane doesn't believe in ghosts.
I just think he's funny.
Go team Shaniac!
Shaniac hype!
Yeah!
Wait, you exist?
Do what?
Hmm.
You mean like a fairy?
Yeah!
Those things are so weak.
What?
Two people don't believe in you and you can't fly anymore?
So...
Come on.
Get...
You need to adopt a better...
A better policy about your existence, you know?
It's okay, we believe in you.
I don't care if you do or don't.
Doesn't mean anything to me.
The weakest!
Hey, one of my former Oshis was a fairy?
Sorry.
I don't mean to Oshi slander.
I don't mean the Oshi slander, my bad.
Sorry, I apologize.
Not to your Oshi, to you.
I did not mean to Oshi slander.
I said I do.oni Yeah, get rekt chat.
Also, you don't need wings to fly as a ghost.
Speaking of... well, it's not flying.
It's more like floating.
But I got a new desk.
I got a standing desk.
But I've been calling it a floating desk.
I got a floating desk for myself.
Oh my gosh, I'm gonna be so healthy.
So you're saying you could beat up a fairy.
Yeah, probably.
Why not?
Yeah...
I've been trying to... because...
Because...
Can I mention this?
You know what?
She mentions things all the time.
It's probably fine if I mention this.
Actually, I think it was already mentioned before.
Because I know that Matara is wanting to come visit...
Yeah!
We mentioned it.
Because I asked if she wanted to play my Apache slot machine.
Because Matara is planning on visiting me, I've been reorganizing the maid cafe a little bit.
I was just like...
Oh gosh, maybe this doesn't look so awesome.
Maybe I gotta reorganize just a little bit.
So...
That was part of what I've been doing this week.
But also, I've been cleaning and reorganizing for another reason.
Good day...
First thing you need to get to go to your standing desk is a tall chair.
No!
Defeast the purpose!
No...
It's so soon?
Hmm...
I'm not gonna say what.
Don't say it.
She needs to hide her lewd snake doggies.
Hey, if you can show me where to get those...
Then I will need to hide them.
3D stream?
No.
No, no, no.
Not anything like that.
I... I... I... I...
I don't even know how long I'll be around for, you know?
So... 3D stream...
We'll see.
I'd like to though.
It'd be really fun to...
What are you guys saying?
Is that what you want?
Oh my gosh, lewd.
You could do the funniest thing right now.
Lewd.
You could do...
The funniest thing right now.
If you make just one, I'll buy it at Ofgine.
If you make just one...
I'll roll up to you in my little robot tablet...
And I'll buy it from your booth.
Just one.
I know that's not how orders work.
I know.
It's like, oh my gosh, I have to order 50 for it to be even worth it, but...
It's okay.
You can put a higher price tag on it.
I'll still buy it.
I know they're like... I've seen ones exist, but...
Imagine my own personal one.
That'd be crazy.
Yes.
Mine.
Me.
Gonna cost $300.
Worth.
Maybe.
Just order one sample, Lewd.
You could do...
Oh, you're so big-brained.
Just order it as a sample.
Exactly.
It doesn't need to be perfect.
Just order the sample.
That's so genius.
Oh my gosh.
That's so smart.
Of course, of course, the vendors would all have all the knowledge, you know?
Yeah, it's just a sample.
It's not for sale, except to me.
This is my official commission.
Okay.
See you at...
At...
Off-Kai.
Yes.
Hacking the system.
Big boss on one side and solid on the other.
No.
Double Plissken.
Double Plisken.
Double pliskin!
Can't wait for all the mint fan merch.
It's so...
I see people posting like I made a mint keychain!
Or...
I saw...
I saw a mockup of a mint plushie and I'm just like...
It's crazy!
It's actually crazy!
I...
never would have thunk...
I never would have thought, you know?
Wow!
Thank you!
Can't just have it out in the world flopping out like that.
Actually messed up.
I get it.
I know.
It's a power that I must handle responsibly.
Thank you!
It's always summer down here so it never ends, right?
Hmm...
You're a bit of a celebrity boss?
No!
I'm just little old me.
Must have been backlogged.
I think some of them are backlogged a little bit.
Yeah.
Well, I have to change the notifs because I can't read them.
Look how tiny!
The text is for ants!
I can't read it!
I...
can't read it at all!
You're famous though?
You think too little of yourself.
You're bigger than Elvis!
You ain't nothing but a hound dog.
Crying all the time.
Hmm...
Was that a Zoolander reference?
Maybe...
So famous she gets banned in chats.
Look...
I don't know... I don't know what you mean.
I've never been banned.
And...
I've always been honest.
I've always been like...
If I go into a chat...
You know...
I...
lol I don't know what you mean.
lol lol lol I'm going to do something real quick.
lol
Was I broken?
I can't tell.
Thank you, thank you!
I can't tell anymore.
Umm... Bustin?
Thank you, thank you!
Since I saw someone donate about Ace Combat a couple days ago, begging you to play Ace Combat...
I just want to say, as much as I love Ace Combat, me and most Ace Combat fans don't want to demand you to play them if you don't want to.
No!
Don't worry, don't worry.
Yes, it is broken.
It's breaking.
It's not loading for me right now.
Hold on.
I'm gonna try...
Yeah, I think it's broken.
I think it's broken.
Thanks!
Oh gosh, now my chat is actually...
50 people are watching?
This is just like old times!
This is just like before I left!
This is... This is nothing new!
This is literally...
How...
How it is for... Oh my god, my chat is not even loading anymore.
Oh my gosh!
We are back to normal, you guys!
This is just like how it was before I left!
Yippee!
Neil Fears How Much People Love You Neil Fears How Much People Love You No, I actually... I just went... and saw if um...
No, I actually... I just went... and saw if um...
I don't know.
Things are not loading... properly.
And I'm seeing it's happening on other channels too, so...
You know what, it's... it's fine.
Small indie company for small indie...
VTuber.
Andrew goes, thanks for the 10 gifted!
Oh, why is nothing...
Oh gosh, it's so frustrating.
Can't see anything.
Time warp back to 2020.
Oh, YouTube.
Please.
Hold on, I can't reach anymore.
Sorry.
I just opened up the backend of YouTube and I got a comment that was like...
WTF, why do you sing so well?
I don't know.
Why?
WTF?
Oh, guys.
Oh, chat is just like old times.
WTF?
Why, YouTuber?
Why?
Why do you sing so well, YouTuber?
Huh?
Why do you have a voice...
on YouTube, YouTuber?
I can't sing...
Oh my gosh.
That reminds me of...
Oh my gosh!
Okay, so...
Sorry, I was gonna say...
I was gonna say like...
Why can't I sing?
Why can't I sing as well as you, YouTuber?
And that reminded me...
It was...
Last night?
No, it was this morning.
This morning, I was...
Okay, so there was this issue on TikTok where...
I don't actually know if it's just a TikTok issue or if it's like a general like...
Young people on the internet issue now.
But...
It started on TikTok.
Or rather, it blew up on TikTok.
Where...
Someone made a bean soup.
Right?
They were like...
Okay, here is a recipe for bean soup.
If you want to have this bean soup.
And they were getting comments like...
Well, what if I don't like beans?
Okay.
Don't make the bean soup.
And they were like...
What if...
What if I can't have that ingredient?
Okay.
Just don't...
Add it then.
You know?
Like just...
Like there was this weird...
Thing where like people are like...
Starting to...
Watch videos.
And that's...
This is why I think it's like...
Younger...
Like younger audiences.
Because they'll be like...
They'll take...
They'll watch a video and take it very personally like...
Well, what if I can't do this thing?
Okay.
Then you can't...
Do it.
That's okay.
And so...
I experienced it first hand this morning.
When I was watching a TikTok video.
And it was about this like...
Crazy grocery store that's in Ohio.
And they were like...
You should go...
It was like...
It's like a...
It's like a real grocery store.
That like has...
Like animatronics in it.
And...
It's...
Only in Ohio.
Yes!
Jungle gyms!
It's called jungle gyms.
And it has like...
Monorails.
Like...
It is crazy.
It's like...
It's super...
Like...
There's a movie theater in it.
To teach you about jungle gym.
Like...
But...
Anyway...
So...
The video was like...
If you are in Ohio...
You gotta go check out jungle gyms.
Like...
It's a really crazy grocery store.
Go check it out.
Awesome.
Cool.
Thanks for the recommendation, guy.
Like...
If I'm ever in Ohio...
I'm gonna go to jungle gyms.
But...
There was a comment...
That was just like...
Hey...
You should check out Omega Mart.
Which...
If you don't know what Omega Mart is...
It's like a...
Mmm...
It's...
It's an...
It's really an art...
An art exhibit.
It's like...
They have like...
Rooms...
Behind...
Like...
Doors...
You open up the...
The thing to think you're getting milk.
But it's actually a secret room.
Um...
Yeah...
It's like an art installation.
That's a better...
Art installation.
Not exhibit.
Um...
A playground for adults.
Yeah...
Like...
It's not a real grocery store.
Right?
It's just like an art exhibit.
And...
So someone was just like...
You should check out...
Omega Mart.
Um...
And the creator who posted the original video about jungle gyms was like...
Oh...
Well...
Omega Mart is different because it's an art installation.
This is an actual grocery store.
So...
It's...
Kind of different.
And then there's one other person.
Comments...
Below...
And says...
Yeah...
Well...
You know...
Um...
I can't go to Ohio.
It's too far away from me.
Actually, Vegas is closer to me.
So I'm gonna go to Omega Mart.
That's like...
Okay...
I mean...
Then...
Don't go.
That's like...
And people were like...
People were like...
I mean...
It depends on where you live.
For some people...
Ohio is pretty close.
You know?
You can just...
Some people can just go.
And they were like...
Yeah...
But I can't.
Vegas is closer to me.
So I'm going to Omega Mart.
I'm like...
Okay...
Have fun.
But...
Like...
I don't know why...
Why kids take these videos so...
Like...
So...
Personally now.
Like...
Kids are like...
They'll watch something and be like...
If this doesn't relate a hundred...
Like...
They take For You page...
Extremely seriously.
They're just like...
I don't know.
This page is supposed to be for me.
So everything...
Everything should be catered to me.
You know what I mean?
I think that's what it is.
I don't know.
It's so strange.
This is what happens when you're raised by an iPad.
I don't...
It's so...
Maybe it is just an entitlement thing.
Right?
I...
It's...
If it isn't for me...
It's against me.
I was like...
Oh...
The algorithm has failed.
It has failed me.
And it's your fault.
Like...
I don't know.
I just never...
Would...
I just...
I don't know if this is a new thing.
Or what.
Because...
You know...
When I was a kid...
Like...
I would never watch a video...
And be like...
Oh...
But...
They didn't think about my needs.
It's a new generation thing.
So crazy.
It's very interesting.
I mean...
It's not good.
Maybe.
But...
I just...
I was so shocked that I experienced it first hand.
You know?
Hmm...
People being isolated at home.
Not socializing in person for a while.
Probably did a whole lot of something.
That's so true.
Oh...
We need to get these kids on Homestar Runner.
Get off the skibbity toilet.
Get them on Homestar Runner.
Have them reading...
Have them sending in strong bad e-mails.
Yeah...
Marzipan.
But yeah...
This was fun.
Hope you guys enjoyed...
Being a little pez...
Well...
We weren't a peasant.
Then we became a peasant.
And...
Okay.
I want your opinion.
Would it make you feel better?
Would your maid be above a peasant or below a peasant?
Like...
What if I...
You know...
What if I'm like a royal maid?
You know?
Like...
What if I'm working at like a...
Above?
Same level?
Equal?
Above?
Same league?
Depends on who you made for, I think.
Above?
Okay.
I...
I was above the peasant.
You...
Are pe...
Wait.
If you're a peasant, then I can't be your maid.
Hmm...
Okay.
You're not peasant.
You're all royalty.
I'm a rich peasant.
You're...
Thank you, Churro.
Ooh...
No dice.
Nanoplasm.
Sorry.
Take this, king.
What happened to...
I said it at the beginning.
I said...
I always say it.
What do you mean?
I said it...
Yeah!
Mint my kami peasant oshi.
Thanks.
Oh no, I meant, how can we be ojousama and also peasant?
Oh!
That's why I said you're not a peasant.
You are above even the peasant.
You are big peasant!
I'm just a merchant.
Sell, sell, sell.
What are you buying?
What are you selling?
Yeah, what are you selling?
What are you selling, merchant?
What are your wares?
What's that?
Royals have noble maids.
Nobles have peasant maids.
Thanks for the five gifted!
Thank you!
RE4 stream win.
You guys, besides Resident Evil 1, I've never played a Resident Evil game before.
I've always wanted to play, but I'm kind of scared.
Aren't maid cafes made for us peasants to experience maids?
No.
Well...
But when you go in, you are not the peasant.
You transform.
Magical moe magic.
Resident 4 is... Resident 4?
Resident 4!
Raymac, thanks for the five gifted!
Merry Music Moth, welcome to Membooship!
Hakurei Mima!
Mima posting in 2024!
Welcome to Membooship!
Ducky, thanks for the five gifted!
Alvin, thank you for the five gifted!
Thank you guys, thank you!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
The four residents.
Not the 50 drop!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Thank you, Mima!
Natsuki, thank you for the five gifted!
LPR, thank you for the five gifted!
Why is everybody suddenly gifting?
RE4 is more action than scary.
You're way scarier.
See, that's why...
That's actually partially why I've never played Resident Evil.
Because...
I always thought the games were more action than scary.
But...
Just...
Stop!
No!
Because they were more action than scary.
And I always was like...
Well, I like scary games more.
But then...
Then VII came out.
And I was like...
They're so scary now!
But they're also like...
So goofy.
I want to see Leon and Cat...
Does he actually wear cat ears?
Or is that just a meme?
Oh my gosh, you guys!
Stop!
Jay, thank you for the five!
Mima, thank you for the Akazufa!
Dungokai, welcome to Mimu's ship!
Niels, thank you for the five gifted!
Dogsdrinks, thank you for the five gifted!
Spank, thank you for the five gifted!
TVTableTrain10, thank you for the five gifted!
Paperbacks, thank you for the five gifted!
Takeoff and Yanyan, thank you for the five gifted!
Bloodlines, thank you for the ten gifted!
No theater, thank you for the five gifted!
Stupid shark!
Thank you for the twenty gifted!
Hey, that's not a shark!
That looks like a bird!
Your profile picture...
Thank you for the five gifted!
Thank you!
Arigato!
Okay.
What were we talking about?
Leon Kennedy's...
Cat ears.
S810!
Ritual, thank you for the five gifted!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Cat ear Leon.
Is it real?
Does he actually wear cat ears or...
To answer your question, the cat ears are after you beat the game.
No!
It's hard.
I was going to say it's hard living, but I don't.
It's hard after living.
We're giving you money so that you can go above a regular peasant.
Stop!
The word game that you're looking for is System Shock 2.
What is that?
System Shock 2.
Did you guys hear me gulping?
Say no.
Actually,
I can't.
I can't tell.
Found the tofu very soon funny myself.
Tofu?
System Shock 2 is a classic.
System...
I was thinking recently That I was like, oh my gosh.
I've been wanting to play Blade Runner for so long.
I was thinking of playing it on Sunday.
I'm not sure yet though.
Tofu is a RE2 thing.
And I didn't...
When I played Resident Evil 1, I didn't even beat it.
I only played a little bit of it.
So...
Blade Runner.
Yeah, I really wanted to play...
They have like the...
Actually, I know they have it on GOG.
I think it's also on...
Blade Runner.
Is it on Steam?
Yeah, they also have it on Steam.
Actually, I can't remember...
The reviews are kind of mixed on it though.
Uh oh.
Thank you!
Thanks for reminding me of Trogdor.
Love your streams.
Thank you!
Maybe I should do the GOG one.
Get the GOG one for the functional one.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, maybe we'll play that on Sunday.
I haven't decided yet.
But I've been wanting to play it.
So...
Blade Runner.
The re-release is buggy.
The Steam one maybe.
It has some positive reviews recently.
I don't know if they...
Oh, it says fixed now!
Wait.
Posted December 30th, 2023.
Seems like Night Dive has largely fixed the issues the remaster had at launch.
Do yourself a favor and just play the enhanced edition.
Oh, nice!
There we go then.
You heard it here, folks.
According to Agent Smith on Steam.
They said that it is fixed as of December 30th, 2023.
That is really recent.
That's really recent.
If anything, it's only $10.
So, you know.
Oh my gosh, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna go...
Oh my gosh, I'm like looking at it right now and it's so nostalgic.
Are there boobies in this game?
Or am I safe?
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
Siege, thanks for the 10 gifted!
Yes!
Boobies...
Oh, yeah!
It was the 90s.
So anything is possible.
I don't know when this...
When this game came out.
1998?
Anyway.
I don't know yet.
Maybe another time.
There's soft nudity.
Don't...
Don't get mad at me, YouTube.
Don't get mad at me.
It's art.
It's not real.
It's fake, it's fake, it's fake.
It's art.
Belly button.
Do you guys want to see my belly button?
I can't see it.
It's covered by an apron.
You'll never know.
For free?
Played like a fiddle.
I mean, you can see...
Well...
You can...
The frills kind of block my...
My armpits a little bit.
It's...
I have to be nice and breezy.
So that when I'm working, you know.
It's got to be nice and breezy.
It's on the summer art.
So, ha!
You're right.
Got to take it down.
Time to take it down.
Get wrecked.
Mass recall.
Cancel the project!
Cancel it!
Shut it down!
There's like a big red button in front of me.
And I'm like...
No!
I forgot it was on the summertime merch.
No, no, no!
No!
I thought I was safe.
Don't look, you guys.
Don't.
Don't look.
Don't look at my belly button.
No!
Thank you for the tag!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Bye!
Who's the fiddle now, Mint?
Why are we here?
Just to suffer.
I perceive.
You better stop it.
You better stop perceiving.
Right now.
If one...
Wait, if you...
If you get ghost busted, do pieces of your outfit get ripped off like...
What is this?
What is this question?
That could apply to anyone, right?
Like...
I don't think that's an Akiba's trip reference.
I think that's just like, you know how...
Yeah, like Senran Kagura, you know?
Like, there's...
There's like a lot of games like that.
When there's...
When characters take damage, they lose...
Like, their clothes just tear apart.
That's why everybody...
If you're going into battle, just don't wear clothes.
Because...
If they're gonna tear apart anyway...
It would be...
It would be a waste to lose that.
That's a big brain.
Just don't wear them.
Don't look!
Where to put the sand?
Pocket sand?
Thank you for the vibe gifted!
I thought this emote...
Looked like Pantsu.
You and everybody else thought so, okay?
But when you put them all together...
It looks fine.
Okay, guys.
I'm gonna go.
I'm gonna leave.
I'm gonna head out.
Tomorrow, no stream.
I got some stuff to do.
But also recording.
That's mainly the thing.
I'm recording.
So...
We are recording for the podcast!
Thank you guys again for watching today.
Thank you for hanging out with me as always.
I really, really, really appreciate it.
Thank you for that 20 gifted.
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
Thank you, Mint.
Thank you guys for always hanging out with me.
This was fun.
Peasant's quest was so silly.
And...
It was a good time.
I don't know.
I feel so awkward all of a sudden.
I don't know why.
Why do I feel so awkward?
I'm just gonna...
I'm just gonna go.
Like this way.
I'll see you guys...
When I see...
When I see you.
Maybe I'll go this way.
Or this way.
I'm gonna...
Okay.
You guys can see yourselves out, right?
Good luck with your recording tomorrow.
Thank you!
Conqueror!
Actually, I'm gonna go...
Okay, wait.
You guys decide.
Are you gonna go out this way or that way?
Are you gonna go out...
Well...
Let's just say it's to the left or to the right.
Which way are you going?
Up?
No, you can't go up.
What are you, live in the rafters?
That's where the rats live!
That's my grandma.
Through the window?
Just show us the door?
No!
I'm gonna go this way.
I changed my mind.
Wait, someone...
Someone said right.
Okay.
I'm going this way.
I'm going to the left.
Okay.
Okay, don't follow me.
You guys said to the right.
So I'm gonna go to the left.
Okay?
Can't follow me.
How do I get out?
I'm stuck here now.
That's how I became a ghost.
So...
Not really.
Wouldn't that be crazy?
If you also got stuck in a maid cafe and then became a ghost.
Yeah, they're gone.
Uh-huh.
No.
I told them to go to the right.
Because...
You know...
That's the way to the fire pit.
They'll never know.
No, no, no.
I covered it really well.
They'll just fall right in, you know?
Yes.
Yes?
No.
No, I forgot.
I forgot.
No, I forgot the...
Well, it's not that I forgot the piranhas.
It's that they just didn't do very well in the fire.
You know what I mean?
Okay, I will put in an order for...
robotic...
piranhas next time.
I'm very sorry.
Uh-huh.
No, they should be...
I'm listening...
I'm going to hear their screams...
any second now.
Hold on.
Oh.
Um...
One second.
You guys, you didn't go to the right!
Come on.
Okay, I'll lead you to the exit.
I'll lead you to the exit.
Okay, come on, come on, come on.
Why are you screaming?
No need to scream right now.
This way, this way, this way.
Yep, yep.
Just keep going straight.
Okay, bye!
Bye-bye!
Okay, they're walking there now.
Yes.
I told them to...
Oh, actually...
Don't forget to go through...
the third door.
That's the correct one.
That's the one...
all the way on the right.
The third door.
I told them to go through...
the third door.
Even though the exit is actually through the first door.
Yes.
The second door...
doesn't lead to anything.
It leads to...
Like...
It's like a...
wildy coyote.
It's just a painted road.
But the third one leads to the fire pit...
that they are about to fall in.
Any second now!
No!
Yeah, I'm going to hear their screams.
Hold on.
I'm listening.
Oh, by the way...
Mr. President...
You're going to want to...
go through door number one.
Yes.
Door number one.
Mr. President.
Otsu Minto!
Bye bye!
Thank you for watching!
Hang out with me!
See you!
Later!
Don't be a stranger!
Bye bye!
Otsu
Minto!
Otsu!
Otsu Minto!