Welcome back, master and lady!
Hello everybody!
Welcome to...
I am part-time worker!
I just noticed the crowbar.
Oh, I thought that was a gun.
No, I think it's a checkout thing.
Part-time maid.
No!
Full-time maid.
Part-time worker.
Full-time ghost.
Scan gun.
Half-life crowbar.
Yeah.
Hello Minty Fresh.
Hello!
I'm ready to watch part-time workery.
You should probably go to sleep.
Good morning!
Wow, the voice.
This is crazy.
Welcome.
I thought this was a super chat.
I thought you were wrong.
It's an ad for Ponti's Pizza.
That's a throwback.
No way.
Me cheese fries.
Part-time crowbar.
What if it's not a crowbar all the time?
What is it?
The other half of the time.
If not a crowbar all the time.
Wait, hold on.
Okay, nevermind.
A noodle.
Just a bar?
Just a bar.
A bar crow.
A bounty hunter?
Anyway,
I don't know much about this game.
I've seen like minimal clips from it.
In this game, you're living your grocery dreams.
And this is truly...
Now I'll be able to find out if I...
If being a grocer was my calling.
Working at a grocery store?
I mean, this is a conbini.
But it could have been my calling.
And I could have maybe lost out on the opportunity.
You know?
I don't know.
Dear ghost of the maid cafe, please haunt this conbini.
Amen.
Oddballboy thanks for the vibe gifted.
Ryan was fired last night.
Now he's like, I don't know.
He's a part-time cashier.
We'll see for sure.
Yeah.
I could have been a natural.
Did you see me?
Did you see me at the...
At the under...
Behind the counter?
And then I'd just be like...
Yoroshimase.
If I...
Well, actually, I was gonna say...
You know...
In a...
It's so funny.
Like at...
Some stores in Japan...
The girls...
The girls like...
Take the...
If you think of a nasally voice...
You know...
Just...
Crank it like...
Another...
Times ten.
And that's what they sound like.
Famichikiyokudasai.
Hai.
Kashi komarimashita.
But like...
So if you go...
It's really like the trendy kind of places.
I say like...
Ichimaru-kyu.
Like Shibuya 109.
You'll like go around there and they'll be like...
Irashimase.
Gorankudasai-masen.
You're welcome.
Like exactly like that.
Gochupansei no hafuneis.
That's exactly like what they sound like.
How immersive.
So...
I don't know why they do it.
I don't know why it's like a...
Why...
That's like the...
Fashion girly voice.
Anyway.
DLC voice pack.
Let's play.
There's stories to this?
Ho ho ho.
Looking forward to your customer service stream today.
Oh.
Customer Johnson.
Yes.
You would know customer service, wouldn't you?
Best of luck on Dressina.
Thank you.
I don't think I'll say anything.
I'm not sure if I'll still be streaming when she comes out.
But just in case, if anybody plays Blue Archive...
If I'm still streaming when Dressina is released on Blue Archive, please let me know.
And I will.
I will roll for her on stream.
I'm so excited.
Will do.
Okay.
I got into Blue Archive because of you?
I'm so excited.
Do you like it?
It's actually such a good story, even.
Hyper Miracle...
Hyper Miracle Positive Girl.
Thank you for the 10 gifted.
Are you part-time workerman?
I don't know what the class of...
I'm a...
I'm a girl boss.
I'm my own boss.
Oh my gosh.
I wonder if there's like VTuber MLMs.
Where I can be like, hey, girly.
Hey, girly.
Do you want to become your own boss?
Do you want to work your own hours?
Join my company.
Obviously.
SCAM?
Oh.
Society...
Can...
Always make it.
No.
Hmm.
I'm so excited.
I need to work this.
I need to workshop this.
Pyramids...
Pyramids Scheme?
No, no, no.
We're in Infinity Scheme.
Autosdenty, thank you for the 5 gifted.
Thank you so much.
Can I have a Karage-kun red, please?
Karage-kun.
The way you are working, you certainly seem like a warlord.
A one -woman company.
Is that a good thing?
Did you see that Oshinoko is getting a live-action series on Amazon Prime?
Yes!
I did see that because one of my...
Well, she's not an idol anymore but I really love her.
Her name is Ano-chan.
She'll be playing Memcho.
She plays Memcho.
And I remember when Ano, she dyed her hair blonde.
And I was like, what are you doing?
Why?
Why did you do this?
And then I was like, oh, it's for Memcho.
Okay, I'm not mad anymore.
I was like, no!
Because she's always had iconic black hair bob and it was so...
It's so cute.
And then she went blonde and I was like, no!
Of course, I still supported her through it but I was secretly a hater.
Toxic fan.
Spookily changing anonymous mooks?
What's that?
Minto, don't eat all the jellies in the store.
You can't.
Okay, I won't eat all the jellies.
Love you, Minto.
Thanks for the stream today.
Thank you!
Thank you for the super chat.
We would support Minto if you went blonde too.
You wouldn't.
She stops being an idol to pretend to be an idol on Amazon TV?
Yes.
Shall we get started?
Prologue.
I'm a part-time worker!
I like the music so much.
Ippatsu!
My name is Ippatsu.
I'm just an ordinary civilian.
I recently moved to the city.
Ichigeki.
I heard that it is generally unsafe and that many residents are a bit... a little bit confrontational.
Gyaru Minto.
Mint Pots.
Not to be confused with...
Mint Pants.
Today is my first day of part-time work.
I have to go now, so I won't be late.
Day 0, part-time mint.
Day 1, jobless mint.
The job location is just past the downtown core.
Okay.
Whoa.
Whoa, I'm headed to work.
Is this a horse?
Is this a horror game, secretly?
Oh.
What the?
Why is running weird?
I'm holding down shift, but nothing's working.
The sensitivity is... I wonder if I can turn it down.
Oh, there we go, there we go, there we go.
Sushi!
Is my work down this really spooky place?
I hope not.
Okay, good.
Oh.
Oh, it's bustling.
Okay, hold on.
Let me see if I can turn...
Oh, sensitivity.
Here we go.
Maybe, like, this much.
Why is there double music?
Oh, that's so much better, I think.
Oh, this is why young people lose days.
Damn it, shut up!
Hey, hey, hey, now.
Oh gosh, I'm getting, like, chill-as-art vibes from this.
Am I in the red light district?
Oh!
Oh my god, he's drunk!
I feel great.
Never mind, he's great!
Okay.
He's feeling good.
He's feeling himself.
Oh, Okonomiyaki.
I don't know the last time I had Okonomiyaki.
I can't even read that.
Would you recognize the red light district?
Um, I've been, well...
I've accidentally walked into, like, a street of love hotels once before.
This guy's hair!
What is going on?
It's like he's, his hair is alive!
It's like it's got little, it's made of bugs.
You know, oh my gosh, you know those, um...
Kazuma Kiryu is somewhere around here, true.
Oh gosh, Kabukicho.
Um, it was on accident!
I swear!
Do you guys know those, like, toys that are, like, it's little magnet pieces that you move around and, like, you give little characters beards and hair and mustaches and stuff like that?
That's what his hair looks like to me.
Wooly Willy!
Is that his name?
Not actually, oh gosh, this guy is...
I don't think he needs help at all.
I want what he's got.
Oh man.
Oh god!
I'm in, oh god!
Oh man.
We can see from his perspective.
Wait, hold on.
Oh man.
Wait, why do I have to be, like...
There we go.
Oh man.
Oh, sorry.
Every time I, like, go out of the game.
Every time I...
Oh man.
Lots of Okonomiyaki around here.
Oh, new person.
Hello, hello, hello.
Wait, are you not from Exit 8?
Or...
Yes, isn't this the guy from Exit 8?
I swear!
But he has hair this time.
This place is wild and...
Wait!
Oh, this is the guy from earlier!
Oh, I don't...
He still feels great, though.
Oh my god.
Okay.
I also...
I should get to work.
I should go to work.
He still feels great.
He's living his best life.
Let me know how the audio is, by the way.
If it's okay.
Oh!
Loading.
This is the convenience store where I will start working part-time.
I have to go say hello to the manager first.
Okay.
This is supposed to be...
Shinjuku.
It's just a little messed up.
It's Florida.
Oh, okay.
Um, hello.
Oh, it's you.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Oh my god.
My coworker is not okay.
Yes, I'll do my best.
No customers are here yet.
So you can take a look inside the convenience store before you start your work.
When you're ready, take your position.
Okay.
Guys, his hair...
His hair is really greased down.
Okay.
We're looking around, everybody.
Oh.
We have our hair...
Hairstyle.
Hair...
Hair stuff.
Wow.
Toilet paper.
We got...
Wait.
I think this is actually the...
Like, very close to the brand that I actually wear.
Because they're the only ones that...
The pink ones are the only ones that fit me.
That's so funny.
Adios.
Okay.
Thank you.
More hair stuff.
Cute.
Okay.
What magazines do we have?
Cosgal?
Oh.
Cosgal.
Wow.
Okay.
Neko Gumi.
Neru Neko.
I'd buy every one of those.
So cute.
Okay.
Oh.
We got manga and everything too.
Alright.
Where's the adult section?
Literally, like, right in here.
It's where they usually sell Playboy and stuff.
As well.
Oh.
This is the restroom.
All is well.
I'm getting...
I feel like I'm in a Chilla's Art game.
I'm not gonna lie.
I'm a little scared that it's gonna turn bad on me.
Coffee.
Snacks.
Oh no.
I mean tea.
Hit.
What are these?
Oh.
It's energy.
Jelly.
I'll take...
What is Akashi's flavor?
Anyway...
Wasabi flavored potato chips.
Lots of snacks.
What's these ones?
Oh.
Just health stuff.
What's in here?
Oh.
Ice cream.
Oh yeah.
Here.
This is so nice.
Best Zero!
Karubito.
Love that.
Vivicorn, thanks for the gifted!
Okay.
Oh wait, what's in here?
More ice cream?
Nice.
They're stocked.
This is the easiest job ever.
Everything is already so stocked.
We'll be fine.
Oh, what have we got?
Bananas, apples...
Egg...
Some bento...
Sandwich!
I love tamago sandal.
Some onigiri.
Hell yeah.
My favorite?
I don't remember which place it is.
But it's a tamago... it's an egg sandwich with...
But it also has...
Ham and cucumber.
It's my favorite thing ever.
I don't remember which one it was.
Maybe it was Family Mart.
Lucky, I think I'm... Oh, get into position.
What about the oden?
Oh, it's just...
It's just a big old...
Okay, there's not much... I mean, there's a lot going on in there.
Wait, hold on.
I'm not ready yet.
I gotta meet my coworker.
Oh!
Nina!
I guess you're the new part-timer.
I'm done for today, but it's nice to meet you.
Yes.
Nice to meet you too.
Do they allow miniskirts at work?
Okay.
It'll be a tough job, but good luck.
I like this guy.
I swear, I think this is the same exact layout as the konbini.
I mean, I know it's like konbini is like, you know...
Oh, I forgot the back room too.
Don't smile at me like that.
He looks like a Ken doll.
Why is one of it... I think he...
Oh my god, he's just so shiny.
Oh my god.
He uses the most amount of gel.
I'm about to look in here.
I think this is the exact layout of the one konbini store.
Oh, was there...
Did I imagine seeing something over here?
Okay.
The Chela's Art game.
But like I said, I know it's like...
Konbini...
Konbini stores are pretty similar, you know, but...
Thank you for your hard work!
Oh my gosh.
Just stormed out of there.
Good night!
Thank you for your hard work!
I'll leave you to your cashier duties.
Actually, I've got some important things to take care of.
But I have not been trained!
I'm sorry, but you'll have to take care of things on your own.
But I haven't been...
I'm going to be on my own for my first day?
Don't worry.
It's a simple job.
I'll give you instructions over the phone.
So take it easy.
Alright then.
Please take care of everything.
Oh no!
Manager-san!
Where are you going though?
Where are you going?
Oh.
I must protect it.
Wait, what is he protecting?
What is he protecting?
Huh?
What do you mean by that?
Karaoke?
There he goes.
I'm stuck by an invisible wall.
Well, there's stuff out here too.
Coin lockers...
Oh!
How do I answer the phone?
How do I...
Oh!
Chocolate sauce on his head.
Can you hear me?
First, hold the item scanner in your hand.
When the customer brings an item to you, scan it with the mouse.
The scanner.
Pretty simple, huh?
Okay.
Scan.
Nobody's here though, right?
What's up, Min?
Good luck with the new job.
Hopefully nothing weird happens.
Scan.
Oh!
Okay.
That's how I scan stuff.
I like lunge it.
Oh my god!
Every time Min says, did I see something, I remember something.
I remember the egg in Outer Wilds.
Welcome!
This guy looks normal.
Ping pong.
Oh my goodness.
Okay.
You're doing well.
Why am I still on the phone with you?
Working the cash register adds to the store's good rating.
Oh, I see.
Oh.
My stocking.
I mean, monitoring work is going well here as well.
Now let's deal with the troublesome customers.
Equip a weapon and beat them up?
It says...
That's what it says!
It's not just me!
I get to attack people?
Oh, that's what the crowbar is for!
Who's a troublesome customer?
Wait, who didn't...
Oh!
Oh, that was me.
Litter!
Any troublesome customers around?
Oh.
How are you?
Are you a troublesome customer?
This guy looks like bad news.
This guy looks like some bad news.
I'm being judgemental.
What are you doing?
Are you trying to pick a fight?
Ah!
I'm part-time worker!
You're doing...
You're doing well.
I'm part-time worker!
Letting troublesome customers loiter adds to the store's bad rating.
Customers are not, in fact, always right.
Yes!
Oh my gosh, that lucky guy.
Everybody stand in line.
So beat up the troublesome ones.
Oh my gosh.
This game feels so personal.
I'm done with my work.
I'm feeling lazy.
I'm feeling lazy now.
Let's go out for a drink.
Is this place not 24-7?
Oh, just kidding.
Actually, I have to go because I got a call from HQ.
Next, use your store scan skill.
You'll be able to see the movements of all the troublesome customers who are hidden in seconds.
What?
You can't use that?
It's an essential skill for convenience store workers.
Meow.
Whoa.
I just saw the vision.
Oh, this guy looks like some bad news.
This guy looks like bad news.
Get out!
I'm touching worker!
I don't even know what he was going to do.
Oh, he was smoking.
No smoking on the premises!
Looks like you've mastered store scan.
Now you're a full-fledged convenience store worker.
You've got it from here.
Boku arubaita!
This is actually how it is on the JP language setting.
Thank you.
Boku arimaita!
Kome fukuro.
I think that's the dev.
I'm ready.
It's taking some time.
Now we can start work approximately 15 minutes, approximately 30 minutes.
Approximately 60 minutes of work?
Wait, is this like real time?
It's like an actual hour or like a 15 minute game?
Yes!
Real time!
Yeah, we'll do the 60 then.
Work until the end of the day.
Okay.
But there were some other question mark things.
Hello!
What a peaceful quiet evening.
You!
Hello, person.
I think I'm just, you know...
I think they're fine.
Probably.
Oh, that person is jazzy.
Hello!
They got a nice little track going on.
Ping pong!
Oh, thank you!
Oh, okay.
I'll pick that up, don't worry.
Don't worry.
Okay.
Bye bye!
What are you doing?
Are you...
No loitering!
Oh.
Why is everybody throwing stuff at me?
Oh my gosh, wait.
There's already so many people here.
Ah!
Okay.
Why are you...
What the?
Where did the bad people go?
Oh my god.
Stop throwing!
Everybody's rude!
Cone man!
Bye bye!
Is he actually gonna buy something?
Or...
Hello?
Beep!
Yes!
Oh!
Nice!
Tits!
Okay.
Oh, this guy...
What do you want?
What are you doing?
Dude, you're not allowed behind here!
Are you being a loiterer?
Where is all the people?
What is that person doing over there?
What are you doing here?
Get out of here!
Oh, maybe he was fine.
Um...
I'm sweeping...
Just stand on him so they don't notice, you know?
Ping-pong!
I like how I scan this, but they don't pay.
Yeah.
What are you doing?
What are you getting?
Pink pants, huh?
Yeah?
That's right.
Oh, that guy is walking way too slowly.
Hey!
I am Pachai Walker!
No slow...
What the?
Who's laughing at me?
Um...
I'm coming!
Okay.
Why?
He was a slow...
I don't know.
He was giving me a bad vibe.
What's going on?
Wait!
Who's laughing at...
We have three people!
Why did you just throw my...
Oh my god.
Ah!
I'm Pachai Walker!
I'm sorry.
Don't throw your stuff at me!
Rude!
We still have two sillies around.
Oh, sorry.
I just realized the chat is like...
Oh my god.
This guy over here!
Oh!
I'm Pachai Walker!
Hi!
Ah!
Go!
I'm Pachai Walker!
Why does this look like Hi Guy?
It won't open!
I'm Pachai Walker!
One second.
I'm going to move you guys over just a little... just a tad.
So you can see our points and stuff.
Yes?
There you go.
That should be better.
My apple!
Hello!
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Sorry for the wait.
Don't worry about it.
That guy looks really sussy.
I'm Pachai Walker!
I don't know anymore.
Oops.
Sorry.
Hold on a second.
One second.
Okay.
Hello!
Oh!
Just...
Why...
Why did you shrug at me?
Get out of here, weirdo!
No running!
Get out of here!
You're in...
No running!
No running in my store!
People are stressing me out, you guys.
This is...
Okay.
Beep.
Thank you.
Pet time worker.
I'm Pet Time Worker!
Yes!
Welcome!
Oh!
What's wrong?
Are you embarrassed?
Maybe you should buy some water, guy.
All you bought is Chuhai and cola.
Turn it down just...
Oh!
Excuse you!
What?
What was that?
Did you just...
Did he just give me a middle finger?
Everybody's so rude to the part-time workers.
I'm sorry.
They don't know what it's like.
You must work...
I think...
I believe everybody should work retail, you know?
At least once.
Oh, it's an okay sign?
Oh, okay.
Hello, hello.
Maybe he was just like, yeah, this is the good stuff.
Maybe they were really impressed with the store.
Uh-oh.
That guy's hair is too yellow.
Did you just go...
My bad.
I dropped the thing on the floor.
Oh!
I'm sorry.
Hello.
Oh, maybe he's normal.
Do you need hair supplies?
Okay.
Fizzy water.
You're normal.
Alright, get out of here.
I judged him.
You guys, I misjudged him.
And I should have judged this guy because he threw all of his stuff at me.
I don't have to, like, restock stuff in this game, right?
Oh, there he is.
There he is.
There's so many people here.
Woah!
Hey!
No!
Matt!
You picked that up!
Oh!
You!
Your thing!
It fell in front!
Two more things?
What?
Oh my god.
Wait.
Where's the...
Where's the one more thing?
Oh!
Here!
What?
She's throwing on both sides.
Hello!
Irasshaimase!
Fukuro go ryo desu ka?
No!
Okay.
Oh!
What will you do for your next trick?
Wait.
What was that?
Ah!
Huh?
This guy is just trying to rob us!
Look.
You say it's heavy, but like, I got it and I screwed up.
I was able to take care of it with just a crowbar.
This guy is weak.
One more thing.
Oh gosh.
Oh my god.
There's a whole line you got.
He's dead?
I sure hope so.
Oh, what did you do?
Why is everybody, like, flashing me?
Uh oh.
We have a little crazy, kooky person going on.
Where are they?
Kooky person, where are you?
Over there?
Oh!
That's not my property.
I don't care about that.
I don't own the parking lot, do I?
What are they doing out there anyway?
Are you eating the dirt?
Earthy?
Why was I right?
Actually, what's wrong with him eating dirt?
That's his prerogative.
Look at this guy.
Teeny weeny here.
That's his prerogative.
Small.
Oh, someone's mad at me.
Why are you mad?
Is it because I took too long?
Eating dirt is illegal.
Oh, this guy... Hey!
Quick, march!
What a jerk!
I hope you choke on this gum!
Asshole!
Hello.
Thank you.
I called him a teeny weeny, but...
Short people, am I right?
He's actually so nice!
Have a good day.
What the?
Is it this guy?
Oh, maybe not.
Maybe he's just a slow walker.
I think I gotta get rid of our dirt eater, you guys.
I think I gotta get rid of the dirt eater.
I'm gonna whack him in the ass.
I am part-time worker!
How many points would you give me for that?
Where's the... Where's the other silly person?
It's not you, is it?
It's not this guy, is it?
Rip dirt eater.
Wait, where's the other one?
Are you stealing from me?
There's one more item.
Oh, here.
This guy!
What are you doing?
Delicious.
Umai, umai, umai.
I'm Perch, I'm Wacker!
Gah.
Yeah.
Oh my gosh.
Oh.
Everybody's really eccentric here.
Another one?
Everybody is troublemaker.
Have a good day.
Oh, it's a person...
What is...
Oh, you got a lot of stuff.
Yeah, very good.
Very nice.
Just a normal day.
What is...
What's like the most eccentric...
Or like...
Like what's...
The craziest person you have ever had come into your work before?
If you like worked retail or a restaurant or anywhere.
Thumbs up.
Hey!
This guy's a...
Sorry, it took so long.
Sorry.
Now we have two crazy people.
Hey, what are you doing over here, man?
Sleepy!
I'm Perch, I'm Wacker!
Wait.
No, that's the guy walking away.
Oh, he's in the back.
He's in the back.
Outside.
He's outside.
Excuse me.
You're here?
Oh, you're here.
What are you doing?
Oh, so sitting is a crime now?
This guy's just chilling.
I'm sorry, guy.
Gotta get your toesies.
No!
Feet out!
I managed a GameStop for like a decade before going to school.
We don't have time for all the stories.
I wish I had a crowbar.
The guy came in right before... what did a haggle on price?
Oh my god.
Wait, did you say before a blizzard?
I'm still in a dream, dirt.
Toes out is a crime.
It is in Japan, actually.
Never wear sandals in Japan.
Oh, you're back!
Oh my god.
Who's laughing at me?
Cookie.
Oh.
Look at me.
Yeah, look at your face!
Where is the other person?
What?
How is this a crime?
Oh my god, she's awesome!
This isn't a crime!
She's a nice place to practice!
This is... oh, there's... okay.
You guys, our reputation is going down the drain.
Oh.
You?
What are you... what are you doing?
Stop it!
Stop searching!
Oh!
Oh my god!
Yay!
Oh!
Yeah!
Wow!
Watch your fingers, sir!
Oh my god!
Public!
This store is insane!
This store is absolutely insane!
Uh-oh, we have a line.
People are gonna start getting mad at me.
Ping-pong!
I'm telling you, the way this guy is walking... he's gonna mug me!
This guy's about to... I think this guy's about to...
Oh.
Oh my god!
Wait!
This is an actual crime!
Get out of my...
Ah!
Anyway.
Continue scanning.
This guy once asked for pepperoni but was... did you say he was vegan?
I think that lady is causing trouble.
The lady in pink?
Yeah, we'll get her.
We'll get her.
You?
Oh my god!
You just eat my apples!
Grandma!
This isn't home!
I am proud of you!
I'm afraid to hit the elderly!
Okay.
Oh, you got a lot of stuff there, buddy.
This is a convenience store.
Not, you know...
Not your grocery store.
Okay.
All is well in the neighborhood.
Rip grandma.
You know what?
Yeah, rip grandma.
She was not cognitively there.
I think she's lived enough life on this earth.
This is not Aeon.
Yeah!
Thumbs up!
Oh, my bad.
I was just... Oh my gosh, that guy is back there.
Drinking my drinks!
Hello.
Hold on.
One moment, please.
Delicious.
I'm part-time worker!
So sorry about the blood.
Anyway...
Beep.
Zoro?
That guy?
Yes.
Everybody is getting noodles.
Please, eat something healthier.
What's wrong with this guy?
Oh.
Nothing is wrong with this guy.
Okay.
Maybe something... Maybe a little something is wrong with this guy.
Give him a knuckle sandwich.
I wish I could use my fist.
The crowbar is fine, but...
Sorry.
I didn't realize this game would be so... Intensive.
But I... Doesn't Chibi Binto have a crowbar?
You're right!
Uh-oh.
We got...
Oh!
What?
This is not a crime.
This is a show!
Yeah!
Let her spin!
I'm part-time worker!
Hey!
Where's the other crazy person?
How did I miss that?
Oh.
Wait.
How am I supposed to... Huh?
Huh?
Why were they... Oh my god!
He's there!
Wait.
How am I supposed to get that other person?
I am part-time worker!
Oh!
Oh my god!
I'm a superhero!
No!
Get out of my store!
I am part-time worker!
Oh gosh!
I don't think we have the insurance for this!
Oh god!
I am part-time worker!
No!
You know what?
It's fine.
Oh my god!
I am part-time worker!
I'm so sorry, sir.
You've been waiting so patiently.
You've been waiting so... I don't know where the other person is.
I think it was really far away.
I don't think...
Oh hello, bucket.
Hello.
Why are you mad at me?
Look to your left.
This guy?
Look at this body.
Oh...
All he's doing... This is not a crime.
I am part-time worker!
You know what?
This place is...
This place is like...
So strict!
This is, I guess, typical Nihon, right?
Hello!
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you for your patience.
Welcome.
Yes, yes.
Do you have a point card?
Oh no.
Okay.
Yes, yes.
Do you want me to warm you up?
Oh.
Okay.
Got a lot of hair...
You bought a lot of hair stuff for someone who's literally bald.
But okay.
Oh my god!
Was that you?
Goodbye?
What does that mean?
I am part-time worker!
What does that even mean?
Don't shame him.
Maybe he just likes how it feels on his head, you know?
It's for his friend, obviously.
Well, the ceiling is not fixed, but...
The rubble has been cleaned up, which is pretty nice.
We have someone around, and I don't know where they are.
Goodbye!
Like, what does that mean?
Oh!
No exercising!
I'm part-time worker!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Is this...
Oh.
Wait, hold on, sir.
Um, actually, I can't use my scan, so...
Is that the person?
Ew, what's that sound?
Hi guy, get out of the water!
I am part-time worker!
Oh my gosh!
Death stranding!
Hold on, I think it's over here.
Oh!
I'm rooting for you.
I love you.
I...
I am part-time worker!
Tain, go!
It's basically saying, like...
Live...
Whoa!
Wait a second.
I don't think you're supposed to be...
They don't know.
How would they know?
I am part-time worker!
So they did find out.
You're not a part-time worker.
Look out!
I am part-time worker!
Get out of my door!
Hello.
Excuse me.
You've been waiting so patiently.
Hmm?
Hm?
I hear other music.
Oh my god!
They...
How is this... how is this neighborhood real?
I had a video.
Game store had someone move a ceiling panel to crawl into the store room.
What?
That's wild!
Wait, the music is kind of beautiful.
Oh my god!
Is that me?
Oh, sorry, sorry.
There's a ghost!
Who's throwing stuff now?
That guy!
Oh my god...
You guys, we're in trouble.
Hey!
Are they
gonna go make some mochi or something?
Oh my god!
Oh, he's done!
He's out of here!
Thing one or thing two?
I am part-time worker!
This is impressive!
I'm part-time...
Oh my god, Hanabi!
It's not the 4th of July!
I'm part-time worker!
Oh my god, she haunted our store!
We'll let her go.
She haunted our store!
Don't mind the lights.
It's just our president ghost.
Oh, Conan's back.
Oh, she's also coming back.
I think she likes it here.
If our...
I mean, let's give it a try.
You know what?
Honestly, a place being a haunted spot, that's like a novelty, you know?
What's going on?
Oh, we have an actual Karen now.
Okay, hold on.
Oh!
Miss?
Ma'am?
It'll bring more customers if they know that.
It's like people will start coming just for the novelty of it being haunted, you know?
Don't we all wish we could crowbar Karens?
Oh!
I guess I have to get rid of her, don't I?
It was an honor meeting you.
Why are your eyes...
Are you even real?
Oh, whoops.
I tried to scan her.
What?
I'm a ghost!
Oh my god.
You guys, we have too many...
I wish I was dead.
We have a guy over here.
Bench pressing.
What did the robot... What did the robot do?
Uh oh.
Wait.
Who else do we have?
Being a nuisance around here.
Oh, you!
Are you... What are you doing?
Okay, I'll check you out.
I'll check you out.
We have three people?
If you bite it, you bought it.
Well, I'll check you out.
Oh yeah.
Oh gosh, we're losing... We're losing... We're losing credibility points.
That guy is just grilling on the street.
That's... That's unsanitary!
We'll get him.
Hey!
Coming through.
Sam Bridges!
Sam Bridges, I didn't get any deliveries!
I'm Valentine Walker!
The slow-mo into like the fast is so disorienting.
I don't like it very much.
Oh!
Uh... This person's just laying on the ground.
It's the thumbnail!
I'm gonna cool you down.
I am Valentine Walker!
Oh my god.
I am Part-Time Walker!
Part-Time Wacker?
Hey!
What are you doing back here?
I'm Part-Time Wacker!
The office work.
Yeah, this is pretty much it, you know?
What?
What do you cut down my tree for?
Spray them with herbicide?
No!
The city needs trees!
I am Part-Time Wacker!
Damn.
What are you doing?
I put up a fucking flag!
I can't be mad at him!
I am Part-Time Wacker!
I have been wondering... Damn!
She's got a... a caboose!
Okay, excuse me.
Sorry it took so long.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Yes!
Thank you very much!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Ooh!
Maybe... What are you... Why are you shrugging at me?
You need better... healthier habits, buddy.
I am the booty.
Can you blame me?
Banana flavored?
What were those?
Chips?
Hmm...
Egg croquette?
Oh my god!
Uh...
I'll get her in just a second.
Aww...
Banana chips.
But they were like banana fl... I don't think they were banana chips.
I think they were banana flavored chips.
Jacksepticeye.
Lady, I think you need a rest.
Ping-pong!
Oh, come on.
Everybody's so rude.
Everybody's so... rude.
Get out of my store!
I'm sure it will get a lot of attention.
Nobody saw that.
Delicious.
You need to pay for that!
Alright, guys.
Oh, where are you going?
You're not allowed to sit at a seat anymore!
What is this?
This is a dictatorship!
I swear!
You're not allowed to do anything!
Don't push him.
I like our skylight.
Oh!
I feel at home in this corner.
Okay.
Um...
I don't even know what to say.
You should sit, not sleep.
I guess so.
Uh-oh.
That guy...
That guy coming through, he's trouble.
That guy is gonna be trouble.
What?
There's a whole car!
Who's driving in?
All he's doing is smoking.
How will
I financially recover from this?
Ah!
Oh.
Everybody, ignore the construction.
Oh my god.
Ma'am, I will get with you in just one second, ma'am.
There's two of them in a row!
Sleepy!
New door.
Yeah.
Just...
It goes perfectly with our skylight, you know?
Hello.
Yes,
yes.
Thank you.
Thank you for shopping here.
All your money will go towards our new...
Our new building.
Did that guy just...
That guy did not walk through the door.
That guy literally walked through the hole in the wall.
I see him over there.
I'm not gonna let you.
What are you gonna do?
Make a mochi or something?
I won't let you, old man.
I am a part-time worker.
I won't let you.
Come out.
Oh my god.
I didn't make fun of you!
I'm so sorry!
Oh.
Wait.
Sorry, I had the wrong person.
Oh my god.
Is that guy bad or not?
He's just standing there.
She called me out!
I'm sorry I called you!
A tiny weedy...
Oh.
There he goes.
I guess he didn't have...
anything.
You guys, I think people are getting weirder and weirder.
We're halfway through, I think.
No standing!
What are you gonna do?
Smash me?
Don't smash my... I'm curious what he's about to do, though.
He's walk... Oh.
What are you about to do?
Don't smash the wall.
Now I have a third door.
Sorry.
Sorry, so sorry, everybody.
Where's your stuff?
Oh, sorry.
He got really impatient.
Hi!
Oh.
Where did he come from?
Where did he go?
Cotton eyes... Joe.
Do you want a drink with that?
Or...
I guess penguins don't have money.
He walks with such swagger.
Okay, good.
I'm glad that the...
Okay.
Hello.
Who's being a nuisance?
Is it that old man?
Oh my gosh, old people are such a nuisance.
Oh.
Oh, bucket.
I know you can't see.
It's not your fault.
Thank you.
Matara, don't listen.
Oh gosh, we're getting docked.
Oh, don't be mad at me.
I'm sorry.
It's my first day.
Please.
Oh.
Oh my... Oh my god.
I'm part-time worker.
Not the fami-tiki.
Wow.
Hey, hey, hey.
What are we wowing about?
What are you doing?
No running on the premises.
I'm part-time worker.
Oh my god.
Yuru camp.
It's warm.
Shiny days.
Atarashii kaise.
It's not the... the mountains.
Oh my gosh.
I can't believe we have a new entrance and people just use it.
Hello.
Oh, that... I just watched that guy walk behind there.
What the hell?
I just watched him walk into the back.
These people have no nerve.
Like, no shame.
Nothing.
They're just like...
Just like, yeah, I'm gonna... No... What's the word?
You know when...
Oh.
Is that a Tengu?
It absolutely is.
That's a normal thing.
Oh my gosh.
Thank you.
Penguin was a manager.
You can see in the employee room.
He was clearing out the expired product.
You're right, Felix.
You're right.
Wait.
Does that mean I would have gotten fired?
How do I like...
Oh gosh.
We have a lot of people.
Okay.
Uh-oh.
We're getting... We're getting bonked.
We're getting bonked.
Excuse me.
Oh.
No sitting!
I'm part-time worker!
No being in the back rooms!
Oh.
I was so drunk, I couldn't move at all.
No!
No laying!
I'm a part-time worker!
Who else is around?
Oh.
Uh, wait.
Oh!
This person again!
No having fun!
I am part-time worker!
Okay.
All is well.
Hello.
Welcome... Oh!
Welcome!
Sorry.
Sorry it took so long.
Okay.
Everybody loves this place!
We have so many likes on Facebook!
Ping-pong!
I worked at a 7-Eleven before and I can confirm...
It's pretty trash working there as a retail...
Wait, like...
Japanese 7-Eleven?
Or somewhere else 7-Eleven.
Ping-pong!
Guy with a backpack.
Oh!
What is he gonna steal?
We'll get him in a second.
We have so many people to take care of.
Oh, shoot.
What is he gonna steal?
Sand bridges?
Hello.
Wow, that's a lot of junk food you got there.
Okay.
Thank you.
Do you think he's coming back?
I can hear someone walking back there.
Oh!
They really just use the new entrances.
They don't even...
Hahaha.
You don't have to judge them, too.
No!
I'm not judging.
One second!
Canadian 7-Eleven.
I am sadly Canadian.
Hahaha.
I'm sorry.
I'll be in Canadia.
I'll be in Canadia this weekend.
Wait, we have two people?
Oh!
Let's go.
You are not...
Oh.
What a convenient sensor.
Ah!
I think I saw this guy.
What are you doing?
He's just standing and giving a middle finger.
Yes.
You can't even...
Oh my God.
This is obscene.
This is the worst one yet.
I was just holding up my finger.
Hahaha.
Two of them.
Oh my gosh, we have a long line.
Looks like Raiden's back there.
Hello!
I'm so sorry!
Thank you for waiting!
Thank you so much for being patient!
Hi!
Dozo!
Retail workers with crowbars is too powerful.
I feel really powerful.
Wow, we have a long line.
Oh gosh, you guys.
I'm going to get fired.
They're going to be like, you have not served enough people.
Oh my gosh.
Hi!
Welcome!
Oh, cookies.
More cookies.
Ice cream.
Okay.
She's having a good night.
Okay, onigiri.
Yuhai.
Yuhi.
Hi!
Oh, I keep forgetting to bring the banana chips.
They just keep coming.
They don't stop coming.
So far, everything's very quiet.
What's that guy doing over there?
Also, another guy with a backpack.
What is he going to steal?
Thank you!
What is he going to steal from us?
Don't jinx it.
I know.
There's a guy that just walked back.
He's going to do something silly.
Hello!
Hi!
Okay, next!
Uh-oh.
Time to go be the silly police, everybody.
That's more like what this game is.
We're the silly police.
Where was he?
Where'd he go?
Wait, where'd the backpack man go?
I saw him.
Huh?
Is that him over there?
So glad we have a...
Oh, no?
Huh?
Lady eating?
Oh.
I am Captain Walker!
Now we have another one.
You!
I don't know where you're off to!
You haven't technically done anything wrong yet, but...
Oh!
Oh, my God.
Two of them.
He's putting broccoli on...
I must plant broccoli.
There's dirt on the other side!
I am Captain Walker!
Boo!
Another silly?
Is it you?
Oh, yep.
I am Perch!
I am Wacker!
Why would you put broccoli on the seats, though?
Hello.
Please, one moment.
I have two silly people around.
Oh.
You're eating hair products!
Are you outside or are you in my...
Oh, no.
You're outside.
One second.
I'll come get you in just a second.
I'll help you in one moment.
Come on.
Go!
Bye, bye!
Wonderful.
Wow, they're leaving, like, little love notes for me!
That makes me feel so bad.
Okay.
Hai, I'm so sorry.
Oh.
What?
We have more silly?
Oh, eww.
In front of my face?
I'm just having no shame!
Let's see, where's our other guy?
Is it you?
No, you're just slow.
Oh!
This guy is whacking the trees!
I'm going to cut down and spray them with herbicide!
Why do you hate the environment?
Minecraft?
Grandma!
Grandma, what are you...
What are you hitting, for real?
Grandma!
What are you...
Grandma, this is obscene!
Grandma!
Sorry,
my depth perception.
My depth perception.
Okay!
Wait, there's one more?
Oh my god.
No!
I'm sorry, lady.
You have six things!
No!
Not the microwave!
I am part-time worker!
Oh my god.
I just saw that guy up here.
What the...
Part-time worker!
Get
out of here!
I am part-time worker!
Oh my god.
What are you doing?
I am part-time worker!
Where are these guys coming from?
Oh.
He's bench pressing...
Oh my god.
Bandles everywhere!
Not even...
I can't even...
I can't even poop in peace!
Guy in a Speedo goggle and swimming cap?
While you were shopping?
Swimming on the ground aisles.
Wait.
No way.
Are you serious?
Are you kidding about that?
Oh my gosh.
They don't stop.
Come on.
Wait.
I think I just saw...
No?
No.
I'm getting bonked.
But I don't see where they are at all.
Oh.
Hmm.
What?
I am part-time worker!
No!
Oh.
Uh.
Did I get hurt too?
Or on accident?
Wait.
What are you doing?
Stop eating!
I am part-time worker!
Oh my god.
It's really revving up.
Get off your phone!
I am part-time worker!
Double kill!
No Karens!
Oh my gosh.
They are flipping me off again.
I don't even want to see the second one.
There is just one left.
Oh wait.
I think he is in here.
I wonder if they have any underwear.
What?
Perfect!
They want my underwear.
Girl.
This lady has been waiting forever.
What?
She is like, I have two things.
Please.
Please help me.
We have three!
Three silly people.
I wouldn't put my underwear in there.
Oh my gosh.
Four silly people!
Nice ass!
I am part-time worker!
Uh.
Oh.
Everybody is just lingering around.
I am part-time worker!
installment!
Oh!
Don't throw your crotch in me.
In me face!
Where was the other one?
I have one left.
Oh.
There he is.
Wait.
Oh.
I think he is in the backroom.
I am part-time worker!
Okay.
Wait.
Still not...
There's only one guy?
Oh, you!
Okay, he was sleepy.
Now he's fine.
I actually helped him sleep, you know?
I helped him sleep.
He'll be sleeping real good now, you know?
Hey!
I just saw that!
I just saw that guy walking to the back.
You bitch!
Come here!
Another one?
Where are you at?
Oh.
No grilling on the premises!
Peace... and quiet.
Oh my god.
There's no customers?
What is that guy doing?
I was gonna say there's no customers, there's no...
What are you doing?
Oh, okay.
You're just leaving.
I got you.
Don't mind the blood in the aisles, everybody.
I've killed everybody.
Where are you going?
You're only sorry because you got caught.
Worthy.
That's my dinner, too!
No eating my dinner.
Hello, hello, hello.
Sorry for the wait.
Wow, that's a sweet, huh?
Have a fun night.
Is it that lady?
Is she the problem?
Oh, peace!
Peace!
One more.
Oh!
Oh my god!
Everybody here is insane!
Work on your technique!
Is it you?
Delicious!
It's hair medicine!
Oh my gosh.
We had a moment to rest, and that was it.
Oh my god.
Oh, wrong thing.
Here we go.
What are you doing?
What are you about to do?
I caught you!
Red-handed.
What are you doing?
Can I get this guy?
I've tasted blood and I want more.
Where are they?
Where's the other...
Oh.
Wait, there's one more?
Oh my god!
Nothing like skipping out on the toilet.
What does that... What does that mean?
Hello, sir.
Thank you for being so patient.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Oh my gosh.
We have a long line now, guys.
Okay.
Maybe please learn to put your belongings down more gently.
So they don't fall, you know.
Hi!
Okay.
Nice.
Onigiri.
To my left?
Nothing to my left.
We're good.
We have no troublemakers right now.
The guy who was sleeping on the shelves?
Well, he's changed his way.
You know.
He's changed his ways.
He's mended his issues, you know.
Shift is almost over.
I know, right?
Crazy.
I'm learning the real retail experience.
I've worked retail.
Okay.
You tried.
You're currently dancing and spraying hairspray.
Absolutely.
Whoa!
How did you carry all that?
This guy is a... fun guy.
Oh.
Okay.
Welcome!
Wow.
Peach-flavored potato chips.
I'd try it.
Okay.
Yes, sir?
The way he, like, slid up was so funny.
Do you like the beach?
I just watched that guy trip outside.
One moment, sir.
I must take care of some riff-raff.
No sitting!
I am part-time worker!
Where?
You?
I'm part-time worker!
I like how he increasingly gets, like, more and more upset.
Where's the other one, though?
Oh.
Aw, I hate punishing this guy.
You're so awesome!
I support what you do!
I'm part-time worker!
What the?
You dropped your sensor.
Grandma!
Yes?
I'm part-time worker!
They dropped their sensor!
What's there?
Oh.
I'm part-time worker!
Destroy all robots!
Grandma's a rebel.
Feels just like home.
You'll...
I am...
Suit your shade!
Oh.
I'm part-time worker!
Let's do it again!
More?
Oh.
Where?
Oh, you?
I am part-time worker!
Why does getting rid of that guy spark joy?
I'm part-time worker!
No!
Wait, what's that sound?
What's that sound?
Stop!
Why are you all so obs...
Oh.
Oh, inside...
Get out of here!
I'm part-time worker!
What were you looking at?
Oh, gosh!
I am part-time worker!
Oh my god, everybody's coming out at the end of my shift!
Um.
Oh, you?
I am part-time worker!
I'm part-time worker!
Oh.
Tick-tick.
I am part-time worker!
There's so many people over here.
Wow, this is a popular area.
I am part -time worker!
I'm dancing on the computer!
Oh, sorry.
Whiplash, for real.
I am part-time worker!
You guys...
Oh.
He put up a fucking flag!
Well, sorry about that.
I know it was a tough day.
Yeah.
It's true that you have to deal with troublesome customers.
But if you don't like it, that's fine.
You can just beat them up.
Take care of yourself.
By the way, I'm going on vaca...
I mean, a business trip.
Could you take care of the store for a month or so?
Is that in real time?
I'm counting on you, part-timer!
Ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha...
Ha...
I am part-time worker!
Yeah!
Okay.
I'm definitely quitting this job.
I'm part-time...
Wow, it's the best ending ever.
I feel so... validated.
Ha...
Oh...
I said that guy, his lip color didn't...
Good shopper.
Oh?
Oh, we missed...
Ordinary people hanging around a convenience store.
A mystery.
Yoga!
Stray, stray person.
Penguin cute!
Voluntary restraints.
Broccoli!
I'll never allow plants!
Reading in bed!
Cat buyer.
Idiot!
Ha-ha-ha!
Fool!
Ha -ha -ha!
Female ghost!
Whee!
Kick cash?
Safe cracker?
Open muscle!
Do you want to heat it up?
Destroy!
A pawn from another store.
I wanted to know if it was extra.
Stuffed toy!
Robbery!
Fireworks!
Leaving a restaurant without paying bill!
Damn flag!
Write jointly!
People who were made fun of on the internet!
Soup!
Fascinating use of hips!
R18!
The strong old man!
Rebel!
Revolution!
Living in a corner!
Dynamic entry!
Superhero!
Huh!
I'm stumped!
Live shopkeeper!
Push-up!
Running along a wall!
Cigarette in the restroom!
Uncle wall breaker!
Yankee!
The worst brothers!
People who can't open the door!
Bench press!
Sleep!
Drunkard!
Smartphone in the restroom!
Noisy person!
Underwear thief!
Person who keeps people safe!
Sleeping films!
Baseball boy 1?
Claimor?
Baseball boy 2?
Chef!
Shoplifting!
Dance!
Warming up exercises!
Person who lost a key!
A robot that says the right things!
Taking a break!
People running around screaming!
Dumbbell!
Earthies!
This is a wild checking out!
And you!
The manager extreme!
Literal shoplifting!
The end!
So there were a few that we didn't... that we actually didn't get!
Huh...
Hmm...
Piano man was good...
I don't...
We ended up...
Oh wait...
Well, we did kind of get rid of him.
Hahaha!
There were a few that we didn't get!
Should we try again?
Yeah, I was thinking maybe like the 15 minute round to see...
Oh, let's see...
Hold on...
Picture book...
Revolution...
Living in a corner...
These names are so funny!
Hahaha!
Hold on though...
This one!
Bad!
One second...
Hahaha!
Oh, I'm a little...
I'm a little off...
But...
Hahaha!
Female ghost!
It's me!
Hahaha!
It's like the pop-out type...
Oh, yeah, I guess I should fix that too, right?
One second...
You're all even...
Try to align it as perfectly as possible...
As...
Oh...
Possible...
Hey!
Hahaha!
Ready for something kinda cool?
Boo!
Now it's the pop-out type, for real!
I'm tiny ghost!
Brr!
Ghost!
Hahaha!
Haunted check key...
Oh my gosh, this is like a check key!
Oh!
Hey!
For real!
Wow!
Oh my gosh!
Okay, how do I go back to normal?
There we go.
Ghost checky!
I love damn flag.
That might be my favorite one.
Damn flag!
See, this one's a mystery one.
Um...
I also like this one too.
The middle finger one.
Um...
Two...
Three...
Oh, it does say R18.
I think it's just three or four maybe.
Oh my gosh, we only missed three!
Do you think we could get them maybe in the 15 minutes?
Maybe we should try.
What's my score?
Yay!
What site asking for a friend?
DL site.
Let's try it!
Let's try the 15 minutes and see if we can get the three.
If not...
Maybe someday.
Okay.
Work until the end of the day.
I'm back here.
Gosh.
Feels strange being back here.
Oh.
Wow.
We have all our...
Everything is back to...
There's no skylight.
Everything's normal.
Wow.
I'm just a normal...
Normal worker, you know?
Oh, the teeny weeny.
Little guy.
That's my little guy.
I never made fun of that little guy.
Feels too normal.
He's normal now.
Yeah.
Actually, I am gonna make fun of you.
You have no shoes on.
What's wrong with you?
What's that guy doing over there, huh?
I'm nervous about him.
Why is he over there?
Short game.
Oh, boy.
It's already started.
Oh, wait.
Oh, my God.
Goodbye!
They haven't even given us a second to...
Oh, my God.
Grandma's already gone.
She's already getting ready for her casket.
Grandma, you have so much to live for still!
Oh.
What do you want?
What are you about to do?
Worn out?
Not on my watch!
Go to sleep!
We have a guy eating dirt and a guy taking out the tree.
I'm part-time worker!
Let her die.
Well, we already lost the window.
Okay.
Hello.
Sorry for taking so long.
You're bald.
You're like really bald.
You just...
This guy looks unnatural.
What are you doing?
Don't do it!
Worn out.
Part-time worker!
What are you doing?
What are you about to do?
Hello.
Welcome.
So close.
We almost saved it.
What?
You're too close to me.
I am part-time worker!
Oh.
My bad.
He was actually a good guy.
Welcome.
He was making me nervous, you guys.
It was his man bun, you know?
He's making me nervous.
I don't know.
Welcome.
Peace.
Victory.
Is it her?
Yeah.
She's eating my chips.
Oh my gosh.
Okay.
I'll take care of your stuff in just one moment.
I am part-time worker!
Personal space.
That's what I'm saying.
Oh, it's just a little pile of rubble.
My poor microwave.
Let's hope for some new crazy antics.
Okay.
We got our cooking man over here.
Oh, wow.
Already three?
Okay.
Fried rice!
Part-time worker!
Um.
Uh.
I don't know.
Nobody's here.
Where's the other ones?
Oh.
Just people laying down.
People chillin'.
Is that a crime?
Is it a crime to be chill?
No more microwave lunches.
I am part-time worker!
Grandma, you're not allowed back here.
Yes, but no.
He's just chill like that, you guys.
He's just chill like that.
I'm hungry.
Thank you!
Thank you.
Yes.
Welcome.
I like croquettes, but they're usually... I like the potato ones, you know?
Oh, there's a lot of people.
Okay.
Where are they?
Oh, they're just... Oh!
Another... another bench.
Oh no, this is the manga reader.
How can you even read with that mask on?
Oh, wait.
I saw them.
I saw them sitting...
Maybe they were sitting inside.
Oh gosh.
Not having the back... the wall destroyed is so inconvenient, actually.
Oh, you're right here.
No growing mushrooms!
Oh.
Oh, he's angry.
Please leave.
Ping -pong!
Oh, this guy needs to sleep.
You want some sticks?
Yeah, get them sticks and chalky.
You want that chalky?
Ping-pong!
Die!
It's an old manga trope.
What?
Growing mushrooms in the corner?
Is it really?
It's not that old, right?
It's not that old of a trope.
Oh my god!
No flash photography!
Paparazzi!
Oh, you were so short, I barely even noticed you there.
Why do you need it?
Why do you need hairspray for?
Ping-pong!
You're his Oshii?
I'm so fast and efficient, aren't I?
Uh-oh.
There comes the robot.
The robot's coming on in.
Cold brew.
There you go.
What the?
Where?
Why is everybody so obsessed with me?
I'm part-time wacker.
That guy looks like he's up to no good.
Oh, I knew it!
I knew it!
I knew you were up to no good!
He was like stalking around like a creep.
Oh, hello.
If it's so hard, why don't you just stop working?
Oh my god.
Get out of here!
Something's going on around here.
The robot does say right things though.
It's true.
Isn't that his name?
The robot that says right things?
Welcome!
Welcome.
Oh my gosh.
I just remembered.
I'm going to be in Japan soon.
I'll be able to get...
Hey, why are you looking sussy, huh?
I am part-time wacker!
Oh, sorry.
Sorry.
He was like looking around like he was doing something.
I don't know!
Part-time wacker!
I can get jelly and also I can get tomato ramen.
Uh-oh.
Wait.
Actually, let's let that guy destroy the back wall.
Not going to lie.
Where's the other two people?
Not on my watch.
Let me speak to your manager.
Quick march?
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
What is quick march?
Oh, he's angry at me.
Sorry.
Ketchup ramen.
No!
Different.
I'm excited about it.
What do you want?
Oh my god!
I'm part-time wacker!
He just walked back here with such confidence.
It's actually so good.
There's like a chain that like has tomato ramen.
What am I missing?
Who am I missing?
Oh, the guy that is about to break the wall!
Right?
Where did he go?
Oh, three of them.
Thank you!
Oh, what are you doing?
Let's play baseball.
You?
Target.
I'm part-time wacker!
All I was doing was playing baseball with you, man!
Isn't that what you wanted, man?
Oh my god.
The pained look on his face.
The crowbar!
It's just another bat!
It's just...
Wow!
Running man!
I'm part-time wacker!
Is this guy going to break the wall?
Or what?
He's going to put up his flag.
I put up a fucking flag!
I'm part-time wacker!
What an idiot.
Oh, piano man.
Sing us a song, piano man.
He's taking his damn time.
That's what he is.
Do I have to get close to him?
Thank you!
Thanks for the back door!
Oh my god, there's just debris everywhere.
Hello.
Excuse me.
Oh sorry, I didn't notice it amongst all the debris.
But it said this guy's a good guy!
Stay positive.
Oh!
You think you can do yoga here?
Stay positive.
Uh oh.
What do I do with the penguin, you guys?
Oh, broccoli!
No, I don't want to be healthy!
I think I have to take Piano Man out.
Wait, where are you going?
What are you about to do?
Oops.
He was normal.
Isn't this guy normal too?
He just runs out, doesn't he?
He just stands there and then he runs away.
I like the piano though.
Pre-emptive strike.
Why was he walking towards the back?
Oh, there he goes.
He ran somewhere.
Thank you!
Oh!
I lose so much!
Oh my goodness, I didn't even realize.
Oops.
Depth perception.
It's okay, I'm not going for scoring, everybody.
We're just...
Oh my god.
We're trying to get the new people.
I am Hatchime Walker!
Jojo was plus zero.
I think because there's like good guys and then there's bad guys.
Like good... there's good...
What the...
Oh!
What were you doing in there?
Oh my god, wait.
Why do you look so happy?
I am Hatchime Walker!
He looks so satisfied!
What are you doing?
Oh, you're just walking.
Never mind.
No!
I am Hatchime Walker!
He was in there for a long time.
Oh.
Depth perception!
I am Hatchime Walker!
Oh wow, so fast.
Oh, the flag.
I am Hatchime Walker!
Lost!
Thanks for the wine, gifted.
Thank you.
Oh.
Let's play baseball.
You, the ball.
Oh, sorry.
Your head looked like a ball to me.
Where are you going?
Hmm, we still have two.
Three.
I am Hatchime Walker!
Go into the garbage!
Oh my god.
Five?
Anybody in here?
No?
Oh my god.
This guy checking himself out.
This guy doing...
What are you doing?
Oh.
I am Hatchime Walker!
Huh!
Gah!
I don't think we got any of the new ones.
I am Hatchime Walker!
I'm surprised your crowbar has no blood on it.
Oh, aw man.
Hmm.
I don't think we got any new ones.
Oh!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You have to deal with troublesome customers, but if you don't like it, that's fine.
You can just beat them up.
I will beat them up.
Hmm.
Jojo?
What do you mean Jojo?
I am Hatchime Walker!
That one wasn't new.
Unless me beating them up was new.
Piano Man Wrecked!
No, we have Piano Man...
He was already listed, wasn't he?
Is there a way to skip this?
Oh.
Nope.
I can't skip the credits.
The R18 guy?
No, we got him.
You have to not bonk the good ones.
Let's see.
This one.
Oh, press Y to close.
OK.
Penguin!
There we go.
Penguin cute.
Still three.
We still didn't get the new ones.
No piano man listen.
No, I could have sworn I saw him in here.
Because I didn't take him out before, right?
Amplifier...
Sorry, it's hard to like, read chat.
If you're like, telling me something, I'm not really reading chat.
Because it's kind of one of those games where you're just like, running all over the place, you know?
Oh, maybe... oh.
Maybe I thought he was listed because I saw the people with the blue and red... this guy.
See this outfit.
Oh, you're right.
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
Ignoring us for a part-time job.
Yeah.
You bonked both times.
Oh, okay, okay.
Oh, okay.
Well, I didn't realize that, like, to...
To get them listed also, that you had to not bonk them, so...
That's my bad.
What was the other ones though?
This is such an epic picture.
Uncle Wallbreaker.
Oh, and the JoJo might be good.
Oh, yeah!
Okay, okay, okay.
So both of them are fine.
So that's two, but what's the last one?
I feel like maybe, then, we've seen all of them, right?
Hmm...
Maybe we've seen all of them.
If there's one more, maybe I accidentally bonked someone that I didn't mean to.
The guy blocking you?
I said the coolest thing ever in chat earlier, too.
Too bad he didn't see.
Are there any other endings?
I don't... I don't think so.
I don't think there are, right?
Seems to be a one ending thing.
Unless you have, like, zero points.
That'd be...
What?
Can you get negative points, you think?
There's a guy that bathes in the water tank next...
Oh, no!
I had that one!
I did get that one, but he can't be a good guy, right?
I did get that guy.
He's in here for sure.
I got that guy.
That guy... That guy... I had him earlier.
What else is there?
Hmm...
Beat everyone.
Beat up everyone, Minto.
You can get negative points?
No way!
We did get him.
Yeah!
Oh, there he is!
Soop!
Go, Soop!
I've never seen the art team guy stay there long enough to leave before.
He looked so satisfied, too, as he was leaving.
He was just like...
That was good.
What a thrill going on... going on those kinds of sites at a convenience store.
Or a PC.
That's crazy.
The guy that throws the food over the counter?
Oh, you think that...
The guys that are rude customers, you think they count?
Because we know the two.
We have, what, three that we haven't been able to get?
It's, uh...
It's three that we haven't been able to get.
So, it's Piano Man, Jojo Pose, and...
Um...
Maybe the guys that throw the thing?
Okay, let's do another 15 minutes and see what we can get.
The guy who stands next to you uncomfortably.
No, but I don't think I bonked that guy once before.
Okay.
Alright, last round!
Last round!
One more time!
Alright, team guy read Ayami-sensei's work.
I don't want to bonk him, then!
He's a man of culture!
He really is a manager.
Why is it...
Why is it Juushimatsu?
Like Osomatsu-san.
Hello!
Welcome!
Got your gum... already?
What is this guy doing?
What are you doing?
You're the bad guy, right?
He's just like checking his shoes out.
Oh!
Uh...
Is he...
Ah!
You are the bad one!
Haha!
Oh!
This is new!
Worn out.
No, he's fine!
This guy is fine!
He's just taking...
That's what the bench is for!
Oh!
Okay.
Bye!
Bye, grandpa!
Oh my...
There's nothing going on in here!
Nothing's going on in here!
I run a well-fed establishment!
Hello, sir!
Wow!
I don't think I've seen that model.
That character model?
Okay, we're...
Oh!
Uh...
We're getting a few new things.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
I don't mean to be so close to you.
You know?
Ping-pong!
Okay.
Thanks for that.
Oh!
Well-fed?
I meant to say...
A well-oiled...
You know?
Like a well-oiled machine.
Oopsie.
Boop!
That guy didn't take anything, right?
Oh!
Ah!
You're rude!
Quick merch!
Oh.
You guys?
Uh...
Ah!
Look at me!
Oh my god!
He just filmed me killing a person!
No witnesses!
Hello.
Oh my god.
Grandpa.
Grandpa, you have to...
Oh.
Actually you're a young guy.
Sorry.
I'm a young guy!
You're a young guy!
Ghosts don't appear on cameras.
They do!
What are you doing?
Are you gonna go eat that dirt?
Who's gonna whack my tree?
I'm gonna whack you!
Smoking guy...
I'm gonna...
Hey!
Oh, he's the flag guy!
Grandpa looking ahead.
Oh my god.
Oh, no, that's not you.
Huh?
Oh.
Ping-pong!
Sometimes you pre-bonk everyone.
Yeah, but sometimes I like to see what they do.
If I... Also, I don't always recognize who's the bad guy.
Sometimes I like to see what they do.
Hello!
Sleep forever.
Is it him?
Okay!
Wow, he's really ganky.
Okay.
Donald!
Thanks for two months!
Thanks!
One second.
One moment.
Yeah!
Lady!
Who am I missing?
Hey, hey!
That's property!
That's good property!
I'm Five Time Walker!
Whoa!
Lost thanks to the five!
Gifted!
I'm Five Time Walker!
That guy is definitely dead.
I like got right on his neck.
Sorry about the wait.
Oh, yeah.
Alright, we need Jojo person back and we need piano back.
Ping-pong!
The way they apologize is so funny.
Parkour is very dangerous.
Yeah, I could...
If they get hurt on my property, they could get mad at me, you know?
They could sue us.
They could be like, I got hurt on your property.
Even though it's my fault.
I'm gonna sue you.
They could say that.
Lemon Carubito, what's wrong with you?
Everybody knows Melon is the best flavor.
Ah!
I can't hurt you or else I'm gonna get a bad name.
I can't score.
I hope you have a prolapsed anus, sir.
Anyway, hello.
Beep.
The robot.
Oh, that's the guy with the bat, isn't it?
It's fine.
He comes over to me.
He comes up to me.
Hey, man.
Oh, there's a guy giving me the finger even!
Hey, chill out.
I'm trying to check out somebody, okay?
Chill out!
I'm part-time worker!
Proportional response.
Of course!
I am part-time worker!
I'm part-time worker!
Oh,
the guy that's gonna destroy the wall.
I am part-time worker!
Oh, flag!
Do it.
I dare you.
I am part-time worker!
Hello.
Sorry for the wait.
One, two, three, four, five.
Five.
It's just a guy smoking.
One, two, three...
Oh, sorry.
One moment, please.
You delinquent!
I'm part-time worker!
Money!
I am part-time worker!
What do you want...
He doesn't even say anything.
What do you mean money?
Like, count the money?
Like, what do you want with the money?
Count it?
Um, you know...
Spend it?
Receive it?
Oh!
Oh, this is the guy that's...
You know what?
Why can't he work here?
Wait, that car...
Isn't that the one that drives into the wall?
Or the window?
Or am I crazy?
I think it is.
Let me see.
Do you have eyebrows?
No eyebrows!
I'm part-time worker!
Let's go take care of this car real quick.
Well, we have a new...
The ghost is back!
Hey, I'm Dragon.
Thanks for the 10 gift.
Thank you.
Welcome!
Nice.
Staying healthy.
Chonky.
The Piano!
And the JoJo!
Okay.
I see the JoJo.
Hello, JoJo.
I'm not going to bonk you.
You're fine.
You're just standing there.
Oh!
Okay.
Standing is not a crime.
Stay positive.
You're a panty thief!
Hello.
Sing us a song, a piano man.
Oh my god.
I don't know where the other...
Our other weirdo is.
Where's the nuisance?
It says we have one nuisance, but I... Oh, there he is.
Is the evil ghost?
No, she's not doing anything yet.
There we go.
Now she's a nuisance.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Boo.
What was under her dress?
Yoga lady's fine, right?
I have to train.
Isn't yoga lady alright?
Hi aunties?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
I see him going in there.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh.
Oh, I thought he was gonna smoke.
Ha, ha, ha.
It's only legs, no details, like Left 4 Dead 2 Zombies.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
I'm a part-time worker!
Oh, starting to ramp up a little bit.
Okay, so now...
I put up a fucking flag!
I'm a part-time worker!
I don't understand!
Hey, come on out!
Shrink!
He's literally a nanomach- Ah!
Where's the nanomachines guy?
I killed a senator!
Goodbye!
How will I stay?
Oh my god.
This guy just smokes!
This guy just smoked...
Nanomachines son.
You're not a superhero!
Your outfit is...
stupid!
What superhero wears vans?
Oh my god.
Chill out!
Where'd you go?
Oh my god, wait.
Is it him?
No!
We never see the R18 guy doing his business.
You know what?
That's probably for the best, isn't it?
That's the third time we've had him.
The first time I didn't know what was going on.
Because it was all yellow.
A lot of troublesome customers.
Do you want to?
I don't know.
I just want to see what he's looking at, you know?
Everybody, let's go to karaoke after this instead.
I propose...
we all instead go to the manga cafe and the karaoke.
What if he's still in there?
I mean...
Yeah...
Had an explosive time!
Um...
Wait...
It's not letting me...
Press Y...
Oh, there we go.
Okay.
Okay, let's see now if we got them.
That hurt to say, didn't it?
No!
Mint, please.
Okay.
Picture book.
Fool.
Strong old man.
It's so funny.
I'm stumped.
The shirt on this guy.
Everything about it.
It's so funny.
This game is so silly.
Oh!
Enigmatic pose!
Yeah, we got it!
Minus two.
Two what?
Or...
Wait, we had yoga before, didn't we?
Yankee.
Fireworks.
Stuff toy.
So now we'll see if we only have one or not.
Robbery.
Street piano!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh...
I think...
We might still have just one then.
Shoplifting.
Baseball.
Baseball 2.
I don't...
What does claymer mean?
Hmm.
Oh...
Oh, wait.
We're all close to the end.
Ahhh!
People...
People running around screaming.
We got him!
Oh!
He's claiming.
Yay, we did it!
Yippee!
I don't know what the third one was at all, but...
The last one was the person sitting on the bench?
Oh, was it?
Wait, did I miss him?
Maybe we just never got him before though, because...
We must not have gotten him, because there's no way I would have...
I don't remember bonking a guy sitting on a bench, you know?
But I also don't remember seeing...
Oh, him!
Ordinary person sitting on a chair!
Yay!
We did it!
We did it, everybody!
Good job!
What a fun game!
What a fun... and creative game.
The dev has a good sense of humor.
That was so fun!
I hope you guys enjoyed going to work with me.
And all that fun stuff.
Weird game.
Fun baka game.
Yeah!
I didn't know so much about it before.
So I... I now understand.
I now understand.
Hold on, I'm looking at some... these are some older...
Sorry for... I didn't hear the donos earlier.
Get by...
Also, Dress Hina gotcha fun.
Thank you so much for the Dress Hina!
Wait, is she up?
Not yet, right?
Soon, right?
No, not yet.
Not yet.
50 more minutes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
In an hour.
Maybe I can talk for 50 minutes.
I can talk for 50 minutes, maybe.
Thank you for the Dress Hina gotcha fun.
Hopefully I don't have to use it on that.
Giant Princess, thank you!
K-Barn, thank you!
I wasn't there at the time, but the boss at my first job was taking the trash outside and came across a guy squatted on top of the commercial-sized garbage bin.
He looked at my boss and calmly said, Sorry, dude.
I got the runs?
Postcard signing?
Will you guys let me sign postcards for real?
Yeah?
While I wait for an hour?
Okay.
I'm gonna quit the game then.
Hold on, give me one second.
Oh wait, give me one second again.
Give me one second again.
Oh wait,
I have no desk.
Where's my desk?
There it is.
Or table, rather.
Not a desk.
Manual labor game.
Wait, menial?
Actual menial labor.
Keynote stream.
Quit the game.
There we go.
Give me one second to pull up some music and then we can...
Then I can sign stuff while we wait.
Here, actually, I'm even gonna write a thing at the bottom.
Oh wait, let me do this.
Ta-da ta-da ta-da.
Um...
Re- assigning postcards until dress Hina.
Gotcha.
ta-da ta-da ta-da.
Oh.
ta-da ta- oh.
Music too.
My bad.
My bad, my bad.
Since we went from jazz, let's keep on the jazz run.
Um...
There we go.
Sorry I'm late for work, boss.
No worries.
I'm just docking your pay.
A little bit.
Thanks for the exciting take your Wisp to work day, Mint.
Yeah!
Did you guys ever do that as a kid?
Well, like the take your...
Oh wait, did you ever...
Well, actually...
Do they...
If you have kids...
Do you have kids?
What if we do?
Do they still do...
Um...
Take your child to work day?
So, will you be a part-time worker?
I'm too ruthless to have kids.
But I visited my dad at work.
Fun!
I think I did that, the take your child to work once before.
But...
Um...
My mom and my...
Uh...
My mom and my dad actually worked at the same place.
And it was kind of...
How do I describe?
Um...
It was...
Like...
Kind of constructionish?
So...
I didn't do anything.
I just sat in the office.
And like...
Didn't do anything.
Cause they were like, you can't go in the back.
You'll...
You'll lose a finger.
Probably.
Alright, let me grab my...
My postcards are right down here.
Uh...
I have about... maybe like...
Maybe like 200 here?
So I could probably finish signing this whole...
Actually, maybe a little more than 200.
I don't know.
I don't think I can sign and like...
Oh gosh, I already messed up.
I don't think I can sign and talk at the same time.
It requires too much mental capacity.
Right?
Because I have to like... think about how I do my signature.
Or else it ends up being...
I mean, I mess up all the time.
And it ends up being kind of ugly all the time anyway.
But if anyone is curious, I'm signing a postcard for the Patreon.
I have this sick...
What's the word?
My ring finger?
Is like...
It's gonna be so strong by the end of this.
It's gonna have the sickest callus.
Like I even... my skin...
Started breaking.
It's okay if mine's ugly?
Okay.
Talking between signatures?
I've already signed five since I first started.
I've already signed a couple.
You'll be able to fit so many rings on it.
Or none.
It's gonna be so...
Beefy.
You know?
It's gonna be like...
The strongest ring finger to ever exist.
It's my fault though.
I should have signed these like...
Because...
Basically, I'm taking...
A few.
I mean...
I say a few.
I'm taking about...
2,000.
To Matara when I see her.
Well, I say to Matara.
But I'm passing them off when I see her this weekend at Otakutan.
I'm saying, okay.
Put it in your suitcase.
Your responsibility now.
I hope it fits.
I basically was just like...
Don't...
Don't bring a lot of stuff.
Bring your biggest suitcase.
And...
But that's just two months.
And that's including the recent ones that we have to...
That I had to do.
Which was kind of hellish.
Because...
I was just like, oh my gosh.
I felt like I just signed all of these.
And now I'm having to sign all of them again.
How much do postcards weigh?
Well, that's why I was gonna bring more.
But one, I don't think I can sign.
I was like, maybe I'll bring three months worth.
But I don't think I can sign that many.
And again, it's my fault.
I should have signed them sooner.
Because, truth be told, I got these.
I came back from Anime Expo.
And I had them.
They had been delivered.
So I've had them for some time now.
But I was like, oh, I'll get to it.
Who's your personal favorite Metal Gear character?
Personally, I love Oss a lot.
I also love Oss...
Ossalot's forgotten twin brother.
Brother?
I thought you weren't signing the replacement ones.
Oh no!
We signed them.
Or I signed them.
Why?
Did Matara say we weren't gonna sign them?
Did I sign all of them for...
Top Blue Archive characters?
Koharu?
Cherry's...
Hina.
You both said it.
Kanna's your fav?
Kanna's so cool.
Kanna's really cool.
I like her.
Her... also her...
Her attack is really good.
Basically, what she does is she like...
You target a character.
You target like a little...
I don't know.
How do I say it?
A villain?
And...
She...
Arrests them.
And then it builds up.
And like does a giant explosion.
And it's so helpful.
Serika, my beloved.
I always call her Azunyan.
Because she looks just like...
Azunyan from...
From K-On!
Only...
Kind of recently...
Did I like...
Call her...
Start calling her Serika.
Baselot over Osnaticon?
So true.
So true, Bessie.
You're in a safe place...
Safe...
Space.
I love Baselot so much.
They do look alike.
It's just that trope, you know?
The...
Black haired...
Twin tailed...
And...
But also like her uniform too.
She's got like the...
The...
Little bow tie...
The blazer...
And the red bow tie...
And...
You know...
Did you know Ayami-sensei has a character in Blue Archive?
The reason Mint's hands are like that is because her hands got tired from signing postcards.
No...
Honestly, I feel like I can sign...
Like my hand doesn't get so tired.
It's just a matter of speed.
You know?
Doshi?
Yeah!
Shimiko!
Shimiko is...
Ayami-sensei's...
Art.
But...
I feel bad.
I wish she was more popular of a character.
I'm pretty sure she's also just a one star.
So...
It was fun seeing you multiple days at A5!
I don't know why I thought I should do a cartwheel for you on Saturday.
I'm...
I was fine with it.
I think staff was just like...
Hey, buddy.
What are you doing?
So funny.
Oh, my gosh.
Everybody...
Oh, I should talk about Anime Fest, huh?
It was so fun.
I was at a...
I did a convention appearance this past weekend.
Apparently, it was like their last year or something?
For the convention?
Which is pretty crazy.
But...
I'm...
It was so funny the amount of people that were just like...
I don't really know who you are.
I just came to see you.
I don't know who you are, but in your bio on the website, it said you liked Metal Gear.
So I was like...
What?
Someone came up to me dressed as Snake and was just like...
I found out about you like 30 minutes ago.
Crazy.
If you watch me...
Thanks.
Cool to see you on the panel.
Yeah.
That's sad.
What?
That it's last year?
Yeah.
I don't know what the dealio is, but...
I'm honored to have been part of the last year of a convention that's been going on for many, many years.
I would like to...
Go to Texas for real one day.
I've been trying to...
You know, I've been doing a lot of events and stuff.
But I've just been...
My main goal is to try and go to as many new places as I possibly can because...
Not just for me because, you know, some of them are digitally.
But just because I know not everybody could go to California four times a year.
So...
Careful, I hear they have cowboys there.
Yee-haw.
Oh, that signature was not pretty.
Sorry.
So sorry.
My signature is getting uglier and uglier.
Meanwhile, me stuck on the East Coast.
I'll be honest.
I tried to get...
So for like...
The podcast, right?
Some of our convention appearances was...
Kind of...
Because Matar is involved.
It was V-Shojo trying to help us out.
And reaching out to cons and stuff as well.
And I was like...
Please more East Coast conventions for us.
But a lot of them also fall within...
Or fall out of the range of the podcast.
So...
Can't really do much about...
Can't really do a podcast thing...
When it is out of...
You know, we end the podcast in September.
So...
But...
That's kind of why it...
Didn't work out.
Well, okay.
I'm done with this.
I grabbed little stacks at a time.
So...
Done with this little stack.
Oops.
There we go.
Let me grab another little stack.
Sad but understandable.
Yeah.
But also I'd like to go more outside of the US as well.
Just places I've never been before.
Brazilian in shambles.
I don't even know what we're waiting for to be honest.
I just like spending time with you guys.
Aside from Japan?
What do you mean?
No, I just mean events and stuff.
I just mean events.
But...
My times going to Japan...
I mean, I'm going to Japan.
Oh gosh.
Am I going to Japan next week?
I'm going to Japan next week!
Oh golly.
I'm going but it's all for work.
It's for work you guys.
It's not...
Oh gosh.
Busy, busy.
A little pause, guys...
I think I'm going to Japan.
No pleasure.
But I'm excited because there's some people I'll be meeting.
I asked Ayami-sensei if she wanted to do an off-collab.
So we'll probably be doing that.
I'm just saying if there's Mintomido somewhere in Southeast Asia, I'll probably fly there.
Wins!
Thank you so much for the peek!
Anime Fest was my first con and you made it a blast.
Shoutout to your superfans that showed up.
I got to take fan group photos and say I'm better for you.
It was an amazing experience.
That's so sweet!
That's so sweet.
I'm so glad you had fun.
Please don't feel obligated to stream often while you're there.
I'm gonna do my best.
I kinda don't know how the first week will go while I'm there.
But I definitely know after the first week I'll be free.
Until Annie-sama!
I'm so excited for Annie-sama!
You guys, I'm going to be seeing Ogura Yui for the first time!
Live!
Oh my gosh!
I'm so excited!
Oh my gosh, if you don't know, Ogura Yui is my...
She's my seiyuu-oshi.
I love her so much.
I've never been able to see her before.
I'm so excited!
Oh my gosh.
And Denpagumi will be performing.
And...
I got tickets for...
Not everyday.
But oh my gosh, it's my first Annie-sama too.
So I'm very excited.
Very, very, very excited.
Isn't she the VA for Shiroko?
She is!
Yes, she's the VA for Shiroko from Blue Archive.
Which is why I love Shiroko.
But also, I just like Shiroko's character too.
I came for Shiroko.
Stayed for everything else, pretty much.
I did all three days of Annie-sama in 2022.
It was fun, but I fell asleep every day.
Yeah.
I don't think I could do more than three days.
I'll be honest.
It's also a lot.
I'm just like...
Just that much noise and stimulation and everything.
Like every day is...
Would be so much.
The current time FGO...
Even is...
Scotty getting a Holy Grail and creating an Endless Summer.
So you're saying I need a Holy Grail to make a Mint and Matara Endless Summer Podcast PRV?
No, please.
End my suffering.
Don't do this to me.
Why are you making me suffer?
Why?
An eternal summer with Matara?
Don't do this to me, please.
Plan.
Learn to astral project to see Minto icons.
I'll try to come to you.
I don't know where you are, but...
I first got exposed to Yui Ogura from...
Yui Kaori.
Me too, actually.
Space guy, right?
Welcome to Membu ship.
Thank you.
And thank you for the 10 gifted.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Yeah, I love Yui Kaori.
I love them so much.
I...
Used to do...
Wait, I just arrived back.
Did she say yes?
Oh.
Huh?
What was I going to say?
You know, before I...
Did this maid cafe...
I did some maid cafes at anime conventions.
And so I...
I...
Learned Yui Kaori dances.
My favorite one is puppy love.
Doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo.
Hi.
Do kyun doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo.
Say no.
Puppy love.
Pu puppy love.
Phantom.
Thanks for the 5 gifted.
Thank you so much.
Can't wait to see you at Otaku-tan this weekend.
See you there, everybody.
See you.
See you there.
Pu puppy love.
Doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo.
Why don't you go back?
Unless it's like a distance thing or money thing.
I get it.
Oh, but I won't be able to...
I won't be able to stream me polling.
Is that okay?
Do you guys mind?
You'll just hear my reactions.
My disappointment.
You'll hear my disappointment.
For me, it's distance and money.
Other side of country and I'm broke.
Wait, I'm sorry.
But other side of country...
That means you're West Coast, right?
That means you get a lot of stuff.
I feel the West Coast gets so much stuff.
The Napping Koala!
Welcome to Mambusha Park.
What a koala-ty name.
Highest...
The price of the highest Patreon tier?
I believe it's $25.
And that's what gets you the postcard.
Sorry.
Checking stuff for Otakutan, actually.
Meanwhile, us Midwesterners...
I'm sorry, Joshua.
You can still get the postcards?
Well, you'll get it starting from the...
When you join, right?
Yeah.
I know we're late with sending them out.
I'm so sorry.
But we're basically doing it like...
We're checking each month.
So each month we'll get a batch, you know?
So this one...
The one I signed for before was...
Oh gosh, April.
And then I'm signing for May.
And then, you know...
We'll send it out to the May people.
And then...
I've only gotten one so far.
Yeah, because we've only sent out one.
I think, you know...
Had it been not signed, it would have gone out way faster.
But it's hard to actually have us meet up, you know?
Because...
Essentially, I'm gonna be probably taking a couple stacks to Otakutan.
And handing them off to...
Matara.
And then her signing her side.
And then shipping them when she can.
And then the next stack...
I'm gonna take with me to Japan.
So I'm gonna be holding on to them for like a whole month until I see her.
And then doing that.
And then probably the last batch, I'll ship to her after I'm finished signing them.
Because I guess we met up...
Or rather, we didn't meet up as much as we thought we would.
And...
Other things...
Other times...
Like for Anime Expo, we thought we would...
Well...
Honestly, they didn't come in time for Anime Expo.
Which was my fault.
Because I was in charge of ordering them and...
You know...
I was...
Yeah...
But...
Our postcards will have traveled the world!
Pretty much, right?
I have social anxiety for big gatherings like conventions.
Maybe I can rope an older brother into going with me to one somewhere.
It's definitely...
More fun to have someone with you, right?
Than to go by yourself.
But...
You know...
If you were to go to a con...
With other Wisps there...
Like if...
Say...
If you go to a con where I'm guesting and...
Um...
Other people were going to come to see me...
I'm sure you would make friends.
Or even other VTuber...
VTuber communities are usually so nice, you know?
And very...
Welcoming.
I think.
Come to South America?
If I get invited to a place...
I had someone at Anime Fest!
They came from Mexico!
And I was like...
I'll try and go to a Mexico convention.
Or somewhere.
I don't know.
Go to Brazil!
It says a great big fan community member to come here.
I'm like the Grinch.
Her heart grew three sizes that day.
Japan?
Maybe one day.
I'll be big in Japan.
Purple Helios!
Thanks for the membership!
Thank you!
Though, you know...
I feel... it's like... I don't know.
I always go back and forth with like...
How do I say?
Growing bigger as a content creator so I can get more opportunities and reach more worldwide and things like that, but...
Also, you know...
I feel like that kind of mentality...
Is a lot of pressure.
And I feel quite comfortable where I'm at.
So...
Kevin!
Welcome to the membership!
Thank you!
I don't want to become...
Someone who... you know...
And obviously I do think about like...
Numbers and subscribers and things like that, but...
I don't want to become someone who focuses only on that kind of stuff.
Mint's US tour win?
I need to see Mint in Minnesota!
What's in Minnesota?
Cows?
I want to see some cows.
Thank you!
If you're gonna leave...
20 more minutes.
Oh no, maybe I won't finish this stack before...
Before time.
After the podcast, are you going to need more sub tiers?
For the cafe?
No, I don't think so.
Memberships?
Nah.
I am...
Entirely comfortable.
It was nice to meet you at Anime Fest Thursday.
It was my first ever meet and greet and I'm glad...
To know I'll never be forgotten for my ballsy mood...
In front of everyone.
Working retail has forever changed me.
Thank you, Magic Doodoo Johnson.
I really appreciate it.
Give us higher tiers.
Why?
Why, Anthony?
Why do you want higher tiers?
Can there be a membership tier where we watch Nacho Libre once a month asking for a friend?
Only if...
No.
Yes.
I literally watched it from the Patreon and you missed it, Raymac.
That's your fault.
Oh my gosh, you made me mess up my signature.
No, it's ugly.
I like making the little ghost's eyes so derpy.
Came back from a con Sunday, your tricks help a lot.
Really?
Thanks, Solin!
Thanks, Solin.
What is this?
Thanks for trying them.
So happy.
What was the most effective?
Okay, here's the post-con survey.
What was most effective?
Konnichiwa, konnichiwa!
Hope the ugly one is sent to me.
They're all ugly, don't worry.
But sometimes I do...
Instead of like...
Eyeballs, I do winky eyeballs.
So...
Some people get a special winky face.
In fact, this one will be a winky face.
Oh, this one is so cute actually!
This one is really cute.
Ayami-sensei sent this.
Eh?
Thank you very much!
Oh my god!
I love you, Ayami-sensei.
Teen Girl Squad.
Their ugly world!
I'm sorry, because English beer is not allowed.
I can't speak Japanese.
I had so much fun with Ayami-sensei.
Her panel was so much fun.
Mama, thanks for the five kisses!
Arigato, arigato.
I'm good at Japanese.
It does!
Let's go!
Hot dog!
Hot dog moment.
Did Ayami get more Baja Blast?
Actually, both of us were there digitally, so...
But, we want to go back.
That's why we were just like, oh, it's the last year of this convention.
Hopefully, another Texas convention will invite us.
Hopefully.
Minty Birch Kyle, thanks for the hot dog.
Hot dog.
Can my signature have a freckle?
Well, I don't know if you'll get it though.
It's the gacha.
Who knows which one you'll get.
Come to San Japan.
If they'll invite me.
I have to... maybe I do have to become more popular.
I have to be more desirable, you guys.
I have to become more desirable.
Can my signature have a frog?
What's something I should draw on this postcard?
Something silly.
Not my regular signature.
What's something that I should draw?
Something silly.
This is the real SSR.
Frog Bird?
I can try drawing...
I can try drawing Frog Bird.
Okay, hold on.
What is a frog...
Oh, here, here.
Okay.
This is a real SSR.
This one's from Frog Bird.
I got a reference picture.
I'm drawing it now.
I'll take a picture.
I'll take a picture of it.
Before I... before... you know?
Or should we wait and see who... if someone gets it?
I think Frog Bird would write with his left hand.
So...
Oh, god.
Writing with my left hand.
I'm going to draw a little fire, too.
It's going to be funny if they don't watch this.
They're going to be like, what the hell?
They're going to be some Matara fan who barely knows who I am.
It's going to be a Momo instead.
They're going to be like, what is this?
I really hope someone Canadian gets it.
Oh gosh.
It's so ominous.
I'm putting it off to the side.
I'll take a picture of it later.
Not knowing Minta.
It's okay.
A lot of people don't know me.
They can't see ghosts.
They don't have a sixth sense.
I'm manifesting it.
Everybody will now be wondering who gets the elusive Frogbert signed postcard.
Every Momo knows you're her stinky wife.
That is a bro moment.
10 minutes.
I think I can get through this little stack.
I'm about halfway through the whole stack as a whole.
Which is, each stack is 250.
Yeah.
I wish you blessed gotcha luck, ghost lady.
Thank you.
Oh, I forgot to change the summer special.
This week.
Or today.
Today was the new episode.
I wasn't in it because...
We wouldn't have had time to record together since she went to LA and I got stuck in LA.
So...
You hate her?
Yeah.
10 minutes for the server to crash.
Don't say that.
Oh...
Escape from LA and all.
But I did eventually escape.
Did you escape from LA like your hero snake?
Actually...
I should have made more escape from LA jokes.
But...
I also haven't seen escape from LA.
I've seen escape from New York.
Maybe we should do a double feature watch along.
Number stream.
Double feature...
Escape from New York.
Escape from LA.
Or I could do it on the Patreon.
I have to do a Patreon stream.
My roommate showed me escape from New York a few years back.
He doesn't even like MGS.
I mean it's a good movie.
You don't have to like Metal Gear to like it.
I think.
Though my favorite...
I mean I do like it.
But I...
Was it David...
David...
David Carpenter?
I like the thing so much more.
Yeah.
Kurt Russell.
He's so awesome.
Such a cool actor.
John Carpenter?
What did I say?
I think it was John Carpenter.
Did I say David?
Sorry.
I said David.
Who the hell is David?
Welcome to membership.
Thank you.
Sorry.
I just got Snake on the brain.
John David Carpenter.
The effect and the thing are just amazing.
I know!
And like the atmosphere and everything.
Love it.
I love it.
David Carpenter and John Hader.
Oh god!
What is this alternative universe?
I'm getting Mandela effect.
What if that was really... I was like, no guys, it's David Hader.
And John Carpenter.
And you're like, what?
No, it's always been John Carpenter.
Wait, I mean David Carpenter and John Hader.
What are you talking about, Mint?
You're going crazy.
You're taking your crazy pills.
And I'm like, no!
Mandela effect!
Sometimes...
Sometimes Mandela effect feels too real though.
Like the Bear and Stain Bears.
Bear and Stain Bears.
And also like the one that's like...
The Fruit of the Loom.
I could have sworn there was a cornucopia.
But there never was.
Why does everybody remember the cornucopia then?
The Fruit of the Loom gets me so bad.
I know!
And I read those bears like every day when I was a kid.
I was obsessed with them bears.
Made Mint and Mint Phantom?
What?
It's always been Made Mint.
Never Mint Phantom.
I'm just like, is it...
Are we crazy?
I don't think I do remember a cornucopia.
The cornucopia was a thing.
It was a knockoff brand.
Bye Mr. Pancake.
Thanks for watching.
Have a good night.
Thanks for hanging out.
If you're heading out.
Thank you so much for hanging out.
Why is it Made Mint instead of Mint Made?
Because I'm...
I don't know.
I'm the maid who is named Mint.
I just really wanted to hammer in the fact that I was a maid.
I guess.
Myoshi's maid channel.
It's so funny because when I get...
When I get spam emails to my email.
They'll say like...
Like there's a ridiculous amount of people that call me Made Mint.
Rather than like Mint Phantom.
But my...
But the spam like...
It'll be like a spam sponsorship or something.
And you know they're very obviously like spam.
It'll be like...
We want to sponsor you for Prada products.
Will you advertise Prada on your...
Things like that.
I'm like...
Okay.
This is...
You know.
But...
Oh gosh.
My signature is getting really sloppy.
I'm so sorry.
But they always...
I know most of the time when they're like...
They're spam.
When they put like my full...
Legal name.
My full YouTube legal name.
Prada Phantom.
Mint and Prada collab win.
Actually though.
I got a pretty cool...
Email the other day.
Of like a...
PR package.
That somebody wanted to send.
That I'm extremely...
Yeah.
It's literally Space Ghost's dear Made Mint channel.
Minto Phantom.
Like they do that every time.
It's so funny.
I got...
I don't know if it's...
I hope it's legit.
I'm like...
I don't know if it was legit.
I hope it's legit.
I gave them my address.
But...
Okay.
I just grabbed the other stack.
Five minutes.
Yippee.
I...
I verify.
Or rather I tried to verify it.
I was like where...
What...
What's their LinkedIn?
And I looked at the website.
But some of them...
Some can be pretty tricky.
Like some of the spam ones.
So that's how like people end up getting like...
Hacked and stuff.
And the...
The...
The little...
Hold on.
This thing?
Where is it?
Oh no.
Did I delete it already?
The little brick.
The brick mint.
That I'll be using.
That I'll be selling.
That...
The one that I announced...
Um...
During my anniversary stream.
I almost thought that one was spam too.
I was just like...
Huh?
What is this?
Oh my gosh.
My signature.
I'm sorry everybody.
I almost thought it was spam.
I was like...
This isn't real.
If it's not English...
It's spam.
Mint probably.
No.
How many times does that happen?
Oh my gosh.
Every day I get...
Um...
Spam emails.
I get more spam emails than I get real offers.
But that's okay.
I love you.
I hope you have a great day.
I drew an art of you.
Yippee!
Cyber!
Thank you so much!
Thank you for the super chat.
And thank you for the art.
Thank you!
Is that my tag?
The funniest one I've ever gotten?
Here.
I'll go check my email.
I'll go check my mail right now.
Let's see what's in there.
Let's see what's in my email.
Private email.
Whoa!
My god.
Sorry!
Matarakan is spamming my inbox.
I have...
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
8 emails from Matara-Kan.
It's for stuff like... It's for a talkathon to add it to my calendar.
But it's so funny.
Let's see.
Oh, I need to respond to that.
I don't know.
I don't know what the funniest one I've ever gotten is.
Hmm...
I don't know.
Crypto?
Oh, I get sometimes like AI collabs.
They'll be like, do you want to promote our AI app?
And I'm like, no!
Leave me alone!
I want to promote your stinky AI app.
Hehehehe.
Stinky...
Yeah.
I want Mint to be my GPS assistant voice.
Oh my gosh, did you see it?
Someone like, put out a uh...
A...
Miku voice for Waze.
That's crazy.
Maybe it will make me start using Waze.
My mom once used Waze.
Waze.
It was the first time I had ever seen someone use it when I was driving with her.
And it was so annoying.
I wanted to tear out the middle console.
I was like, shut up!
Waze is so... oh my gosh, I hate it.
It'll be like, you missed that turn, but that's okay.
And I'm like, shut up!
What are you talking about?
Oh my gosh, they're so annoying.
It's like this stupid toxic positivity thing that just drives me crazy.
It's so annoying.
It sounds a bit passive-aggressive.
It didn't seem condescending.
I can't remember it now because it was a long time ago that I heard it.
But it was just like, some things would be like, hey, I was just letting you know that you're going to want to turn.
And like, five miles.
I don't know.
I'm like, shut up!
What do you mean?
Wrong way, baka!
Would you prefer regular toxicity?
No, just give it to me straight.
Just give it to me straight.
Turn in two minutes.
Or 500 feet.
Or whatever.
Not minutes.
What if it was Snake's voice or Otacon?
Well, that's just unfair.
Of course I wouldn't...
Of course!
Negative toxicity.
GPS it is.
Be like, where the hell are you going, dummy?
What the hell are you doing, idiot?
You made the wrong turn!
Who taught you to drive?
Yeah.
What if there was like...
Actually, I was going to say, what if there was a GPS app that like, you...
It just told you directions, but you didn't know where you were going.
And you just went to a random place.
But I was thinking, that's kind of like the Randonautica, right?
Did you guys ever do that?
It was like geocaching, but not really.
Randonautica, but just...
Mintway's voice pack.
Turn now.
Haha, just kidding.
Made the turn.
Teehee, pedo.
Dressina!
Oh my gosh.
She's live?
Oh, wait.
Wait.
Fast!
Oh my god.
Oh my gosh, also summer.
Swimsuit Hoshino.
Wait, but Swimsuit Hoshino is so cute!
Okay, here I go.
I have one free tent pole recruit.
Okay, here, I'm gonna turn... here.
I'm gonna turn off the music and see it.
Can you hear that?
Okay.
Oh, I also have some free one recruit tickets too.
Okay, we can hear?
Okay.
Okay, here I go.
I'm using my free tent pole.
I'm drawing a sad face.
Okay, skip.
Okay, I'm gonna use all my free tickets.
So this is an individual one.
Awesome.
Listen up.
You nerd.
What did I get?
Oh.
Oops.
Oh, it's yellow.
Wow.
Heidi.
Okay.
Recruit one.
Pink!
Blue.
I love drawing the faces.
We need pink.
Kotori.
Recruit again.
Come on, Arona.
Pink!
Blue.
Okay.
These are just singles, by the way, so...
Kotama.
Kotama...
Okay, this is my last single free pole.
Oh, sorry.
Oops.
Oh, it's skull, at least.
Hanai...
Okay.
Back to 10-pul.
Second 10-pul.
Pink.
Blue.
Haha.
Flip!
Blue!
It's the coveted... It's the coveted 9 blue 1 2 star!
Okay, recruit again!
2!
I got 2!
You guys!
Ah, first one!
Yuzu!
That's okay.
Oh, second one!
No, it's not her though.
Wow!
Oh my gosh, I finally got Wakamo though.
Oh my god.
Oh my gosh, sorry.
I finally got Wakamo at least.
That's okay.
Okay.
Kind of worse.
Third one?
Or fourth?
Fourth 10 pull?
I've been wanting Wakamo for a while though, so that's good.
Recruit again!
I'm below 20,000 now.
Blue!
Oh gosh, it took all my luck in the... in the... what's it called?
In the free units.
Please.
Oh, here we go.
Why can't we see the screen?
Because it's on my phone.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, it's on my phone.
Okay, I'm at 18,000.
Okay, sixth time.
Sixth time's the charm, baby!
Oh!
It's actually pink!
Oh my god!
Yow!
Come on!
Whee!
Oh!
First one!
Small Shun.
One more!
I
got Rumi.
At least it was somebody new.
Out of three, only one of them was new.
That's so rude.
There were three of them!
Okay, I'm at 17,000.
Hina, please.
Hina, come home.
Hina, come home!
Recruit again!
Pink!
Just one.
That's okay.
It's better than none.
Come on.
Hina, come home!
Hina, come home, please!
So I can also pull for swimsuit.
Hina, come home!
Small Shun.
Again.
Why am I getting here so many times?
It's only two times, but still.
Pink!
Pink
What is this luck, man?
I've gotten, what, three new?
How many, how many, ten, how many, how many...
I'm at 94 ten pulls, but how many new characters have I got?
How many three stars have I had?
This is insane!
Oh my gosh.
Okay.
I'm at 13,000 still.
I can do a little bit more.
Why, Hina, why?
Yeah,
94 pulls.
It flipped!
And I got two!
What is happening?
That's, oh my god.
Oh, please, Hina!
First one?
Wait.
Who is this?
Oh, I got, um, tracksuit Haruna.
I didn't have her before, so that's nice.
Please, please!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, one more, one more!
Yes!
On the floor!
I flipped one!
Oh my gosh, it showed up as blue!
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god!
Nice, nice, nice, nice!
I might be able to spark for, uh, for...
Oh, she's not at this rate.
Yubi!
We did it!
Oh, Hina secured!
Spark?
No, I have a... I still have to have 100 more pulls.
I don't know, should I... I still have 12,000.
I still have 12,000, but maybe I should save it.
Hoshino's swimsuit is really cute, though.
Okay, I'm gonna try it once for Hoshino.
I'm gonna try it once.
Blue!
Wow, I got four... four...
Two stars, though.
Maybe... okay, one more!
One more.
Okay, this is it.
For real.
Blue!
Ugh, okay, nevermind.
Blue archive.
Yes!
That's right.
The banner is 6% right now, worth sparking.
I mean...
Congrats on getting just Hina.
Thanks for sharing your luck.
Managed to get her in 80 pulls.
Yippee.
Wow, thanks for bragging.
Yeah, but I don't want to spend all my gems, you guys.
Did you need anything else from this banner?
I've gotten so many new girls.
Let's see.
Let me count how many new girls I've gotten.
Uh...
How many new girls did I get?
Let's see.
Um...
Uh...
Oh, uh...
Where is it?
I got one, Wakamo.
Meru, two.
Haruna, three.
Dress Hina, four.
Rumi, five.
Five girl... five new girls.
And then... oh, okay.
Oh, no.
Iroha was from the previous banner.
But five new girls is really good.
Got Hina and Hoshino after 280 pulls.
Save for Shiroko Terror.
There's no good units until next Fest, so you have six months.
I guess that's true.
But wait, isn't Mika coming back soon though?
I don't have Mika.
I thought Mika was coming back soon.
Oh, she's next Fest.
Oh, okay.
Alright, let's pull, baby.
Let's keep pulling.
Hoshino!
Blue.
You can borrow my Mika.
I already do, Oimo.
Actually, I don't think you have her.
As her... as your...
As your character.
You do?
Oh.
One more!
Next one!
Blue!
I got used to seeing pink so often.
Skip.
Skip, skip, skip.
I'm at 7600.
Alright, next!
Blue.
I'm drawing a picture.
Ehhh.
Full blue.
Oh my God, all three of my two stars are...
Oh gosh, what's her name?
I can't remember her name.
I don't use her.
The...
The red-haired devil girl.
What's her name?
Junko!
Yeah.
Next!
I'm gonna end up using all of them at this rate.
Pink!
I'm gonna end up using all of my gems at this point.
Junko is very cute.
Serina.
Shimiko.
Sensei's daughter.
It doesn't count as a daughter.
I'm so used to VTubers.
Here it is!
Sakurako.
Is Dress Hina already out?
Yeah!
I'm at 164 pulls.
Got both Hina and Hoshino within 40 rolls.
Stop bragging to me!
Stop bragging!
This is so messed up!
Pink!
Please.
I've been a good sensei.
I do all my dailies.
Oh, it's the second one.
Okay, we can...
rip off the band-aid.
Oh!
Someone new though.
I got Denge.
Oh, my bad.
Sorry, Denge.
I don't...
I'm like...
Sorry, I'm like...
Who?
You guys have 4000 left!
4000!
Next one!
Blue!
I'm scared to pull.
You should be.
This is a bloodbath.
Mamai!
Alright.
I can do two more pulls.
This is it.
Don't brag unless you intend to send her money to keep rolling cowards.
Oh, yeah.
It does have a pity system, but only after 200 pulls.
So...
Oh, my god.
I got the nine blue ones.
Alright.
Last one.
Wait!
I'll be able to spark for her though.
At this point.
Here it is.
Blue.
And... flip.
Nope.
I'm gonna get so many ellips though.
Yippee!
I got so many ellips, you guys.
I can spark for her.
I have 402 left.
Secured Hina and Hoshino in 13.
Thank you for your energy.
Stop bragging!
Keep pulling for your own pride.
Thank you.
Stop bragging.
Oh, gosh.
Very confused.
Sorry.
I'm pulling in blue archive right now.
It's a special event.
How many did I have saved up?
I had...
20,000.
Maybe...
23,000.
Mima...
Pulling fun.
Thank you.
How many pulls is that?
About 200.
200 of them.
I want Hoshino swimsuit.
Should I pull?
Or should I...
Should I buy?
I got 150 more because I...
I pulled so many new students.
Now...
I pulled 6 new students.
It's not bad.
And then I also...
From the previous banner, I pulled Kasumi and Iroha.
So, out of...
In the past week, I got...
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
8.
And then also, I got Dressako.
So, 9.
And also, Makoto.
So, 10.
In the past week, I got 10 new students.
But my luck has always been very bad.
So, I don't have very many 3 stars.
You don't deserve summer Hoshido.
What are you talking about?
I'm banning you, Oimo Buster.
Fuck off.
Get this bitch out of my chat.
In time out for 24 hours.
I
hear your bullshit.
Goodbye, Oimo.
I have...
You don't even understand.
I just got the achievement that was like...
Have 93 star students.
My luck in this game is shit.
Okay?
You don't deserve her.
What are you talking about?
I still don't have Shiroko.
Regular Shiroko.
I can claim her.
I have...
I have 221 of her Eliphs.
But I'm just waiting for the day I pull her.
Are you free to play Mint?
I do the monthly...
The monthly package.
You know where you get the little bit every day.
And then you also get the extra...
The extra...
What's it called?
Scrimmage tickets and the extra bounty tickets.
Do you have Kohaku?
I had to use a ticket on her.
I didn't have her.
Can't believe you killed Oimo.
Good.
Sorry I'm in my cafe now.
What level are you?
I'm only 75 I think.
76?
Oh nice.
You can't back out on stream.
Hashtag Oimo did nothing wrong.
Also she showed her BA room yesterday and it was not as bad as you made it out to be.
You're just an Oimo hater.
What are you talking about?
She had to have added more stuff.
Are you kidding me?
She added more stuff.
What are you saying?
She said that I didn't deserve Summer Hoshino.
I spent all my gems.
How much is it for Carrier Boy here?
Carrier boy here, Oimo said she rolled 3 stars in 200 polls last fest She also said, please forgive me.
It's because I have so few.
It's because I have so few stars to...
Get out of here, Carrier Boy.
Oh gosh, they're so expensive.
I never looked at these prices before.
Oh my god, what if I spent $65, but I don't get it?
If it makes you feel better, it took me 1910 rolls for Summer Hoshino, so I just went ahead and pitied for Hina.
That's basically me right now, Takezo.
I'm like, maybe I should just...
I mean, I've already sparred.
I can recruit her without buying.
The packages are expensive.
$65 for a moment of joy.
It's not joy!
It's disappointment!
It always is!
I have 204 recruitment points.
I can get her right now.
I saved 21 gems and had to pity for Dressako.
No!
But the free pulls!
The free pulls!
I think I'm just gonna...
Even the free pulls didn't save me.
I'm so sorry.
How was Anime Fest?
A blast!
I had so much fun!
Safer maid Midoriya Momoi.
Oh!
Okay.
I was gonna spark for Aqua since they gave us 100 free rolls, but then she showed up on roll 200!
Yeah!
No!
No, not Momoi.
Momoi.
Momoi is cute.
Okay, you guys.
I'm gonna... I'm just gonna spark for Hoshino.
I'm gonna spark for Hoshino!
I'm pressing the button!
It feels so...
Come here, Sensei.
It's really cool here.
Yay!
I got her.
Hoshino!
Well, I have all the units for the Fest now.
Sorry, that's Chirino.
Imagine you do a single pull and she pops up.
Okay, I'll try.
One single pull!
Let's see.
Nope.
Wait, memory.
What if it flips?
That'd be crazy.
No, I'm just kidding.
Haruka.
Yeah.
How many Elves do I have now?
I'm so curious.
Let's see.
Shop.
My Eligma.
I have 7,206.
I got Dressina at 20.
Shut up, Raybag!
Shut up!
I never spend them, ever.
I never spend them.
I hoard everything.
Like for my normal tickets, like just the regular currency thing.
I have 200 million.
I have 212 million.
Hoarder Oshii.
Yeah.
I never also, I never also use like the, what's it called?
The select, you know how you can do the, oops.
I pressed the wrong thing.
Did you hear Arona?
Hold on, she'll say my name.
Wait, hold on.
No, Arona, say my name.
Don't embarrass me now.
Nevermind.
You heard it?
You heard the Minto-sensei?
Yeah.
Oh, she's camera shy.
What's it?
The, you know when you can like level up your character?
I always just...
When you have to get like the Blu-rays and things, I always just save up for them.
I never use the selectable ones.
So maybe that's why I'm like a little lower level than stuff.
But, you know, I like to save up everything.
Okay.
But now, I have a dress Hina.
And I can put her right next to swimsuit Hina.
And regular Hina.
Wait, what does she look like when you pick her up?
Wait, hold on.
What does she look like?
Let me just go into a random mission.
Wait.
Where is she?
Hina.
She's so cute!
Her little...
Irene, welcome to Mabushop.
Listening to my ghost Oshii giggle and drool.
Yeah, she picks up.
Hina, Blue Archive.
Blue Archive, please sponsor me.
I'm your targeted audience.
She's so cute.
Look at her go around.
Hold on.
My other favorite is Koharu.
Where are you, Koharu?
Vancherino.
Sorry.
Let go of me.
I'm gonna go into the cafe.
I can't wait to pat her head.
Oh gosh.
I'm gonna go...
Wait.
I'm gonna go to the cafe.
Can I summon her?
Oh no.
I don't have any.
I can't invite her, yet.
I'm gonna invite her and then I'm gonna give her...
I'm gonna give her the big stuff and I'm gonna get her recollection.
And then I'm gonna be so happy!
Hahahaha.
There's a special animation.
I've seen this special animation if you use Dress Ako and Dress Hina at the end.
I can't wait for Shiroko Terror.
Maybe then I'll...
Maybe once... maybe once...
I'm gonna put the music back on.
Maybe once Shiroko Terror comes out, if I haven't gotten Shiroko by then, I'll just pull for her.
Or I'll get her, you know?
I pulled Hoshino Swimsuit on my second 10 pull.
I'm so happy for you.
I'm going to be...
I'm going to a famous hot dog restaurant this weekend!
I'll make sure to leave you one as an offering.
What kind of toppings do you want?
Onion, onion, onion!
Yeah!
Oh, sounds delicious!
What's a famous hot dog place?
Hifumi Daisuke.
Oh my gosh!
Jelly straight up butt doctor!
Hifumi's pretty cute.
Going to the gym for the first time in like 8 months tonight!
Can you possess me?
And go for a walk?
No.
If not, can I get some encouraging words instead?
Work, work, work!
Get those gains!
Minto gains!
Ghosty gains!
Your space is ghost!
Hashtag ghosty gains!
Costco is most famous.
Oh, my favorite character in Blue Archive!
I have three.
Cherino, Koharu, and Hina.
Minto gains!
Yeah!
It's a place in New Jersey that does deep-fried hot dogs called Rippers!
That sounds amazing.
Wow.
Thanks for accompanying me during my part-time job, Minto!
I don't work retail, but it was fun hearing you beat customers up.
It's also my birthday today!
Can I get a happy birthday?
Of course!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, dear SoborGuy!
Happy birthday!
SolidMarine, welcome to membership!
And with that, I'm going to end the stream.
Thank you guys for hanging out with me for all of my polls and everything.
Streamer luck is questionable.
But!
I will see you guys tomorrow!
I have a double stream.
One afternoon stream for me, and then another...
I'll be streaming on...
On...
Well, I'll be on, I think, Berry's channel?
I think?
Wow, Tsum Tsum!
Hoshino is so cute!
I just got her, too!
I'm so happy for you!
At Berry's, yeah.
Yeah!
I think that we were...
Before, we were still trying to decide.
But anyway...
Otsumita!
Have a great night!
Good luck with all your gacha polls.
And I will see you guys later!
Itterashai!
Bye bye!
Thank you for hanging out with me!
Thank you, thank you!
Thanks for the fun stream!
Thank you, Bakery!
Thank you!
And...
For the Akasupa earlier, thank you.
I will probably have to use it for Shiroko Terror, so...
Thank you guys!
Thank you guys so much!
Bye bye!
Otsumita!