Oh no, wait, I actually forgot something.
Thank you.
Oh no, wait, I forgot something.
Stop, I forgot.
Wait, no, no, no, I just realized now.
Oh my gosh, why am I just realizing now?
Oh, I forgot my noise gain.
Thank you, thank you.
Oh, shoot.
It's fine for today.
It's fine for today probably.
Hello.
Oh my god.
You're a super...
I didn't think, I didn't think I...
Oh gosh.
You guys, the main cafe is so messy.
No one has paid the power bill.
It's so...
There's not even any lights on.
There's cobwebs even.
I haven't had a chance to really clean up.
I didn't think anybody would be back here.
You know, I...
You're a super...
Hello.
Hi.
You're a super...
You can help me clean it?
You can?
Help me clean it?
You're a super...
Maybe I should turn off the note if so.
I'll turn them off for karaoke later.
Thank you, thank you.
Give me, give me, give me, give me a second.
Hi...
Hold on.
Okay.
Okay, I got it.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
I think I'm...
Uh...
H-okay...
Ah...
Huh...
Ha...
Thank you, thank you.
Chuu.
Hello!
Welcome back!
Master!
Lady!
Welcome to my...
bed...
cafe!
Well, hold on, hold on.
Hold on.
I have my...
I have my trusty broom here.
So we can...
We can...
clean up the cobwebs, right?
See?
You see it?
Okay.
Hold on, hold on.
Yay!
Okay, let's get the other side.
It looks like I'm...
sweeping up the...
nodefs.
Get out of here!
Wait, where is it?
This one.
Yay!
Okay, now I can...
throw it away.
Into the garbage.
There it goes.
I never need to clean again.
Arigato Arigato-chu.
Oh my gosh.
This is already...
It's too much.
That's too much already.
It's too much already.
Thanks for cleaning up.
You're welcome!
Yeah!
Nice and...
refreshed...
in here now.
Except... except it's kind of dark.
I'm sorry.
Again, I haven't... I'm just the ghost haunting here.
I don't pay the bills.
I truly think this place was abandoned.
Aren't your hands tired?
No, my hands are like this!
Because I'm a ghost.
It's just naturally up.
Why?
Do you want me to put my hands down?
It's really cursed.
It's perhaps more cursed than if my hands are up.
To be honest.
Do you want to see?
Do you... want to see my hands down?
You want to see?
My hands down?
Oh my god.
Your house.
Oh wait, hold on, hold on, hold on.
I have something for this instead.
I just flew in here and... boy, are my arms tired.
That's it.
That's all I got.
You can go home now.
Boo!
Oh my gosh!
You guys love it!
Thank you!
Yes!
Boo!
Yes, yes, yes!
Yes, I'm a ghost!
Boo!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
You guys get it!
Yes, you guys love it!
You guys love it!
I knew it!
I knew you guys would be... would be...
Patrons of good cultured taste, I had a feeling.
Memberships when?
I saw multiple people asking before stream even.
If I was gonna open up memberships but...
I can't do anything.
I can't have super chats.
I can't have...
Hold on, I don't like this anymore.
I can't have memberships.
I can't have super chats.
Until I have three videos uploaded.
So today is my first video.
So after three streams...
Most likely.
I think.
Probably.
Anyways, hello.
Thank you.
You're a simp.
Gosh, my...
It's so weird hearing these don't know sounds.
They're from three years ago.
It's so weird hearing them.
Oh my gosh, it's so weird being here.
It's so weird.
Oh, I was gonna introduce her.
You're a simp.
I was gonna introduce myself, yes.
Because I think there's many people here that...
Thank you, thank you.
That...
I...
That don't know me.
Because there's a lot of people that I don't know either.
But back in the day, I was...
I was just a, you know, teeny tiny spirit.
So now...
I think...
My maid cafe is at max capacity.
There's like a five hour waiting line.
It's Disney World up in here.
I only know her from the podcast.
Thanks for listening.
Thank you.
Yes.
I am...
I'm back because Matara summoned me.
Oh, goodness gracious.
Arigato.
Thank you so much.
I really appreciate all the donuts.
Thank you guys.
Thank you.
I will turn off the Dono sounds eventually.
Because we'll be doing karaoke later, so...
But yeah, Matara summoned me for a podcast.
And now I'm back haunting you.
Arigato.
What else?
Oh, my name is Mint.
My name is...
My name is... My name is Mint.
Phantom.
Minto.
That's me.
Watashi.
Watashi no namae wa.
Watakushi no namae wa.
Minto to moshimasu.
I have to speak in Keigo because because I'm the maid.
I'm the lowly maid.
And you guys are the goshijinsama and ojousama.
Yep.
Oh, gosh.
I have to serve you guys.
Yeesh.
Age hasn't slowed you down one bit.
Thank you.
Does that one say you're a soup?
No.
I don't remember why I made it.
It was you're a simp.
I think it was from Seigi.
Thank you.
You guys, I'm back and all my friends are gone.
Well, not all of them.
But a lot of my friends are gone.
A lot of things have changed in the three years.
It was Seigi.
Yeah, it was Seigi.
Wasn't it?
A lot of things have changed in three years.
But I think I think I can say I think I can say I'm still me.
Right?
I think I can say that.
Thank you.
I think.
I think I can say I'm still I'm still minty fresh.
You're a soup.
Despite everything, maybe.
Amori!
Oh.
Thank you.
Happy to have you back.
Yeah!
Sorry.
I'm getting... I'm working over a cold.
So maybe actually today's not the best day to sing but I don't know.
I didn't know what else to do.
So I thought maybe singing would...
kind of...
Oh gosh.
Sorry.
Okay.
I'm gonna turn off the notification sounds because I think it's a little overwhelming when it's only streamlabs and no and no superchats because I don't usually turn on sounds for superchats.
Thank you.
I had a great grand nostalgia hearing all these sounds.
I hope you guys did too.
Okay.
Congrats on coming back.
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
Maybe it's a backlog.
There!
Sorry.
There are many messages.
I will read them.
Oh.
Hey.
Wait.
Wait a second.
Oh.
Wait.
I think it's a...
Okay.
Now I think it's done.
Unless it's just a backlog.
Sorry.
I said there would be a little bit of scuff.
Yay!
You're a soup.
Soup.
What kind of soup?
Chicken and... Chicken...
No.
Hold on.
I used to...
I used to love the cream of chicken.
Mint soup?
Corns!
Corn soup.
Yes!
Yes.
My favorite.
How did you know?
Oh my gosh.
I have a feeling we're already going to be getting along pretty well.
If you already suggest corn soup.
Corn potage!
That stuff.
That's the yummy scrumptious dilly dilly dumpious stuff.
Right there.
Ectoplasm soup.
No.
That's not for consumption.
I think.
But yeah.
Welcome to my maid cafe.
Can I turn on the lights actually or will it be a flash bang?
Will it be too bright?
I could do a spongebob thing.
Where I just flick around the lights or something.
Hahaha.
Turn them on.
Flash bang us.
You ready for the big bang?
Oh.
Three.
Two.
Okay.
Now I can welcome you to my maid cafe.
Yay.
Welcome.
Welcome to my maid cafe.
I haunt this place.
Light mode my eyes.
Hahaha.
Get used to it.
I see some familiar names in the chat.
Hello.
Hahaha.
Let there be light.
Hmm.
Hahaha.
Sorry.
I keep expanding sometimes.
Ahem.
Um.
What do I say now?
Uh.
This isn't.
Okay.
Oh.
Yes.
I have stuff that I want to talk about.
This is not like a debut.
Or even a re-debut.
I guess it's just me coming back and saying howdy doody to you all.
Um.
Hold on.
I wrote notes on my howdy doody.
Hahaha.
Yeah.
It's me saying howdy doody.
Oh.
Sorry.
That's TikTok.
Ah!
Sorry.
Hahaha.
Okay.
Sorry.
I was watching TikToks for the nerves.
Okay.
Um.
Hahaha.
Ah.
Let's see.
Um.
Okay.
I said that I would be answering questions today, right?
Hahaha.
I said that I would be answering questions today.
Bye, Xiaoming!
Welcome back!
Congratulations, Mint-chan!
Thank you!
Hahaha.
Long time no see!
I missed you.
Ah.
I saw you in the open space.
I missed you.
Um.
I saw you.
What do you call it?
The, the, the, the tours.
Akiba's...
Like...
Virtual tour.
But...
It's like in Akiba, they have like some people sometimes are on backpacks and stuff.
Japanese is good.
Thanks.
I just got back from Japan.
Hahaha.
I'm so Japanese good right now.
What's special in my cafe?
Drinks or sweets?
Um...
Me!
Hahaha.
This is, this...
You can't find another ghost in your...
Well, there's probably actually other maid ghosts, aren't there?
Probably, right?
Hahaha.
I'm sold!
Yeah!
But yeah, I said today I would be answering some questions cause it's probably just like, what's going on?
Me too!
I also wonder what's going on.
Thank you for the donuts!
Thank you guys so much!
Thank you!
There's a lot.
The notifications are not stopping.
I appreciate you guys so, so much!
Thank you!
Um... Where's my notes app?
Notes...
Oh, here.
Okay.
Where's your notes?
Hey, you can't say that anymore, okay?
Oh, oh, oh.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You can't say that anymore.
You literally can see my notes, okay?
I don't want to hear that from anybody.
My notes...
is actually so existent.
Okay?
Oh my gosh, I sound so scraggly cause of my sore throat.
I hope the karaoke doesn't sound so bad.
What notes?
Look, if I look to the side...
Oh!
Like that!
Look!
Did you see that?
Look, look, look, look, look!
Oh, I'm off the screen.
Phantom notes.
Hannah!
Oh my gosh, everybody's here.
Why?
Okay.
Let's see.
I have a notes called questions for coming back stream.
Questions that nobody asked, but I thought maybe people would ask.
So...
Yeah.
Let's get started, I guess.
Okay!
First question that I wrote down.
That people might be...
This is so awkward.
I'm so sorry.
Did ask.
Do care.
I'm glad.
Okay.
Yeah, you do care.
Yeah, you do.
You do care.
Yeah.
Please answer.
The first question I wrote down that maybe people are wondering.
Is MI coming back permanently?
Is this like...
Is this it?
Is this...
Is this the finale...
The final return of Mint Phantom?
Is this...
Is this everything?
And...
The simple answer is...
truly...
I don't know.
Um...
Uh...
But as long as the podcast is going, I'll be around.
I wish I could give you...
a more concrete answer.
I wish I could tell you guys a lot of things.
I wish I could tell you guys...
everything that...
is going on in my brain.
Everything that is going on behind the scenes.
But unfortunately...
I can't.
So I'm really sorry.
I wish I could tell you everything that my brain has been swirling like...
ugh...
literal ectoplasm leaking out my ears all the time.
Tell me all of it.
But um...
Uh...
Yeah, just to be honest...
I'm still trying to figure out...
what I want to do.
And...
Um...
Yeah...
But I'm excited to be back.
I'm very excited to be back.
So...
Yes!
I'm happy to be here.
I'm really...
Even though I'm so anxious.
I'm really happy to be...
uh...
meeting you guys.
This is nice to meet you for a lot of people.
Um...
I know there were some people that...
knew me...
3 years ago.
But there's also a lot of people that don't know me...
now.
So, hi!
I hope you like what you see.
I hope you don't mind...
being haunted...
and stuff.
Is it okay if I haunt you?
Is it okay?
If I...
If I haunt you for a little bit?
If I steal some of your...
life force a little bit?
Is it okay?
I consent.
Yes?
Please do?
Yes please?
I'm gonna take it all.
All your life force.
That's fine.
Like...
Maybe like a few years off your life.
And then you can be a ghost!
Just like me!
Isn't that so exciting?
Hmm...
Okay.
Yeah.
Another question.
Will I be streaming regularly?
And I plan to be streaming...
about...
I wrote 3 to 4 times a week.
It might be more.
I think I'm...
I think I like streaming.
Back when...
Back a couple years ago...
I could only do...
so little because I worked at another maid cafe...
at the same time.
So...
It was...
much more difficult...
for me.
But now I'm a free ghost.
So...
I mean I am kind of...
I don't know.
I don't know if I should be...
a free ghost or not.
I kind of talked...
about it on...
with Matara.
If you listen to the...
If you listen to the podcast...
I was like...
Oh my gosh.
Maybe...
Maybe I'll get like a job at a...
Like a part-time job at a grocery store or something.
You would...
It is surprising how expensive it is...
to be a ghost.
You wouldn't think about it.
But there's so many things...
that I have to take care of.
Like...
I just frog blinked...
when I said that.
There's truly nothing...
going on in my head.
Ghost dollars.
Ghost taxes.
Oh my gosh.
You just reminded me.
My tax person has been ghosting me.
Not the good kind of...
ghosting though.
This is so bad.
Okay.
Thank you for reminding me.
I'm gonna write that down.
Email...
Hold on.
Tax person.
Okay.
Never mind.
Phantom tax.
Who are the patriots?
Oh my gosh you guys.
Heaven?
Oh yes.
I probably should talk about that, right?
I graduated...
three years ago.
Today, actually.
Because I graduated on 4-4.
4 in Japanese.
And I think it's...
in other Asian countries too.
It's death.
It's a lucky number for me.
I graduated on the luckiest day.
And...
Yeah.
So now I'm back.
On the luckiest day.
You graduated on death death?
Yep.
Death death.
But I went to heaven.
And...
I don't know.
I think I'm more suited to...
being a ghost.
I think I had too many...
unresolved issues.
You know?
Like being an angel was fun.
And all.
But I just felt...
still this urge to...
to like...
haunt you guys.
And...
Like...
I don't know.
Being a ghost...
feels more up my alley.
Bustin makes you feel good.
No no.
That's not what you're supposed to do though.
You know?
You're supposed to...
I mean...
I know I covered that.
But like...
But...
Um...
Don't bust me.
Okay?
I ain't afraid of no sleep.
I ain't afraid of no bed.
Let's see.
What else?
So yeah.
I'll be streaming...
somewhat regularly.
It might turn into more.
But I don't wanna...
With the podcast.
I don't wanna do too much.
Um...
Oh!
I wrote that down.
Why did you come back?
I wrote...
Even in heaven, I felt restless.
Like I had some unfinished business.
I don't think I was ready to go.
So maybe I'm best at being a ghost...
than an angel.
Maybe.
I even got my wings and everything.
I think they were fake though.
I think they were cardboard.
Couldn't even fly properly.
Um...
Question.
Is this a re-debut?
Nope.
It's just me.
Coming back to streaming.
And if I decide to stay...
What was that?
Batara, don't look!
Look!
Oh my gosh.
You didn't said that?
No!
That wasn't me!
I think that was...
I think that was part of the...
The...
The donation.
That's so funny.
Hold on.
I'm gonna keep drinking my tea.
Mmm...
Will you play Delta?
Oh hell yeah!
I'm gonna play Delta!
Are you kidding me?
Yeah!
I'm gonna play Delta!
So excited.
Oh my gosh.
This is just me returning to streaming.
Um...
If I decide to stay...
Then I'll make it a bigger deal.
Like...
New outfit?
Or...
Graphics?
New shiny stuff?
So...
Yeah.
I already have plans.
If that happens.
Yes.
You will have to stick around.
And me too!
Um...
But for now...
I'm gonna be mostly sticking to this...
Outfit.
If you watched me in the past...
You know that I had an original outfit.
At the moment...
I don't plan on...
Using it.
I'm sorry.
Just like...
It's really outdated.
And kind of embarrassing to use.
I think.
So...
Matara was...
Was very generous to...
Even get me...
Uh...
Rigged again.
So I'm...
A little more shiny and new.
I actually will touch on that in the...
In the next podcast episode.
So...
Yeah.
This one is very cute.
You like it?
You...
I have faces.
I can show you guys.
I can show you guys all my faces.
Like...
Or...
But yeah...
I'm...
Uh...
It's the same face.
No, it's not.
Can you do a surprise one though?
Okay, hold on.
I'll do a really good one.
Show us the chibi mode again.
Okay, patience.
Patience.
Let me get through these questions first.
That I wrote myself.
And no one wrote but me.
Um...
Uh...
Oh!
This one we talked about on Matara's stream.
But I will say it here as well.
Does the podcast mean that you are joining Bishoujo?
And no!
Does not mean that I am joining Bishoujo.
I'm just collaborating.
Collaborating?
Collaborating with Matara.
So I can haunt her and suck her life force.
And cause her discomfort in her daily life.
So...
Yes.
That's it.
But uh...
Bishoujo has been helping with um...
With some of the stuff like the merchandise.
Um...
Hashtag save Mata.
No!
Me!
I was summoned against my will!
What are you talking about?
Is this model all new?
No, just the rigging.
Um...
I got this model just before...
Or this outfit...
This new look.
Just before I...
Uh...
What's the word?
Left for heaven.
Yeah, yeah.
So...
Um...
But yeah...
Everything is so confusing.
People always say...
That I'm doing this and doing that.
I don't even know...
What I'm having for breakfast tomorrow.
So...
Let's just take it.
Let's just take things...
One step at a time.
Okay?
Um...
Another question...
That I wrote down.
Why didn't you come back sooner?
Um... I don't know.
Uh...
I don't know.
I probably...
I guess I could have come back anytime.
Maybe.
But I...
Honestly, I wanted to take some time...
To myself...
And shrugging emoji.
Basically.
I wanted to take some time...
To myself...
Be a little productive.
I just came back from studying in Japan.
So...
I just kind of wanted to take some time...
Away from my usual area.
And uh...
Clear my head and figure out what I want to do going forward.
And did I do that?
No!
I'm even more confused.
I have no idea.
What was the next question I wrote?
Did you clear your head and figure out what you wanted to do going forward?
No!
Next question!
Will you un-private your old VODs?
Um...
This one is like a tricky one for me, right?
Because...
I'm still deciding.
Uh...
A lot has changed from back then.
And...
I cringe every time I see an old clip.
I cringe at my old mic quality.
I...
I cringe...
At a lot of things.
A lot has changed.
I feel... I'm worried that maybe if I...
Uh...
If people watch...
The old VODs, they'll be like...
Oh, she's so different...
Than how she was 3 years ago.
Now, you know?
So...
I don't know.
Um...
Uh...
I know there's like...
Old... old... old...
You boomers out there!
I'm maybe... I'm not the boomer.
You guys are the boomers.
Get it?
Boomer?
People that watched me before...
And uh...
You know...
Might wanna like bring up old jokes...
And things that we did.
Things that we...
You know...
Talked about and everything.
But I kinda wanna like just...
I don't know.
Make this...
A place where...
Even newcomers can...
Can come in and be like...
You know...
Can...
Enjoy right away.
You know, I don't want it to be like...
Oh, I don't get this joke.
What is she talking about?
Things like that.
I want it to be...
Welcoming for everybody.
Yeah, new chapter.
Maybe.
Does that mean no Metal Gear Solid jokes?
What are you talking about?
I can't...I can't stop talking...
About Metal Gear.
Heaven had Metal Gear, you guys.
It's probably the best thing...
Not the best.
Well anyway, it had Metal Gear, and I'm sorry that I must tell you that I've come back brain-rotted.
Welcome back to the living?
Hey, I'm not living though.
I'm definitely deceased.
We can tell.
I'm so sorry.
Outer heaven.
That's literally me right now.
I think I am...
Oh my gosh.
The phantom...
The phantom pain!
Have I been...
Have I been snake this whole time?
Oh my gosh.
It all makes sense right now.
It was predestined.
Truly.
The phantom pain.
Oh my gosh.
Let's see what else do I have.
Oh!
Question.
If you decide to stay around longer, what can we expect?
Okay, this is kind of funny.
I wrote a lot!
More consistent schedule, comma, and then nothing else.
Oh boy, I'm selling it, aren't I?
You can expect so much from me.
You can expect...
...
you can expect...
That's all I ever wanted, really?
Yep!
So...
I'll take your entire stock.
Sign me up.
Sold!
Yes.
Sold.
What a deal.
Expect redacted.
Something.
It's something big.
I can't... I'm keeping you guys on your toes.
I can't let you in on all my secrets.
So...
Why is Snake Fortnite emoting in my screen?
Hold on.
I gotta cough.
I coughed.
A thousand.
What?
Thank you.
How are my studies going?
Oh, I'm done.
It was just a short program.
It was just a short study.
It wasn't...
Well, originally I wanted it to be six months, but the school could only do two, and so now I'm back.
I'm back home.
Yeah.
So...
But it was good.
I learned a lot.
Yeah, I learned a lot.
Hahaha.
Yeah.
What did you study?
I studied Nihongo.
I studied Nihongo so I could talk to my idol Oshis better.
But...
A lot of it was like...
A lot of it was like keigo.
It's just...
Ikki.
Ikki Nihongo.
I mean, Ikki keigo.
Yeah, yeah.
Too based?
What do you mean?
Oh, sorry.
I guess I can show you guys now...
Um...
A little bit more of my...
Uh...
What's the word?
My face This is that I can do.
Um...
This feels like a real... Hold on.
Oh!
Do I have to do the Vtuber thing where I show my body?
Do you guys want to see my body?
Here I am.
This is how I look.
I step to the left.
I step to the right.
That's...
This is...
What you see is what you get.
Oh yeah.
Totemo jozu.
Arigato.
Arigato chu.
Tipee time.
I'm dancing.
I'm grooving.
I'm schmoving.
Oh yeah.
Um...
Let's see what else.
Faces.
Um...
The drip animation is so shiny.
Oh yes!
I was...
I was so shocked by that.
Look!
My thighs are dripping!
The chocolate is actually dripping!
It's...
My ectoplasm a little bit.
My...
Even the chocolate is possessed.
Isn't that crazy?
Yummy.
Except it's not for licking.
It's a decoration.
It's actually poisoned.
If you...
Lick it, you will die.
Um... Okay.
I have.
This is how I'm feeling.
This whole time with so many people.
So many people.
Actually, I don't even know what the number is.
I don't even... I'm afraid to look.
I'm afraid to look.
I don't even know how...
In my brain, there's only two of you guys.
There's... Okay.
At least two.
Exactly.
Don't say it!
Don't say the number!
We're just typing really fast.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't say it!
I can... I can blush even more.
I can blush a little bit.
I can blush a lot a bit.
This is when... This is...
This is when... This is when...
Uh... This is when...
This... This is... This is when...
This is when I'm still flustered...
Flustered, flustered, flustered.
I can't speak.
Hahaha.
This is when...
When you see Raiden naked, so true.
Oh my gosh, so true.
Hey, you guys didn't hear...
You didn't hear anything!
Okay!
You heard nothing!
Can I have a bite of my pizza?
Sorry, I forgot to eat.
I got...
My stomach before this was like...
Like really growling at me.
Um...
I think we're comfortable enough now that...
I could eat on stream.
What the hell is that?
Who was that?
Who was...
Oh, you can hear me chewing on that.
I'm gonna mute.
It was the pizza delivery man.
Oh, it was Ryan Gosling.
I uh...
When I...
When I'm on the plane...
I...
Usually watch...
I usually watch one of...
Or actually...
I usually watch two movies for sure.
Or three.
Actually three movies for sure.
The first one...
Is Indiana Jones.
Some Indiana Jones movie.
This last time I watched The Temple of Doom.
And then...
I always watch Top Gun.
Most...
Usually I watch Top Gun Maverick.
I think Top Gun Maverick is...
My favorite movie of all time by this point.
I have watched Top Gun Maverick...
So many times.
I just...
I can't...
I...
I don't know how many times I have watched it at this point.
I watch it going...
Going...
To Japan and going back...
Every time that I've gone for like the past...
Year and a half.
I think...
It's so...
Good!
Oh my gosh.
I love the original Top Gun too.
But Top Gun Maverick is just...
Oh my god.
My favorite...
My favorite scene is when...
Maverick...
Tom Cruise...
That's...
That's him, right?
It's Tom Cruise, right?
Yeah.
When he is showing...
When he's showing the class...
When they have...
When he is like...
Showing them that the mission is possible.
Oh my gosh.
Wait.
He's in Mission Impossible.
No.
I didn't mean...
What?
Oops.
It's Top Gunning time.
When he is showing...
What?
When he does...
When he is like...
When they are just like...
Oh my gosh.
We can't...
We can't complete the mission in the time limit.
And with the...
Enough accuracy.
Oh my gosh.
Thanks for the raid.
Thank you.
But...
I love that scene.
And I love...
What was it?
Oh, yeah.
That's the scene I love.
But...
It's...
It gets me so hype.
Sorry.
Are we talking about the same movie?
Yes.
We're talking about Top Gun Maverick.
That's Ryan Reynolds.
No, it's not.
Oh.
That's...
That's what I was getting at though.
The third movie I usually watch is La La Land.
And I think before then...
Before La La Land...
I wasn't...
I wasn't so into Ryan Reynolds.
I know that he was like a meme for a long time.
But...
But now...
I...
I think I...
I think I get it.
Because of La La Land.
Oh, wait.
Sorry.
That's Ryan Gosling.
Ryan Reynolds is dead fully.
I...
I know.
My throat.
I can't even laugh properly.
Sorry.
I sound so raspy.
I think.
Sorry.
I get them...
I tend to get them confused.
Along with other Hollywood actors.
Hold on.
I'm going to mute so I can eat.
Okay.
Oh my gosh.
Thank you for the acca donut.
Thank you.
You guys are way too generous.
Holy cow.
You know.
What do you think of making Old Bob's members only?
Maybe.
That's an idea.
That is an idea that I can think of.
Thanks for the suggestion.
Oh my gosh.
Even before streams, someone was already backsating me in the donuts.
They were like...
And I was like, what?
Why am I already being vaccinated?
There's a discord?
There apparently is a discord.
If anybody wants to join it, I suppose.
Where was I?
Oh, I can be...
I can be sad.
I can be more sad!
Oh god!
My eyes are so wobbly.
I'm so sad.
I'm so sad right now.
That...
That you...
Um...
Don't want me to join the discord.
Why can't I join the discord?
Why can't I join?
Why don't you guys want me around?
Not saying howdy.
You're not invited.
Oh, there was another gif?
Oh no, I missed it.
I missed it!
Uh, let's see.
What else?
Oh, I can be...
You guys have seen this one before.
I've seen several.
Several people using this as a reaction.
Oh...
Wah...
Shock... I'm so shocked.
Um...
This is me joining the discord.
And seeing everything that you guys are saying.
Yeah.
And then...
This is me!
Join... This is me!
What the hell?
Oh my god.
I was like, why are there naked men?
Is this God's...
Thank you, see?
Oh my gosh.
This is me...
Five minutes after joining the discord.
Maybe I didn't...
Need to join the discord.
Ah...
Yeah, yeah.
Eh...
Oh gosh.
There's gonna be...
Wait, I don't even know how many...
Donations there are.
I'm scared.
Uh oh.
I declare...
Bankruptcy.
I...
I prematurely declare...
Bankruptcy.
No, I'm just kidding.
Uh... Let's see.
Oh, this one.
Mm-hmm.
This is...
This is when any...
When Metal Gear discussion...
Metal Gear, Metal Gear...
Metal Gear discussion, let's go!
But also...
When I think about the discord.
You better not be saying...
Crazy things in there.
The next one, I'm never gonna use.
So...
This is your one time to see it.
Okay?
I'm gonna get in real close for you.
This is your one time to see...
This face...
What is that?
What is...
What was that?
Hold on, I'm gonna move the notice somewhere else.
I'm gonna move you guys down here.
I'm never gonna use this one.
So...
Just today.
Bye.
I have no...
I don't even know...
What I would use this one for.
Okay.
This might be a mistake, showing you guys, at all.
This might be a mistake.
No!
Oh my gosh!
Okay, but the worst part is...
Why?
Why is there steam coming out of my mouth?
Hot pot.
This is me seeing corn soup.
I want some more!
It's cold outside.
True, true, true, true.
True, true, true.
You don't want to see if I combine it.
I have the coconut to eat.
Dream works, anybody?
No, no, no!
No, no, go away!
Okay, we're fine.
We're normal, we're normal, we're normal.
Get outta here!
Oh my god!
These gifts are so cursed.
I completely forgot that was a theme.
I turned it off before, so I completely forgot it was a thing for Streamlabs to be able to do that.
No, we are not.
Mint looking at Snake.
Snake!
No, this is me looking at Plissken.
Plissken.
He's so cool.
Maybe I do have a reason to use him.
I do have Fortnite, because I got Snake.
But I have to change my name on it.
My name right now is something ridiculous.
And also...
Because it got on my tongue.
I'm not going to open my mouth all the way though.
I'm not going to give you weirdos what you want.
But I can give you...
Don't combine that with the heart eyes.
I'm not going to give you guys what you want.
I know better.
Please, it's my birthday.
It's not.
So cute.
Oh.
Wait, who was that?
Usami!
Oh my gosh!
Oh my gosh, it's been so long.
Hello!
Oh my gosh.
So many people have come back.
Hello, hello.
I think that was all I had.
Oh, I can...
Top Gun!
Yeah, baby.
Oh my god, wait.
Jakedo, you sent the other one before too.
The other gif.
Love it when Tom Cruise...
Oh, I missed it.
Wait.
Oh, shows that the mission is possible.
Stop.
I can also be very smug.
Oh, I also...
I saw...
I showed this one earlier.
Oh, head empty.
No thoughts.
Nothing.
Nothing going on behind my brain.
And also...
Hmm.
I like combining...
I like this one.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Hmm...
Come on.
Hmm.
Conada face.
For real though, actually.
I think that's everything now.
Oh, can I...
I can also...
Oh!
That's not everything!
Oh my gosh.
Tara hooked me up.
I can also...
Hmm.
Hmmm.
That's the best one?
You think so?
The GIFs.
What is it?
It was Brian Reynolds again.
Oh, I can also... I can cross my eyes.
Whoa!
I feel like a Dreamworks.
Oh my gosh.
I think that's everything.
Now, I think.
Maybe.
Oh, there's also... well, this is like...
I can... I can start sweating.
When I'm just feeling a little bit sweaty.
I'm sweaty!
Sweaty gaming.
Sniffa?
Hey!
That's my ectoplasm.
Stop it.
How much for a mint sweat bottle?
You don't want it.
Microwave scene.
Okay.
Are we ready to sing?
I feel a little less nervous, but...
How are we feeling?
How are we...
Do you guys...
I know I... I know I look a little different.
I really... I did talk about this in the podcast.
I really did love Yua's rigging.
Yua did such an amazing job.
And I love Yua so much.
She saved me.
And...
Snake!
What does it say?
I've heard it.
Hahaha.
Oh, the TV model.
That's right.
It's a little disturbing to watch me switch back and forth.
So, it's kind of like body of where it feels.
Um...
But, uh...
What was I gonna say?
Oh my god, Kermit!
Minty fresh!
I don't even remember what I was saying.
Oh, I was gonna say...
Oh, yes.
I was saying I loved Yua's rigging so much.
Yua as my papa was the best ever.
But, uh...
And I mentioned this...
Sorry, I know I keep saying that.
I've said it in the podcast.
But I...
Um...
But the...
It was actually incomplete.
Because we had to get it done so quickly.
So...
Um...
It...
It was...
It's a little incomplete because...
Or...
It was incomplete because of that.
So, with this I was able to...
Get a bunch of stuff that I had originally wanted.
Here.
Now.
Yeah.
Gosh!
This like enhances my chest.
I'm a chibi!
And I do steppies.
Steppy tap.
Steppy tap tap.
Tippy tap.
Um...
Get on.
You razzle dazzle.
Razzle.
Dazzle-umn.
Um!
How can they see you?
With sequins in their eyes?
Yup.
I look like a...
I look like a baby.
I'm a baby.
You got games on your phone?
Do kids still play Roblox?
What do...
Ew, what are like... what is gen alpha play now?
If not... Roblox and uh...
They do?
Yes?
I have no idea.
Nobody puts baby in the corner.
You know, I only know that line from... from... uh...
How do I say?
Okay.
I guess I'll be honest with you guys.
You know, in the past...
I wasn't entirely honest with you guys.
When I said...
I was going to go work at a maid cafe...
I lied.
In fact, I only haunt...
this one maid cafe.
I...
was working...
an office job.
I was haunting an office.
I'm sorry to have lied to you.
You probably thought I was some super maid.
Who...
was going around to every maid cafe ever.
And being so productive and awesome.
And like I was the best maid ever.
I'm a big phony.
But that's how I know that...
Who was that?
I'm getting a bunch of strangers coming in.
You're so mean new to me.
So you pay me the bills.
You like to call me the phony.
Waiter is like a damn fiddle.
But yeah...
I'm so sorry to have...
To have lied to you like that.
Oh my gosh.
It's weird seeing my...
There was a lady at one of my jobs who would always say, Nobody puts baby in the corner.
I don't know what it's from.
It's from a movie, right?
But she would say it all the time.
And she would say that and she would say, Dingo ate your baby!
Dirty dancing!
I've never seen it.
I'm Say-So.
I don't dirty dance.
I'm Dirty Dan.
Singing time.
Give me a second to set up.
I haven't used this in a long time.
Okay.
I think we're good.
Hold on.
Okay.
I think we're good.
Oh!
We're not good!
Oh my gosh!
Anya!
Hold on.
Before singing.
I'm an idiot.
I should have done this at the beginning of the stream.
This is a small introduction.
For people that don't know who I am.
A small introduction.
Welcome back.
Master.
Lady.
Um...
I made this when I actually debuted this model.
A long time ago.
Um...
When I had my 2.0 debut.
And I didn't change anything.
Because...
I don't have Photoshop anymore.
I was like...
Oh...
I don't even know what to change.
Everything was pretty much the same.
So...
Hmm...
This is me.
I'm Forever 19.
And my birthday is also my death day.
Which is October 1st.
Um...
Maybe we'll celebrate it.
This year.
This year, right?
Um...
I'm 149 centimeters.
And usually you don't ask a lady her weight.
But...
Since I'm a ghost.
I'm zero kilograms.
So...
It doesn't matter.
Um...
My special trait...
Is my toad impression.
I'm pretty good at impressions.
Actually.
I'd say.
Skinny legend.
What...
What would toads say in a situation like this?
Skinny legend!
Ah!
Any frog pretends?
Oh!
I can kind of do a Kermit impression.
Right?
Ah!
Hold on...
I have to really channel it...
Through my throat.
HEY!
What does the Kermit say?
Welcome to the Muppets.
I'm going to Muppet all over the place.
I can't do it.
He says hello Canada.
He dies?
Maybe it's like a special episode that I've never seen.
I don't know what he would say.
Hello Canada.
Like that?
Is that how he would say it?
Yeah.
I have hashtags.
But I saw...
I think...
I don't know.
I only had a general hashtag.
I never needed...
an art hashtag in the past.
So...
Maybe...
I don't know.
Maybe we should keep it?
I don't feel like I need more than a general hashtag and a stream hashtag.
Which...
The general hashtag is Mintoshindeishashin Which is basically ghost photography.
When you're like...
If you're searching spooky ghost photos in Japanese, it's Shindeishashin.
Please art tag?
Okay.
I can come up with one later.
And uh...
Stream hashtag is Mintolive.
Maybe it should be Mintodead.
Because I'm never live.
I'm always dead.
You have to know.
But yeah.
I mean it's just a general hashtag.
I guess maybe hashtag MintPhantom can be the general hashtag.
I don't know.
But there's my oshimark.
It's a ghost and sparkles.
In case you're curious.
Uh...
My likes and my dislikes.
I like anime.
I like horror.
I like sweet things.
I like riding trains.
I like idols.
I like REM.
I love REM.
So sweet.
Actually, I think I need to...
No, not replace.
But I think I need to add someone else.
Okay.
Yeah, I think I need to add someone else.
Because...
You guys, I think I'm seriously in love with FreeRen.
I think...
I think I love FreeRen too much.
There was a tweet going around when FreeRen was airing.
It was a Japanese tweet.
About how...
They were like...
If you say that you're too in love with FreeRen.
That's okay.
Because FreeRen is this generation's Ruri.
From Nadesco.
And I love Ruri.
I love Ruri so much.
But...
I love...
I love FreeRen.
She's like...
Ruri with like a little extra attitude.
And I just...
I love her so much.
I need to add Metal Gear.
That too!
My heart.
Thanks for the donut.
Thank you so much.
Thank you guys.
I think we're all caught up.
I think.
I love...
Thank you.
Loyalty to the end.
Yes.
But yeah.
I love Rem.
And I love FreeRen.
I've been so obsessed with FreeRen recently.
I love cute.
I love anything that's cute.
I love anything Moi.
Moi is justice.
Martian successor Nadesco.
Yeah!
It's one of my favorite enemies.
So, so, so, so good.
And I love dad jokes.
Cause they're funny.
I think.
Things I don't like are spicy food.
Don't like spicy food.
I don't like messes.
Cause I'm a maid.
And if there's a mess, I gotta clean it up.
I don't like jumpy things.
Like...
Cockroaches.
And...
Crickets.
...
I don't like the cold.
I prefer warmer weather.
And I don't like it when you don't leave snacks.
If I'm visiting you.
If I'm visiting you in your bedroom.
At night while you're asleep.
I'm like...
I'm like a ghostly...
I'm like a ghostly Santa Claus.
Okay?
You gotta leave me like a little something.
A little offering.
Okay?
Yeah.
So you're like Santa Claus.
That's what I just said.
Ayo, my bedroom.
Look.
It's just part of like being a ghost.
I go around and I haunt.
Sometimes...
It's gonna be a maid cafe.
You know I gotta check up on...
the master and the mistress.
Just leave some snacks, okay?
You never know.
That's all you gotta do.
Oh, that's it.
Yay!
My introduction.
Okay, now we sing.
Woohoo!
Wahoo!
I hope we can sing.
My throat is getting...
gradually worse.
I think.
Oh my gosh.
Thank you for the Akadora.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Welcome back to this world makes us all smile knowing you're back.
Thank you.
I really thought that...
nobody...
Well, you know, there was people that watched me obviously.
Back in the day.
But I didn't think people would remember me.
So I was really...
surprised.
Especially...
that there's so many people here.
So...
I'm just gonna sing for a little bit.
I don't even know what to sing.
Do you guys have any...
I will take requests.
Oh, hold on.
Let's do this.
Sorry.
I only have like this scene.
And...
nothing else.
I have my intro.
And this scene.
So we're just gonna do karaoke here.
I hope that's okay.
But I have...
Hold on.
Setting up a little bit.
Get out of here, music.
It's...
this...
time.
Oh...
That's not adorable audio, is it?
I tested it...
before, but...
Is it...
audio okay?
Is it good?
Okay.
Hello?
Why isn't this one activated?
Oh, there we go.
Okay.
Nice, nice, nice.
This is...
This is JoySound on...
the Switch.
So if you're ever like...
Man, I wish I could do Japanese karaoke.
And I'm not just gonna sing...
Japanese songs.
I can sing whatever I want!
Yippee!
So...
Yeah.
If they don't have it on here, we can see...
if there's like a karaoke version of it on...
YouTube or something.
But...
Yeah!
Oh...
What should I sing?
Snake... Snake Eater.
You guys, I have a bad...
They don't have Snake Eater on here.
What am I searching?
Oh...
Me...
Meta...
Metal...
Yeah...
They only have two...
I looked it up earlier because I was testing it.
Metal Gear songs on here.
And the first...
I kept seeing this one at karaoke in Japan.
I have no idea what this song is.
The Phantom Pain by White Ash.
I looked it up.
I looked...
And I had never heard this song before.
I was like...
What is this?
The Phantom Pain.
I have no idea.
Really good band?
Oh, you know that?
Japan only song?
Maybe...
Do they have Busted on there?
They probably have Ghostbusters.
But I can sing Can't Say Goodbye to Yesterday.
But I think maybe...
That's like...
We need a better starter song.
Right?
But you know what?
Let's do Ghostbusters.
Yeah.
Ghost...
Ghostbusters!
I'm not afraid.
Didn't... What's that group?
Atarashii Gakko?
I think they recently did a...
A...
What is the I'm not afraid version?
What's the Fall Out Boy?
Huh?
Featuring Missy Elliott.
Anyway...
Ghostbusters.
Oh, they don't have the...
Atarashii Gakko version.
That's okay.
Utau!
Do you guys like my meme?
This is...
This is to get us a little warmed up.
Oh!
It's kind of loud.
Oh, there's
something strange...
In the neighborhood.
Who you gonna call?
Mint Phantom!
If there's something weird...
And...
Who you gonna call?
Mint Phantom!
Is the audio okay?
I ain't afraid of no ghost!
Things...
Running through your...
An invisible man...
Sleeping in your bed...
Who you gonna call?
Ghostbusters!
I ain't afraid of no ghost!
Of no
ghost!
I ain't afraid of no ghost!
Oh, who you gonna call?
Ghostbusters!
If you're all alone...
Pick up the phone...
And call...
Ghostbusters!
I ain't afraid of no ghost!
Garfield!
I hear it likes the girls!
Is that actually the lyrics?
I ain't afraid of no ghost!
Yeah!
I have
ghost mama!
Freaky ghost baby!
You better call!
I don't know that part!
I just know freaky ghost baby!
Freaky ghost man!
Freaky man baby!
I don't know the original of this song!
Let me tell you something!
Ghostbusters makes me feel good!
Yeah!
I ain't afraid of no ghost!
Oh,
don't get caught alone!
Ghostbusters!
When it comes through your door!
Unless you just want some fun!
Ghostbusters!
Who you gonna call?
I think you better call...
Ghostbusters!
Who you gonna call?
I can't hear you!
Ghostbusters!
Who you gonna call?
What's the number?
Ghostbusters!
No one gave me the number!
I have to google it myself?
Ghostbusters!
It's not very informative though.
What's the number to call them?
Yay!
Please check out Super Ghostbusters Karaoke by FatBirdKaraoke for some good laughs!
I'll check it out later.
Thank you.
Alright what else can we sing guys?
I don't I don't I don't know Oh, I know it.
I know that song, obviously, but I don't know how to sing it.
Ikenai Borderline?
You guys aren't sick of me singing Ikenai Borderline?
Really?
You're not sick of me singing it?
I sang it 50 times.
Really?
You want me to sing Ikenai Borderline again?
My Joy-Con is not very responsive right now.
Really?
We haven't seen you in 3 years, Mint?
Okay, I guess that's true.
But I sang it enough times to make up for 3 years.
And then some.
Ikenai Borderline 444 times.
Okay,
this will be the real test of my throat.
Of my voice.
I only got my voice back like...
What's today?
Thursday?
Got it back like Tuesday.
Wee-oo-wee-oo!
We look at each other, we fall in love We chase each other, we chase each other But I want to know more, I'm feeling dizzy The more I wish, the more mysteries The more I think, the hotter it gets That's why I jump in more I'm in a world of mystery Ah,
I believe in love and dreams I believe in everyone But I don't want to be the one to blame
Giri Giri Ai Ikenai Borderline Even if I have no life I'll try to break it all I'll show it to you Giri Giri Mai I'll get used to it My consciousness is melting My body can't control it I might just say it My
friends who made fun of me And the person I've been looking for I'm sparkling for the sake of meeting them again
This is the second one.
A little pause... and we are back.
I'm
so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Almost spilled my tea everywhere.
Nice!
Oh, Emily is playing Pokmon.
I know what you are doing, Emily.
I know you are playing Pokmon.
What else?
Let's see, what else?
Oh my gosh, I can sing so much.
It's hard to know what to sing.
It's been so long since I've sung that.
I have a cover.
Oh, Hamtaro!
A bunch of people have been requesting Hamtaro.
Of course I can do Hamtaro.
Also, it doesn't have to be just...
This program has English songs too.
So, and like I said, you can request whatever.
Whatever?
Hamtaro.
Nope.
You can request whatever.
And...
Yeah.
I'll do my best to do as many as possible.
Without killing my throat.
Without killing my throat too much, I think.
Oh gosh, I have to be careful here though.
Doing the calls.
Do you guys know Otage?
What?
Omijou..?
Omijou would agree with me.
He would agree.
Ok, on it!
Ok,
I'll try to sing.
Don't worry.
Ok, here we go.
I'm gonna sing.
This is a bit...
I'm
gonna sing.
You can sing.
Ok, I'll sing as well.
Ok, that's it.
Ok, let's go, let's go.
I'm going to sing.
Wait, I never sang when I was a kid.
I just sang at the same time.
Why
did the
chat stop?
Why did the chat stop?
Hold on.
Oh!
I think YouTube froze.
For me.
Am I still streaming?
Uh oh.
I am?
I can only read you guys through OBS.
YouTube completely crashed for me.
Uh oh.
Not even like going to YouTube.com is working.
Oh, here we go.
Okay.
Hold on.
Live stream.
There we go.
Let's go.
Well, I thought it was too powerful.
Truly.
Truly, truly, truly.
Snake Eater?
Are you sure?
I've never... I've never...
I've never sung it.
What if I can't sing it well?
I'm nervous.
What if I can't do it justice, you guys?
I wonder.
Hold on.
Snake, Eater, Karaoke.
Oh, I think this one would work.
It'll be fine.
You say that, please sing Break Stuff by Limp Bizkit.
I can probably do that one too.
You guys have interesting choices.
Okay, well this one is not obvious.
This one, obviously...
The...
Joy Sound didn't have it, so I'm gonna hide that.
Goodbye.
Oh gosh, I'm nervous!
Oh, I'm nervous!
Let me... let me hear this real quick and make sure it's okay.
Oh wow, it's just the original karaoke though.
I wonder if I'll get copyright struck.
Hmm...
This one has like...
Like, 360p audio quality, 240p audio quality.
So maybe that one's the safer one even though...
Okay, we can try it.
You know what?
I think it's okay.
Okay.
Whoa...
Oh my god.
What a thrill With darkness and silence through the night What a thrill I'm searching and I'm melting to you What a fear in my heart, but you're so supreme.
I give my life, not for honor,
take it all in my time.
There'll be no one else...
Oh my gosh, I'm so nervous.
Cry, it's the way I fly to you.
I'm still in a dream, snaking up.
Someday you'll go through the rain.
And someday you'll feed on a tree frog.
This ordeal, the trial to survive.
For the day we see new light.
I give my life, not for honor, but for...
In my time.
There'll be no one
else...
Cry, it's the way I fly to you.
I'm still in a dream, snaking up.
This ordeal, the trial to survive.
Oh my god.
I'm still in a dream, snaking up.
Snaking up.
Snake it up.
Hold on, I need a cough drop.
Oh my god!
That was so fun.
Man, that was so fun.
Okay.
Sorry, you can hear a cough drop probably.
Cynthia Harold will be proud.
I hope so.
If I ever get to meet her.
I'm gonna be like, rape me.
No, actually don't rape me.
Don't rape me, I'll cry.
She'll be like...
Cough drop ASMR.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Let's see, let's go back to Joystyle.
What else?
What else can we sing?
We can sing anything.
Practically anything.
The world is our oyster.
Oh wait.
There were some requests.
Oh, Plastic loves a good one.
Actually, I do want to sing that one.
I hope it's okay.
Wait.
I wonder if it'll show up in English.
Let's try the English first.
See if it comes up in English.
I'm just playing games.
I know that's plastic.
Wow, is that produced?
101 or whatever?
Plastic.
Plastic love.
Really?
Nothing yet?
Plastic love.
There it is.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Juice juice?
What?
No way.
There's a juice juice version.
Oh, sorry.
I haven't been writing down the set list.
That was beautiful.
Thank you so much!
Thank you for the donations!
Thank you guys for all the donations.
You guys are way too generous, for real.
Oh, it's loud.
I only cried a little bit.
Me too.
I actually cried a little bit.
Oh, Matari's not Ahmad!
Yep.
Sorry, Ahmadju!
Not anymore.
This is not enough.
It's not enough.
Ma- Mah ko do it.
What the hell
is she doing?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Where is she?
If you're here, say something!
Say something!
Where are you?
Where are
you?
Where are you?
I'm trying to look like we're singing at the same time!
I'm trying to look like we're singing
at the same time!
I'm trying to look like we're singing at the same time!
I'm just playing games, I know that's plastic love Dance to the plastic beat, another Oh, I almost put you in time out!
I'm just playing games, I know that's plastic love
Dance to the plastic beat, another morning comes
Oh, that's plastic love
Dance to the plastic beat, another morning
comes Yay!
Oh my gosh, I have a cough drop in my mouth the whole time.
Nom nom nom You're doing great, Min.
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
Love that?
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Well, oh, she's requested what?
Lips of a... what was it?
Lips of an angel?
With the lips of an angel.
I wonder if they have it.
I don't feel like, I don't know why they wouldn't ask a lot.
With the lips of an angel.
Oh my god, there it is!
No way!
They're pretty good.
Snake.
May I ask which karaoke software this is?
This is JoySound on the Switch.
You need a Japanese account to get it?
It's free to download it, but to sing, you have to get like a Japanese... oh, hold on.
Honey, why you calling me so late?
You need a, like a Japanese...
It's kinda hard to talk right now.
Cause I'm singing, sorry.
Honey, why you crying?
Is everything okay?
I gotta whisper cause I can't be too loud.
Sometimes I wish she was you.
I guess we never really moved on.
It's really good to hear your voice.
Saying my name, it sounds so sweet.
Coming from the lips of an angel.
Hearing those words, it makes me weak.
And I never wanna say goodbye.
But girl, you make it hard to be faithful.
With the lips of an angel.
Oh yeah, you need to have like a...
Oh my gosh, there's more?
It's funny that you're coming to me tonight.
And yes, I've dreamt of you too.
And does he know you're talking to me?
Will it start a fight?
No, I don't think she has a clue.
Well, my girl's in the next room.
Sometimes I wish she was you.
I guess we never really moved on.
It's really good to hear your voice.
Saying my name, it sounds so sweet.
Coming from the lips of an angel.
Hearing those words, it makes me weak.
And I never wanna say goodbye.
But girl, you make it hard to be faithful.
With the lips of an angel.
Okay.
Yes, you need a Japanese account.
But you also need to get...
A Japanese...
Um...
Nintendo...
You need Yen.
It's like...
300 Yen.
No, 500 Yen for 24 hours.
So, if you know a site that will, like, sell...
Like, uh...
Japanese e-card...
E-e-e-sim card?
Not sim cards.
You know what I mean.
Nintendo box.
It's really good to hear your voice.
Saying my name, it sounds so sweet.
Coming from the lips of an angel.
Hearing those words, it makes me weak.
And I wanna say goodbye.
But girl, you make it hard to be faithful.
Hard
to be faith...
The lips of an angel.
eShop...
eShop card.
Yes, thank you.
Not someone saying...
those Spotify ads are getting crazy.
Man...
So funny.
There's actually a song I want to sing.
I don't know if they have it though.
Because every time I would go to karaoke to sing this song...
It always be some weirdo remix version.
I wonder if they have it.
Do you guys know?
Actually, can you adjust the... Yeah, I think you can.
Oh!
They don't have it!
Wow!
Was that one song called Golden?
Oh, Slumbers.
I had me sweating for a second.
I did not read...
Golden Slumbers.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for being my Oshii.
Can you sing Ikanaide?
Ikanaide?
Oh, I wonder if they have it.
I'll check.
Nebika-
Which one would it be though?
This one, right?
Oh, they do have it.
Nice!
Oh, my gosh.
Great, Billy Mays.
Thank you for the Akadono.
Did somebody say Nintendo Bucks?
Man...
Oi.
I've never...
Actually, maybe I have sung this one before.
I'll get it.
I wonder if it's a fast version?
I
hope this stays archived.
Me too.
It would be really embarrassing to come back and have my first stream back be unarchived.
There was something else that I thought of while I was singing that.
I can't remember.
Sing sing?
Oh, FANZA is also a good one.
Okay, let me start making notes so I don't forget any.
I'll do FANZA first.
Wait, oh.
Can I do a small ah?
Oh wait.
Fa.
There we go.
FANZA.
Crazy frog.
What?
Oh my gosh!
Wait, no way!
There's a Hololive version of it!
What?
That's so cool!
Wait, what's different about it?
What?
So I guess this is from the Hololive Honeyworks crossover?
But what's different about it, I wonder?
Let's try it!
Ooh!
The hamster song.
Maybe it's the same.
Suki ni natte motto watashi wo mite motto On gaeshi wa ai no komatta nagekisu de Hehehe.
Kinosei janai me wa atteru yo Heart tsukutte That's so cute!
Koi shichatte kudasai Yareru koto nan demo shimasu NG inashi de Dai atari ni chousen Egoso de mitsuketa anchi no kame Fusage na dare yori wakatteru ne Shite mo daijoubu Tsuteite tate wa minna ga iru Iku ya!
On
gaeshi wa ai no komatta nagekisu de Koi kori suru motto Yume wo miseru motto Tanoshinde te Ai no komatta special night Fanta shichau no!
Hahaha.
Dan dan la la la la
Nando mo yonde Takaramono ni shimasu
Sengen shitto kimasu Shitto iagarase ni make na Ibu seke na Shittyoku de kateru yaru Dakara yame ni watashi wa iru Iku ya!
Wakubushi agete motto Ase wo kaite motto On gaeshi wa ai no komatta Horobi mode!
Mai gansei!
Motto!
Mada mada ne!
Uketoete ne!
Ai no komatta shichau no!
Kari ga chikazuku Sabishii ne Tanoshii nono Nakisou da yo Tsugi mo tsugi mo Mata aeru yo ne Yakusoku!
Aaaaah!
My throat is giving out!
Yasashisa ni otobu no tokoba mo Kokoro nai dareka no no kotoba sae mo Hitsuyo nanda!
Hitsuyo nanda!
Tsuyoku narou!
Suki ni sakebe!
Motto!
Tanoshin jae!
Wasurenaide!
Tokubetsu na hi ni narimasu you ni Tomo ni utaou Zutto!
Tomo ni ayumou Zutto!
Aikotoba wa Tobikiri no E-R-O-B-E!
Suki ni natte Natsuji wo mite Onkaeshi wa Ai no komatta nagekisu de Sorikoni suru Motto!
Yume wo miseru Motto!
Tanoshindete Ai no komatta special night Fansha shichau!
I'm still eating this one cough drop.
Oh my god.
Yay!
Fansha!
Suki ni natte Motto!
Oh my gosh, that was so cute!
The hollow beam!
Mint, are you taking karaoke requests?
I am!
Suzume by Radwimps Oh, I don't know it.
I'm so sorry.
It's probably on here.
I could do another Radwimps song.
Oh my gosh, thank you for the akatono!
I hope you know how amazing you are.
How much you mean to us.
No matter what you decide to do in the future.
We will support you.
I'll also do your taxes.
I will.
Thank you.
I don't want to do my taxes.
Red Night Circulation.
Oh, I could do Red Night Circulation.
It's fast though.
I don't know if I can do it so quickly.
Hololive songs.
I wonder what Hololive songs are on here.
Actually, I'm curious.
Paul...
No.
Like if we just search Hololive.
Which one would it be then?
The English one or the Japanese one?
Also, I am taking requests.
So I will sing Sousen Aquarium.
Sousen Aquarium.
Whoa!
I don't think I could sing many of them confidently though.
Maybe another time.
Next time.
Like I know SHINee's smiley story the mostest.
But I still don't feel confident.
But there's a lot on here.
I wonder if I do the Japanese if it changes.
Wait.
So no.
Hello EM.
Oh, wait.
Wait.
Let me try...
Let me try if I search like a member.
Oh.
What did I just click?
Oopsie.
Ah.
Kiss, kiss.
What if I...
Let's see.
Like cari...
Cariope.
No.
Wait.
Oh no.
Or ki...
Ah.
Wait.
It would be Takanashi.
Takanashi.
Ta...
Ka...
Na...
Shi...
O...
Ki...
No.
Ah, man.
That's okay.
In English maybe?
Oh, we can try.
I actually have a video from the last time I went to karaoke.
Calliope had a message.
Oh.
No way.
Oh my god.
Calliope is on here.
For real.
Oh my gosh.
That's so awesome.
Wait.
Hold on.
Ka...
Wait.
Ta...
Ka...
It's right below it.
I can't read.
Na...
Shi...
Sometimes it's...
Oh no.
What if I...
Wait.
What if I just put in Kiara?
Ki...
Na...
Tiara.
Sometimes it's more fun going seeing what songs they have on here than actually like singing.
It's...
Instead...
Hmm?
If I search...
Ik...
Wait.
Kiara Tiara is an equal love song?
That's so funny.
Oh!
Oh my gosh!
Wait.
It's...
This is the...
Also the Honeyworks...
The Honeyworks collab.
That's so funny.
Kobo and Kiara.
Oh my gosh.
Wait.
What if I...
She's on here a little bit.
So happy.
Let's go Kiara.
I love you.
Okay.
Let's see.
Yeah.
Unfortunately, this doesn't have like as many songs as it would in like maybe a Japanese karaoke place.
But it does have a ton, which is really exciting.
It's really fun.
So...
Stellar, Stellar.
Oh my gosh.
Do you want me to die?
I don't think I could sing Stellar, Stellar.
I'm sure they have it.
Science game!
There's so much here!
Oh ha!
Oh my gosh!
There is so much here.
Yo!
Oh!
Let's go!
Please!
Baka mitai?
I wonder if they even have it.
Would it be in Japanese or English?
Let's try it.
Baka mitai.
Baka...
No way.
I don't think it was in Kanji though.
I don't think this is right, right?
What is this one?
Does it have blue clapper?
It did!
They did have blue clapper.
Love deterrence?
They unfortunately don't have love deterrence.
I'm so sad.
Odorika.
That's not the right lyrics.
No, they don't have the actual baka mitai.
Wait, what's the lyrics for this one?
That's what I like about this.
You can kind of see what the start of the song is.
No.
Dang.
Odorika.
I like that song too.
You guys are requesting so many.
I'm not going to be able to do all of them.
I'm sorry.
Odorika.
Wait, I just saw it.
Oh wait, I saw it.
Kiss, kiss, kiss.
Odorika.
I think I have to do plus two.
I think
I have to do plus two.
Love live song?
Maybe.
Is this the key I usually sing in?
I'm
not sure.
Oite kita yu na ito ga hitotsu futatsu Oite...
Can't always get that part.
Chanto hirotte iko o hajikete wasurete shimau wa Mawari dashita ano koto boku no mirai ga
Oh my god, my throat!
Thank you for watching this video.
I hope you enjoyed it.
See you in the next video.
My voice!
Thank you for watching this video.
I hope you enjoyed it.
See you in the next video.
Thank you for watching this video.
I hope you
enjoyed it.
Bye!
So...
Say...
There it is.
Wait, which one?
They're both the same.
Weird.
Oh,
cool!
There's so many!
Oh, this is like the anime.
And then there... okay.
Yeah!
Oh my gosh, simple and clean?
I could do it!
I could!
Oh my gosh, I can't read!
I said Macross!
It's Aquarian!
It can't kill me twice.
The cough adds to it, you think so?
Here, I'm gonna eat some of our pizza.
We'll take a little snack break.
A little snack break.
Does a ghost get sick?
There's ghost germs, obviously.
You know, it just happens and stuff.
So...
A.K.B.?
I can't even imagine the amount of A.K.B.s on here.
Do you have a specific A.K.B.
song?
Mm-mm-mm-mm-mm-mm-mm-mm.
Mm-mm.
Any suggestions of songs that I've seen so many times?
Request a Haruko Momoi song?
Yes!
Oh my gosh, yes!
Actually, that reminds me, I wanted to sing Love, Yixing earlier.
I thought about it.
But actually, there's another one.
If they have it.
Minta, I've definitely never seen you before, but I can definitely tell already I would love your content.
Really?
Thank you.
Floss on the menu.
I've never...
I could try.
Can we get a Shiny Days?
Yes, we can!
Okay, I have a list.
I have a list, you guys.
I have a list.
Oh, simple and clean.
Break stuff.
I have a list.
24 Hours Cinderella.
If they didn't have Baka Mita, I don't think they'll have 24 Hours Cinderella.
Look at all this AKB.
But yeah, I feel like I'm...
I don't know.
Just seeing suggestions of songs that I've seen a lot in other streams.
Look, guys.
This is our opportunity to sing songs that you may have not seen on stream before.
That you want to hear.
I can't guarantee that I'll know it, but I can try.
Anytime, anywhere.
Who's that by?
I'm not sure I know it.
Do you see his puffs?
God,
there's so much.
Do you see the scroll bar?
Oh, she ate her mommy.
Actually, there is a...
There is an AKB song I want to sing.
I love this AKB song.
I love this song.
Any La La Land?
I always sing La La Land.
I put La La... I keep writing La La Lady when I'm typing it.
I put La La Lady, then I put La La Landy.
And
then Mayuyu shows up and she's so beautiful!
What song was it?
The last song?
What was the last song I sang?
Weekend
Yeah, Aquarian!
Oh my gosh, sorry.
There's a little bit of lag for me.
11 11
Oh my god, I'm getting the timing wrong.
A little pause... and we are back.
Okay,
I'm going to try and write a set list.
Do we remember what we sang?
Oh gosh.
I'm going to try and write a set list, you guys.
Set list.
One.
What was the first song that I sang?
Oh my gosh.
No way!
You have the whole thing, Shimeji!
Thank you!
Ghostbusters.
Two.
Ikenai Borderline.
Three.
Hamtaro.
Four.
Snake Eater.
Five.
Plastic Love.
Six.
E...
Ikanaide.
Seven.
Fansa.
Eight.
Odoriko.
Nine.
Genesis Aquarium.
Ten.
Enclit of November.
Juichi Gatsu.
No.
Enclit.
By Ikebi.
Probably nobody knows.
Oh!
Sorry!
I just realized it's so big.
Well done.
Thank you.
I'll give you a second.
That's the outline.
Let's give it a pretty...
black.
There we go!
We're back, baby!
We're back, baby.
Let's do a different font.
This one.
No.
That's ugly.
Why does it look like that?
Why does it look even worse?
This one.
Whatever.
It's fine.
How long have I been streaming for?
Almost three hours.
I'm gonna probably finish up these songs that I have written down.
And then I'm gonna call it, I think.
But that's okay.
It's still one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight songs.
It's still eight songs.
Oh!
Lips of an Angel.
He is missing.
You're right.
I trusted you.
When did I sing that?
Heaven's Divide Vinyl Addict.
Okay.
That will be the last song I sing.
Oh.
What happened?
Okay.
I have a list.
Sorry if you just heard the biggest gulp I've ever done in my life.
I don't think I chewed that properly.
I think if I sing this song, I'm going to cry.
I don't know.
For some reason, this song makes me cry.
But I'll do my best.
Oh.
Um.
Wait.
Who is it by again?
Oh.
There it is.
Hahaha.
I hope you're hydrated enough throughout the karaoke.
I am.
Thank you!
Thank you.
Okay.
Hahaha.
Beep beep.
Sing.
Sing a song.
Sing out loud.
Sing out strong.
Sing of good things, not bad.
Sing of sorrow, not conflict.
A little pause... and we are back.
Make it simple to last your whole life long.
Don't worry that it's not good enough for anyone else to hear.
Just sing.
Sing a song.
I don't think...
I don't think my version does justice the version that I like to listen to.
Sing!
Actually, there's another Carpenter song that I've been listening to a lot.
Wait, what's it called again?
Oh shoot, hold on.
One second.
Carpenter is so good.
I know, right?
I've never sung this one before.
So it might be bad.
I wonder if there's Final Fantasy.
Oh my gosh.
Every time I'm just like, this is all the songs that I will sing.
I change my mind.
I'm just like, wait, I wonder if there's Final Fantasy songs on here that I can sing.
Close to you.
They have like eyes on me.
I want to sing it.
Let's go!
I've never sung this song before.
I'm kind of nervous.
I've never
sung this song before.
I'm kind of nervous.
Why do birds sing?
Every time you are near, just like me, they long to be close to you.
Why do stars fall down from the sky?
Every time you walk by, just like me, they long to be close to you.
My throat is giving out a little bit.
On the day that you were born, the angels got together and decided to create a dream come true.
So they sprinkled moon dust in your hair and gold and starlight in your eyes of blue.
That is why all the girls in town follow you all around.
Just like me, they long to be close to you.
On the
day that you were born, the angels got together and decided to create a dream come true.
So they sprinkled moon dust in your hair and gold and starlight in your eyes of blue.
That is why all the girls in town follow you all around.
Just like me, they long to be close to you Just like me, they long to be close to you
Just like me,
they long to be close to
you Haruko?
Haruko?
Oh, nope, nope, nope.
Kiss, kiss, kiss.
Oh, I wanted to also sing maybe some Dempagumi.
There's too many songs I want to sing.
Wait, since I can't do a dot, maybe just the X again.
No, no.
Okay, space.
E... X...
No!
Okay, hold on.
Let me search Momo and Haruko.
Let's see what they have.
No, Momo!
10 hour stream, for real though.
No, I'm not going to keep you guys so long, don't worry.
They do have under 17, which is another...
Popotan!
I wasn't going to sing Popotan, but I was thinking of another under 17 song.
Wait, is this Mouse?
Chu Mouse.
Oh no, there's Mouse.
Wait, they do have I Know Medicine.
That's the one I was going to sing, not Popotan.
They do have it.
I just had to search Balder Force instead.
Okay.
I'll have to do it.
Yeah, I'll have to do a dedicated karaoke stream sometime.
Okay, sorry.
Without pushing the fleeting beat of a war I chase the flowing time And run through the world Ahh!
I
can use it to separate good and bad I'm sure
my heart, my life is here Off
to a new tomorrow Here I go!
Without pushing the fleeting beat
of a war I chase the flowing time And run through the world A little pause...
and we are back.
A little pause... and we are back.
A
little pause... and we are back.
With your arm movements, you kind of like make an X.
Widen your mind and think.
If you find yourself again If you find yourself again Even if your tears Even if your tears Shine Shine Shine
Shine Hey Trink!
Hey Trink!
I'm having so much fun though!
Even though my throat is starting to get worse and worse I don't want to stop!
Momoi...
Actually, since I did that one...
No!
I lied.
I am gonna do that one.
I said I was only...
I was like, maybe I'll only do one Momoi Haruko song.
No.
I want to do two.
This is one of my favorite anime ever.
The list gets longer, it does.
Wait, I need to also set a list.
Love.
No,
no, no, no, no.
Don't make me, don't make me.
I can't stop.
No more.
I can't stand it anymore.
Heart.
Little child.
I'm gonna blame you.
I'm gonna laugh.
I'm
gonna laugh.
Genes.
I'll make my wish come true.
It's gonna take a long time.
But I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
Magical.
I love this show!
So much!
Soul Taker is fine too, but I love Nurse of Chikamugi the most.
Magical, magical nurse.
A wonderful throbbing.
I'm sure this is the end.
I'm okay.
That was the medicine of love.
The medicine of love.
That was my medicine.
Are you?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Next song!
Next song...
Sorry guys, I already have... If you're still sending songs, I already have a list that I'm gonna...
That I've already decided...
Unless I decide to add my own...
Wait, is it Shiny with an E?
Oh, there it is.
Right below Shiny's smiley story.
Asaka!
I love Asaka.
Asaka, maybe, has become one of my top...
Not maybe.
She is one of my top favorite anime song singers.
She's so awesome.
She's so nice.
I love her.
I love her so, so much.
Happy Yutacamp Day, everybody!
This
is the best song I've ever heard.
She's a nice girl.
She's so sweet!
I love her.
This is cute.
I love her so much.
I thought I heard you were going to say something.
Me too.
At least I know this song.
I like Yutacamp.
That is the coolest song.
I love Yutacamp!
This is fun.
Shining days, atarashii kaze Hazuraya no na stepu fun de go my way Can you feel?
Sukitoru sora Mune sawagi tsureteiku brand new world Listen to the melody Toku kuchibue hibikasetara Tobidasou mirai e Tuk tuk tuk
Maramiagetara cloudless sky So happy kukki ippai ni sute Atarimae no chisana kiseki wo One by one massugu kamishimeteru Sukoshi no yuuki ga kikakete Ugokidasu sekai Alright!
Koe demo ikeru
Shining days Dokomademo mae Sukina utaguchi zunde Feel so good Can you see?
Kirameita heaven Muneita kaze hokondeiku brand new mind Please save your memories Kaseneteiku Yume to tomo ni Fumidasou mirai e
Taiyou no you na egao de Take it easy kata no chikara Sugoshiteikou Kyou mo asu mo So it will be fine
Sing a song issho ni utaou
Oh god, I'm so sorry!
Cut some of the song list and cut some of it out.
I'm so sorry!
I can't stop!
Oh god, we'll do one last song.
If I can make it to one more.
I don't even know if I can!
Oh, the hang.
I have another cough drop.
And I drink.
Sorry, someone suggested Diamond Crevice.
I really want to sing it, but I don't think I'll be able to.
Or break stuff.
Or La La Land.
Or simply clean.
But I'll just have to do another karaoke sometime.
Right?
Probably.
Okay.
Let me check if this is good.
One second.
Okay.
Yeah, good enough.
Last song, everybody.
I'm so sorry about that.
I wish I could sing more, but...
Thank you again for welcoming me back so warmly.
I didn't expect so many people to be here.
But I really appreciate it.
Thank you for all the donations.
Thank you for subbing.
Thank you for even just remembering me even a tiny little bit.
I really, really, really, really, really, really appreciate it.
I'm so shocked.
But...
Yeah.
Really happy to be here.
To be able to hang out with you guys some more.
And everything.
Look at that.
The cough drop helped so much.
Maybe I can do Diamond Crevice.
Hmm...
No, I shouldn't.
I shouldn't.
I'll save it for next time.
Glamatara introduced me to you.
Yeah!
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
I'm just a little ghost.
And I'm just a little maid.
But...
I'll do my best to...
Hopefully we can have a fun time and make lots of awesome memories.
And...
Yeah.
Um...
Hmm...
Thank you for the Hakadono!
Thank you!
Hope we weren't too flustered by all your new adoring fans.
Keep rocking and being you.
We believe in you.
Thank you!
Thank you.
I can't wait to do so many things.
Did you guys know that I own a Metal Gear patchy slot machine?
Hmm...
I haven't thought...
Like...
I don't know at all what I'm doing next week.
Uh...
I don't know when the next stream is even.
I don't know anything.
Um...
So...
I hope that you guys will be a little patient with me.
I kind of just really jumped back in.
I was just like, you know what?
I'll come back on Thursday.
And now...
Like I don't think I'm gonna stream tomorrow.
Maybe...
I don't know.
I'll try and make schedules.
Um...
Yeah.
It's just...
How about some block game?
I don't...
I don't know.
I don't have a server.
Or anything.
But I guess I should start streaming soon so I can hit monetization or something.
I don't know.
It's fine.
Okay.
Where did my other Joy-Con go?
Oh, I dropped it.
Okay.
That's fine.
But yeah.
Back with our Revengeance.
Yeah!
Back with our Revengeance!
So...
Um...
Hmm...
I don't know.
I'm really...
Uh...
Excited.
Like I said.
I'll keep doing my best.
Thank you guys for allowing me back.
Um...
So...
Here's to you!
Well, it's not here's to you but here's to you!
Well...
I thought the song would start sooner.
Bye!
This is our second song.
Uh...
Um...
At least...
It's been a long time.
I'm so glad this is over.
Okay.
Thank you for watching this video, I hope you enjoyed it, and I will see you in the next video.
I
will dive into the fire, spilling the blood of my desire.
The very last time, my name scorched into the sky.
When heavens divide, I will see the choices within my hands.
How can we ever protect?
And fight with our tiny souls?
Let me shine, like the sun, through the doubts and fear.
Do you feel the storm approach, as the end draws near?
When heavens divide, time will come to softly lay me down.
Then I can see your face.
That I long to see.
And for you, only you, I would give anything.
Leaving a trace for love to find a way.
When heavens divide...
See you guys next when I see you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
See you next...
Thank you!