Is this thing on?
Hello?
Can you hear me?
Is it working?
Am I alive?
No.
Am I?
It sounds good?
Am I good?
I'm muted?
Stream muted?
Don't lie to me.
Is she talking?
Wait, I can't tell.
Am I actually muted?
Now I'm confused.
Wait, am I muted?
Oh, I'm not muted.
Stop lying to me.
Hi, Minto.
Oh my god.
Welcome back, Minto.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Thanks for the Hakusupa.
Thanks for all the members.
Welcome back, Minto.
Thanks.
We hear you.
Oh my god.
It doesn't even feel like I've been gone because I've been doing so many things.
Can you hear my PC going?
Can you hear it?
It's making... it's a little loud.
It feels like...
...you've been gone.
I've been doing events and stuff, so...
If it was your birthday last week, but your Oshi wasn't around so long ago to wish you a happy birthday, did you get any older?
Happy late birthday, Korin.
I'm assuming you're talking about P jewelery.
Boosting my volume?
Wait am I quiet Blahblahblah.
Wait no, I'm not quiet.
I don't think.
Wait.
No, don't turn that on.
What the hell?
Is the music okay?
Thank you for the anime Revo concert.
I have a wisp plushie.
I could be louder, seriously?
But on OBS it's showing me in the red.
That's crazy.
Huh?
There's music?
Oh, I'll turn it up.
There you go.
Really nice to finally attend one of your meet and greets that I've talked with on your reaction when you found out I was made with priceless and made me happy.
Hope you had a nice time when you were here in Montreal.
Yeah, oh my gosh.
I... I... I... I went to...
Toronto?
Wait, where's anime Revo?
Wait, anime Revo...
Vancouver?
Just kidding.
Sorry, Toronto.
Wait, but what's the other one in Toronto?
Anime North!
Yeah, yeah, I didn't go there.
I went to Vancouver.
I went to Montreal.
I went to the UK.
All in the span of like three weeks.
Two weeks.
Oh my god.
Everything's crazy.
Please anime North next year.
I mean, I kind of... I was...
I guess I was technically in the parking lot.
Minto Worldwide.
I know.
And then I don't know if you guys saw but I got announced for a concert here in Malaysia.
And~~ Umm...
More to come, too.
We coming to Malaysia?
Yeah.
We're going there, too.
Hold on, let me find it.
I retweeted it, I think.
I'll have more stuff of my normal setup later.
It's called Vmuse.
This... hold on, I'm saving the picture.
I'm saving the picture.
I go to OBS.
I load the picture.
This... Yippee!
Yeah!
Selfie there.
Worldwide Minto.
Real.
Thanks for the free super.
No, thank you!
Yeah.
And...
Yeah, how have you guys been?
Oh my gosh, it's been...
too long since I streamed.
I'm really sorry.
It didn't feel, like I said, since I've been doing so much.
Stummy, stop looking at my tummy.
Since I...
Since I have been doing so much, like, offline.
But events?
It still feels like I've been streaming, but not really, you know.
The MC from your concert at Annie Revo auctions off his shirt at the end of the con every year.
As a tradition.
Did you get it?
I was the solid Minto of Vexpo.
I feel the need to apologize for spilling my spaghet...
Stop!
I was too nervous to properly talk.
I won't say that.
I'm endlessly thankful.
Stop!
You were fine!
Go, stop it!
Thanks for coming to my hometown of Montreal.
I was the samurai...
I know!
I know you were the samurai cosplayer.
I just started my new job.
Can I get a moe-moe?
Good luck, Bim!
Moe!
Good luck!
Bim!
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Good luck!
Oh, wrong word.
Bim!
Nobody saw.
I just finished watching an MGS4 VOD epilogue and I'm an emotional mess.
Yeah, the Metal Gear episode of the podcast released.
I missed you so much.
Thanks, Nan!
I missed you guys too, kind of.
Don't tell you guys, though, that I missed you guys.
It's a secret.
Nobody, you guys can't know.
You guys can't know that I missed you guys.
Wait.
She missed us.
No, I didn't.
I'm telling you, I didn't miss you guys.
At all.
But I did miss you guys.
You just can't know that I missed you guys.
That's all.
She didn't miss us.
But yeah, I'm in Japan.
For those who don't know, I'm in Japan.
I'm in Nihon.
I've been here for some time.
For about a week.
Almost a little under a week now.
She missed us.
Thank you guys for all the super chats.
Thank you.
Remember that third option you showed us at your docket rallies?
It's the same pose as Johnny Akiba in MGS1.
Release image for Metal Gear.
No, because Dayui...
Dayui sent me like more...
You guys wanna see?
Dayui sent me some more things.
Some more previews.
I think you guys will...
Hold on, I'll show you guys this one.
They were like...
They like messaged me.
I hope you don't get in trouble with YouTube.
We're showing the...
The other one.
I was like, nah, we're all good.
I think YouTube's a coward.
They're not gonna do anything to me.
I say as my channel gets nuked right now.
It was amazing to see you sing and passing my spoons.
Thank you.
Okay, hold on.
Let me show you guys this version first.
And then you guys tell me.
Okay?
Hold on though.
Let me make sure I make it small.
So YouTube doesn't get mad.
Okay.
Alrighty.
It's cute.
So...
You know it's still a little bit of spice.
And then it's gone.
That's your preview.
That's your preview of the other side of the Ducky Makura.
See!
Stop!
You guys are making me embarrassed!
Wait!
Spicy goes, wait I'm embarrassed now!
Stop!
I got to meet you.
I'm expo this weekend.
I was so nervous I forgot to even give my name.
Thank you for meeting all of us.
That was a pleasure.
Thanks George!
Thanks for coming to meet me.
You've done this to yourself.
You can... well it's really Dayui's influence.
Because they were like...
I feel like it would be a disservice to not have your butt out.
Because of the moles.
And I was like...
Maybe you're right!
Because originally I wanted to have it like...
You know how some Ducky Makura will have like a horizontal size?
I wanted it to be a little more horizontal with me like hugging a wisp plushie.
Because I don't really...
I was like... I don't know...
I mean having a Ducky Makura is like...
I guess a sort of implication?
I don't even know...
I don't know.
But I was just like...
I don't even know if people...
If you guys like...
Will even be like...
Oh this is kind of weird Minto.
I don't see you like that.
You know?
I don't...
I don't know!
I don't even know what I'm saying anymore.
I'm embarrassed.
Oh
my god.
I'm just embarrassed.
I'm a streamer so...
If I buy the Ducky it will be the most embarrassing thing I own and I own some embarrassing things.
But to me I'm also just like... I like...
Well like I own Ducky Makuras of my friends.
Like I own a Ducky Makura of Yua.
She's another Vtuber.
And...
But you know...
I mean...
Well I kind of slobber on it.
I'm like...
Don't slobber on my Ducky Makura maybe.
Minto it's my birthday today.
I love your streams so much.
Thanks for always putting a big smile on my face.
Wait you can reply to people's super chats now.
What is this?
Hooray happy birthday!
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday dear Ray.
Wow like kind of...
Wow it's like the chat is so orange now.
I promised nothing.
My dog will slobber on it.
That dog in you right?
You got that dog in you.
The dog and me will slobber all over it.
Orange?
It's like a yellow-orange.
But also, maybe it's my laptop, right?
Yellow-orange.
Yeah, oh!
Another thing!
Okay, you guys.
So you're probably just like, What adventures has Minto gotten up to in Japan?
Because she's been here for a couple days.
She's probably gone shopping.
She's probably gone to Akihabara a million times.
She's probably gone to every maid cafe.
You guys?
I forgot my wallet at home.
I have no cash.
I have no means of withdrawing cash.
I have no credit card.
I am...
I'm living off the yenis in my pocket.
I have nothing.
So...
Luckily though...
I've been actually...
So I came a little bit early because...
Some scheduling stuff.
Wasn't supposed to come so early.
Because of that too, I'll also be like hotel hopping a little bit.
So...
It's a little...
Annoying.
But...
But actually I have...
I've met up with Sakana.
From Face Connect.
And he's been helping me pay for food.
Thank you for the dono!
Thank you!
I've been listening to Kesha recently and her songs.
Tear It Off really fits you, Minto.
Lots of talks of freaks.
Oh, let's go.
Face Connect.
He's been helping me...
Pay for food.
And...
Somebody is super chatty.
I have no card to use.
I have to stop.
My roommate actually...
This is where...
This is why I was...
I brought this up.
My roommate actually sent...
My...
Wallet.
And I've been checking the tracking every day.
I've been like, please get here sooner.
But...
Another thing.
This was supposed to come before I left.
Unfortunately it didn't.
But they...
It did come...
By the time that they...
It literally came the day after I left.
But my roommate sent it with my wallet.
I got...
The...
Simple...
Prototype...
Of the new Minto plushie.
So...
I will be able to show you guys...
Soon...
Once it comes...
All...
Of...
My little adventures with her.
And...
Then you'll kind of...
Be like, wow...
She's such a marketable plushie.
I must have it.
And...
You will then also soon hopefully have her.
Go on your own Minto adventures.
Yay!
You're going to actually pass...
On when someone brings the daki to a car.
Don't say...
Don't say that.
Oh my god.
But...
Yeah.
So...
It's marketable.
I'll be taking her...
I'll be posting lots of pictures...
With the plushie...
In lots of places...
So you can be like...
Wow...
I must have my own...
And then you can also see what...
The size is like...
And stuff like that.
So...
Is there a hole in the bottom of the plush?
No!
I don't know which one is...
Which number...
This one!
There is no hole...
There is no hole in the bottom of the plushie.
You can make one with that knife!
Stop!
But yeah, thank you Fishman for helping me out.
And I got to hang out a bit with the FaZe girls.
They've been very nice, very sweet.
So yeah, it's been fun.
What else have I done?
I did go to Akihabara once.
And he made fun of the fact that I wanted to go to Moss Burger.
He's kind of an asshole.
Could I hand you an apple?
Sure.
Shocker.
The FaZe girls love to bully him.
Yeah.
I think I've been putting... I've been collecting witness statements.
Or I'm the witness.
Of his... of him towards... like how he acts towards them.
And I'm like...
Wait, which one is my notes taking?
Nope.
Yes.
I've been like...
Okay.
I see.
This is how he acts towards them.
Spill the beans.
Has he asked you to dress as Marin Sancho yet?
No, but he has brought up Marin several times.
And of course, this is what it is...
Who did you meet from FaZe?
I'm a...
Well, I'm a...
Oh...
I know.
I met Leah.
I always used to call her Leah.
I met Ruka.
I met Pippa.
I...
I think I saw Clara for like two seconds.
Maybe.
Maybe that was it.
This is an illusion.
Or a dream.
Not much has happened because I don't have any money.
And also because I've been doing events.
One day for EXPO.
So basically I woke up at...
I woke up at 1 a.m.
for the concert.
So I got the times wrong.
I thought that my meet and greet was the day before.
And so I went to sleep at 4 p.m.
Woke up at like 8 p.m.
Because I thought my meet and greet was at 9.
And then I was like, oh, my meet and greet is actually tomorrow.
So I went back to sleep and I woke up at 1 a.m.
And then I did the concert.
For VEXPO.
And I was so excited afterwards.
It was like...
It was around like 4 p.m.
Because it started at 3 p.m.
It was around like 4 a.m.
And I was like, I can't sleep.
I'm too excited after...
Oh, I have a screenshot.
Of people in the crowd.
Hold on.
I took a screenshot.
Look at you guys.
It's kind of blurry.
But this is...
I was like...
Oops, sorry.
That was kind of loud.
I was like...
Look at everybody.
So much green.
I know.
And so...
It was around 4 a.m.
And I was like, I can't sleep.
I'm too excited.
And so I stayed up.
Actually...
And then I went out that day.
Just like walking around.
And then...
And then my meet and greets.
First I did the iPad walk around.
That was at like 9 p.m.
And then I did...
Meet and greets for real.
And that was at 11 p.m.
And by the time I was done.
It was 1 a.m.
And I was like...
I've been awake 24 hours, baby.
And I can keep going.
And then I seen that there was that guy.
That's been like trying to stay awake for like 4 hours.
Like, I don't know how many hours it is.
I was like, I could beat him.
I think.
I think if I did meet and greets the entire time, I could beat him because...
Because just seeing you guys fills me with so much energy.
Please don't.
11 days?
Okay, never mind.
Never mind.
I don't like you guys that much.
No, I'm just kidding.
He's at 11.
The guy is literally gonna like permanently damage his brain.
Oh yeah, we were also having some technical difficulties before the concert.
Look at this cursed picture of me.
There were even more cursed ones, but this is the only screenshot I got.
It was so cursed.
I look like the grudge is happening.
Spooky.
That was haunting.
The stage, you know, a little bit.
Oh, and then of course for if you are at.
Any arrival.
I do really really really want to apologize.
I think Doki kind of brought it up a little bit, but basically.
To to make things as easy for me and also as What's the word?
I guess assurance the quality assurance.
I guess I brought my whole set up like it's a laptop, but I brought like my whole Yamaha AGO 8 which if you don't know is quite big I brought like an external keyboard I brought everything like so that I could you know one be comfortable with my setup and also make sure that the meet and greets went well.
The concerts went well.
Because I it was not my intention to be traveling during those events.
So I wanted to I you know, I wanted to make sure that everything would go smoothly.
But then for any rival basically when we were doing soundcheck like they said things sounded a little bit weird.
But then eventually they said that it sounded okay and they were the kind of just like oh just turn your Oh, I just realized something.
Hold on.
Sorry, I'm going to pause the music real quick.
Because I'm changing some sound settings.
They basically said like that means the problem was on their end.
No, no, no.
I think they didn't understand and I also didn't understand how they were saying like what the problem was.
Basically.
They said that it was noise cancelling.
But I was like, I don't have.
I don't have like a noise.
Gate or anything on this mixer.
So there was nothing for me to turn off and it literally was just one single button.
I wonder if I press it now.
I don't want to like it to pop and hurt your ears or anything, you know, but it was just a single button that I did not realize.
And so do it really?
Okay, I'm going to press it.
I'll turn your here.
I'll turn the mic down.
I'll turn the mic down so that hello.
This is what this is what I sounded like.
And so it did that to the music as well.
And they were like turn your music down turn your music up and I was doing everything.
Even mid song.
They were like, you know, they were like messaging me being like your music is is getting filtered.
You try adjusting the settings.
And so I was like a little stressed like trying to adjust settings while mid song and I was like, I don't know what to do.
And I just felt, you know, I feel so awful because you know, Doki invited me to her event.
And you know, it was my first time working with any rival staff and everything.
And I just felt so I just felt so so so bad.
I'm really sorry if you are at the concert and I know some people are just like don't worry about it.
But for everybody at the concert, you know, I'm really really sorry that I was not prepared enough and and didn't
I wasn't prepared enough to fix it.
I'm really sorry.
But because of that Doki and I are cooking.
We're kind of cooking you guys.
So maybe be on the lookout.
In the future for stuff that we're cooking revenge revenge time.
Why do we even have that button?
You know, every every mic has like their own different settings and stuff.
So it was just so that was so frustrated.
That was a learning experience.
Yes, for sure revengeance.
Yeah revengeance.
Yeah, so they're becoming chefs with this one.
From here on out.
I think things will start picking up pace a little bit.
Not that they but in terms of my projects and such so I'm very excited for all the things that got planned got going on.
Yeah,
especially once I'm back and once I'm back you guys, I think that'll be the end of the podcast.
Oh my gosh.
No, but while I'm here, I have plans for off collabs with several people that I hopefully hopefully it works out.
I'm here.
I know some people's schedules are kind of crazy.
Hopefully they work out.
Who with us?
Fall season fall season by Mata.
Will you say hi to Kiara?
It's actually so funny because you know how I said my AGO8 is huge.
Kiara mentioned that she was using an AGO8 on stream and I was like, hey girl, I have an extra one.
So essentially what happened is I ordered by AGO8, which if you don't know it's an interface like it's how I'm how you're able to hear me right now.
It's the Yamaha AGO8 and I really like it.
It's probably been my favorite of you know, I really like the effects the go XLR had but a lot of people are moving away from the go XLR because the company went out of business.
And so there's stopping like updates on it.
So I got I ended up getting this to try it out and I really like it.
And yeah, no support.
So Kiara mentioned that she liked it and I had ordered one and it got lost in the mail.
And so I told I told them I was like, hey Amazon my AGO8 got lost in the mail.
Send me a new one.
And so they did and then the original one came back.
And I was like, and
and so I also brought the entire other one here with me to Japan for Kiara because I love her so much that I didn't mind carrying three suitcases just for her.
Any thoughts on a collab with Michi?
No pressure.
Just wait to come.
Yoshi's is my dream.
Like cute.
What funny and dumb.
What are you talking about?
I would love to collab with Michi.
I think right now she is on a hiatus though, right?
So maybe when she comes back.
Did you see that Jerma collab with Kiara?
Yes.
I saw the EDF.
I saw a clips of it actually.
Yeah.
She is healthifying herself.
Good because she needs it.
I hope that she...
I hope I hope that she recovers well.
Neurosama collab maybe?
Actually, I really want to collab with Neurosama.
It's funny you mention that because I was like, I was I was thinking probably once I get back I'll shoot Vito a message and say hey, can I collab with Neurosama?
But I kind of want to do like, not just like a talking like I want to do something something.
So,
mental cooking.
Her cover a wink.
I don't think I saw it.
Oh, I saw someone mention also.
Like maybe I was thinking like don't be like if it's possible like a like a what's it called?
No talking or some people explode because I would love to see how Neuro if it's possible, how she would describe some of the the ways to disarm the ball.
Oh, the keep talking.
Yeah.
Yeah, the bomb game.
She's played it before.
Oh, she has a couple of streams.
Okay.
So yeah, then it might work out.
That's like the V to begin.
I have like long long time ago.
I did a collab of that with a friend and she had like tech issues the whole time.
And so it made it very funny because she would be just be delayed or her audio would just give out and I was just like, what are you saying?
So I have good memories with the game.
See her roast you.
I can take it.
You know me.
She also likes trolling beetle to make him explode.
I like what?
Yeah, like I like I don't catch her streams so often because I'm not on Twitch, but I a lot of people upload like longer clips of her and I like the clips will be like I say it's a clip but it's like 30 minutes long and I just I just watch the entire thing.
It's just she's just so funny.
It's so funny.
I wonder like if I had created her if I you know, like I would feel like she's my actual daughter.
I would feel so attached to her.
You know, I would be like this is my literal baby.
She's I don't know.
She's just got this.
This charm.
I just love it so much.
Baby Minto.
No, she's the baby.
Beetle does seem like a dad.
Why did I take you for the 50 gifted?
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Oh, you have a charm that we love.
So much.
Stop.
Baby.
You're always looking for a psychiatrist.
At the airport.
Sorry.
I was just thinking of my how I mentioned that I brought like the whole box for for Kiara.
I also brought two more months worth of postcards.
Okay.
So to give you an idea.
I brought a full-size suitcase.
Right?
I had I had and in just just the suitcase.
I had the ag08 box for Kiara and then I had the postcards for Mata and just and that nothing else just those two things in a whole suitcase and just those two things alone almost brought me to the weight limit.
Kunari.
Thank you so much for the 10 gifted.
Thank you.
Yeah, so and then when I went through security, I put all my streaming stuff.
I was like if anything like if anything happens to my suitcases, I will go without clothes for a couple days, but I must have all of my every single streaming thing in my carry-on because Because the events are the most important, right?
Wow.
Oh my gosh, good playlist.
Thank you for the 50 gifts.
Thank you so much.
You guys.
Thank you.
But when I went through security, this has never happened to me before.
They got mad at me.
The lady was just like you have too many electronics in your bag.
She got mad.
I was like, sorry, lady.
I'm And so I had packed everything very meticulously to kind of like make sure that my my second monitor didn't get damaged to make sure my phone was okay.
My laptop was okay.
My keyboard was okay.
And then she just started tearing it out and throwing it into bins.
I was like, and so it took me to like a I was like you bitch.
So angry.
You traveled with the second monitor.
Yes.
I'm telling you one of the reasons I don't like streaming when I am when I'm away is because I feel so uncomfortable, you know, I was like, I hate using laptop keyboard.
I hate not having my normal interface.
I hate not having two screens.
And so yeah, I brought pretty much everything so that I would feel most comfortable so that I could stream the most since I'm not home.
The Patriots made her do it.
We record thanks to the five gifted.
Thank you.
And I didn't want to not Oh my God.
I just said that girl.
Your concert of Expo is amazing.
I love your version of you can avoid the lines.
Absolutely.
Love doing what they get with you.
Thank you for the iPad.
Be great.
You're the best.
Oh, she ever be don't love.
Thank you.
Say it.
Imagine a timeline where your clothes luggage was sacrificed.
So you're doing all these content stuff and being they don't know.
I'm closed.
Let's window traveling to suitcases for tech.
No clothes.
No wallet.
It's three suitcases actually.
Yeah, I was really happy to I know a lot of people didn't get the meet-and-greet at the expo.
So I was like if I can go around on the iPad and meet as many people as I could there.
I feel like also I perform a lot of the same songs at concerts, but I try to do the same songs at different.
So for example, you know, that was my first time performing in Europe.
So I was like I should you know, do these songs that I think are really fun to do with the gate to because you know, for me, it's me performing it for the hundredth time, but for these, you know, for these guys, it might be their first time hearing it.
So that's what kind of but I feel bad.
I'm like, I have no I feel like I have no variety.
I'd rather not.
Thanks for the five gifted hermocrates.
Thank you for the vibe.
Good to take you.
Hello from Canada.
So yeah, any revival last weekend.
The with croaky will be remembered for years.
I felt so uncomfortable about the fact not being able to play games on my actual PC during off-time.
So just the Steve that I know right when you're not in.
You're like comfortable.
And you're not in your comfortable place.
It's weird, right?
Minty sweat.
Baintoe.
Yeah.
Or four or four or four or four or four or four.
My comfort zone.
Can't any new maid cafes?
No, because I have no money.
I have no money.
He.
I have like luckily I have I have my iPhone like the iPhone that I use for streaming that I have my Suica card on.
So a lot of places do take Suica tap.
So I've been paying with that as well.
And I have my cards on my phone.
So places that take tap.
I'll do that too.
But not every places.
Maid cafes are like all cash.
Not everyone, but a lot of them are cash.
So, yeah, I just, you know, hopefully it comes soon.
Especially I hope because I have a hair appointment on Friday.
Thanks for coming to the expo.
Crashing the Wisp meetup.
Your performance at the concert was amazing.
Here's my meet and greet feed.
And the postage stamp for the personal message to the Buggley.
Eww.
Palazzo.
Gosh, that's a throw back.
Does anyone remember XL Saga?
Do you have any plans on collabing with some ultra-violent guard dogs?
Minto.
lol Um.
Uh.
I would love to.
I believe that their schedule is a little busy right now.
So.
Um.
But...
I love them so much.
Their 3D was so awesome.
So, so awesome.
Don't hurt to ask.
Oh, why do you think I haven't asked?
Extreme violence.
Bow?
Bow-bow!
Wow!
I'm in 3D, when?
Yeah, you know, I get so motivated by stuff like that.
I'm just like, I hope I can get 3D soon and I hope I can do really cool things too.
It's so fun.
I love seeing people being creative and fun.
Because it makes me want to also be creative and fun and do things.
So, you know.
Right now, I'm in cooking.
Cooking mode.
But...
Eventually, hopefully.
Hopefully, eventually.
Right?
Vexpo Celeb is awesome!
Perfect for my first time doing Otakeyara live event because I used those songs to prepare.
Let's go, Ken-chan!
Wait, you literally told me last time, last event.
You were just like, yeah, I think I'm gonna go to Vexpo.
And you actually win.
You're so crazy.
Oh my god.
You're creative and fun.
I love seeing you.
Thanks a lot!
Oh, your cooking has been worth the wait?
I think you're more impatient than us.
Maybe.
I just don't feel like I'm ever doing enough.
I think I saw that's like an anxiety thing though.
When you are working but you feel like you're not working hard enough.
Your new catchphrase should be, do you want to fight it out or freak it out?
What the fuck?
Thank you so much for coming to our Mito Mito!
Thank you!
Now I'm so happy to meet so many new people.
I really hope you get your wallet soon so you can have fun in Japan.
Really glad that I got to meet you at Otaku time.
Thanks Merlin!
Just like grandma.
How do you know?
I didn't know my grandma.
Actually I haven't...
It just reminded me my mom called me to text her back.
My mom doesn't know I'm in Japan and I'm afraid to tell her because...
I know she's going to freak out about the mega earthquake.
She's going to freak out about the mega quake.
She's going to be like...
Mom, I'm home right now!
If you guys...
She doesn't know.
She thinks I'm still in California.
I was like...
Mom, I haven't been in California for a while now.
Did you feel the earthquake?
I felt...
There was like a...
I keep wanting to say level five.
What's the proper term?
A five quake.
A couple days ago.
Magnitude?
Yeah, magnitude.
Magnitude five.
The other day.
But I didn't feel it very much.
Like I felt it.
But it was very fast.
Yeah.
It was very fast though.
I didn't...
It wasn't so bad.
I don't know.
I'm glad you're fine.
Yeah, hopefully.
Hopefully, it's okay.
They all say...
The big one's coming to you.
You know?
But...
Other than that one...
It's been...
It's been quiet.
Knock on wood.
And it's so weird because like...
Sometimes I...
I think I like...
Gaslight myself.
Like...
I feel myself into thinking there's an earthquake.
I don't know if it's like...
A me...
Feeling something that's not there.
Or...
Like a...
Like sometimes I'll lay down and I'll be like...
Did my bed just shake?
Maybe it's a ghost.
I don't know.
It could be a ghost.
Okay.
Here's some possible explanations.
One.
Ghost.
Two.
Earthquake.
My tummy.
Three.
Tummy.
Four.
What's a...
What's that thing when you get dizzy?
What's a thing when you get...
Vertical.
Yeah.
I can't tell.
I'll just be laying in bed and I'm just like, huh.
But it's also because like...
You know.
It's...
Oh.
There is a one distinct feeling I remember.
I remember.
I remember one time I went to the beach as a kid, and after the beach, you know, you're playing in the water, you're like, woohoo, I'm splashing around, I'm being a kid in the water, you know?
And then you go home that night and you lay down.
I remember this distinct feeling because I was just like, how is this possible?
And then, when you're lying down, you feel yourself like... in the... you feel like you're still in the waves.
I think that might be kind of what I feel.
I'm back!
How's the sound and the everything, by the way?
I forgot to ask.
If, like, the connection is good and everything.
Just finished up a big project at work and catching up with your VODs have helped me a lot.
I need to restore my sanity this week.
Oh, I don't know!
Congrats!
Love the Metal Gear podcast yesterday.
It's so cool to see how much passion you have towards MGS.
I hope one day I'll be able to see how you feel about my franchise, too, once you've finished it.
A bit muffled compared to usual stream.
Really?
Maybe it's because I'm not... is this better?
I don't think I was, like, talking into the mic.
My mic is, like...
this direction.
But it's also a different mic, so...
Oh, it's louder.
That's nice.
I actually thought... so I do kind of have, like, a little bit of a schedule this week.
So tomorrow, I'm gonna do Typing of the Dead.
And then I thought maybe I was just like, well, if I'm... here?
Um, I can't do, like, the bi...
bi...
I can't do the bi... ears.
What's it called?
The bi...
It's clearer now.
Okay, I'll move my mic a little bit.
I'll have to adjust it then.
The bi...
bi...
neural...
aural...
bi... aural...
Typing of the Dad, yeah.
.
The bi...
neural...
bi...
aural...
Why is that word so hard to say?
Oh my gosh.
I sound like I'm peaking.
Am I peaking?
Hold on.
Beep boop bop, beep boop bop, beep boop bop, beep boop bop, beep boop bop, beep boop bop.
Yeah!
Ah.
Maybe that's okay.
?
I don't know.
I don't have anything for ASMR.
.
I was thinking, I was trying to brainstorm something to do.
Mmm... crisp.
We don't need ASMR?
Well then you don't have to watch.
Some people like things that you don't like.
And that's okay.
If you don't like ASMR, I know a lot of people will be like, Oh I hate ASMR, why are you doing that?
I'm not going to become an ASMR streamer, don't get me wrong.
But...
But, you know.
I think sometimes it's kind of fun to experiment with different things.
You know?
I'm a variety streamer.
Just ASMR us some MGS Codex.
Pring, pring.
Hey.
You're pretty good.
Tchew.
Read us MGS lore.
But I probably will do it when it's night time in Japan.
So it might be morning for a lot of you guys.
Because I have to get into the mood.
I have to get into like the... you know.
Oh my god, I just looked over at my...
I don't know if you guys saw my tweet.
About how there was a child staring into my room.
From the other hotel room.
And I just looked over and their blinds are up.
Okay, I'm lowering my blinds.
Hold on.
I don't want them to see me.
No, I'm lowering my blinds.
Hold on.
You almost just lost me there.
Oh my god, you almost just lost.
Okay.
My...
My webcam almost just fell.
Are you sure it was a child?
Oh yeah.
I know.
Yeah.
I'm 100%.
I saw him.
I saw his eyes wide.
Clear.
It was night time.
But it was clear as day.
I was like...
Yeah.
Once I...
Once I'm out of this hotel, I will show you guys.
And you'll be like...
First of all, you'll be like...
Holy cow.
Why was...
Why?
Why are the rooms like this?
That child hasn't moved from there since yesterday.
It's...
So bizarre.
It's so strange.
Japan is freaky.
No, clearly.
I'm having a hard time picturing it.
Yeah.
Once...
Once I...
Once I am gone and can show you guys a picture, you'll be like...
She wasn't kidding.
Because I think some people are probably like, there's no way this is possible.
No, no, no, no.
It's very possible.
I was so glad I was able to meet you.
I don't talk a lot.
I was so nervous, I didn't even introduce myself.
I was wearing the Bill fan.
And you signed my MGS shirt!
Yes!
I'm gonna cherish it forever.
Thank you Zozo!
Thank you for coming to see me.
I always wonder, like...
I'm always just like, I wonder...
How many people are actually gonna see me at some of these events?
Like...
You know, like I said, I'm doing the concert in Malaysia and I'm just like...
Do I...
Like, do I have any fans in Malaysia?
I don't know, you know?
So...
A kid died in that room 12 years ago.
What you saw was a ghost.
Why am I laughing at it?
No, I think it was a human child.
It makes it even scarier.
Ghost.
I'm sure you have fans in all corners of the world.
I have fans?
Been lots of events.
I think next up is...
The concert at ANYC.
Is anybody going to New York, New York?
Actually, is it in New York, New York?
I don't know.
The room for the podcast at Otakuton was insane.
That is...
There were so many people, yeah.
There were a lot of people.
Whist from Malaysia here.
Thank you!
New York, New York.
Looking forward to the ANYC concert.
Me too!
Oh my gosh, I'm so super duper excited.
We love our worldwide fans.
It's so funny because...
What was it?
Oh my gosh!
Judy!
Thank you for the 50!
Holy cow!
Give it up to...
Fan for Poland here.
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
What was I going to say?
The same day that I asked...
I mistyped world.
I was supposed to type a worldwide Minto.
And instead, I tweeted out worldwide Minto.
But the same day, I saw like some tweet.
It was just a random like thing that showed up in my For You page, you know.
And it was some girl that was just like...
If you're above 20 years old and not married, what are you doing?
And I wanted to quote retweet it and be like...
World.
Wife.
Minto.
I got married today.
I don't know how many people...
But I also was just like...
Well, you know what?
Maybe I should get married before the mega quake.
This works!
It all works.
You're forever seven...
Forever 19.
Sorry, I almost said forever...
I said forever 17...
Out of...
Out of reflex.
Yeah, I am forever 19.
My time has arrived to get married.
Should we have a ceremony?
Who would we...
Who would be our...
The officiant?
Um...
Who would marry us?
World wife, Minto, and typing of the dad.
Never change me.
David Hader.
Doki?
No!
Oymo can officiate.
It's only fair.
I will let her if she lets me.
At her wedding.
Oymo, you hear that?
Let me be the officiant.
The person at your wedding.
Wifey time.
Having David Hader would be amazing, though.
But then...
If he's like, does anyone object?
I'd be like...
I would just close my eyes and I'd be like, me.
Because...
I object.
Because I...
How could I let Snake...
You know?
If Snake was...
I would...
I would just...
I would be like...
No!
I'd close my eyes and I'd be like, the man of my dreams is right in front of me.
Have Ayami-sensei be our mother?
Ayami...
Ayami-sensei!
I can't tell if we're getting married or if she's marrying other people.
Or...
Or what's going on?
Snake is right there.
Please switch places.
Please...
She's the real world wife.
All of her fans are her boyfriends.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Where's the loyalty?
She'll marry you.
Yeah, you have to have a gun.
But like...
At Anime Fest, when she and I did a panel together, she was just like, do you have a gun?
Okay.
Let's get married.
She's always accepting the marriage certificate.
So...
Sorry if you hear my coffee.
Maya or Yua would walk you down the aisle.
Yua, my papa.
You're so true.
You're so right.
Coffee ASMR.
Okay.
Here, I'll turn off the music real quick.
Koshichin-sama.
Ojou-sama.
Your tea is ready.
See?
I can do ASMR.
Wait,
she's a real maid?
Shut up!
Yes!
I'm a real maid.
What are you talking about?
What time is it over there?
It's 10 a.m.
10 a.m.
I gotta get going in about 50 minutes.
Sorry, it's a bit shorter today.
We still have an hour, so don't leave.
Don't leave.
But...
So, a.m.
It's very p.m.
over here.
Yeah.
But don't worry.
I'll try and stream in the mornings as much, in mornings JST, as much as I can, so it kind of keeps with my schedule.
My normal streaming schedule.
Yeah.
Did you get to see the maid cafe of Expo?
All right, Janet!
Which I'm so sad, because I've been a fan of Maids of England for a very long time.
So...
Oh, V!
Thank you for the 50 gifted!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Yeah.
I want to collab with the maid cafe.
Six o'clock.
11 p.m.
here.
Oh, it's perfect timing for you.
PST gang rise!
So, probably more streams will...
I know it's like not my super normal streaming time, but probably most streams will start around the time that I started today.
Maybe a little earlier sometimes.
So, just if I have like other plans that day.
I'll have to like start making plans pretty soon, since I do want to get started.
So, I need to get schedules out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ruin my sleep for Minto...
NOOOOOO!!!
Stop it.
When are you returning from Japan?
Uh... in September.
That's why I also wanted to be very comfortable with my streaming schedule, because I'm here for a... a while.
So, uh...
Yeah.
Wake us up when September comes.
When September?
I don't know actually.
It's great to meet you Otakutan.
I hope you had a good time.
Thanks Pao!
I did.
I had so much fun.
Do I have any pictures from Otakutan?
Don Daze, welcome to membership.
Thank you!
Let's see.
What pictures do I have?
I can't wait to show you guys how I've been streaming.
Like my setup right now is so nice.
Winter, welcome to membership, dark girl.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Oh my gosh, let me show you guys.
On my way home from Otakutan.
Hold on.
Not home.
On the way home.
On the way to the airport from Otakutan.
Hold on.
Where's the chat that I sent this in?
Where's the chat?
Oh here, here, here.
I saw this guy.
On the way there.
Oh my god.
On the way to the airport.
I was like...
Hold on.
I was so excited.
I had a group chat with Emuri and Mata.
And I was like...
Ready?
Ta-da!
Look at that!
There's him.
Hold on, I got a better picture too.
Ready?
Ta-da!
He looked directly at me!
I was so excited.
He looked directly at me.
Oh wait...
Hold on.
This picture.
Well, look at his size.
He reminds me of my cat.
I saw that guy.
I was very excited about him.
That's great seeing you.
I'm exposed.
Without it, I wouldn't have met all the Eos Spyro for the first time.
Mordekaiser!
I want to see you.
Sorry I said, oh my god, I'm next before the meet and greet.
I didn't have time to prep because I was given to be last minute.
That was you!
That was so funny.
Unfortunately, for Vexpo, the iPad was a little scuffed sometimes.
So people were talking to me, but because of the noise cancellation, it was hard to hear sometimes.
So I was like, I know!
I'm just a bit hairy.
What, are you that guy?
Are you that little guy?
What would Paramedic have to say about our little guy?
Groundhog.
She'd be like, Snake, have you heard of Groundhog's Day?
If you're a real maid, can you clean up my room for me?
A maid cafe maid?
It's a pretty big decision.
The distinction between a maid maid and a maid cafe.
You know, it's like a...
It's like a...
She's still cleaning mine?
Get out of here!
Get out!
Are you saying you're a cosplayer?
No!
Why would you say that?
Can I get a coffee?
No!
I'm a real maid in a maid cafe.
Eat us, delete us, welcome to membership.
Thank you!
No, no, not a fake maid.
It's called a maid cafe.
Is it a real maid cafe?
Yes!
Look at all my patrons!
Hold on, hold on.
Look!
This is a real cafe.
Yes, what would you...
Are you enjoying your meal?
Oh, they're talking.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to disturb you.
I'm gonna sit right here.
And hang out with this guy.
Are you having a nice day?
Oh, that seat was taken.
Sorry, I didn't notice.
I sat on that guy.
Hold on!
I'm gonna be on the stage!
I'm on the stage!
Minto World!
VIP service.
He was totally unfazed.
Nice maid cosplay.
Shut up!
I'm gonna eat!
I'm
gonna eat!
Minto World!
Hold on.
Which one is it?
Yaaaah!
Can you make my meal delicious?
Of course!
Oishikunare!
Moll!
Cuuuun!
I used to have an Elmo doll that I would pluck all the fur off of.
He became bald because of me.
If you want to collab with the maid cafe, maybe consider the Chest of Wonder Mint Cafe.
I've done VTuber collabs before.
Oh!
What the?
Oh my god.
That's my alarm.
Mint pattern baldness.
He came out of nowhere.
No, we were talking about Elmo!
Oh, I didn't know that.
We were talking about Elmo.
And I had an Elmo doll that I would...
I also ripped his nose open and started ripping out the stuffing inside his nose too.
So it looked like a long trail of snot.
Do you guys remember when Elmo tweeted like, I hope everybody's okay!
And people were like, No, Elmo.
We are not okay.
Tiki on the phone.
Hi!
Tiki!
Cheese!
Cheese, cheese, cheese.
Poor Elmo.
Why the knife?
I don't know.
Is this better?
Oh, sorry.
Surely she won't notice.
Oh, just a box.
Otakus, that was great.
Thanks for coming.
I got to meet you and I was able to spend...
Oh, send you a gift.
Hope you enjoyed the con too.
Hashtag bored.
Oh, yes.
I got the bored, yes.
I got the cutting bored.
Shut up in there, will ya?
Knock, knock, knock.
Was there a knife?
No.
What's this one?
A rose.
There was a rose.
There's no knife in this rose.
Put it away.
She lied to us as easily as she breathes.
I don't breathe.
I'm dead.
I'm a ghost.
I don't need to breathe.
What did I just do?
Oh.
What have you guys been up to...
in the two weeks?
Did you guys go to any events?
Are there anything that you're looking forward to?
I'll...
Oh.
A secret project?
Waiting for you to come back?
Stop it.
Start playing Metal Gear?
The old one.
So Metal Gear, not Metal Gear Solid.
Breaking Dimensions.
Yeah?
Did you guys hear the new song?
It's so good.
It's making me feel emotional.
Breaking Dimensions in one week.
And then also...
Mint concert in one week too.
Yeah.
If you're going to Breaking Dimensions, maybe you can try and go to Mint concert too.
Maybe.
That's the plan.
I wanted to go to both...
Oh, not to both.
I'm going to the one.
But I wanted to go to Breaking Dimensions too.
What is Breaking Dimensions?
It's the Hololive concert.
At...
During...
I don't think it's at...
Well, it's during Anime NYC.
So...
Hmm.
Minto, please East Coast.
New York is East Coast!
It's East Coast!
It's just North Coast.
Did you watch Advent 3D?
I did!
I think...
Actually, the only...
Actually, I need to catch up on Shiori's.
Because...
Hers happened while I was busy.
New York isn't on the coast.
Oh, buddy.
Just shut up.
Sounds like they want South East.
Okay, well ask a convention in the South East...
To invite me.
Ask...
A convention...
In the South East...
To invite me.
Contact...
Your local convention.
Check DMs, I just invited you.
Huh?
Oh my god.
Oh my god, you really did DM me.
I'm interested!
Thanks, Kira.
Gone in my RTA.
Yo, no way!
Yippee!
Okay, see you guys in the South East.
America.
The dream is alive.
You were sick.
But, you know...
Obviously, I'm not gonna say...
Anything yet.
Cause...
You know...
Oh no, she's going to Florida.
I would love to go to Florida.
And...
Find...
Florida man.
Collab with him.
And...
Um...
See what happens.
It's me.
I'm Florida man.
Where's your credentials?
No, I watched that guy.
There's a guy on TikTok.
That goes to the Florida Everglades.
And he's like, hey guys, I'm in the Florida Everglades.
And I'm walking around barefoot.
Oh, here's a snake.
Yoink.
And then...
He just walks around.
Yoink.
Yeah, the swamp puppies.
I love watching his videos.
Yoink.
I wonder if I could collab with him.
Do you think he could take me on one of his adventures?
He's like the modern day...
Steve Irwin.
Actually, I watch...
I follow only like...
Like a couple creators on TikTok.
Let's see.
I'm gonna open up TikTok.
But I'm not gonna watch videos.
It's just for the numbers.
I...
I follow...
Who the hell is...
Okay, some of these are misclicks.
Oh gosh.
Wait.
Okay.
I follow a bunch of idols.
And then I follow...
Um...
I follow the Yoink guy.
And I follow Robert Irwin.
Which is Steve Irwin's son.
I follow idols and animal people.
That's about it.
Yeah, his son.
Son of Steve Irwin.
Yeah.
I like his videos too.
And then they make me cry.
Because it's like...
Oh, Steve Irwin.
Oh no.
I'm gonna cry.
No.
I'm gonna cry thinking about...
Steve Irwin.
Because it makes me...
No.
I like animals.
I'm gonna cry thinking about...
Oh boy, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, you're too late.
I'm just sad.
Go.
Naah...
Yeah right now...
So worse now.
Okay.
Gah!
What's wrong with me?
Hold on, I'm gonna go get a tissue.
Hold on.
Stop making fun of me.
I'm normal.
Still thinking of Steve?
Say it!
Don't say his name!
Hold!
Steve Minecraft.
Minecraft!
I'm better now!
Actually, I probably...
There's a Minecraft thing I wanna do soon-ish.
I'm waiting for someone.
I don't wanna say it because...
Just yet.
Because...
I don't know if they wanted to keep it a surprise or not.
I think Pusskink will wear those shorts.
Like Steve Irwin's shorts?
Oh, yeah.
No!
No, his shorts!
I'm fine.
I'm okay.
What is going on?
I don't know anymore!
I don't even know anymore.
I'm okay now.
There's a minto-shaped hole in my heart since the last two weeks.
You might want to get that checked out.
I feel cold again, so here's money for you to spend on.
Oh right, no wallet.
Why are you so mean to me?
I'm literally... I have... You know what?
Let's do an activity.
Let's count the amount of yen I have in my wallet.
Hold on, I'm gonna go get it.
I said wallet.
I meant to say coin purse.
Because I don't have my wallet.
It's my coin purse.
I brought that though.
I brought my coin purse.
Okay, let's see.
I'm gonna put the fives in a category.
The fifties in a category.
Hundreds in a category.
Okay, lots of tens.
Got a lot of tens.
The yenies in a category.
Let's see if we can...
I know you guys can't see it, but try and guess without going over, okay?
Let's put in your guesses.
Actually, here, I'll make a poll.
I'll make a poll.
And you can kind of...
Let's see.
How much yen?
Yen.
No...
Let's say...
Since you guys can't see it, I'll give you 700 yen.
About...
About 1,500 yen.
About... yeah.
That should be good.
So, can't go over.
Alright, I'm organizing.
I'm organizing.
I have a lot of tens.
I have a couple 100s.
I have a few 50s.
Uh...
Is this like deal or no deal?
Yeah.
I'm sorting them first, and then I'm gonna count them.
I almost dropped it.
I almost dropped my money.
You keep the money.
Oh, Asuka.
I almost dropped my money.
You keep the money.
I dropped my money.
Oh, Asuka.
I'm dropping the money for real.
Okay, hold on.
Thanks, everyone.
I was wondering...
How you only realized the wallet was gone in Japan and not during Otakutan.
Okay.
I can explain to you why I left my wallet.
So, the purse that I use for my wallet...
Um...
Is the same purse.
Like, all the time.
So, I never really take my wallet out.
But, I ended up going to the grocery store...
To get some stuff before I left.
Because I needed...
Uh...
I needed...
Um...
I mean, I just needed some like...
Some toiletry stuff, you know?
Um, like face wash and things like that.
Which I guess I could have gotten in Japan.
Anyway...
I went...
And I...
Um...
Did not bring my purse.
I took my wallet out.
And on the way back, I was like...
Oh, my wallet is...
I cannot have any place to put it.
I'll put it in the grocery bag.
And so I put it in the grocery bag.
And then I left it in there.
And then so...
When I left for the airport...
I...
So, basically what had happened was...
I went to Otakutan.
I came back home.
I had one day to pack for Japan.
And then I left the next day.
So...
That's when I went into my grocery shopping.
If you're just like, wait, but didn't you come from Otakutan?
Yeah, so I had like one day.
And so I left it in the grocery bag.
And uh...
That's what happened.
That's why I left.
Because I never put it in the grocery bag.
And I was stressed about packing.
It's so...
Did you not bring any of your groceries?
Well, some of it was food.
And I just kind of left my wallet in there.
Like some of it was like...
Oh, this is dinner, you know?
Why don't you put your wallet in your pocket?
Because it wasn't big enough!
Why did you go grocery shopping the day before you left for Japan?
No, it wasn't like...
It was like for stuff that I needed...
Like for my trip.
And then also like dinner that night.
It wasn't like grocery grocery shopping.
It was just a few things.
Why are you...
Why are you getting...
I think this story is an actual nightmare for traveling.
But at least you brought your passport.
Yeah, I had my passport.
I was able to leave.
Okay, guys.
I have a 100 yen.
Okay, hold on.
How many tens do I have?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 100.
What if I go over my own...
I think we're going to go over 1,000 yen, you guys.
Uh-oh.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 6, 60, 65, 66, 67, 100,
300, 400, 450.
Wait, hold on.
Wait, I'm getting confused.
Okay, wait.
Okay, hold on.
500, 6, 7, 8, 900 yen?
1,000?
1,100?
1200?
1300?
1,400?
1, 200, 3, 4.
1,500?
1,500.
1,516 1,170.
Oh, Oh, we went over.
See, two things in life.
We all lost!
Yippee!
Uh-oh, my tummy is growling.
I should probably go get some food.
I should go get some food since I have to leave in like an hour.
Well guys, this was fun!
We'll be streaming again tomorrow.
Scammed.
I have 1,500 yen so I can eat.
My first midstream, I got here late.
But thanks for dropping by!
You weren't late.
You're here to hang out at all.
I appreciate it.
Oh, my tummy is really starting to growl.
Okay guys, I'm gonna go get some food.
And I'm gonna go get some food at a convenience store or something.
And do you have your sweet corn?
I do, I do, I do, I do.
It's okay.
I'll be fine until my wallet comes.
No worries.
Don't worry about me.
Don't worry.
Okay, I'm gonna check this tracking right now though.
It hasn't moved in three days.
So it's on its way.
Probably.
Oh, my gosh.
Make day!
Thanks for the 50.
Thanks for the stream and welcome back.
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Oh, my chat has been weird.
Okay, there it is.
Not you guys.
The YouTube.
Welcome back to YouTube.
See you again soon, Mintome.
See you again tomorrow if you guys come see me.
Mintome!
Fellow Mint.
Thanks for the three months.
Thank you.
Okie dokie.
Otsuminto, everybody.
Otsuminto.
Have a good rest of your night or your day.
I'm gonna have a busy day ahead of me.
So I'm gonna go do myself.
I didn't mean to scam you guys.
Okay.
You know what?
I'm just gonna get out of here.
We all lost.
So we're all complicit.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
See you soon.
See you.
Bye.
Ha!