Three, two, one, swap.
Why are you laughing?
What
did I say?
Nothing, nothing.
What did I say?
You've been dealing with this for years now.
Why now you laugh?
Nothing, nothing.
Hi guys.
Hey everybody.
So first off, I just want you guys to know, we were selling technical difficulties for at least 30 minutes.
Oh my god, we were so prepared.
Yeah, we were so prepared guys.
It was just very unfortunate that the last five minutes that we had, just something came up unexpectedly.
It was crazy.
It was so crazy.
Oh yeah, and it was on Min's side, not on mine.
Whoa, wait, wait, wait.
I plead mac and cheese, you plead Germany.
What are you talking about?
Okay, look, the reason why I didn't start and Min started before me was because Dokkaebi, we had to connect to a special server to be there.
And I forgot I was connected to that special server.
So I was streaming over at Dokkaebi.
I was streaming over at Germany.
So someone out there was watching the starting screen in Germany and being like, where did this person come from?
It's like Grandpa Joe just trying to watch Jeopardy and he's like...
The worst part was the starting screen was not even playing.
It was just a still image.
So he must be freaking out right now and being like aliens or some shit.
How
do you say that in German?
What do you think I know German?
Well, you okay.
Miss invited to a German convention.
Look, I would say an European convention is a is a convention for all of EU.
Europe is not just German mint.
Wow.
Gotta open your mind.
It was in Germany.
Yeah, open your mind and be more inclusive to the other countries in Europe.
Okay.
Name every country in Europe.
All right.
European Union.
Who's not in the European Union?
Well, then they're not European.
Guys, that was a joke, guys.
That was a joke, everybody.
Wow.
And now she's lumping everyone in Europe under the European Union.
No one can have individuality here.
Oh, yeah.
You name every country in Europe then.
I already asked you.
Yeah, but you're like, oh, you're ragging me on about my lack of European knowledge.
You think I know?
I don't know.
Then why are you ragging me?
I could have named random countries and you wouldn't know because you don't know Europe apparently.
Okay.
Name three countries and I'll tell you which one is real.
We're going to play that.
All right.
Give me a sec.
Oh, no.
She has to Google.
Give me a sec.
All right.
I also have Google.
You got to Google.
That's not knowing the answer if you're Googling.
I don't know.
All right.
Oh, what are you Googling?
I'm googling, huh?
What are the countries of the world?
I googled nice things to send to my mom.
So you're not even prioritizing the stream.
I'm waiting on you, Dokie.
You're the one holding us up.
Okay, alright, alright.
Fine, fine.
Okay.
Peso.
Why are you laughing?
Wait, what?
Peso?
Yeah, Peso.
Malawi.
Eritrea.
Which one's the fake?
What's the third one?
Eritrea.
I would like to phone a friend.
You don't know either!
They were all real!
They were all in Africa!
Please stop!
We said Europe!
You said you know every country in the world.
So I gave you every country in the world.
I gave you specific...
You don't know any African countries.
That's fucked up.
I know, I know some.
I know Zanzibar.
I gave you three and you couldn't even tell which one was the real one, but they were all real.
We said Europe!
Yeah, and then you went with countries in the entire world.
So I was like, entire world, huh?
Okay, entire world!
Oh my god, this is this is slander.
Oh my god.
Anyway, shall we play the game?
Okay.
I'm over playing GeoGuessr.
Alright, we'll play GeoGuessr now.
You're right.
I should have selected South America country.
Oh yeah, how many countries have you been to in South America?
Like...
zero?
I've been to one!
Yeah?
Which one was it?
Argentina!
Oh yeah.
Yeah, but you were there for like one second.
Does that really count?
No, I talked to the locals and they said, Papa Frita is so small.
That's all you got from it?
What even was the fucking context?
I was eating really small fries from McDonald's at the airport.
So they were like making fun of you?
Yeah.
She was like, I need to take a picture of this.
Eating the small fries.
So I turned up mid a little bit, guys.
I turned her up so you guys could hear her better.
It's not like she's giving us any good input or anything, but at least hear me.
I'm gonna send you to Brazil.
We're gonna go to Brazil together.
We're gonna go to Brazil, guys!
I don't care if men are coming to Brazil!
Brazil mentioned!
So apparently we found out that we can actually potentially kill people in this game.
And like, if any of that actually happens...
Wait, so if my characters die, do I just stop playing the game?
I think you just take over a different character.
Maybe?
I don't know.
We'll find out.
I guess we'll see when you kill off your character.
Also, there's QuickTime events, by the way.
Did you know that?
This is basically like Until Dawn.
My chat was like, oh, men and QuickTime events.
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't know.
I'm good at the QuickTime.
I wonder if I should play this with a controller.
Oh, cause I am.
Oh, you are?
Okay, I'm gonna grab my controller.
Yeah, I feel like this game is meant to be.
Until Dawn was meant to be played on a controller.
You're right.
Hold on.
Okay, I'm good.
Isn't this the creators of Until Dawn?
I'm pretty sure.
I think so.
Yeah, so it was meant to play.
Alright, you guys ready?
New slot.
Oh, I want to be Joe or Charlie.
Guys, which one has a higher chance of living?
Oh.
Joe.
Joe Schmo.
Joe Schmo?
Charlie Warley?
Charlie Warley.
Joey.
He believes in the heart of the cards.
Okay.
Oh, you're right.
I'm gonna be Joe.
I identify with Joey.
Just kidding.
Joey's a wimp.
I'm ready.
I'm ready, Charlie.
I am your Charlie.
It says it right there on the screen.
For now.
Okay.
Alright, here we go.
Wait.
To play with a controller, press E.
Okay, that's cool.
That'd be funny if we were like, you can only play with one.
The other has to do M and K.
Oh my god.
That would be torture.
Man of Medan.
Medan?
What is it?
You don't know either.
I think it's Medan.
Right?
Okay, to be fair, everybody knows I pronounce things wrong 99% of the time.
That's gonna be you.
That's gonna be you in that box.
Oh wait, in the box it did!
I know, that's what I'm saying.
That's it.
Woo.
Elvis Presley.
I bet like...
Oh my god.
Are we coming back from the war?
I guess so.
What war though?
There's a lot.
In America.
I don't know.
There's so many choices.
You know this is based on like a real ship, right?
Wait, it is?
Wait, this is based off real life?
Yeah, they found a ship that like, everybody died on.
Oh.
And they couldn't figure out why they all died.
Doki Bird is Joe.
That's what it said in the corner.
That's right.
The director called me up to act on this movie.
Game.
That's you, Charlie!
Well, I'm wasted.
Yeah, you're so drunk.
Oh no, Charlie.
There's no subtitles.
Oh yeah, you turn it on yourself.
I turn mine on.
Guys, I have subtitles.
Wait, how do I turn it on?
I guess we'll find...
You'll have to find out after this scene.
Okay.
Where is...
I have subtitles.
Look it, she's hot.
Oh my god, he's fighting that thing.
Kick his ass.
Oh wait, this is me!
Oh my god.
Punch!
R to aim, R T to punch.
What do I punch?
This thing?
Use R to choose.
Can I like move it for you?
Oh, I can.
You can?
Yeah.
Can I move it?
Wait, I am moving it.
No, I'm moving it.
This is totally me.
You're not?
Okay.
I wanna know...
Oh my god, me!
Wait, how do I pick?
Oh my god.
I'm killing it.
What are you doing?
I'm doing QTEs.
Oh, we're doing different things.
Why can't I pick?
Cause... oh.
Why'd you pause the game?
Don't you have to...
Go do your fucking settings.
Yeah, hold on.
I'm doing my subtitles.
Oh, you're actually doing it?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm doing my subtitles.
Okay, we're good.
Continue.
I'm ready.
Okay.
Four, three, two, one.
You threw off my groove.
Wait, you're fighting?
Yes, I'm fighting!
Wait, I can't press anything!
Wait!
You should've picked Charlie.
Yeah, I didn't turn you up anyway.
This gives me a chance to turn you up.
Oh my god.
I'm continuing the game.
I want to pick!
I'm pressing B!
Yeah, it's my QTEs!
What's R?
It's not letting me pick!
I swear I'm pressing everything!
Yeah, because I'm the one who's playing!
No, I have my own screen!
I have my own screen!
I don't know what's going on on your side!
I'm playing the game!
It's not letting me pick!
I'm pressing everything!
You suck at the game!
I already beat it!
Oh, I said nothing.
Oh, you're already done?
Yes, I didn't say anything.
Wait, were you playing a game of cards or something?
I was trying to do the dialogue section if I couldn't pick a dialogue.
What do I look like?
I was gaming.
And you were dying to some old man who's asleep.
What do I got coming my way?
Oh wait, now I have to do the thing you just did.
Oh, you were doing this.
Um...
Were you able to pick a dialogue?
You have this?
Are you freaking out?
I picked it!
I picked a thing.
What did you press?
You just move with R.
Yeah, but how did you select it?
Oh, I'm going to use the rooster tile.
You just hover over it.
You just hover over it?
That's all you did?
Guys, you're wrong too.
It wasn't just press R.
You just hover.
Oh, wait.
I didn't pick it up.
Oh my god, I don't know anything about my son!
What about my son?
I don't think you'll never know.
I think you're dead.
I'll never know about my son or if I'll ever be rich.
I just did nothing.
I feel like it's hard to balance the audio in this.
He's told me like...
Blood?
Huh?
Oh, are you done?
Yeah, I'm done.
You don't need to know anything more about your future.
If I don't know my future, you don't know your future.
Did you beat the dummy?
Yeah, I beat the dummy.
I did it faster than you.
Did you get hit?
No.
I don't believe you.
No, I did not!
Did you get hit on the QuickTime events?
No.
If anybody's dying, it's on your side.
No, I got an achievement for it.
I got an achievement.
I think all of us get an achievement for finishing it.
Oh, shit.
The death box.
That's gonna be you.
I mean, judging by the QuickTime events stuff, I think it's you.
Don't write death POV.
Me?
I might not make right dialogue.
See, we got our strengths.
I'm the QuickTime event person, and you're the dialogue person.
Wait, why are there three boxes of death?
Wait, who's the third person?
Uh-oh, it's chat.
It's chat.
Wait, one of our chats survives.
Uh-oh.
Oh, who's that guy?
Where's my 50 cents?
Yeah, I was like, what 50 cents?
Come on, chat.
Mitch, you don't need 50 cents.
You stole my 50 cents.
Oh, that's the third guy.
No, that was you.
You just got punched by a dude.
The
audio is like so...
Why is it so loud, but he's so quiet?
Yeah, I know.
Why is the sound effect so loud?
Why are you dead already?
Come on, don't keep it up.
You're the drunk one.
You are too.
You got punched in the face.
You hit me for fucking 50 cents and then I got punched?
Like...
Guys, it's not the game voice that's low.
It's the...
It's everything else is high.
Yeah, I think that, yeah.
I keep trying to like adjust it, but it's like all over the place.
Okay.
Uh-oh.
Oh, there's the ship.
Whoa!
Oh, no.
What the fuck?
Titanic moment.
It struck...
Oh!
What is that?
That's some ghoul.
The death is leaking into the water.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
Frankenstein.
Do you guys know that Frankenstein...
The reason his arms are stuck out is because he was supposed to be blind and they just wrote that out of the story, but kept his arms sticking out.
It's kind of messed up.
Um, it's Frankenstein's monster.
Whatever.
Um...
Actually...
If you're gonna give a fact about Frankenstein...
I'm sorry.
Frankenstein's monster.
What the fuck?
Whoa!
What's going on?
I'm in the bridge.
This is Charlie.
Oh, no.
Oh, wait.
That's me.
Yeah, you're looking at yourself.
Oh, yeah, I'm looking at myself.
Wait, where are you?
I'm at the sickbay.
Why'd you pause?
Because I didn't just see audio!
The audio is fucked up!
You're right, you're right, you're right.
I'm putting the sound effects and the music down.
We do not need such high sound effects.
No, I'm gonna put it, like, 70.
I'm gonna put it at 72, yeah.
See?
You're welcome.
What is audio preset?
I don't know.
Oh, never mind.
Alright, I turned down music and the sound effects.
Are you ready?
Hold on.
Alright, fine, you press continue then.
I'm pressing continue.
Did you press continue?
Oh, I pressed continue.
Yeah, I waited too long, so now I'm adjusting again.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
Okay, now you can press continue.
I already did.
Alright, there we go.
Three, two, one.
I guess people can use, like, the settings thing to fuck each other over.
Whoa, there's blood on the wall.
Wait, there's blood?
Oh, wait, I got the med kit.
Don't worry, I got you.
Okay.
It's not my blood.
Call an ambulance, but not for me.
Okay, I know where the blood came from.
I know where the blood came from.
Yeah, there's text that's on the, um, right side.
What a dick.
Okay, I know where the blood came from.
Okay, hold on.
I'm paused.
Sorry.
I'm moving us over, I'm moving us over, I'm moving us over.
Chat, come over here, Chat.
That's not a med kit.
Chat, come here.
Oh, you guys are, like, censored to...
Oh, gosh.
Okay.
You guys, don't worry about it.
Okay, sorry.
Five, four, three, two, one.
There's a dead body on my side.
Um, there's just blood on the wall here.
Let's see.
Oh, I'm looking at a key.
Whoa, what a key.
I have a key.
I'm just looking at blood.
Come get me out of here then, maybe.
Maybe that's for me to get out.
I need to see... wait, it's a doctor.
Is he dead?
There's a dead... yes.
I'm pretty sure he was stuffed in the locker.
I'm pretty sure he's dead.
Private Charles Anderson.
What happened?
Wait, what happened while I was sleeping?
Oh.
Oh, we were both sleeping.
Ten days approved.
Yeah, what the heck happened?
To Pops, come back soon.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure we weren't sleeping for that long.
Nah.
I'm opening up...
Do you have a safe code?
I'm opening up a lock.
I'm coming out.
I'm coming out of the ship.
Out of the ship?
Where are you?
I'm outside the ship now.
Okay, I don't like how you don't know what's going on.
I'm stuck in the brig.
Oh my gosh, this is tank...
Oh, it's Resident Evil.
I'm stuck in the brig.
The brig?
Something's gonna pop out at me.
Wait, is that you?
Are you in this side?
Yeah, that's me!
That's you, Charlie!
Just get me out of here already.
Oh, you were in detention for punching me.
I didn't punch you!
Oh yeah?
Why were you locked inside?
I don't know.
Of course.
Something's wrong.
Let's get out of here.
What are these guys looking at?
What is happening?
Find out what's happening on this ship.
Where are we gonna go?
I don't know.
This way, this way, this way.
Don't you hear it?
I don't know.
I'm stuck in the wall.
This way, this way.
Go, Charlie.
Go, my heart.
Oh, what's that?
I don't know.
Run!
Oh, God.
That's gonna be you.
What's that?
Oh.
Press A in time with a heart beat?
Okay.
If you don't get this right, I swear to God.
You fucked up!
I swear to God!
You fucked me!
We were fine!
Where did we come from?
Where did we go?
Oh, wait.
This is where we came from.
Turn around.
We're just two bumbling guys.
Charlie and Joe.
The adventures of Charlie and Joe.
What is this?
How did you mess up that?
You just pressed A!
I wanted to see what would happen if he caught us.
Yeah, you wanted to see what would happen.
He didn't shoot us.
It's fine.
He was safe.
Okay.
What the hell?
I'm speaking.
Oh, wait.
Hold on.
I'm gonna put settings up right now, okay?
Get ready.
I need to turn you up again.
Okay.
Settings time.
Actually, this works for me.
I need to fix it.
Okay, we both need to fix it, so that's fine.
Okay.
I turned my sound effects to 60.
Why is the sound effects so loud?
I don't know.
Actually, I'm gonna turn mine down a little bit, too.
Yeah.
Okay, I'm gonna turn you up a little bit.
And I'm turning the overall game a little bit.
60.
Alright.
Okay.
This should work.
Is this A Way Out or whatever that game is?
Well, it feels like it.
It's like the horror version of A Way Out.
Sorry, chat.
You're cut off a little bit.
Sorry, guys.
Alright, here.
I'm ready.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
I already clicked ready.
Okay.
I don't know that.
I can't see.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Okay.
Here we go.
We're walking down the hall.
We're fine.
Everything's good.
Wait.
Where did you go?
Oh, there you are.
Didn't we come here?
What was that?
What was that, Joe?
Did you not see it?
Poor Joe.
Did you not see Charlie?
Did you not see the guy running in front of us?
No.
There was no guy.
Wait.
Oh, no.
What's going on?
What are you talking about?
Charlie, I think I'm so drunk.
Joe, take your meds.
Joe.
I couldn't.
The doctor's dead.
There's a door flashing over here.
Yeah.
Over here.
Why are our feet smelly?
Ew.
Wait.
Do you not see?
There's like a flashing over here.
Yeah.
Get it.
I'm getting it.
Come on, Joe.
Yeah.
Help me.
I just came back from the sickbay.
Why is my face just so...
Alright.
Oh.
A.
Okay.
I'm pressing A repeatedly.
Pressing A repeatedly.
Yeah.
He's dead.
You said it.
Fubar and then some.
What the fuck?
What does that even mean?
What does that mean?
Oh, my God.
Oh, that's a lot of blood.
Are we getting invaded?
What's happening?
What happened on the ship?
Stays on the ship.
Oh.
Okay.
I'm first, I guess.
Yeah.
Even though I opened the door?
Our feet are really smelly.
Wait.
Why is there, like, gas on the floor?
That's what I'm saying.
We're smelly.
Go.
I'm checking him out.
I'm trying to check him out.
Wait.
I'm stuck.
I can't.
Oh, there it is.
What's going on?
He looks like Peter Griffin.
Wait.
I want to see, too.
What the fuck?
Oh, my God.
It's him.
Wait.
What's wrong with his eyes?
He's, like, looking.
He's, like, blank eyes.
Yeah.
Let's go this way.
What's going on, guys?
There's nothing this way.
We gotta go through the door.
I feel like those, like, the frat boys be like, hey, guys.
What's going on?
What do we do?
Wow.
Look at these camera angles.
So cinematic.
Oh, you went through that door?
I can't see anything.
Where are you?
I'm heading downstairs.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
It is so cinematic.
I can't see where I'm going.
Do I just go straight?
Fubar is a military snap for fucked unbelievably beyond all recognition.
Whoa.
Oh, you can LB.
Oh, my God.
To walk faster.
Okay.
Yeah.
I like that.
Okay.
All right.
Now we can... Can we run?
I don't feel like I'm walking very much.
Me, too.
I feel like...
I don't think I'm walking that fast.
Me, either.
Maybe we're not pressing the right button.
It's LB.
I don't know.
It's just...
Maybe it's wrong.
Which one is me?
I'm the one... Oh, this is me.
Whoa.
Did you not see that?
No, I didn't see anything.
Oh, it's only me.
It was a child.
Are you feeling all right?
Joe, what's wrong with you?
Of course, you, Doki, would be the one.
You would be the one.
To go crazy.
So you're walking in circles.
You're just like, I don't know.
I don't know, Charlie.
I don't feel so good.
I don't feel so good, Charlie.
I'm seeing children.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Go, go, go.
Uh-oh.
Is that a good idea?
Oh, why did I grab a knife?
What the hell?
Why can't I ever have a gun?
You know why.
This is accurate.
This is very accurate.
Why can't I ever have a gun?
You were meant to have the katana.
The katana.
I don't think you...
You are having hallucinations.
I don't think you should be holding anything.
Is that you?
That's me.
I saw another child.
I saw a child again.
What the fuck do you see on your screen?
The dead people are actually talking to me right now.
Oh, what?
What is happening?
It's you talking to me.
But you're dead.
Wait, what?
Yeah, you're looking at me.
But you're dead.
I'm going to investigate.
Wait, how do I investigate?
Oh, there we go.
How are you investigating?
I'm still hallucinating.
I'm investigating your body.
Oh, there's a man here.
Wait, there's me.
No, I think you're the man.
Wait, what?
No child!
The child has your knife!
You gave the child the knife!
No, I still have it!
I shot the child!
Oh my god, he's a zombie!
I missed!
How could you miss?
Are you shooting me?
I don't know, but I missed apparently.
Where did I die from that?
I think I'm dead too.
This guy used the force on me and killed me.
I tried...
I missed the child and then I died from a heart attack.
You died from cringe because you were so bad.
You died of cringe, real.
Hello, can anyone out there hear me?
Who is he?
Of course not Charlie or Joe.
Give us your location, do it!
Do it, man!
You're our only hope!
Random sailor!
Uh oh.
Wait, what?
He has four arms!
Doki, I think something weird is going on here.
Yeah, I don't think that...
I think that shit might be haunted.
He's got his little baby cross.
God cannot save you now!
Whoa!
Oh, he's...
He's dead!
Oh my god, he's dead!
Oh my god, she died of cringe too!
Everybody's dying of cringe!
Oh my god, it's so loud.
I cannot...
I like how they were like, picked between Joe and Charlie and they're already dead.
Yeah, that was the prologue.
We get the prologue.
We get the whole... we get the game now.
This isn't the ship we're at a mansion now.
Do they still make these games?
I don't know.
I know they're doing really bad right now.
You know what?
I saw the reviews for it.
Fair.
The newer episodes were not doing so well.
Uh oh.
Who's this guy?
Isn't he the guy that was the psychiatrist in Until Dawn?
Oh, is he?
I think so.
Oh, apparently we're gonna get a copyright strike because of this song.
I'm turning it down.
It's okay, they're just gonna get our ad money.
That's alright.
Alright.
Look at this.
The ring girl.
What is going on?
Why is she there?
Is this like some paranormal activity?
Is this like the video game version of the Annabelle ship?
Probably.
What were they called?
They had names.
They were like a couple that investigated paranormal activities.
Anne and Lorraine Warren or whatever.
Yeah, yeah.
What was the name of those movies called?
Wasn't it just Annabelle, right?
No, they had a name.
There was a series.
The Conjuring.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Insidious?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
We're the Conjuring.
Joe and Charlie.
Charlie, who died.
Walking down his own hallway so dramatically.
Yeah.
Oh, now he's lighting candles.
Hello.
Is the sound on?
And welcome.
Yeah, thank you.
To my repository.
Okay.
His suppository?
Is that the things you stick up your ass?
I think so.
If you're wondering why I know this, guys, it's because I watch a lot of doctor shows.
Yeah, that's the only reason she knows.
That's the only reason I know.
Then why do you know it, huh?
The curator of stories.
Stories of love.
You're not answering the question, man.
Wait, what did you say?
I wasn't listening.
Why do you know what suppositories are?
Oh, because I watch the shows with you.
Oh, true.
Oh, yeah.
You were there.
The story you choose to tell.
You see, this tale is only part written.
It's breaking the fourth wall.
He's talking to us.
And determine whether the lives of those with whom you are interfering continue to flourish or whether they are snuffed out.
Snuffed out.
Yeah.
You see, we each make decisions according to our own moral compass.
I think I have a great moral compass.
You literally couldn't press A.
It was a lot of pressure.
Okay.
It is the tax one pays for having lived and it comes eventually to everybody.
Still, none of us want for it to come too soon.
Yeah, Mint.
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm already dead.
I fear nothing.
Sometimes separately.
What one does may not make complete sense to the other because we all have different perspectives.
Yeah, anything you do makes no sense to me.
And neither does you.
That's why it's perfect.
We're playing this.
Yeah, it's perfect.
I think the goal is to at least have one person survive.
Probably.
Who will it be?
You or me?
Here's one for free.
There are pictures in this world that can show you some possible future.
Oh, so it's like a hint.
Yeah.
They may just help you to make better decisions.
Oh no.
I think that's subjective.
If they're better or not.
Yeah, like how do we know if they're better decisions?
That's all for the moment.
We'll talk again soon enough.
We'll have the opportunity to account for all the actions that you've taken.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you, man of Medan.
Do we need to pay you now?
I don't know this guy.
Is this a trial period?
Oh, that's where we were.
That's the opening screen.
It was just the water.
Ooh.
Donkey Bird is Alex.
You're Brad?
I'm Brad.
You're Brad.
I'm probably really cool.
Which one is this?
Brad's a cool name.
Is this the Brad or the Alex?
Oh, I look like a nerd.
I'm your brother.
We're brothers.
How do we always end up being brothers?
Wait, which one?
Is that you?
Are you the nerd?
Yes.
Look at this nerd.
You're insecure.
Why does yours say innocent?
What does that imply about me?
I'm an innocent maiden.
Down.
Diving.
Maybe you could show me how the pros do it.
Ooh.
Donkey Bird is deciding.
Let's see.
You didn't take lessons?
Yeah.
Kind of.
You think I can just save you like that?
I'm gonna say nothing.
That's right.
Know your place, nerd.
Hey.
Oh, yeah.
I'm an influencer.
You're an influencer?
Maybe.
I don't know.
I have a camera.
So don't sweat the little stuff, man.
It's not cool.
Don't make me regret letting you tag along.
Yeah.
Don't make me regret it.
Are you deciding again?
Dude, you know I'm not like the best around new people.
Oh, you're anxious.
My anxiety went up.
Yeah.
Make me feel better.
Bread.
We're buddies.
Oh, wait.
I can see your traits.
Oh, that's what you're looking at.
What was it?
RB?
Oh, I can't see it.
Yeah, RB.
We have secrets, too.
I can't see it since I'm in the pause.
Oh, my God.
I'm guarded.
Genuine.
I'm genuine.
Insecure.
Generous.
Who the fuck is Conrad and Fliss?
We're not there yet.
We have other people.
Alex reminded Brad he's not just a tag along.
Alex was annoyed that Brad had not taken diving lessons.
Oh, my God.
Come on.
So I can't even see them.
Now I'm gonna see it.
Now you're gonna see it.
It's RB.
It's collections and characters.
That's what it was.
I'm witty.
I'm eager.
I'm innocent.
Yeah, but are you genuine like me?
You're not genuine.
Mine literally says genuine.
How do I see the other one?
If you're not genuine, oh, you can't see it.
We can only see ourselves.
Mine says guarded, generous.
Genuine.
Yeah, I'm gen...
I mean, I let you come over to the diving to the diving place.
I could let you drown if I wanted to.
You're my bro.
You're not my brother.
See, I'm being supportive.
I mean, like, we're buddies, you know?
Oh my god, we're buddies.
Just out here to fucking hang, cool out, kick it.
Yeah, you gotta loosen up, bro.
Let's just kick it and be legends, man.
You're Apex Legends?
Alright, amigo.
Sorry, I'm a little snappy.
I'm just...
Medical school would be stressful, you know?
I'm a medical school doctor!
Oh my god!
At least I'm a cool nerd.
You're a fucking influencer.
It's been like two weeks.
Come on, man.
Right on cue.
I'm smart and cool.
What are you?
I'm innocent.
I'm not gonna be a doctor.
I'm gonna save lives.
You need to save your own first.
So, uh...
Can I get your input on something?
Oh my god, I'm gonna propose!
Oh, you are?
I have a big thing I'm trying to make a decision about.
About finishing med school?
No, but...
It's just kind of a big life choice, you know?
I don't know what's the right thing to do.
Do I marry her or not?
I'm gonna say nothing.
Why are you so supportive?
Oh my god!
That's my girlfriend!
Your girlfriend, Julia!
That's her brother!
He's relaxed.
He's foolhardy.
What does that mean?
Yo, you want me to hook you up with her brother?
Oh, wow.
You like that?
This is Alex.
Hey, what's up, man?
Conrad.
Watch it, sis.
Lady killer.
Right here.
That's me.
He's ignoring you.
This Conrad guy looks like...
Bradley!
She looks like that actor.
Dr. Horrible.
Neil Patrick Harris.
Hey, man.
Wanna crack a cold one?
Of course.
I'm cracking a cold one!
Every second.
I love you.
I'm gonna be cool.
I'm gonna be cool, you guys.
Cool.
We're cracking a cold one.
No!
She called me needy!
I love you.
I'm not needy!
I swear!
I think this is my first time having a beer.
Are you cracking a beer?
Yeah, I'm cracking a cold one.
It's the jib.
Oh, wait.
I thought I was throwing up.
Throw up, I did.
I can't believe it.
Wait, who's that?
Who's this?
This is my love interest now.
Where's the old crust bucket skipper?
It's burning out.
Captain of the Duke of Milan.
Oh, dang.
She looks like a badass.
Oh my gosh, did you see her tattoo?
Yeah.
I'd invite you to make yourselves at home, but...
Why is everybody...
Why is it so awkward?
Yeah, isn't she the captain?
Yeah, you don't know who's sailing the ship?
Like, what's going on?
Here we go.
You're selling.
I'm buying.
I hope Conrad dies first.
Yeah, me too.
Conrad, that's fucked up.
Do not flirt with the person who knows how to drive the boat.
Yeah.
What are we doing here anyway?
We're diving?
Is that it?
Yeah, we're learning how to dive.
Cool.
The Duke of Milan.
Oh, that's you.
No, that's you.
You're the blue shit.
Oh, you're right.
We're the fucking blue shit.
Look, she's like comforting me.
She likes it when they're weak.
What?
Oh.
What is this?
She's going through the picks.
Can you see me going through the picks?
No, I'm fucking talking to the captain right now.
I'm looking at something.
Oh!
I found a ship.
Well, hot diggity dong.
Dong?
Alex, come here.
I think we got something.
I think it's hot diggity dong.
Wait, you did your homework?
What do you mean?
Oh.
Yeah, we got a wreck.
We got a wreck.
We have to do some diving.
You suggested.
The captain said it's not a good idea, but I trusted you, Mint.
Okay, cool.
Thanks.
I trusted your call.
Check it out.
If we die, it's on you.
Hot diggity dong.
I'm looking at the pictures now.
Brad's calculations were right on the money.
Always bet on Brad.
See?
I'm smart.
Brad is smart.
We found a plane.
I don't know.
The captain was like, not a good idea.
Technically, we should call this in to port authorities.
As an unreported wreck.
Technically.
Are you sure you don't want to do this the right way?
Wow.
Doki Bird is deciding.
Don't let Doki Bird to sell it.
Look at the look on his face.
I'm gonna be disappointed.
Wait.
Are you saying we shouldn't dive?
Oh.
Why am I Conrad?
Wait, you're Conrad now?
Guys, look.
I think we gotta listen to our experienced, beautiful, smart, and beautiful captain here.
If she says we should do things the right way.
Connie, please.
I didn't bring you on this trip to get laid.
Wait, what?
No, no, no.
It's not.
I'm just saying she's right.
Not because she's beautiful.
I mean, she is beautiful.
But that's like a coincidence.
Oh my god.
I'm Conrad now.
I have to do what I have to do.
Generously, we're diving.
You're the client.
Oh my god.
I think I'm gonna marry a bitch.
I just can't wait.
She's like a Karen for real.
Yeah, I think I'm gonna marry a Karen.
Why did you not say anything?
Why did you say nothing when I asked you?
I'll set up the tanks.
The boys will do the final check.
It's not my call.
Take a look at the camera.
See if you can find anything useful.
Yeah, what the hell is that?
Maybe you should check on your bro.
Yeah, where's the bro?
Where's Brad?
Brad, where are you?
Where are you, Brad?
I wanna look at the binoculars.
The way you like walk and glide around.
I'll find you later.
I'm looking at the binoculars.
I'm looking at the pictures again.
I like the pictures.
I'm an iPad kid.
Oh, that opening.
Okay, we got it.
Can I put it back?
This is like such a tiny ship.
Where could Brad go?
I think he's laying down.
Oh, I'm stuck.
Wait, where am I?
Hey, I'm gonna talk to my girlfriend.
Me too.
Almost got the gear.
Good to go.
You're vibrating.
I'm in this conversation too.
Let me in.
I think we're in good shape.
It's probably not a bad idea.
I'm actually in the conversation.
Hey, JJ.
You alright?
JJ?
Punky Dory.
Gotta say, not too happy with our captain at the moment.
She's right there!
Wait, what?
Who are you deciding?
I'm gonna be annoyed.
Are you gonna be white knight hair?
We paid top dollar to come out here in the middle of nowhere to do whatever the hell we want without any Namby Pambys breathing down our neck.
That's the good old American way.
I'm serious, Connie.
Alright, I'm gonna get these rebreathers set up and then we'll go through the final steps together.
Great.
I'm gonna kick back and enjoy the sights for a little while.
I can't believe the captain didn't even hear that.
I know, me too.
He admits to being a creep!
Oh my god!
He's self-aware!
Why are you vibrating in this place?
Hey, hold on!
I'm trying to go to Brad's!
I wanna talk to him!
I wanna look at the weather!
I'm going to Brad.
Alright.
What's this?
Oh, I turned it off.
Wait, I think I see a picture.
Wait, hold on.
Is this one of those sneaky pictures?
Well, hello.
I found one.
What's this?
What are you looking at?
That told me nothing.
I'm heading over.
I unlocked a premonition.
Oh, that's gonna help us with decisions, remember?
Yeah.
I wanna see so I know that you won't fuck up.
He's gonna be in here.
Where's his premonition?
Wait, that's Brad.
Yeah.
Shouldn't have had that beer.
It doesn't do anything.
What does that mean?
I'm gonna be out.
I'm trying to make a decision!
I'm trying to look at a premonition right now.
I'm making a decision!
Okay.
Brad's like in the bathroom.
I'm gonna be a dick to him.
You're gonna be a dick to my bro?
You're gonna be a dick to yourself?
I hate myself.
You got that whole brainiac thing going on.
That's nothing to sneeze at.
Don't worry, stud.
She's all yours.
Oh!
Why did he do that?
Okay, that's my cue to beat it.
What is this?
What is cologne?
Captain Kiss?
I'm looking at cologne while you're bullying yourself.
Where are you?
Are you in the bathroom?
I was opening the closet.
I can't open it.
There's another room here.
Oh, I'm going in?
Yeah, now I'll talk to my little bro.
What's up?
What are you doing?
Hello, locker.
Oh, I'm going through people's things.
That's really normal.
What's this now?
Oh, I'm looking at the cologne, too.
Fancy.
Good on ya, Alex.
Why am I going through your stuff?
What the hell?
Look, I comfort my bro after you bullied him.
Hey, hey, hey!
I was just snooping a little.
What are you doing?
I was, uh, up to code.
I'm just being normal.
I saw you looking at my cologne.
I took your cologne, actually.
Wait, you took my cologne?
That door doesn't open.
And then we talked to our bro.
Alright, I'm gonna go talk to the captain now.
Captain Kiss.
I'm gonna watch you talk to the captain.
Watch me riz her up.
Hey, girl.
Oh, captain, my captain.
Get out of my cutscene.
You know, we have rules out here for a reason.
You guys gotta respect that.
At least you showed me a little respect.
Even if you're the only one in the group.
Really?
Oh, captain, my captain?
I like it when you're strict.
Hey, I like it when you're strict.
Sometimes I just want to be kept in line, you know what I'm saying?
I don't mind a little submission that way.
Oh my god!
Turn that off.
Turn what off?
That thing where you have to hit on me, like, every two seconds.
I think she likes it.
Oh my god.
Bro.
So, is it working?
Where are you?
Come back to my cutscene.
Do you have brain damage?
Oh, there you are!
These rules are all pretty basic stuff.
How much experience do you have with these kind of dives?
Are you still talking to me?
Yeah!
Pretty much an authority back home.
If you move around, does he move?
Then why don't you want to follow the rules for unreported wrecks?
For all you know, this could be a war group.
This derby hit would be illegal anymore.
I'm gonna be playful.
You know, you're even more toxic than me right now.
And I'm gonna get wasted.
You've literally never spoken to a woman before in your life, have you?
You've only talked to your sister.
Damn!
It's my turn to talk to her now.
Alright, you talk to her, you talk to her.
I'm watching, I'm watching.
Are you talking to her?
No, I'm stuck.
Wait, the conversation!
Wait, I'm stuck!
I'm stuck!
I can't progress!
No!
What's going on?
We broke the game!
You broke the game!
Fix it!
Talk to our sister!
Oh, wait, wait, wait, there you go, there you go, there you go.
Alright, try again, try again.
No, I can't move!
You can't move!
Wait, wait, there's something over here.
Hold on, I'm gonna go look at it.
Yeah, yeah, start the next scene, Min!
Start the next scene!
Oh!
She said something.
Oh, what's going on?
Oh my god, I'm looking at her driver's license!
I'm such a freak!
It looks like it might be bogus.
How do we start the next scene?
Um, hold on...
I just doubted her credentials.
Wait, she's your sister, what do you mean you doubted her credentials?
No, no, no!
Oh my god, you're still standing there!
How do we start the game?
I can't!
Hold on, I'm gonna push you, I'm gonna push you, I'm gonna push you.
Put me into the boat!
I can't push you, I can't push you!
Hold on, I'm gonna go talk to my sister!
Oh my god!
Yo, Alex!
Don't get out here!
Oh my god, it's fixed!
...
It's all that CO2 that you'd normally just exhale into the water, and instead, it gets totally reused.
Then it repeats.
Oh yeah, we have to do it.
We won't die, we won't die here.
O2 check done.
Okay.
I don't think I'm diving.
I'm not suited up for...
Are you gonna be my girlfriend now?
You gotta check your O2 first.
Oh, maybe.
Oh, okay.
Thanks for being playful.
I'm gonna be playful.
I'd like to take you underwater.
That's my sis you're talking about.
What the fuck?
You were like creeping on the captain earlier.
Jesus, why is he so loud?
This is the line, this is the line.
When I was looking at the dive cam, I saw this huge hole in the tail.
Kabooey.
Kabooey?
That's your way into the plane.
Nice work, man.
Thanks, Conrad.
Okay, you little clownfishes.
I'm gonna go see what Fliss is up to.
Oh my god, leave her alone!
Right after defending you, sissy, you're like, Anyway, I'm gonna hit Rob up the captain again.
I'm gonna beat you.
Are those two going in or what?
Wait, what's the baton stick or the camera?
We don't need a camera.
We're gonna need that baton.
Alright, kids!
Good to go!
I don't know what this is.
Just remember the rules, please!
A bang stick?
Haha.
You ever have to use one?
On a shark?
Nope.
Okay, are you going in?
Oh, you're deciding.
Take the camera or Julia?
Why is the lighting really dark all of a sudden?
Oh!
I can't!
What's happening?
Alright.
Please better not be pissy this whole trip.
Why is the lighting so dark all of a sudden?
And she should remember who's signing the checks.
Very large checks.
How to buy us out of this little wiggle room with the rules.
Oh, it's fixed.
It's fixed.
Oh my god.
What's happening?
Oh, you guys are going in.
I don't know.
Why is she just looking at us like that?
I think she's nervous.
Whoa, these are high tech.
I got a bang stick.
You got a...
I got a stick that... that bangs.
Uh-huh.
That's why.
Is that why you took it?
Julia liked it last night.
Whoa.
Wait, so am I doing nothing?
Nice.
Alright, it's up to you, Dokie.
Wait a minute.
You were Brad, now Conrad, and now Julia?
Like, pick a lane.
There's no way.
Oh my god, there's dead bodies in here.
Wait, there's dead bodies in here.
Is this Madon?
No, this is a plane.
It's a plane?
Yeah.
Why are we going in here?
Oh my god.
Because we found this wreck.
Here we go.
Down we go.
Why are we diving when it's the sun setting?
Should we just wait for day?
Whoa.
You good?
Are you still talking to her?
No, I'm watching the cutscene.
Oh shit, the sharks.
Uh oh.
You're gonna need to use your bag stick.
The boat looks really far away.
I'm gonna be flipped.
Okay.
Alright, you know what?
Sure.
I'll give you one.
Wait, are you on the boat?
Yeah, I'm flipped.
I'm underwater!
No way!
We know why somebody died.
Let's swim around a little and find a way in.
Oh my god.
One of the pictures showed an opening.
Doki Bird is flipped.
Why am I?
Why am I Julia?
All of a sudden.
You're the Karen.
Oh my god.
Here I go.
I'm going inside the ship.
Oh my god.
Comrade wants to invest in my business.
What?
Okay.
Oh, I want Conrad's money.
Oh, I almost just killed Julia, I think.
Be careful.
It could be dangerous.
Oh my god, that scared me.
Oh my god, I just noticed something was wrong.
Wait, what do you mean?
Explore the plane.
Can I just take a second to say, holy shit, Alex, we did it.
Let's see.
Wait for the others to return from the dive.
Oh, you are doing...
Why are you doing the action part?
I don't know.
Why am I doing the action part?
I'm just chilling.
I'm just chilling on the ship right now.
Wait, what was that?
What was that?
Hold on.
Oh, I can talk to you.
You can?
Yeah.
Hello.
I didn't hear...
Do you guys hear me?
Oh, I heard it.
I heard it.
We're looking at a hole.
Ignore her.
Ignore Fliss.
Julia, leave it.
You're saying ignore me?
Not worth it.
That pipe's pretty tight.
She's angry.
I'm gonna call you guys again.
I'm not even...
You think you can just ignore me like that?
Ring, ring, ring.
Don't be such a gonad, Alex.
I'll be fine.
Julia?
Gonad?
Seriously?
Oh, you're gonna ghost me now?
Yeah, I'm doing risky business, okay?
Don't be such a gonad, Doki God.
You think I'm not gonna spam call you now?
Oh, my God.
I think she might die.
Uh-oh.
Don't worry.
I'm calling you guys again.
Don't...
Uh-oh.
Oh, there's an octopus in here!
Don't be such a gonad.
Okay, if you guys die, stop.
You guys die.
I got it.
Uh-oh.
Let's see.
What's this?
Uh-oh.
Those are the photos.
I'm lost.
Oh, he's here.
You're a good boyfriend.
He gave me oxygen.
Oh, nice.
Now you're gonna kill fucking Alex.
You're gonna kill Alex.
I spent so much...
I spent a lot of difficult decisions to get Alex to where he's at.
And now you're just gonna kill him off.
I know what I'm doing.
I know what I'm doing, okay?
I don't need a lifeguard.
She is so rude.
I told you.
She's such a Karen.
I hope she dies.
This... this... oh.
You found a secret.
Yeah.
Yeah, because I did risky business.
I told you.
Oh, I'm lagging.
Oh, my God.
What's happening?
Okay.
Search...
Go easy on the booze.
I'm gonna... I'm bullying Brad right now.
See?
It's easy to bully him.
Well, let's avoid that tube.
Here we go.
What do you know, Brad?
He doesn't know anything.
He's Brad.
It's a loser.
Okay.
All right.
Oh, the ship is around World War II.
Yeah.
Right?
Because...
You hear that?
What is that?
Let's check it out.
Oh, God.
Uh-oh.
What is that?
I'm using my bang stick.
What am I banging?
You're welcome.
I got you that bang stick.
I did it.
I used it.
Did you like it?
Oh, my God.
It's a dead man.
She's banging.
I'm banging.
I'm investigating the ghost.
What happened?
An eel attacked me.
All I get is the ship with fucking Conrad.
You get to explore.
I have to deal with fucking Conrad.
Got it.
Plane crashed not high on my list of ways to perish.
I'm just saying.
Maybe you should have picked Brad instead.
Oh, there's another guy.
Wait.
Hold on.
Let me investigate him, please.
Investigate.
I'm trying to turn around.
So, are you beached?
Easy now.
This stuff's been down here a long time.
I'm piloting the plane.
Oh, my God.
I'm piloting.
Should I hit him?
Should I hit on Conrad?
Yeah.
Do I do it?
I'm gonna hit on Conrad.
Do it.
Don't touch anything else, please.
Oh, my God.
Conrad said he'll invest in my business.
You're in.
I'm in.
Good God.
Oh, my God.
My business is gonna flourish now.
I like how the girl was just like, it's not like we're gonna ruin the ship or anything.
And here I go ruining the ship.
Yeah.
I like how I'm also being your wingman right now.
Oh, he's holding something.
His wife and kids.
Oh, my God.
He's in.
How to turn this on?
Am I just waiting on you guys to return to the ship?
I think so.
I'm just literally waiting.
Guys, hurry up.
Didn't what's his name say that like wrecking, wreck, like diving was his thing?
Oh, there he is.
There's pirates.
What?
Uh-oh.
What do you mean there's pirates?
Like, yo ho.
That's not the Coast Guard.
Uh-oh.
Wait.
What do you mean?
Oh, I'm stuck.
I think.
I'm stuck.
Hold on.
I think.
Do I need to come back?
You should call me back.
I think there's pirates.
You should call and say like, hey.
Get up here.
Oh, no.
Oh, what's going on?
There's pirates.
Fucked up.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
They're moving the ship.
They're moving the plane.
Oh, my God.
They're destroying it.
Wait.
What?
They're destroying the plane.
Grab that.
Oh, my God.
There's a shark.
Who's that?
I don't know.
Shark?
Now there's a shark?
Something cold.
Come at me, shark.
It's a great weak shark.
Not interested in us.
Let's go.
Wow.
Your guy is a doctor.
Oh, my God.
And he's a doctor.
And also a marine biologist.
How does he know everything?
Okay, Mint?
We're coming back.
Mint...
Comrade's a bitch.
Okay.
He's antagonizing the pirates.
What?
Why are you fidgeting?
Oh, my God.
I think Alex is trying to propose under here.
I wanted to bring something up with you, but...
In the water.
I think he's trying to propose.
You're a pirate.
Oh, my God.
What?
What's going on?
Oh my god.
I don't know what to say.
I'm just gonna say nothing.
What's going on?
Oh, he gave up.
Okay.
Seriously?
What's going on?
What's going on, Alex?
What is going on down there?
There's so many things going on!
My relationship with Alex is going down.
My relationship with Conrad is also going down.
It's nice to know we're both sabotaging each other's relationships.
I know.
It's fine.
I can make it up.
I make it up in tenfold.
Whatever you say to her doesn't mean anything.
Oh my god.
Conrad's fucking... Oh!
Conrad's barbecuing.
And he's fucked up.
I'm more like you.
What do you mean?
I'm controlling the captain!
I don't even get to make a choice.
I'm going.
Fuck it.
He's like, we gotta decompress.
She's heroic.
Oh, and Alex is just like chilling in the water.
Wait.
I'm like stuck on... Okay.
Alright, Conrad, it's going down.
Guys, I'm messing up Conrad after all the hard work I did flirting.
Hey, JJ, don't worry about it.
What's going on?
Why did they go at sunset?
You set money in the...
Yeah, what's that money for?
There was a little mishap with the barbecue.
I'm all true stick now.
Jesus, looks like the whole boat was lit up.
Yeah, for real.
It was Conrad's fault.
So, why are you paying the ocean?
Yeah, why are you paying the ocean?
A fishing boat came by and got damaged on the dive line.
Oh, that's what happened.
Yeah, they were being a little surly about it, so Conrad made it rain and they pissed off.
Wow.
Whatever.
They didn't even take the money.
What I want to know is, what did you guys find?
Yeah, what did you find?
We found the plane.
And it is huge.
That's cool stuff.
Yeah, like eels and sharks apparently.
We did not leave it as pristine as we could.
What?
Why?
The dive line actually.
Yeah, the dive line.
How bad?
Uh, there's no cockpit anymore for starters.
Well, that's just fucking perfect.
Well, that's not our fault.
Like, we didn't do that.
That's yours.
You're the captain of the ship.
Well, how is it my fault?
Yeah.
No, I'm just saying.
Conrad fucking threw money on the ship.
Oh, hey.
Did we do okay?
Yeah, how we do, man?
Oh, we do.
He's laughing at us.
You're getting to know these intrepid adventurers then.
Yeah.
Alex and his little brother Brad trying to swim with the big fish.
Are we doing okay?
Both seem out of their depth.
Yeah.
And Julia.
Julia.
The love of Alex's life.
I don't know after what meant to.
I don't know about that.
It's not one diving trip that's going to destroy their relationship.
I don't know what to do.
And then there's Captain Fliss.
Strong.
Forthright.
Stubborn.
Do I detect a spark between her and Conrad?
I don't know what I'm doing.
I forced them to like each other.
Wait, we have a special feature unlocked.
What's the special feature?
And some I think they may regret.
His jacket looks like a giraffe.
Like a cantaloupe skin.
Apparently we made some decisions that they're going to regret, lady.
No.
I mean, they regret.
I think you made some decisions that they're going to regret.
No.
It was like traveling through time.
Oh, shit.
Well, it was like traveling through time and accidentally ending up in a dimension where the past is underwater and like everything is covered in particles.
I think Julia is stupid.
Sharks?
It was like a reef.
It was like traveling to the past.
I'm stupid.
It was like traveling to the past, but everything is underwater.
And everything is covered in particles.
I can't believe there's sharks in the ocean.
Did you know that?
Sounds like you've had some experience with this kind of phenomenon.
Yeah.
I've been studying it for years.
I'll go look for them.
I didn't even meet...
Oh, wait.
I'm Brad now.
Wait, who are you?
I'm watching...
Oh, I'm Julia.
I'm Julia.
You're Julia?
You got the short end of the stick.
You're like an open book.
I'm going to eavesdrop.
I can read you from a mile away.
Something's up.
Oh, wait.
Why are you in my cutscene?
I can see you.
I don't know what's going on.
Are you happy?
Don't fuck this up.
Privacy?
Oh, he's telling you to leave.
Okay.
Don't worry.
I'll watch from here.
Yeah.
Maybe.
I think so.
You think so?
Or you know so?
Oh, my God.
Is everything okay?
I see you in the car.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Is everything okay?
Man.
What are you going to do?
Man, did you ruin a ten year relationship?
Can we go from here?
That's fine.
It's fine.
He's just staring.
Look.
When we get home, we can talk about some stuff.
What do you mean, we can talk about some stuff?
But, I mean, it's not like we're breaking up.
Man, what are you doing?
There are a whole eight to a relationship.
Okay.
Oh my god, this guy acts like an AI for real.
Brad is right there!
Yeah, I got distracted.
Let's go get him.
Wait, are they like making out downstairs?
Are they?
I did that, you're welcome, man.
I worked so hard on this for you.
Jesus Christ, Conrad.
What's going on?
Sorry to interrupt your seven seconds in heaven.
Oh yeah, the beers.
I was just getting them now.
What?
We're not gonna address that?
We're just gonna...
Oh man, you worked so hard and I brought it home run.
I brought it home for you.
No, no.
You tried to sabotage it after I worked so hard for it.
It's a seven year relationship.
If you weren't going strong, they would...
My intervention would mean nothing.
Maybe we can figure out why the plane was out of here.
What happened underwater, man?
Oh,
search for the nav pad.
Got the nav pad, DivemasterJ?
Oh, no, not yet.
What's that?
What's the nav pad?
Oh, this thing.
You alright?
You seem kind of preoccupied.
I'm grabbing it!
Wait, is this it?
What is this?
I'm talking to my brother.
What am I doing?
Oh, I'm looking at the pictures.
Wow!
Ooh, fishies!
Air Rescue Service.
Conwin Islands.
Oh, that's me.
That's me.
Oh, I can't wait.
What are you doing?
We're having a conversation with everybody.
Except for Julia.
Oh, sorry.
I was looking at pictures.
Oh.
What?
Yeah.
Oh, I thought it was a tablet.
What?
See, I did that.
I did that.
What did you do?
Oh.
I'm making out with Alex right now.
Yeah.
Right here.
Wait, you kissed Alex?
Yeah.
You fixed it!
You fixed the problem you caused.
Well, yeah.
No, I did it.
I caused that.
I mean, I caused the relationship to flourish.
You did cause it.
It's blooming.
If you did decompress too fast, then you should go easy on the beer.
Alex, I'm fine.
I think if I got the Benz, I would know by now.
I think I'm fine.
Not always.
Sometimes the Benz can be super delayed.
It could be hours or a day or two.
What's the Benz?
Yeah, what's the Benz?
It's when you come up from a dive too fast.
Oh, yeah.
Decompression sickness.
Oh.
Nerd.
Wow!
That was in all caps!
It's pretty serious.
Divers get sick and die from decompression sickness every year.
And that is why the good Dr. Conrad says drink them if you got them, cause either you're fine or you're gonna want a little something.
I don't think I want to listen to Dr. Conrad.
Yeah.
I think Alex is an actual doctor.
Take orders from this guy.
Just drink a beer.
Oh, no.
I have to make the decision?
Beer o'clock?
Nerd!
Oh, my God!
If she dies, it's on you!
Manchurian gold.
Literally docked.
There's doctors or there's...
Beer o'clock!
Those are coordinates, alright.
Let me listen to my brother who throws money at problems.
Hey, I'm not Julia.
You'll be Julia eventually, too.
Wow.
I had to be Julia to take care of the mess you made.
Reckless.
All of you.
Excuse me?
I told you to leave everything down there alone.
Oh, come on.
We've been through this already.
I'm not talking about the law.
Oh.
Talking about curse.
Superstition?
Is that it?
Really?
The dead don't sleep well in these waters.
May sound silly enough to you all, but I was raised on this shit and it sticks.
Ooh.
Are you gonna call her like a liar?
Yeah.
Maybe it's not Julia being a Karen.
Maybe it's you.
No respect for anyone else's tradition.
I just don't like Julia.
I don't want anyone else to like Julia either.
You think you can scavenge down there and it makes no difference, but every single thing you bring back has an essence.
It's like a ghost you invite to the surface.
Here we go.
Oh my god, you're so rude.
You never think about much of anything.
You're so rude.
You made her rude.
People drown in these waters and you have to respect their resting place.
Damn straight.
Brett, you got a fun ghost story, right?
Ooh.
Oh, I do?
Do you?
Come on, say a ghost story.
Yeah, yeah.
Once upon a time.
Let's hear it.
We can all use a good show.
Yeah, come on, let's hear it.
Ooh.
Yeah, let's hear it.
Let's hear it.
I bet you can spin a good yarn.
It's kind of messed up, actually.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Scare away, little bro.
Okay.
Here goes.
This story is true.
It happened right near here.
In an old lighthouse.
Classic setup.
Wait, true story?
Where'd you hear this?
I thought Alex already knew the story.
Why are you deciding?
Like you don't know what's going on.
A creepy old guy.
Down by the dockside, I found an ancient old man.
Skin like a leather book.
Why did your wig go up?
He told me his secrets.
You're just a dolly.
Here we go.
Okay.
The lighthouse stood atop an atoll.
Isolated from the rest of the world.
A lone beacon in the night.
Because it was a spooky lighthouse.
The lighthouse keeper would hear the waves pounding the rocky shore.
One misty morning, he comes upon a woman.
Covered in blood.
Women?
He hurries to her aid and she falls into his arms.
Sobbing.
As he hurries her back to the lighthouse, he asks where she's from.
He doesn't waste any time.
Smooth.
Conrad, shut up.
Yeah, shut up.
Shut up.
I live here.
In the lighthouse.
My parents are upstairs right now.
Dun dun dun.
The lighthouse keeper says, that isn't so.
Of course, he's lived there alone for years.
And the woman becomes hysterical.
His pupils are so dire.
So, they go to the top of the lighthouse.
And there, splayed out on the floor, is a man and a woman brutally murdered with an axe.
Oh my god.
I mean, do people even use axes anymore?
I'm just reporting the facts.
Chopped up into little tiny giblets.
Giblets?
It's a good story, man.
It's a very good story.
You know, sometimes you have to embellish the facts a little.
Wow, you tell a better story then.
You're literally the one that asked for the story.
Shut up.
Come on, Zach.
Say it was you.
You did it.
I'm gonna do relax.
The woman says, it was my husband.
And she turns to the closet.
Says, he's in there.
Ah, yes, the husband.
And that's why I've always been a little weary of marriage.
So, the lighthouse keeper creeps into the closet.
No, Alex, no.
Alex is putting his head in his hands right now.
Sure enough, there's a man inside.
What?
But he's cut his own throat.
Ugh.
He looks closer to see the dead man's face in the dark.
Closer.
Oh my god, the uncanny.
It's his own face.
And then its eyes bulge out and screams.
Whoa.
What the fuck?
What the hell?
Where did that come from?
I think Brad is possessed.
Yeah.
I think he's possessed.
Holy shit.
Oh, come on.
That wasn't scary.
Okay.
Do better next time, Brad.
Don't you pick better prompts next time.
Wow.
I saw you scream.
I saw the screams around me.
One more beard before hitting the hay.
What regular issues are these?
Standard issue.
Regulatory.
I don't think I trust Conrad with anything.
I don't either.
Who invited this guy?
He's like that type of guy that's like, I'm going to tell my dad what you said about me.
Yeah.
Do we not notice the storm that's incoming?
And we're on a tiny little boat that's going to capsize.
Uh oh.
I think we're in trouble.
Now there's a storm.
Oh my god.
I think we fucked up.
I think we messed up, yeah.
Yeah.
Uh oh.
You think those guys are going to come back and take our ship?
The fishermen?
Yeah.
What the fuck?
Where did they come from?
Did you bring stuff up to the ship?
It was the tablet.
You brought a tablet?
That's why we looked at the gold.
Uh oh.
They have opposable thumbs.
They're fine.
We're fine.
They're looking over us.
Is that the treasure?
That looks human.
Wait.
Are they the pirates?
Oh my god.
He's got a gun.
What do I...
I tried right triggering but it didn't let me do anything.
I think he's about to die.
What did you do?
Did you not do your quick time effect?
I couldn't figure out where I was supposed to go.
Oh my god.
I did my quick time.
Look at where it's gotten you.
You're still trapped too.
Because you failed the quick time.
From his head.
Where's Brad?
Oh.
There's Fliss.
Oh there they are.
That's the fisherman.
That's the pirate.
I told you.
This guy means business.
Why did you piss him off?
It's your fault they're here.
Because you pissed him off.
You threw money at them.
It's your fault.
I can't control Conrad.
Oh you're deciding.
Okay Conrad.
What's your genius idea this time?
What is she doing?
She's crying on his...
What is happening?
What are you doing?
I don't know.
Oh.
But I missed my event.
And it's my fault.
I'm trying to...
I'm trying to pee myself right now.
Did you miss it?
You missed it.
There was no...
Okay.
Oh no.
I have to choose.
You do it then.
You gotta see what I meant.
Yeah.
I did it.
And you do it.
I had to choose between Conrad and Julia.
Okay let me try this again.
Let me try this again.
Oh my god.
This really is... How did you do it?
This is how we're gonna die.
How did you do it?
I right trigger and then I pull with the right.
I'm trying but let me pull.
Just use your right stick.
I swear.
I'm doing it.
I swear to god.
Fliss will never be...
Alright.
You fucking do it again.
I'll do it.
Okay watch this.
It's so easy.
How did you do that?
How did you?
How did you do it?
Okay your turn.
Never mind.
Why is he bleeding?
Where's Brad?
Oh no.
I gotta turn the sound down again on this thing.
It's so bad.
I don't know what you said.
How did you guys do it?
Wow you let Fliss die because you couldn't un-gag her.
I don't know what you said.
How did you?
How did you do it?
Hahaha.
What's the good news?
Oh my god Conrad.
What?
How's that good news?
Oh wait.
I'm gonna untie him.
We have to get free.
Right now.
Yeah come here.
Come here Conrad.
Put on some pants man.
Wait did you have to hold?
You hold down the right stick?
Yes.
Why did you say that?
I told you.
Look.
I didn't realize you had to hold it.
Who's the gamer now?
You failed your quick time event twice.
What?
It was just the gun.
Oh my god this guy.
Sit back down idiot.
Wouldn't they think it's weird that we're un-gagged?
I know right?
Oh what the?
I succeeded my quick time event.
I did mine.
I stopped you from getting beat up.
Conrad kind of deserves it though right?
Wait Conrad's gone.
Bye Conrad.
Bye.
Wait are you getting taken away?
Yeah.
I'm seeing what's happening.
Oh shit.
Oh what's happening?
Oh so like the guy was like you're fucked.
Oh and then Conrad gets punched.
I saw that.
Oh where is he going?
Oh my god they're taking him out.
I mean if they kill Conrad that's okay right?
They're beating Conrad.
We don't care about that right?
I'm making Julia scared.
Okay what do you want?
What are they talking about?
Okay I didn't say fuckers.
Wait they're actually killing Conrad!
You did this!
I just said what do you want?
Y'all you pissed him off.
Uh oh.
Oh wait they have the gun?
Oh no it's a knife.
Oh my god they're gonna kill Conrad.
I'm gonna say nothing.
Don't say anything.
Oh my god they're gonna kill him.
If I say something I feel like they're gonna get agitated.
I got it.
What is that?
I saved Conrad.
You're welcome.
No why would you want to save Conrad?
Cause you told me to.
You literally told me to.
Oh I got a cuticle cutter.
I'm cutting the ropes.
I'm gonna say nothing again.
Oh they're coming back.
I feel like if I say something they would agitate him more.
Oh he's coming back.
Hey welcome back Conrad.
I'm back.
I saved Conrad just for you Min.
Cause you love Conrad so much.
Yeah I wanna see him get us killed even in a different way.
I feel like that.
I feel like you have higher survivability.
Oh my god.
He's dead.
Alex why did you get up so slowly?
You have no restraint.
Shut the fuck up.
Just open the door.
Julia breaking heads.
Not the other way around.
Fliss sure seems to be getting buddy-buddy with him.
Wait why is Fliss...
What's going on your end?
I'm with Conrad and Alex.
Oh you're with us?
You're Conrad!
No I'm Alex!
I'm Conrad!
No.
But I'm sure he's fine.
These guys probably just want money or something.
Man if I let Conrad die here I wouldn't have to be forced to play Conrad.
Everyone has to play Conrad at least once.
Everyone has to feel the shame of being Conrad.
I thought by saving Conrad you would have to deal with Conrad later.
No they knew that you liked him so much.
They let you stay with him.
I literally saved him for you!
What did they do to Julia?
Are you okay?
Are you okay little Julia?
Hey hey are you okay?
Are you okay little girl?
They didn't touch me.
Okay.
They asked about our parents.
What?
Oh.
It's going to be a hostage situation.
Yeah.
There you go.
Nice.
What if everybody dies but Conrad?
Should we do that?
Make it a bit worse?
Our mission is to keep Conrad alive!
Keep Conrad alive!
Does he just count it?
Yeah.
What is he counting?
Oh I think he's seeing the time between the lightning and the thunder.
Oh.
That's smart.
Yeah he is.
Wow.
Spoken like a true Conrad.
Nerd.
We came here on a boat.
Maybe we can take it.
Yeah.
Yeah it's a speed boat.
The main guy here.
He's got a gun.
Uh oh.
At least one of us can get on their boat.
Get some help.
We're gonna get on that boat.
Right.
Okay I'm gonna say nothing.
So you have to get on the boat.
What?
Oh what do you think?
She's asking you.
I can get out through the window.
We gotta break these off first.
Oh.
That's you.
We're gonna get through the window.
Yeah good call!
Good call!
No Conrad!
Conrad the goat!
I said nothing!
So you don't see me sneaking.
Okay sneaking mission.
Alright be sneaky.
Oh no please.
I don't wanna be Conrad anymore.
Three.
No!
Be Conrad!
Uh oh.
Go Conrad go!
Go Conrad.
Oh my god.
Go Conrad go!
Is this me?
Is this my quick time event?
Oh shoot.
Ah!
Don't fuck this up!
I got it!
Get the scissors!
Don't fuck this up!
I might have fucked it up a little bit.
What did you do?
I'm doing my quick time event right now!
I thought it said X.
Get out!
Oh Bradley!
I'm escaping.
Get out of here.
Get out of here Conrad.
Go live.
Live a long life.
I got it.
I did it.
I think Liz is gonna die.
I have a hostage.
I went escape.
I didn't grab a knife.
What?
What do you mean?
What did you do?
I have a guy hostage.
I'm gonna kill him.
Oh my god!
There you are like Spiderman!
Goodbye!
Our Conrad's leaving!
Wait!
I think they're gonna shoot me!
Attack him!
I don't care about you Julie!
I tried.
I really did try.
No!
Stop it!
Oh my god.
Is he dead?
Did you dodge it?
Conrad's escaped!
We did it!
Yeah!
Conrad's gone!
We did it!
Conrad lived!
I live!
Thank god I was condarreded during the quick time of that.
I saved you!
I could've shielded Julia!
But I saved you instead!
Yeah!
Yeah, because you know we need her to save Conrad!
He's gone!
Oh my god!
He's gone on his little big adventure!
He's just Conrad!
Oh my god, we did it!
Guys, apparently...
People were like, people usually never save Conrad.
He usually dies there!
Conrad deserves better.
Conrad?
We did it guys!
He's gonna be the hero in the end!
Oh my god, the sound effects.
Can I turn the sound effects down real quick?
Okay, I'm turning them down again.
Oh my god.
I can't believe it.
They're like, usually Conrad gets shot.
I don't know how you guys...
Um, we have our priorities straight.
Absolutely.
Okay, I'm good.
The only two people who saved Conrad.
Willingly.
Not for like, completionist sake.
Okay.
We're hostages.
Cool, what do we do now?
She's like, looking for him.
What?
Why do you make all the important decisions?
Connie!
Alright!
Shut the fuck up!
Why can't you wipe the blood off your face?
What?
Why is she looking like this?
We were only talking!
There's no harm in just talking.
You wanna talk?
Yeah.
We practically won the game.
Cheat the body of cow.
We have one survivor, so we basically won.
I'm just gonna say it.
Flitz has gotta be in on this.
Jeez, guys.
What?
We travel in the same watch.
We're in the same place as in the bus.
I bet you told them about the Manchurian gold.
They're in cahoots.
They don't even know about the gold.
Why did you tell them about the gold?
Oh my god.
Well, Flitz, what do you have to say?
I can't believe what I'm hearing.
I just lost everything I have.
And this is what you think?
What do you mean you lost everything?
This is a trap.
I lost my boat.
This is my boat.
Son of a asshole.
Put a cork in it.
Oh my god.
Oh, dang it.
That quick time event was to save Julia?
Oh, Flitz again.
Cahoots, cahoots, cahoots.
What happened to Brad?
Talk to this guy.
Brad is right next to me.
Why not?
Why won't you talk to me?
Move the gun.
Take the gun off of us.
We should save Julia next.
Save all of us.
We'll save the worst people.
They can have each other.
Julia and her brother.
What's going on, Alex?
How bad is the storm?
We need to keep an eye on Flitz.
She's helping them.
She's gotta be.
You really think she is?
Why are you like this?
Why are you like this, Alex?
What do you want?
I don't know.
I'm just talking to you, man.
Should I provoke them, you guys?
Or what should I do?
I literally was compliant.
I'm not.
You're just a little kitten, ain't you?
A kitten.
A Discord kitten.
You wanna test that theory?
Come here.
Come on.
Talk to me.
No.
Look, I'm being compliant.
Look, he's being a little baby.
That's enough.
No talking.
What the fuck are you doing down there?
We need to try and make sure we don't die.
Where are you?
Oh, you're with Flitz.
You're antagonizing the fucking other pirates.
Oh my god.
Quick time event.
Quick time.
I got both of mine.
Did you?
I got mine, too.
Okay.
Alright.
I doubt it.
The water.
Oh, my Titanic moment.
At least you're downstairs.
I'm upstairs.
Our ship is flooding.
We're gonna drown.
Get out.
Wait, what's going on?
The ship is flooding.
Oh my god.
There you guys are.
We're drowning.
I'm gonna hold on.
I'm gonna rescue Brad instead.
Get out of here, Brad.
Get out of here.
I hope you guys are okay, because I had a choice to save, but I chose not to.
Hey.
Move it.
We're gonna drown.
Now.
Oh my god.
Why was there so much water in there?
Because we're in the ocean.
The water's not supposed to go in the boat.
I had to help Brad.
Good job looking after number one.
Real smooth.
Great leadership, Flitz.
What did I do?
I literally saved us by...
Brad can't help himself.
He's a little baby.
Uh-oh.
Oh my god.
We found the ship.
We found Madonne.
Yeah.
There's Madonne.
There it is.
Oh my god.
Get in there.
Whoa.
Oh.
There's Madonne.
The man.
That was the man of him.
The man of Madonne.
Yeah.
That's the man.
Oh my god.
Wait.
That wasn't Conrad.
You don't think, right?
No, because...
I think it was Conrad.
Everyone's still alive.
Yeah.
We did it.
We're keeping people alive.
I think he's disappointed.
He's disappointed in us.
I think he wanted Conrad to die.
Yeah.
You appear to have saved somebody.
A bold move that paid off.
What do you mean?
Conrad.
Yeah.
Does this make the rest of your group more vulnerable?
I would have done it too if it would have been me.
Yeah.
It was a quick time event.
I don't think you would have.
I did all my quick time events.
Most of them.
The kind-hearted creature I am, I'd like to offer you some forewarning of what's to come.
Do you want to see it?
Tempted?
Ooh.
Oh.
We can decide.
Ooh.
Wait.
Do you want to know or not?
I want to know.
Okay.
Let's know.
I got to make a decision.
Yeah.
In agreement.
Clue it is.
Yeah.
The Merchant of Venice, Act 2, Scene 7.
The Prince of Morocco pulls a scroll from the eye of a skull and reads, All that glisters is not gold.
Glisters?
Often have you heard that told.
What the fuck does that mean?
I don't...
What?
Anyway.
That wasn't a hint.
That's not even a bit.
It's barely a riddle.
I presume you'll be good to get back to your story.
What?
But here's the thing.
Everything may not be entirely as it seems.
And he quoted Smash Mouth.
All that glisters is gold.
Probably shouldn't have said that.
Oh, don't be greedy.
Mint, don't be greedy.
I'm not.
It's you.
Did you get the tablet?
I had to to progress.
I think.
Oh, yeah, I did.
You're Julia now.
Oh, no.
You're Fliss.
Oh, I'm Fliss now.
Okay, this is my first time being Fliss.
Oh, no.
Now I'm Julia.
Now to fix the relationship you've ruined.
Like I said.
If they were truly happy for those seven years, my little tiny decisions did nothing.
But how many tiny decisions did you make?
There was like...
No decisions.
Why are we going to that ship?
Why can't we stay in our little ship?
What is that?
Oh, what'd they find?
It's a dynamite, isn't it?
What?
I don't think so.
What was that?
Why did they suddenly decide to search in there?
I know.
That's what I'm saying.
Why can't we just stay in our tiny ship?
Oh, it's an engine part.
Oh.
Come on, Julia.
Oh, apparently it was sinking.
What the hell is wrong with me?
Yeah, that's what I said.
And you were like, we're in the ocean.
How was I supposed to know we were sinking?
I thought just water got in.
Oh, my God.
We're all going to die in here.
Yeah, we're going to die in the ship of Madon.
But we know Brad would live in the bathroom here.
No, that was the bathroom of the other boat.
No, it was the bathroom of this boat.
No, I don't think so.
Right?
It was blue.
The ship is blue.
Oh, we're walking now.
Oh, we are.
I was going to say stay here.
Hey, remember you can walk faster, LB.
Oh, LB, LB.
I'm walking, I'm walking.
What's here?
I'm walking here.
I got a thing.
What is this?
Guard duty.
Oh, he's watching me.
He's watching you.
Hey, I was reading that.
Yeah, stop reading.
This guy sucks.
You're supposed to be walking.
I'm walking barefoot.
I'm doing my job.
I'm going to get tetanus.
Oh, who are you walking to?
This guy?
Oh, I walk...
Oh, oh.
He pushed me too.
Okay, my bad, my bad, my bad.
We're walking, we're walking.
Apparently, we can't even walk right.
Here we go.
Oh, no, your little bracelet.
Oh, my God, no.
No, my bracelet.
That's like $100,000.
Daddy bought it for me.
That's like real gold.
What's wrong with your head?
Oh, that's a dead body.
Am I able to walk?
Am I walking?
Oh, I am.
Oh, wait, oh, yeah, we're walking.
Oh, I got pushed back.
Sorry, I walked the wrong way.
Are you okay?
You look a little worried.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
Oh, Scooby, what do we do?
Scooby, Scooby, what do we do?
Oh, gosh.
Oh, Shaggy, I don't know.
I don't know about this, Shaggy.
All right, let's go.
Raggy, Raggy, I don't know about this, Raggy.
I don't know about this, Raggy.
Oh, wait.
Wait, what is that?
What is that?
Hey, move.
I want to see what the poster says.
The Mask of Madness.
If you dare to look death in the eye, now showing in the mess hall.
Whoa.
Are you...
Do you see what I'm seeing?
I'm in the dormitories.
What are you seeing?
I don't know.
I'm just walking.
Well, I can...
There's an item here.
Grab it.
Are these guys going to do this now?
Why...
Oh, there's Miller.
Miller.
Why are they, like, not...
They're not supervising us anymore.
I know.
Where are they?
Oh, I can also look at it.
What is it?
It says, Miller.
Miller.
I'm waiting for you here.
I'm at the other side.
Okay.
I'm coming.
Master Miller?
Oh, no.
Oh, there's Alex.
Oh.
They're slow.
Dude, just as slow as we are.
I don't think LB works.
I'll be honest.
I don't feel any faster.
I don't think so, though.
I don't think it works either.
Why is every...
Why is he moving like he's one of us?
Like...
I don't think he's moving like an NPC.
What were we supposed to do?
Oh!
There's rats!
Rats?
Where are the rats, Rocky?
I didn't see any rats.
Oh, there's something over here.
Oh.
What's this?
It's an internal memorandum.
Is it going to give us a hint?
You're covering Patterson's guard duties tomorrow.
He is sick again.
Conveniently, it's always when he has guard duties.
And hold 3A.
First is 24 o'clock.
Check the chart.
Start for rotation.
Oh!
Again?
You found a secret!
Maybe that'll help us.
This is the third time this week.
None of us like it down there.
Maybe Patterson should buck up.
Get...
Just get on it.
Okay.
Maybe it'll...
Oh, hello.
Maybe it'll, like, help us.
Hello.
I want to look at the secret, too.
Yeah, go look at the secret.
I want to look at it.
How do I look at the secret?
It might be in the menu now, right?
No!
I think so.
Yeah, I think you got the secret, so I don't have to look at the secret.
That's two for two secrets for me.
Okay.
Oh.
Oh, son!
You're involved, you see!
Okay.
All of you.
There's lots of doors here.
Into the sea.
Yeah.
Are they putting us in the brig?
Wait, this is where we were, isn't it?
When we were Conrad and...
No, we were never here.
I don't remember this area.
Oh.
Oh!
We're locked in.
Oh, my God.
Hey!
It's pitch black in here!
Give us the light!
Where did that light come from?
It doesn't look like it.
It doesn't look that dark.
Yeah.
Oh, they gave us a flashlight!
They're such nice pirates!
They're actually so nice!
Yeah!
Wow.
You know, pirates aren't that bad.
Yeah.
I bet you weren't actually gonna shoot Conrad.
She had a...
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Wait, how did we have a lighting?
Oh, gosh.
I almost missed that.
My controller was like in my lap.
How is that still good?
Like, not waterlogged?
I know.
Wait, maybe it's because the ship never stopped.
Oh, my God.
This is a fucking place.
It never went into the ocean.
Manchurian gold.
It has to have something to do with the Manchurian gold.
We're not far from those coordinates.
Anyone else creep the fuck out by this ship?
Bradley.
What's the ship's name?
So, was Manchurian gold the name of the ship?
That'd be a weird name.
I've seen some pretty weird names for ships.
Man, I'm a man.
Maybe they took a vote?
What's the ship's name?
Oh, wow.
Your relationship with Alex went down!
Oh, snap.
What?
How did it go down?
I literally just asked about the ship's name!
You're so...
Okay, what is this relationship you're trying to save, huh?
Brad went to get us help.
We should wait for him.
Wait for Brad.
Um...
We should just leave.
I didn't know that meant we...
We need to call the Coast Guard, but the Duke's radio is shocked.
We gotta find a radio on this ship.
Oh, yeah.
Good luck.
So...
What's the status of the Duke?
How would the radio still be working?
I saw one of the goons...
I know, right?
It's been, like, out of commission for so long.
The Duke of Milan is a floating brick without it.
We need to get it back.
If I thought it was sinking.
If it was sinking, then...
Whatever they think they're gonna find on this floating coffin...
Is the ship gonna be still there?
We gotta take advantage and look around and find a way out of here.
Yeah, exactly.
I don't think it was sinking.
Fliss?
I don't think so.
You told me it was sinking!
That's why I agreed with you!
You're the one that told me it was sinking!
No, you said it first!
I didn't know!
I was like, why don't we do this?
I was like, why don't we just stay in this ship?
And you're like, no, it's sinking, Toki.
You know, you were working to get us out of here with these guys.
Or whatever.
But I...
I mean, obviously that's not true.
They're being just as bad to eat as they are us.
There was water!
We were drowning.
There's water everywhere!
He's saying that he's sorry.
Just get a fucking bucket!
Oh my god, it was Julius who was just like, we're gonna drown!
Oh, hey, we apologized to each other.
Cool.
Well, after we were arguing with each other, they apologized.
What's that?
I don't know.
We did our job.
I grabbed something.
Secure the room.
Oh, I got something here, too.
Some glasses.
I don't know.
We were too busy arguing.
I know.
Okay.
How are you doing?
What's this?
Oh, I found a secret.
Hey, baby doll.
I miss you like crazy.
Three months until my next leave and jumping into your arms.
Three months.
I've been on the shore leave with these guys.
Had a few beers.
But don't worry.
I'm keeping everything ready for you.
If you catch my drift.
How's life?
How's work?
I hope that boss of yours is leaving you alone.
I know you can take care of yourself, but I feel helpless being so far away and I want to keep you safe.
Skyden Miller was really freaked out.
I got a lot of time to think while I'm guarding the cargo holds.
It's dark and spooky down there.
Some of the other guys have seen a figure roaming around, but I've always got you with me to keep me safe, too.
I'll be with you soon and get a job as a mechanic and we can get married and have two children.
We'll be happy together forever.
Love you so much, Miller.
Oh my god.
There's Sam again.
Look at the picture on the wall.
Oh, what picture?
Come here.
This one.
This one right here.
Right here.
Oh, okay.
Is that going to give us a secret?
Yeah.
All right.
And like look at it and then like look up.
Are you good?
There you go.
I don't know.
What's wrong?
I wonder what happened.
All right.
I'm looking up.
Wait.
It won't let me look up.
What do you mean?
With the right hand.
It's analog.
It didn't let me.
What?
It didn't let me look up.
Oh, you missed the secret.
You missed the secret.
I missed the secret?
No.
Yeah.
But I want to look at that too.
Move.
I'm listening to the...
Do you know French?
Yeah.
Oui?
He says, I don't have the tools to do as I say and that's all.
What the hell?
You do know French?
I'm live translating.
Fuck you.
I'm live translating for you.
Oh, okay.
Thanks.
Nothing actually.
Hello, my urbex?
Can you hear me?
Yes.
Thanksuanx.
Oh yeah.
Well, laughing like wming?
Have a listen.
I don't feel like you're watching my talk anymore.
You know what I want to say?
Can you play and exchange the code?
I don't know how, I don't know how.
You will see.
I'm talking to... the boyfriend.
I'm still listening to these guys.
I'm telling him... I'm telling Alex about the ghost.
Oh, I'm gonna listen.
Hold on, I'm stuck.
I'm stuck, I can't get over there.
Hold on.
I'm stuck, hold on.
Hold on, I can't get over there.
How did you get over there?
Hold on, I'm coming.
LBLB.
Yeah, I wanna know what the fisherman's gonna be doing.
Yeah.
Oh, there you are.
Maybe they'll let us go if they find all that gold?
Maybe they don't find any gold?
This whole situation's gonna go really bad.
What happened?
Alex just disappeared on my screen.
What did you do to Alex?
Oh my god.
This is a fucking old ship, but maybe it still has a radio that works.
I doubt it.
Maybe we'll find it.
The bridge.
That is very hopeful.
Where the fuck is Brad in all of this?
He's in the room somewhere.
The radio still works.
He's just existing.
Okay, well we're not gonna do anything from in here.
We need to keep looking around and try to find a way out.
I can't look around.
Just be careful.
Okay, in the end, we gotta make sure Julia survives.
Yeah.
Alright, hold on.
There was some stuff over here.
Oh, there is.
There is over here.
Oh, here.
There's one over here.
I'm staring.
Where?
What's this?
Oh.
You got it?
You got this.
Yeah, I know how to hold now.
You're pushing me out of the way.
I did it.
I did it, Mint.
Nice.
Oh, what's this?
Oh.
No!
I found it.
A way out.
That's the game we're playing.
A way out, everybody.
A way out.
How am I?
Oh, there we go.
Wait, what's this?
I wonder why it's abandoned.
There's a newspaper.
I'm going to see if I can get it off.
Secret found.
Wait, we're looking at the same secret.
1947.
Archaeologists missing in Iraq.
24 British archaeologists have gone missing in the mountains of Iraq.
The Hudson Expedition arrived in the kingdom in September last year with the starting goal unearthing and then...
Oh, this must be the thing we found in the cargo.
Yeah.
This must be the thing we found in the cargo.
This could be the carnal thing.
That's why they're all possessed and scared.
Yeah.
They're cursed.
This is cursed.
Is there anything else we missed in here?
Oh, what's this?
Oh my god, Bradley scared the crap out of us.
Oh my god, there he is.
Right there.
Oh my god, he scared me so bad.
He just doesn't do anything.
He's useless.
Yeah, I'm here to help you.
We know somebody that's not gonna survive.
I can't get it open.
We can get it open.
We're not keeping Bradley alive, right?
No, Bradley can die.
Yeah, Brad's just gonna die.
Yeah.
Down with the nerd.
No nerds allowed.
Freedom.
Oh, uh...
This is the way out.
Yeah.
I'm excited.
My excitement's going up.
Doki Bird is deciding.
Alright, I got this.
No, I got this.
Oh, yeah.
Someone should create a distraction.
This is gonna be loud.
Okay.
Alex relationships.
Oh, Julia goes up.
Oh.
What is she doing?
What is going on?
Wait, wait.
Yeah, you make a distraction.
Fliss.
Me?
Yeah, why don't you do the distraction?
Um, I'm gonna distract.
Here I go.
I hope Fliss doesn't die.
I'm back.
Bradley, get away.
Hey, you dumb, sweaty mongrel.
Whoa.
Maybe I shouldn't let you distract.
Yeah, hey, all that stuff she said, but double is gross.
Your mother's... It's your mother's mother, too.
Whoa.
Don't talk about my mom.
Oh, are you doing it?
I'm doing the quick time event.
Oh, thank God I'm doing the quick time event.
Everyone of you smells like barrel of fish heads.
That's right.
Your mother's all sucking.
Let us out.
Yeah, your mother's.
Your mother's.
Yeah, dear.
Yeah.
Are they coming?
Why are you screaming?
Because they don't want them to hear us doing the vent.
We're already done, Fliss.
Shut up.
Come on.
What do you mean?
You're Fliss.
I'm not... I...
Uh-oh.
Wait, what's going on?
Come on, Fliss.
Fliss.
Fliss, come on.
There you go.
Nice.
God, I can't believe she's not wearing shoes.
Replace it.
Yeah.
They'll never know.
Oh, no.
Where did it go?
We're venting.
Among Us?
Oh, man.
We're gonna get separated at some point.
I feel like it too.
Find a way off the ship.
We need to keep going.
Come on.
There's gotta be...
There's gotta be some stairs around here.
Okay.
What's going on?
Wait, why am I holding the light?
Wait, who am I?
Oh, wait, who am I?
What do you mean, who are you?
You're always...
Wait, are you Alex?
I'm Alex.
Are you Alex?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now that we're... Oh, wait, there's something over here too.
There's stuff in here, yeah.
They're all leaving.
But we gotta...
We're splitting up already, guys?
I found a piece of paper.
It's good to know that we're splitting up already.
I found the guard duty regulations.
They say...
I found the uniforms.
Wait, how do I...
Oh, there we go.
Guys, nobody is allowed into 3A.
Seriously.
Nobody.
Okay, guys.
I'm coming back.
Where are you?
No alcohol.
Where are you, man?
Hold on.
I'm right by the front door.
The door we just... Here, look at me.
Turn around.
I'm turning around?
You see me?
Where are you?
I'm right in front of you.
Where are we?
I already went through that door.
There's nothing in there.
I already went through that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think we're gonna get caught up by the pirates.
No, why are you looking down like that?
Why are you always looking down?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm trying to look at where I'm standing.
I'm the one with the lights.
I have a...
I have a flashlight too.
How do you have a... Oh, wait.
I found a map.
Why is the light flickering there?
That would have bounced.
What was that?
Oh, okay.
So, Cargo Hole 2 is out of bounds.
Oh, yeah.
They didn't program that part.
Do you remember that?
Cargo Hole 2 is out of bounds.
Yeah, when are we gonna get to Cargo Hole 2?
Wait, where do we go?
Why was the light flashing over here?
Yeah, you first.
What's going on in here?
What's going on?
The lights actually work?
Oh, my God.
Wait, I'm in the bathroom.
I'm in the bathroom.
I found the light in the bathroom.
Ladies first.
All right.
It's reading time.
Dear Eyeless, I'm finally coming home.
This is it, darling.
One last trip across the Pacific and I'll be back to you and the girls.
I can't wait to see your faces.
Tell Ned and Nancy to get excited.
They're gonna see Daddy real soon.
And he's got gifts for y'all.
I'm sure glad to be back at sea.
It's hotter than an Oklahoma summer out there on the land.
And there's no escape from it.
I've been all right.
Because I got your letters to keep me going.
They censored them.
Which is probably for the best.
Because sometimes the others steal them to read.
And I don't like them reading our letters.
It really creeps me out.
It keeps telling me there's a little boy on board.
And it sounds like Ted.
What?
Wait, Dokie, our feet are smelly.
Oh, we gotta go.
We gotta go.
I think that's the sign.
We gotta get out of here, man.
Guys, I think...
Where did they go?
Oh, this way.
I think the moment it starts getting smelly.
That's when death is coming.
And we split up.
No, no, they're right here.
They're right here.
They're right in front of me.
I like how we're the only ones with the flashlight.
And we're like...
In the very back.
Oh, my bad.
Time to explore.
That's a lot of people who are suspiciously nowhere to be found.
Yeah, there's something here.
What's that?
Are you picking it?
Are you picking it up?
I think it's a skull of a rat.
Oh, there's another thing here, too.
It's a rat skull.
A rat skull.
Oh, my God.
I just got grabbed by a ghost hand.
It was the loudest thing I've ever heard in my life.
Skipper has K.O'd the boost for this goddamn trip.
Okay, none of this is...
Skipper, what the hell are you doing?
This lore is not interesting.
He's just talking about alcohol.
Can I turn down the...
Is it the sound effects that is what the music...
It has to be the sound effects, right?
I think I'm gonna... hold on.
I'm turning it down.
I think it's the music.
No, it's so bad.
It's going down to 35.
You got the spooky.
You got the 35.
Yeah.
It was so loud.
Oh my god.
Wait, how are you scared of ghosts?
You are a ghost.
I'm scared of jump scares.
Yeah, but it's just your neighbor grabbing your hand.
I don't know every ghost.
Look at our feet.
I could grab... Wait, okay.
I wanna see what this jump scare is.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Do the rat.
I'll do the rat.
I'm watching.
Oh, I'm looking at it.
Am I going crazy?
I might be going crazy.
There's nothing.
You lied to me.
There was nothing there.
What?
You're going crazy.
You didn't take your meds.
I have smelly feet.
Dokia, I have smelly feet.
It's not my fault.
Someone here was lying.
Uh-oh.
I found a picture frame.
I think this is a clue.
Is this a premonition?
Yeah.
Uh-oh.
What is it?
Here you might wanna... What's the premonition?
You might wanna look at that one.
Okay.
We gotta make sure nobody dies.
Yeah, I think...
Oh.
Uh-oh.
Alright.
We gotta make sure Alex doesn't die.
But you're Alex.
It's in your hands.
It's me.
No.
I got... No.
They already warned you how to save Alex.
I don't know what was going on there.
Oh my god.
Bradley doesn't have shoes either.
What's wrong with you guys?
Min has to protect herself.
It's not my fault.
Hey.
I'm dead.
So that means I couldn't protect myself from the beginning.
Oh my god.
The flashlights.
Turn it off!
There's someone down there alright.
Shh.
Everyone quiet.
I'm the loudest whisperer ever.
Just turn it off.
Why are you putting your hand over a flashlight?
Oh, there's the pirates.
Save the battery, man.
Could be those charging flashlights, you know?
The...
The whirring ones.
We actually can get that?
Yeah, we gotta get that so we can leave, right?
Oh no.
Oh?
He's gonna destroy it so nobody can use it.
Oh, nevermind.
What's he doing?
He grabbed a weapon.
We need one.
He has a hammer, yeah.
Ummm...
Alright.
Grab it then, hurry.
I don't need you barking on this big guy.
I swear to god, if I have to play Fliss because of that, I swear to god, man.
I swear to fucking god.
I swear to the player.
Well, she was the one who was like, I'm gonna go get it.
Okay, then go.
Oh, you're coming back in.
Bradley's a hero now.
Brad!
Brad, don't do this!
Alright, who's gonna be Brad and who's gonna be Fliss?
Uh oh.
Alright, if I'm getting Brad, I'm making sure he dies.
Just so you know.
Oh yeah, if I get Brad, I'll do the same.
I'll do the same.
Oh my god.
Um...
No, I won't warn Brad.
I'm just gonna hide.
Good luck, Brad.
Good luck.
Brad is the victim.
Oh my god.
07 Brad.
We were very clear that we don't want Brad anymore.
Brad has been voted off the island.
Oh my god!
Oh my god.
Uh oh.
Oh no, Fliss.
Oh no.
He sounds really concerned.
Where are the others?
Oh no, Fliss.
Oh no, the other pirates are coming over.
This is such a long cutscene.
Oh my god, don't gasp like that.
Oh wait, it's the gun!
It's the guy with the gun!
Stop screaming.
I'm trying to hear what's going on.
I'm not screaming.
Shut up.
I want to know where the others are.
Oh.
Bye Fliss.
Brad.
Oh my god.
Who's Brad?
Who's gonna be doing it?
Not yet.
No.
Oh my god.
Alright.
I see you.
Oh come on, Brad.
What the hell?
That's not us.
It's the AI.
Yeah, it's the AI.
Wow, you guys.
Come on.
Don't let him out of your sight.
Okay.
Girl, you're holding a whole ass lantern.
Like they're gonna see you.
I think it's our...
I think...
No, it's your fault.
You literally told Fliss to go down and...
I mean, she should've...
She was the one who brought it up in the first place.
Hey.
I got this.
Rat.
That's a very sick rat.
Oh, you're Fliss?
Am I Fliss?
Yes.
Uh-oh.
We're split up.
Wait, what are you?
Who are you?
I'm Alex.
Are you Alex?
Yeah.
I'm Alex.
Are you getting...
Are you...
Oh, no.
We're split up.
Why do I need to see this now?
This is you.
Are they interrogating you?
Are they torturing you?
No, we're just...
We're just walking.
We're walking somewhere.
Oh, okay.
I'm here.
All right.
We went somewhere else.
I might...
We might have these two die.
What?
Are you sacrificing Fliss so that...
No, Fliss is cool.
No, I said both of us.
You're the one that...
Go down.
Fliss, they're fucking...
Go down there.
No, she...
It was her.
It was her idea.
She said, I'm gonna go down there and get it.
What's this?
And I said, okay.
Do it.
Bet.
That's what I said to her.
Oh, my God.
Julie looks really scary.
She just looks like a...
She looks so scary just standing there in the middle of the walkway.
Yeah, we like Fliss.
We don't want Fliss to die.
Oh.
You're the one that sent Fliss down there.
You had a choice not to send Fliss down there.
She probably...
She wasn't gonna listen to me.
Let's be honest.
She was gonna be like...
I'm going down there whether you want me to or not.
We don't know that.
You gave her the choice.
Oh, my God.
Fliss wasn't telling you to do it.
No, she...
No, she wasn't.
She said, I'm gonna go get that.
And then my choice was tell her don't or go get it.
And she made her choice.
She should...
She could have been like...
Yeah.
But you said go get it.
You chose go get it, didn't you?
I'm stuck.
Hold on.
Where's the door?
Okay, everybody.
I'm stuck.
You guys, I'm stuck for real.
How do I go through this door?
There's a dead guy.
Uh-oh.
Dead person.
Oh, it was a...
It was just a hat.
JK.
Wow.
I'm stuck.
I'm so stuck.
How do I get through here?
So, we have a very paranoid gunsman.
Oh.
He's very scared.
Is he experiencing...
Oh, there we go.
Finally.
Is he experiencing...
No.
I'm stuck.
Oh, I'm stuck.
What's going on?
What's going on on your side?
I'm fine.
Everything's fine.
I have a hat now.
Really?
We've been here before.
We have?
Yeah.
I got Medan.
I got Medan's hat.
What!
You got the man.
Of Medan.
I got the man.
Wait.
Hold on.
There's gotta be stuff in here to find.
Right?
There's not a dead body in here.
There's not a dead body.
There's screams on my end.
Take your meds, take your meds.
Don't look, it's fine.
There's scary stuff over here!
I just saw some organs, okay?
Chill.
Calm down.
You saw organs?
Yes, they were organs.
They were like live organs.
Somehow they were live in the... Wait, what?
You found a secret!
Oh!
I found... I'm having beef casserole.
Everything just ground to a halt on this one day.
No way.
The whole ship just stopped functioning.
Tuesday was cereal.
Home fried potatoes.
Boiled eggs.
I found a body.
You're like, cereal!
Back on jokey side, there's a body.
That's not until... That's not until Fridays.
Come on.
The body is not on the menu yet.
Wait, there's soup here.
You want some?
Oh.
Soup du jour mademoiselle?
Oh, I found another secret.
Oh my god, Julia.
There's no time for messing around.
Alex.
God.
No, the stinky feet is here.
Oh, I have stinky feet too.
I just noticed.
Oh, we're so... Oh my god, where are you?
Why did we split up?
It's fine!
Oh, there's a child.
I think there's running children.
Okay, you're really in trouble.
I haven't seen anything yet.
I remember the last time there was running children.
Uh oh.
Wait, so I heard something.
What did I hear?
I found a notebook.
It says...
Let's see.
Uh, nothing.
I can't even open... Open the notebook, idiot!
I just... Oh, there we go.
Oh.
Okay, it's a diary!
Oh, read it!
Read that diary!
June 18th.
Wednesday.
We hadn't been at sea long and I'm sick of the damn food already.
That muck we ate tonight was a joke.
The cooks do their best with what we got, I'm sure.
But man, I'd kill for something fresh.
First thing I'm doing when I get home is having me a tall glass of milk.
June 19th.
Thursday.
Every one of the US papers was talking about that massacre in Philly.
Are these guys American?
All I'm saying is while you're reading this diary, our kidnapper fucking died.
.
I can't... I'm just like, listen, you ate the diary and a kidnapper disappeared.
It's crazy to think how we're out here traveling the world trying to keep our country safe and there's people killing each other in the streets back home.
I could sure use a beer after reading about home.
But the captain has issued a ban on booze.
Guess I'll be counting sheep tonight.
Oh my god, there's more?
Oh no.
Oh my god, there's more.
Oh!
Secret?
Who found a secret?
Was it you?
Yeah, I found a secret!
June 20th, Friday.
Some of the guys had a little wrestling competition in one of the cargo holds today.
I did okay, but Wagner eventually knocked me out of it.
I joked he should be disqualified on account of his size, but no dice.
I like how you're reading it.
I'm still trying to find a way out.
You're just standing there reading the diary.
It'd take a whole crowd of people to pin him down.
He certainly ain't eating the same as the rest of us, that's for sure.
June 21st, Saturday.
I'm sure the cargo we have in the hold has something to do with the squad that went missing.
Their leader, Jones, heard a legend about a room full of ancient solid gold statues from a Manchurian child emperor!
They were said to be cursed!
But that sounds like a load of baloney!
It's the child!
Also, Min, I hope to God that you're heading over to where I'm heading over, because I'm progressing right now!
I'm reading!
I'm progressing in knowledge, okay?
I don't know if they found them, but they never did return from their mission.
Maybe they're returning now.
Okay, that's all of it.
Cool.
Alright, cool.
I got away, and, like, I'm back in the cargo hold.
Oh, I'm, like, far.
I don't know where I am.
I'm in the kitchen.
Yeah, I could tell.
Oh, I got the knife!
I heard something, though.
I think I'm starting to hear people.
Uh-oh.
Wait, I see a premonition picture!
I'm getting a premonition.
Oh?
Right now.
What was your premonition?
Mine was the one where, like, it was a guy in a hood with a stick.
Oh my God!
I just saw Bradley's death!
Wait, how does he die?
How does he die?
He gets stabbed!
Wait, I have the knife!
Wait, but it's someone... I just picked up the knife!
It's someone wearing a raincoat.
Why'd you pick up the knife?
No, he was the one that was holding the... I didn't know!
I picked up the knife!
I literally just picked up the knife while you said that.
What just happened?
There's something in here with us.
Bradley, what's going on?
I zoomed in.
Did you hear anything?
I picked up the knife!
I'm scared.
I know I saw something.
It was moving in the shadows.
Something's moving in the shadows.
It's probably just a rat.
Oh, Charles!
Rats.
Probably just rats.
That's all it was.
Don't fucking laugh at me!
My relationship with Julia went up!
But she was really bitchy about it.
Alright, we've been here before.
Oh my god, they split me and Brad!
What do you want to do?
Turn around?
We've seen all this before.
Wait, I got split off!
Wait, you split up?
You're by yourself now?
Yeah!
Yeah, I'm by myself!
The door closed on us!
Okay, no.
Uh-oh.
Oh my god!
Wait, I'm in the room with the dead bodies!
Uh-oh.
Which dead bodies?
The, the, the, the ones that were carried on the ship at the beginning!
Gotta get out of here too sweet.
Okay, so can we just get the fuck out of here?
Oh my god, I'm going crazy!
I couldn't pick the other option.
Brad, Brad like, I'm seeing hallucinations!
Uh-oh.
Oh my god, I'm with the bodies!
I'm with the dead body!
Oh, I can, look at that!
I can observe every single body!
Oh god, I'm scared, I'm scared.
Oh god, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared!
We're both fucking up!
I found the secret!
Wait, there's two bodies in here!
There's two bodies!
What the?
What's this?
Practically falling off.
Anyway, what does that mean?
Oh, that's a bullet.
Um, is this even human?
What is this?
Look at this.
It's insane.
What is going on?
Is this even human?
I just want to reunite with at least somebody.
I mean, is it ever human?
I don't want to understand.
What's the deal with this place?
Leave.
Now!
Leave, leave, leave!
Hold on, I'm not done yet.
I'm not done yet, Julia.
Oh, there's zombies!
Are you okay?
What's going on?
I'm not!
You found a secret and there's zombies!
I'm just looking at the bodies!
I don't...
I found another secret!
I don't want to know.
Let's get out of here.
Save Brad!
Save him!
I got some serious locks in these caskets.
I got another secret.
Plus four for four!
What do you mean?
You're getting secrets!
Woo!
What do you mean?
Hold on, there's something over here.
Uh-oh.
Something's gonna be behind here!
There might be...
Brad might be dead.
What?
Wait, it's not letting me do it now.
Oh no!
I'm in the ballroom!
Hold on.
I remember what happens on Ghost Ship, not the ballroom!
It's okay, that was outside.
That was outside.
Wait, it's not letting me do it.
It was inside the ballroom!
I saw the movie!
No, they were out on the deck!
They were out on the deck and then that's when it happened.
They were dancing on the...
They were dancing in the ballroom!
The ballroom's not a deck.
Uh-oh.
It might be stuck.
You guys hear that?
I'm trying to use... I'm trying to do this!
I'm trying to do this, but it's not letting me.
My right stick is stuck.
I think... press it?
What is press?
I think I'm having a Doki Bird problem.
You gotta wait until I progress.
Keep holding the trigger.
I am!
It doesn't let me progress unless I hold the trigger.
Hmm.
Is it the left one maybe?
No?
Right?
You're going through my problem now.
Yeah.
Good.
Wait.
I don't think it'll let me...
I don't think it'll actually let me progress unless I do...
Oh wait.
No.
There's a room over here.
Never mind.
Okay.
Let's go.
Sorry guys.
I tried.
I really did.
Alright.
Let's see.
What did you have to do?
Spin it.
It was like...
I'm trying to open up a curtain.
Oh my god.
Hold the stick I was!
I'll try one more time.
Oh.
There's a pentagram book.
There's like a sorcery Satan book in the ballroom.
That's not good.
I don't know.
I guess we'll never know.
I read the spooky book.
Oh.
You caught...
You're cursing us.
If we...
I read the spooky book and there's blood here.
There's blood in the ballroom.
You are seeing a whole lot of bad stuff.
I haven't seen anything.
That's on you.
You nearly put me in this situation.
What do you mean?
I didn't do anything.
Oh.
I'm in like a really bad area.
I feel like I'm...
Oh.
What the?
Why so spick and span?
Oh.
There's a blood fountain.
Why do I get all the bad stuff?
I think I see a corpse.
Oh.
Fuck!
Oh my god.
Oh.
There's really a blood fountain here.
I can't take it.
Wait.
What's going on?
Now they're real people.
Oh my god.
What's happening?
What's going on?
Oh.
What the?
I'm touching...
What the fuck?
Why are you touching me?
I touched it.
You touched it?
You touched the bad thing?
Oh.
And you were telling me not to touch the bad thing when you're touching the bad thing.
I just booped a guy.
Come on.
A dead body became alive.
Is that not bad enough?
I just went boop on his face.
Oh.
I see another premonition.
Oh my god.
Wait.
What just happened?
What?
Somebody's drowning on this one.
We gotta hurry.
Yeah.
I found a picture.
Oh.
Okay.
I think I was too slow.
Oh.
I turned on the lights.
The lights are on now.
Oh.
The lights are on.
Oh no!
It's the guy!
It's the guy with the hammer!
He's after me!
Oh wait.
I'm Bradley!
Bradley?
Wait.
Is he alive?
Bradley's alive?
Yeah!
Why am I by myself?
That's right.
I kept...
What?
Fliss?
I was following you.
He's like talking to it.
He's like, Fliss?
Hello?
Fliss?
Wait.
Where'd you go?
I think I was following you.
Fliss?
I think I'm in trouble.
Oh!
There's a dead body!
Yeah.
You are in trouble.
I left you there.
I'm gonna touch this guy.
Don't.
Don't jump at me.
Why?
Am I taking the bullet out of it?
Ew!
Whoa.
You're definitely in trouble.
I left you there.
Why'd you do that?
I tried to save you.
I did quick time events.
What?
You said you were gonna kill...
Now I have to save myself.
I was scared.
I'm sure I just left you.
You know what?
I kept him alive so you had to play him.
I'm playing P.T.
actually.
Fliss, hey.
Who are you?
I'm playing P.T.
I'm following you but you have less clothes on.
Huh?
I think you're trying to seduce me.
I'm watching.
I'm following.
Wait.
What happened?
Fliss!
Oh!
She just disappeared.
She's back.
I think Fliss is a ghost.
Yeah.
That's what I saw too.
You saw yourself?
No.
I knew you were a ghost.
Oh.
I'm looking at the bullet again.
This time it says my name.
No.
It says Alex on it.
Is Alex gonna get shot?
I think so.
Oh no.
Fliss, what does that mean?
Girl, what does that mean?
Do I open this again?
Nuke.
Oh!
Matura gold!
You found the gold.
I found the gold.
Guys, we're gonna be rich.
Don't be greedy.
I'm up with the hint.
Are you playing P.T.?
I'm playing P.T.
real?
Now you know how I felt.
The guy with the gun is here now?
What's going on?
This is why I kept Bradley alive.
I can't see.
You're in the way.
This is why I kept Brad alive.
Now you have to deal with it.
The body is now...
It has textures floating.
What is that?
What is that floating texture?
What is going on on your head?
The game is glitching a little bit, I think.
Oh, the bullet turned into a slug and it's eating me?
Okay, okay.
Are you killing Bradley off right now?
Oh, we got slugs on us!
We got slugs on us!
Oh my god!
I'm exploring.
Yippee-ki-yay!
Oh, look at all these items.
I'm playing P.T.
Look at all these items around me.
Let me read some more.
Let me...
Oh, I'm stuck.
Okay, never mind.
Oh, look at all this lore.
Okay, read it out loud.
What's the lore?
Come on.
Alright, I got a book too.
Oh my god.
The Stanford Operating Procedure for Handling Hazardous Chemicals.
Oh, are you ready for some science?
What the?
I put the book down.
This is my fourth time going through the same hallway.
There's just blood on the ground and a bullet.
Let's see.
It says... Oh!
It says, Ha!
Oh!
Ha!
Oh, I just saw Alex die.
Wait, what?
No, it's not really him.
I'm hallucinating.
Oh, okay.
Okay, that's good.
Because we only want a crab to die.
Oh my god.
I fucked it up, but I'm pretty sure you can take it home.
You had every opportunity.
I was panicking!
Oh!
That was a quick time event.
My bad.
Uh oh.
Oh, he might actually die.
Ow!
Wait!
Did you actually kill him?
I was adjusting the sound and I missed the quick time.
Oh no, he's fine.
He's fine.
Oh, okay.
You can't die from a hallucination.
Okay, this is...
What just happened?
Duh, you guys.
No, we're in a different hallway now.
We made it out.
I can't believe it.
You were given one quick time.
I had to do like 20 during that entire run.
You and...
You get one quick time event and you messed it up.
I was adjusting my sound.
Alex was so loud.
It's fine.
Don't worry about it.
Just worry about yourself.
Why are you so obsessed with what I'm doing on my end?
Oh, I feel like something's gonna come out now.
What's over here?
Who's that?
I'm hearing screams.
Get away!
I don't even know where to go.
Where do I go?
I don't know either.
I'm just... drop down?
I'm stuck.
Gosh, there's so much to do.
There's so many options.
This is really cool.
Skeletons.
This is really choose your own adventure.
It really is because I don't know what to do right now.
I'm looking at Skeleton 1.
Some sort of altercation.
Okay.
Oh, there's the...
Internal memorandum.
What?
You will ask to be kept informed of the radio situation.
We attempted outgoing messages at the following times with no response.
Oh my god, I'm going crazy.
You found a secret, but I'm going crazy.
That's how it tends to be, isn't it?
I mean, Bradley's been pretty crazy this whole time, so like...
Oh!
I found a wrench!
Oh my god!
Take that!
Weapon!
Back to the ballroom.
Take that!
Yes!
Oh, that's the wrench!
I found that wrench earlier!
Wait, next to the guy that was hanging?
Yeah!
Okay.
Wait, what?
Next to the guy that hung himself?
There was no hung person when I was there.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm...
I'm pretty sure.
Are you sure?
Yeah...
What's that?
Oh, the tiniest A button I've ever seen in my entire life.
Wait, what's going on?
Oh, there.
Press A.
Okay, I'm gonna head outside to the deck again and see if I can get out again.
Oh, I think I'm trying the door.
I'm gonna go outside.
You're going outside?
Yeah, I'm going back outside.
I can go outside again!
I still haven't seen...
No.
No, I'm not hearing this.
I'm not hearing this.
I'm outside!
The outside is real!
It's an old boat, Bradley.
Chill out.
Okay, I'm going downstairs.
I got my wrench.
When you go outside, it makes you go back inside.
Oh, so he'll PT, PT.
Yeah.
Wait, I'm back here!
Here we go.
Oh, you cannot see the bottom.
Oh, boy.
Bradley, you're gonna die.
You're gonna die, Bradley!
What's going on?
Oh, I think I'm fine, actually.
Oh, you dropped the wrench!
No, don't drop the wrench!
We worked so hard for that!
What was the point of all of that?
Brad, is that you?
Oh, I'm seeing shadow people.
Uh-oh, I'm in trouble.
Brad, is that you?
No, wait, is that... do you see me?
Oh, no!
I missed the cutscene!
I can kill Brad right now!
Wait, no, don't!
That's me!
I'm gonna kill you!
You're as happy!
No, it's not you!
That's me!
Don't do it!
That's literally me!
Do not!
Wait, there's multiple!
There's like five zombies here!
There's nothing!
Don't do anything!
I almost bashed your head in, I'm serious.
God damn it, Liz!
Who were you playing as, Fliss?
I think so.
Holy shit, you almost I almost killed you.
It's because you begged for it.
Oh my god, the guy is right behind us!
Oh shit!
You're like, Alfred, don't break my head!
You're like, hmm...
Do I choose it?
Wait, are you Alex, right?
I think so.
Wait, I got pulled out.
What do you see in the water?
I'm...
I don't know, I got pulled out now.
Oh, I'm in the ship.
I thought baby.
Or I'm in the plane, like before.
Oh, he's a...
Oh my god, it's out!
There's a zombie!
Oh!
Kill the zombie, kill the zombie.
I punched him, I punched him.
I think Julia's gonna drown.
Wait, you're Julia.
Yeah, I know.
I did everything I was supposed to do.
No, I'm fine.
Oh, hello.
You seem really calm.
Oh, what the?
Okay, I have to help you now.
Wait, there's multiple of you!
What just happened?
Wait, what's going on?
It's all just black.
I can't see anything.
I can't see anything!
Oh, this is a premonition!
What's going on?
Who do I save?
Do I do it?
I'm heroic!
I mean, who do you save?
Wait, who's drowning?
Who's drowning?
Do it!
Keep going.
Oh my god!
Holy shit!
You made me kill a man!
Wait, was it you who died?
No!
You made me kill a man!
You were already working on it!
I was making sure he got fainted!
I had to kill him!
Do it!
You were the one.
You could have let go at any time.
Okay, I'm just saying.
Okay,
I'm just saying.
Thanks, Min.
You made me kill a person.
You could have stopped me!
I don't have any control!
I'm sorry.
You did the right thing.
Yeah, you did the right thing.
It was him or us.
See?
What the?
What the fuck?
How did he get thrown over?
Oh my god!
It's him!
What the?
What is going on?
Oh my god.
What's going on?
Punch him!
Do something!
Oh my god.
Run!
Are we doing anything?
Quick time event.
Maybe.
Who is he?
That's the guy that had the hammer, right?
That's the hammer guy?
Yeah.
Why does he look pruney?
He was in the water.
It's John Medan.
Oh my god, it's Medan!
It's the man of Medan!
Oh my god.
Hey, stop.
Don't mess up your QTE.
You can't trip on the stairs.
Fuck.
Uh oh.
Come on, Julia.
Hit it.
He's here!
What's the matter, dreamboat?
Don't show up to me anymore!
Uh oh.
Whoa!
Time to use our fists.
We killed daddy!
Oh my god!
Oh my god, you did it!
Oh my god, I'm so proud of you!
Holy shit!
Those are the most quick time events I've ever...
I'm actually proud of you.
Wait, which way do we go?
I don't know.
Are you this side or am I this side?
I don't know!
Jump!
Shit.
Let's jump.
My bad.
It's okay.
Okay.
Just to help me up, you know?
Maybe we shouldn't have jumped.
I pressed Y, but I also pressed...
Keep going!
Oh, okay.
That's fine.
You're gonna kill a second man.
You're obsessed with it.
Oh my god!
Oh my god, keep going.
Oh, we're outside.
Oh my god!
You're killing him!
I'm bloodthirsty!
Oh, this is the...
Premonition!
Yeah, you saved him!
Oh my god, it's Fliss.
Yeah, it's me.
Come on, let's go.
Where's Bradley?
Oh my god!
Everybody's alive!
Oh my gosh, we're doing it.
We're doing it.
We're supposed to kill people, but somehow it's working.
Wait, how is Bradley alive?
We're too good at the game, I think.
We're so good.
Oh my god.
Keep going, keep going.
Murder works?
I think...
Yeah, I think we'll be alright here.
Okay.
What?
Why do you think that?
I don't trust you, Bradley.
Bradley, you almost killed Fliss!
Oh, hello.
I think he's just as surprised that everybody's alive.
Wouldn't you say?
Yeah, it's kind of crazy.
I didn't see so many dead people.
I'm kind of disappointed in that.
Why don't we meet?
You hadn't saw them come alive.
Apparently.
Have you figured out what's going on?
How to stop it?
How to save the lives of your poor unfortunate stowaway?
No, we just gotta leave.
Yeah, just leave!
I hope.
Although it seems the ship's previous occupants never managed to.
Quite a lot of deaths that night.
The whole ship died, right?
Let me help you out.
Oh boy, another hint.
Yeah, I would do two.
Yeah, I need some help.
Give me a hint, man.
I don't want spoilers.
Really?
Well then, how can I put this?
There may be forces at play here that are more scientific.
Scientific?
Even some that are more political.
You know?
Less supernatural.
What?
Perhaps you've started to realize something.
Spatial expression?
Everything and everyone may not be quite what they appear to be.
What the fuck does that mean?
I hope that helps.
What does that mean?
Well, aren't you excited to find out what your poor unfortunates are making of all this and how you might avoid any more unnecessary Is it the gas?
Yeah, it's all gas.
It's not supernatural.
It's not curses.
We're hallucinating because of the gases.
The more we're inside, the more we're getting hallucinations.
Gas, gas.
I don't think we should go back inside.
Alright.
What the hell was wrong with you back there?
I don't know, Mitt.
You almost bashed my head.
Come on.
That's ridiculous.
What the fuck is going on with this ship?
We're seeing dead people.
It feels like there's some evil, like literal evil going on down there.
Let's just stay calm and relatively sane about this.
Okay?
I saw.
It's like there were these old soldiers.
They were bodies.
They were dead.
But then they came alive and...
That doesn't sound that crazy right about now.
Alex wasn't the only Alex.
Oh.
That's why I was confused.
It was horrifying.
What do you mean Alex wasn't the only Alex?
I wouldn't hurt you.
I'd never hurt you.
You know that, right?
True, I know.
This can't all be happening.
Our relationship went up.
We're fixing it.
We're fixing your mess.
No, your mess.
Their prior mess.
They had a mess already.
We're just making it better.
What do we know that's real?
Um...
Is this a ghost ship?
Am I crazy or are we on a ghost ship?
Ghost ships are real and this is one and we're totally on it and holy shit we're so totally fucked.
I was gonna say the same thing.
Yeah, I'm not crazy.
I'm one of the first people to see weird shit here.
Apparently the guards were super freaked out by something they saw in the cargo holds.
Oooh.
Ghost ship real.
Because they were really freaked out by something.
Yeah.
Oh, there might be bacteria on the gold that's eating our brains.
It's a brain-eating bacteria.
Anyone figure out what happened to all the sailors?
Did they catch a rescue boat or something?
I mean, we've seen their bodies.
It all feels more like a mausoleum than a ship.
So where did all the corpses come from?
They actually look like they've been scared to death.
Heart attack.
Heart attack, yeah.
I'm not gonna ask about the gold.
It keeps being like, ask about the gold.
Why not?
It's a cursed gold.
Our kid was like, don't be greedy.
No.
Oh, I'll ask about the gold.
Don't worry, I got you.
That gold should be around here, right?
Anybody catch a glimpse of it?
It's actually gold.
It's looking all over our gold.
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure this isn't exactly what our I got you, I got you.
Don't worry.
This should go over well.
We know more than we did before.
That's supposed to be greedy.
I'm just wondering.
What's wrong with being curious?
Time to get off this ship.
We're not going anywhere without the distributor cap.
The Duke needs it to run.
Didn't you grab that though?
She grabbed it.
No, one of the captains grabbed it.
If we can find it and use it.
Oh, it's working.
That's great, but do you think it still works?
Yeah, but where's the radio?
It was blinking, see?
I know that means the radio's on, but where's the radio station?
Probably over there, right?
Yeah.
Oh, what the fuck?
Oh, okay.
Wait, who am I?
Oh, I'm Fliss.
I'm Fliss.
Okay, I'm Alex.
Okay, before we start...
Wait, I need to pause.
I need the bathroom.
Okay.
I'll be right back.
Let's look at the collections and characters, everybody.
I'm Fliss.
I'm innocent.
I'm relaxed.
Oh, all of our...
Oh my god, my relationship with Alex is insane.
I just watched it go all the way down.
Brad is whatever.
Julia's pretty down.
Conrad, but I'm innocent.
I'm relaxed.
I'm excited.
I'm altruistic.
I'm guarded.
I'm motivated.
Oh my god.
What secrets?
Wow.
Oh, actually we haven't even found that many, have we?
What's this?
Flight plan.
Uh-huh.
Private Miller.
Master Miller.
Our bearings.
What are these?
The kitchen knife.
Oh, these are the hints that we've gotten, I think.
Yeah, these are the hints.
Our premonitions.
Cut of your jib.
In the offing.
High and dry.
Master Miller.
Yeah, Master Miller.
Let's see.
Oh gosh, I'm so used to playing Japanese games where there's circles to press okay.
Oh my gosh.
Ryan Carter.
I'm back.
Oh, welcome back.
What were you doing?
I was looking at our secrets.
Yeah, did we get some good secrets?
Oh yeah.
I'm surprised we're making it this far.
Alright, I'm ready.
Honestly.
Okay.
Anything else in here?
I don't think so.
I think we're supposed to go outside.
The longer we stay inside, the more we inhale the gas.
You're right.
But we're outside.
It's fine.
Yeah, that's why we gotta stay outside now.
Totally effed.
Oh my god, we're so effed right now.
I'm just going for it.
Are you playing as Fliss and not my girlfriend?
Julia.
Yeah, I don't know.
Yeah.
I looked at our relationship.
Fliss' relationship with Alex is completely down.
What?
What did you do?
What do you mean what did I?
You literally go like, Fliss go down there.
I've never been Fliss.
I've been Fliss like...
Fliss go down there.
What's this?
I'm gonna look at it.
I'm looking at it.
I'm looking at it too.
Holes.
Bullet holes.
Oh, there's bullet holes there.
We can't use them.
We gotta go forward.
Oh yeah, he did accuse her of being in cahoots.
That's true.
Yeah, didn't you accuse me?
No, I didn't do that.
It was Alex.
Oh, we're finding a way up?
Is that what we're doing?
We have to find a way to get to the radio tower.
Oh, I thought...
Okay, I thought we had to just get over there.
Oh my gosh, we're acting really casual for like, you know, some guys that are...
We're like, you know...
for almost... for seeing several dead people.
And I killed a man.
I killed several men.
I found a way up!
Over here!
Help me out!
I think this is our way up.
I mean, it's the only way up.
Give me a lift.
What?
Give you a lift?
Yeah, you're a strong, powerful woman.
Oh my god!
Damn!
Shouldn't it be me?
Right!
Holy shit!
And he doesn't even help her get all the way up.
Yeah, he just pulls you a little bit.
I was like, alright.
I did my job.
I'm a gentleman.
Dang, she's strong.
Oh, we're back.
Did no one help Brad?
Nope, there he is.
He's standing right there.
I know, I know.
But no one helped him get up.
Brad, are you okay?
Wait, I'm gonna go talk to him.
You're gonna talk to him?
Bro, we gotta find the radio tower!
What are you thinking, Brad?
The longer we're here, the more we're inhaling the gas.
He doesn't care!
He really doesn't care about me.
He doesn't care about you.
You literally almost bashed your head.
Well, he almost bashed my head.
If anything, I shouldn't be wanting to talk to him.
Okay, we gotta split up, maybe.
No, we're not splitting up.
Who's that down there?
Who's that?
There's someone down there.
No, but that's Brad.
No, no, no.
Over here.
Wait, there is.
You're right.
Who's that?
I'm going the other way.
See?
I told you this way was the better way.
I told you.
Oh.
Ladies first.
You have the flashlight.
I'm a gentleman.
I'll go here.
No, I can't see.
It's so dark.
Madame.
I can't see.
I'm holding the flashlight in front of you now.
No.
It's on the wall.
Oh my god.
What is going on here?
I don't like that camera angle.
I can't see what's in front of us.
Oh my god.
Oh, it's gone.
It's gone?
Oh, it's Julia.
Oh my god.
It's Julia.
Why were you so afraid of your own girlfriend?
Over here.
No, I just wanted you to go first.
Because I'm ladies first, you know?
Oh, okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Come on.
Yeah, I guess I'll do it myself.
Yeah, do it yourself.
Why were you screaming at my girlfriend?
I mean, it's Julia.
I thought we wanted to keep Julia alive.
Yeah, but I still don't like her.
Oh my god.
Okay, we're trapped in there.
Okay, we're trapped in the toxic gas again.
Yeah, great thinking, Alex.
Good job.
Oh, there's a guy in here.
There's a dead body.
Oh, this has to be the radio tower, right?
No, this is the captain's room, right?
Oh, this is the captain's room.
There's Brad.
I'm looking for...
Premonition!
We need to know the premonition.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh my god!
What is it?
It was one of the bad guys.
He just shoots himself.
Oh, what?
We have to convince him to shoot himself then.
I'm taking in these gases.
There's a door to our right.
Yeah, there's a door over here.
Bradley, are you okay?
Why are you like...
I don't think Bradley's okay.
I feel like at any point I'm gonna walk over and they're gonna be T-posing.
Oh, the door doesn't work.
Can you open that door?
No, okay.
I guess we'll go this way then.
Alright.
Here we go.
Oh my god, Julia, please!
Julia, what the f...
Why are you so chill?
Why are you just standing there like that?
I know!
She's chill like that.
She's so chill.
Is that another premonition?
They went from California...
Oh.
They went to the United States and then...
Korea?
Whoa.
It's almost like they didn't want anyone to know they were coming.
This is such a messed up...
That is a long route.
Why'd they go all the way down there?
Yeah.
There's no islands there.
Oh, I got a secret.
We got a secret.
I found a note.
Oh, I see you.
I'm watching you.
Pick it up.
Let's see.
The United States Department of the Navy.
The ship was blown off course.
The cloud cover was bad.
They couldn't establish a position.
Oh, there was a storm.
Well, and somebody went overboard.
Oh, someone failed their quick time events.
That could have been you, Mint.
That could have been me, but it wasn't.
Oh, there's a dead guy here.
The radio!
I found it.
There's only one way.
No freaking way.
I found it, Mint.
This thing actually still works?
Yeah, I found it.
Alright, there goes nothing.
Alright, let's see if you know how to do it.
You found it!
Good old shortwave radio.
What am I listening for?
Oh, fuck.
It's a number station.
Number station?
Military bandwidth.
Which one are we trying to find?
Military, probably, right?
Yeah.
Come in, please.
Do you read us?
Over.
Please, over.
That guy doesn't... I don't think that guy's really...
At least there's someone listening.
The signal's in and out.
That guy is too panicked.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking, too.
I'm gonna say our coordinates.
If you can hear me, we're on board an abandoned freighter.
12 degrees, 30 minutes south.
Just like when it's 911, say your address first.
251 degrees, 20 minutes west.
Over.
Please repeat.
Is this guy okay?
Why is he panicking?
Mayday, mayday.
Thank you, sir.
We're on a large freighter.
Say the address.
Over.
Coordinates, coordinates!
Coordinates!
Come in, over.
Come in, come in, please, anyone.
We screwed it up.
Oh, no!
Fliss, you ruined it.
What's this?
No!
Hey, come here, look!
Oh, no.
Brad wants to go down.
Hey, look at this.
Bradley's awfully brave, isn't he?
Just push him in, Fliss.
Push him in.
This has got to lead somewhere.
Maybe we can find a way to get the power back.
Anywhere will lead somewhere.
We need to get that radio working.
I think someone should wait here in case a message comes through.
I'll go, obviously.
I can do this.
Let Brad go!
Sounds like you're scared of someone stepping out of your shadow.
Scared of my idiot brother getting himself killed?
You almost killed somebody!
How about showing me some brotherly love?
We should have left him to die.
Oh, you decide.
If you're sure you're up for it.
If he dies, he dies.
Julia, what?
Julia, no.
She's not my bodyguard.
I can take care of myself.
What?
Why are you going?
Fliss and Brad again?
Julia says she can handle it.
She can handle it.
Case closed.
Oh, my God!
You guys left Julia and Brad.
One of us slain Julia and Brad.
Brad, the other.
Oh, my God.
Don't say that you're going to do it, if you're not going to do it.
Don't say that!
Oh, my God.
So loud.
I hope you get Julia and Brad.
Oh, I'm Julia.
I'm Julia, I'm Brad.
Julia definitely has tetanus.
She's all scraped up.
Oh, no.
Is everything still working?
Eric?
Everyone okay?
Decide.
Are we okay?
We're okay.
Oh god, you're the crazier one.
You're gonna try and kill me at some point.
Now you'll know how I felt.
We're gonna have to find the generator.
If we can get it started, we can power up the radio.
Okay.
We'll wait here by the radio.
Finally, somebody's gonna die now.
Someone will die.
Oh, thanks for the tiny lighter.
Yes.
To set you on fire.
Let's go.
I feel like we should not put a lighter up with toxic gas around it.
I know, right?
It just doesn't feel like a very good idea.
Yeah.
Are you okay?
There you go.
After you.
Ooh, we look like real Scooby Doo gang.
Oh, was that the sick bed?
Is that what that said over there?
We need to find the generator.
Let's go to the sick bed.
Move it up, guys.
It's probably really nasty in here.
Really gassy in here.
That's where all the dirtiest of germs are.
This is where all the gas is.
There's a door here.
Yeah.
Inhale the gases, guys.
Sniffer, sniffer.
Yeah.
Yeah, I love going crazy.
More hallucinations.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Medical officers report.
Minutes of meeting between scientist X, CWO Walter Bishop and CWO Tom Palmer with Sergeant Peter Wood observing and X for meeting with our team and says we can mutually learn.
Wait, what'd you find?
Oh, my thing talks about Charles and Joe.
It talks about, like, Charles beating up Joe.
Oh, my thing talks about Manchurian.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, this is actually really important.
Okay.
The United States has been aware of certain agencies investigating the chemical...
Yeah.
and biological agents in warfare.
Our act...
Limited by the Geneva Protocol...
Have experiments.
We are unable to describe...
Describes an investigation during...
To test the effects of human subjects on the molecule crystal structure hallucinogens codenamed Manchurian gold.
Chemical...
Oh, my God.
That is...
Munitions battle.
It was...
Even relatively minor.
Observed to trigger significant hallucinations.
Men...
Highly convincing...
Subjects seeing and hearing things that were not really there.
Even...
The danger was manifold.
And...
And its intensity.
Okay.
So, it is toxic gas that we're inhaling right now.
What else was over here?
It was nothing.
Lock me in jail, bad boy.
You have a boyfriend.
What the fuck?
I'm unhappy in my relationship.
I can tell.
I can tell you've been actively sabotaging it.
Oh, this is the...
Oh, this is where I was at.
Yeah, you're right.
This is a Charles...
The Charles and Jo beating up thing.
Yeah.
This is the thing I read.
And then there should be blood on the wall here.
I can't believe you tried an NTR with his brother.
That's fucked up.
Yeah, there's the blood that I saw earlier.
Oh, my gosh.
Don't worry about it.
Anyway.
Guys, the longer we stay here...
The more toxic gas we're gonna get.
Ooh.
Toxic gas.
I can't wait to see children.
Yummy.
I can't wait to see the kids.
Ooh.
How did you...
Whoa.
That's me.
I'm in the sick bay.
Whoa.
Did you hear that?
I heard...
Oh, that's the body.
That's the dead body I found.
That's him.
The little kid?
What?
Maybe this was somebody's son from on board?
Two pops.
Come back soon.
No, there's a dead body literally right next to me.
Where?
There.
I'm gonna go see it.
Oh.
I don't see a body.
Let's see.
There's literally no body here.
Wait.
What?
Oh!
On the ground.
Yeah.
I mean, like, what do you mean?
Oh.
Arf.
I'm looking at him.
Aw.
What is this?
Is this important?
I observed signs of severe distress consistent with evidence of panic observed in the same soldier during his watch duty.
Oh, it's talking about the hallucination that he's been getting.
Yeah.
Ooh.
Manchurian gold.
Yeah.
This is the body.
This dead body.
Yeah.
I didn't see him.
I thought he went in the bed.
Because that's where, like, sick bodies normally would be.
Yeah.
He was stuffed in this closet locker.
Oh!
Yeah.
You saved him.
That was, like...
Yeah.
Like, a hundred years ago.
Wait.
Where did you go?
I'm here.
Oh, there you are.
I was like...
Oh, this way?
Are we splitting up already?
Yeah.
We're splitting up.
We gotta get that generator.
Oh, come on.
Go.
I'm stuck.
Wait.
Hold on.
Stuck.
Really?
We can go down.
Let's see what's around.
We can only go down.
Go down.
Ladies first.
Nope.
I think Bradley's the lady right here.
Okay.
Touche.
Here, come check this out.
Yeah.
I found the ladder.
Oh.
Sure.
Yeah.
Wait.
What are you looking at?
Is this the generator?
Oh.
Gotta find the kitchen, Raggy.
Well, it sure looks gassy in here.
Rock roll.
Uh-oh.
I think I can just...
Wait.
Ow.
Are you okay?
Ooh.
Dang.
Come down here.
Come down here, Julia.
She won't be able to get back up if you tell her to come down.
Come down.
Oh, my God.
You have shoes.
I have bare feet.
I'm just a lady.
Please.
Oh, God.
What's up?
It was...
Wait.
I didn't see anything.
I just heard it.
Did you see it?
Me too.
I just heard it too.
I was not paying attention.
I don't think there was something there.
Okay.
So, I'm seeing things, but you're not.
So, follow my thinking here.
Okay.
We know this ship was carrying the Manchurian gold.
Yeah.
But that was really some sort of hallucinogenic bioweapon developed in China during World War II.
Right.
And we know that it was...
It was super unstable.
And it leaked all over the ship.
Yeah.
So, maybe it's still here.
Maybe it hasn't dispersed after 70 years.
Wait.
But why am I...
But it's having the same effect on us.
You know?
Oh.
Paranoid hallucinations.
Yeah.
Oh, my God, Brad.
You're so smart.
It's not like we figured that out.
He's the...
He's the brainy nerd.
And the officers thought it was just a bunch of jumpy GIs trying to get out of guard duty.
This isn't a ghost ship.
It's a floating bioweapon.
That's crazy.
We might die because the military wants to keep it a secret.
Yeah.
Ooh.
I mean, maybe there was a connection.
Maybe they made contact.
Maybe in the end, only Conrad survives.
It's a theory.
Oh, my God.
None of us...
All right.
Let's get going.
Nobody here lives.
Because that's usually how it goes.
The military wants to keep it a secret.
Yeah.
They'll be like...
So, they'll be like...
Well, we know those coordinates.
Yeah.
No.
They'll be like...
We'll be like, we're saved.
And then the military shoots us.
That's how it always goes.
Yup.
Oh.
Netherland.
Diesel engine.
Netherlands?
Oh.
Rotterdam.
Yeah.
Oh, here.
Oh, my God.
This is not an American ship.
No.
Oh, my God.
It's not American at all.
It's not made in America.
They lied to us.
How dare they?
You go the other way.
You explore the other way.
No.
We're not splitting up.
Yeah.
Why not?
I can't believe we outsourced this ship to Europeans.
That's why it's cursed.
That's...
I don't think there's anything over here except gas.
Look at this.
I didn't say about...
Huff it up.
Huff up the gas.
My delusions.
Oh, my God.
Anime girl...
Anime girls are real.
We're gonna see the children.
It's this way.
There's stuff here.
Oh, okay.
I'm seeing anime girls.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my God.
Remember to huff up the gas.
Huff up the gas.
Oh, what's this?
Wait.
Did we come this way?
No.
We didn't.
We came from upstairs.
And it's like a...
Oh, you're right.
Yeah.
This is it.
All right.
Just throw the switch and let's get back upstairs.
How?
Yeah.
How do we go back upstairs?
Okay.
Let's get back upstairs.
There's gotta be another way up.
Sure.
Oh.
Yay.
Baby.
We've lost power, but we have it back.
Can you hear me?
Over.
Please make your situation over.
Cool.
We need help now.
There are things on the ship that are trying to hurt us.
Over.
Recovery mission is on route to your location.
Oh.
Again?
Come on.
Work, dammit.
Okay.
Well...
We have people coming to shoot us.
Yeah.
We have people coming to shoot you.
Oh, my God.
We did it.
There's a way over here, but there was also a other area all the way on the other side.
Oh, gas.
Sweet, sweet gas.
My waifu will...
She will be mine.
Oh, my God.
This is how your waifu's become 3D.
No, 3DPD.
We won't...
Oh, there's a dead guy here.
Wait.
Where are you?
I'm looking at a dead guy.
Whoa.
Where did you go?
He is not looking so hot.
Where the fuck did you go?
Did you go this way?
I split up.
Oh, we definitely split up.
I split up, Doki.
Chloe.
Okay.
Oh, wait.
What?
What the hell?
I brought you back.
The fisherman must have bothered over from the Duke of Milan.
You think it still works?
Looks like it's got a little juice left.
Wait, they were here?
Maybe a couple of minutes.
Should we bring it with us?
I mean, it's heavy.
Yeah, take it.
Still, you should.
Might as well.
Yeah, why not?
Hell, yeah, we should.
Half the boat is submerged.
Yeah.
The crows.
Uh-oh.
Oh, no.
Just when we need to...
Yeah.
You're right.
Oh, no.
This is where he's going to shoot himself?
Wait, what the fuck?
Oh.
Oh, he's...
He's totally lost it.
Yeah, he's crazy.
Uh-oh.
Oh, you see it?
Uh.
Wow, imagine the smell in there.
It's so good.
Is it a ram?
Let's see.
What is he doing?
That's the guy...
There's the...
Oh, there's the thing!
The after the pole!
What is he trying to do?
Is he going to cut him?
He's opening... He's going to open him up to see his secrets.
There's gold inside him.
Open him up!
Open me up!
There's gold inside!
Oh, he's hallucinating.
He's hallucinating again.
You could totally like scare him.
Just be like...
I see you.
Oh my god.
Okay, okay.
Don't you dare.
Don't you dare fuck this up.
Okay.
There's a lot of pressure here, Doki.
There's a lot of...
There's a lot of pressure.
No, I didn't!
I didn't fail!
It sounds like you.
You failed.
Avoid Olsen?
Uh-oh.
What are we supposed to do?
I have time to read notes, right?
Okay.
Wait, what?
Oh my god.
There's mucho texto.
Wait, what?
Human bodies that have undergone mistreatment.
I don't think we have time to read!
Okay, I'm coming.
What's going on?
Oh, what's going on?
Oh god!
Hide!
Oh.
We've got to split.
What?
Split?
We've got to split!
He's holding something.
I'm just going to check it real quick.
There's something in there!
Holy shit.
I swear to God...
I swear to God.
I was just curious.
This guy, he can only, he's, you know, he can only hallucinate and...
He'll hallucinate us, killing us, it's fine.
Where are we gonna go anyway?
Oh no, again?
Oh god, oh god, please.
You can have all the gold, and I'm to be left here to die.
But I am...
Rin, Rin, I swear to god!
I told you it's so much pressure!
I knew it!
I knew I shouldn't have given you the pressure!
If I can't give you pressure, then okay!
It's fine, we'll just kill him!
We'll just kill him!
I joked!
I told you I sucked at giving you pressure!
See, it's fine!
Just keep going!
Just keep...
Bradley, please.
The doors are rusted.
Come on, we gotta keep going.
This is where he tries to shoot, where he tries to shoot himself.
Yeah, this is the guy that I saw shoot himself.
Slow.
Real slow.
Then we'll get a gun, it'll be fine.
Yeah, real slow.
Okay.
Why is he here?
None of that.
No changing.
Put your hands up!
Slow.
Yeah, why is he here?
How did he get here?
Not like that.
What do you mean, not...
I said, no changing.
What?
Mint, I swear to god.
It's so cute!
I'm not... I'm not...
Please, we've got no problem with you.
Mint, I swear...
We just wanna get out of here.
Please.
I'm sorry, but if you're breathing, then you don't get much of a choice in the matter.
You don't got a say.
What?
What do you mean?
Oh, he's seeing him.
He's seeing him.
Not again.
It's all gone changing on me.
Oh, the gas.
What?
What's changing?
The gas.
Stay away.
Stay back from the mist.
Oh my god.
Wait, what's happening?
Stay back from the mist.
Oh, there's a man!
Oh, there's a man.
Don't breathe the mist.
The man in the den.
Oh my god, I saw him too.
Don't breathe the mist.
The mist, the mist.
Oh, oh, I'm gonna say nothing.
Really?
I'm gonna say nothing.
You coward, you coward.
Inside with us.
Now.
Please, just calm down.
Why did you say something?
Why did I make the decision?
It's in one of us.
Isn't it?
We have to convince this on him.
It's in him.
We have to say it's in him.
Oh, yeah.
I'll say I haven't breathed...
I don't...
I don't know.
I haven't breathed any weird mist.
Please.
I promise.
My deceitful went up.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah, you breathed in the mist.
No.
I'm gonna say no.
It's happening.
You breathed...
Yeah, Bradley, you breathed...
I can feel it.
You breathed in the mist.
No.
He's gonna shoot Brad.
Shoot Brad.
There is no...
There was something back...
Oh, what are you doing?
There is no mist.
There was something back there.
Okay.
All right.
Look.
I think he's gonna shoot Brad.
Uh-oh.
He's gonna shoot Brad.
Oh, you just killed...
See?
All right.
We won it.
Did you breathe it in?
No.
Say no.
We held our breath.
Oh.
No.
Look.
We held our breath.
We did not breathe any of that stuff.
I fucked up.
Brad's gonna die.
I think you...
Brad is too...
I fucked up.
We've been down here for hours.
You've been holding your breath this whole time.
It's true.
You're holding your breath right now.
Uh-oh.
It's in me.
Wait.
You did it.
I did it.
We did it.
It's in me.
Isn't it?
We did it.
How do...
He's gonna shoot...
What if he shoots us first?
He's chasing me.
Okay.
Come on, man.
Come on.
Shoot yourself.
The mist.
Persona.
What the hell would they grab this sword this draft?
Wait.
What are you doing?
What do you do?
You decide.
Stop.
Stop lying.
You can only see it in me, can't you?
What did you..
Come on.
I didn't say anything.
Why are you making him stall?
Oh...
Oh there it is.
Oh maybe.
Maybe?
We did it!
Let's go!
We killed another man!
Murder is the option!
Wait, why don't you keep the gun?
Is it empty?
Someone's like, you could have saved him.
Wait, we're supposed to save him?
Oh.
No, it wasn't our premonition!
It was our premonition!
I thought we were supposed to kill him!
Oh, I'm flished.
Oh, it's 4.44 AM.
How spooky.
Oh my god, so spooky.
Yeah, they took us hostage.
Why are we supposed to save him?
He's the bad guy!
Doesn't sound like my problem.
There might be some more gear down there.
Murderers of Medan!
We were the murderers all along!
Oh, they're going down.
Okay.
Why are we saving the kidnappers?
Oh my god!
I swear to god.
No, I'm Fliss.
I'm Fliss.
Okay.
I think it's all you.
I'm doing this then.
Yeah.
Okay.
Are you doing it right now?
Yes, I am.
Mess up.
Hey.
I had a good track record with this!
It's on you!
How do you mess this up?
It's too much pressure!
The moment I give you pressure, you do better!
I don't understand how that works with you!
When I stress you out, you actually mess it up!
Oh my god!
There's a man down there!
The man of Medan!
The murderers of Medan!
Come on!
Let's go!
Why can't I walk fast?
Come on!
Move, Fliss!
Move!
Move you!
I'm trying!
She's so slow!
Every time I pass it, it says, Mint failed it.
Even though you don't have to do it.
Even the game says you failed it.
What if it calls me out?
Oh!
You disappeared!
Over here!
Where did you go?
I'm here!
I'm heading over!
I'm slowly heading over!
Oh my god...
Hello?
Oh no, what's that?
Oh, he's coming over.
It doesn't matter.
We need that distributor cab.
Stop talking!
Here!
He had to have come this way.
He's so loud, Alex!
I know!
He's like, Hey!
It's over here!
Hey!
It's here!
This is not the way that we win.
How...
How are they gonna find us?
Oh!
Was that your hand?
I don't know.
I sure hope so.
I sure hope so, too.
I hope so, too.
Oh, uh-oh.
Wait, I don't think we can go this way.
How is there still more?
Wait, who's that?
Oh, he is!
Oh!
It's just...
Oh, he's us!
Oh!
I think we can make it across.
What?
Jump.
Are we actually gonna do it?
Here we go.
This is a lot deeper than I expected.
Yeah, it's pretty...
It's fine.
Get ready for the quick time.
What's the first one?
Oh, wait!
I don't think I had to do it!
The gases!
Oh, no!
The gases are, like, really bad here.
He dropped the hammer!
Oh, no!
Wait, what is...
Oh, what is it zooming on?
The hammer?
The hammer!
Yeah.
We'll get it.
We'll grab that.
I swear.
Do not use the hammer against me!
Oh, is he getting a heart attack?
Oh, he's gonna get scared to death!
Yeah!
He's getting scared to death now!
We have to do this...
I think we have to do this fast.
Uh-oh.
But we're gonna get hard...
Yeah!
This is the moment.
I'm not gonna make this jump, Alex.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Get the fucking...
Oh, my God!
I have to make sure I don't get a heart attack!
I chickened out!
Let's go!
Are you fucking...
Alright!
I chickened out!
I gotta make sure I don't get a heart attack.
I guess.
Oh, I'm outside.
Breathing that fresh air.
I can't believe it!
Is this actual bullshit?
Oh, yeah.
I'm fucking going as fast as I can!
I'm going, too!
I'm pressing LB!
LB!
Is this it here?
Oh, I can't see anything.
Oh, my God.
This is pitch black.
I'm going to the door.
It's fine.
Wait, what's...
Who's that?
Who's that down there?
Oh, my God.
Hold on.
I think those are bodies.
Wait.
That's a guy right there.
Oh!
Of course.
But they will shrink your movement.
Notaries indicate that...
I'm coming.
...M5 platoons have gone missing.
What?
I'm coming.
Hold on.
Are there any notes?
Oh, there's a lot of stuff in here.
There's a lot of stuff in here.
Hold on.
I'm trying to figure it out where he is.
He's dead.
It's fine.
Diplomat immunity.
Oh, no.
The rats.
Water purification.
There's rats eating the dead body.
Already?
Why do you get to go outside?
I'm reading.
I'm exploring.
It's kind of nice.
Oh, my God.
I saw a dead body.
He was just chilling though.
Manifest a personal effects.
Oh, no.
The dog died.
Oh, these are the guys that died.
Oh, no.
Oops.
I'm trying to figure it out.
I see the car.
Okay.
Oh, no.
Oh, there is a rat.
I gotta go.
Oh, no.
It's the rat.
I'm trying to figure it out.
No.
I'm going to close this one.
Good.
I'm freaking out!
I'm freaking out over the rats!
Oh, I see you freaking out over the rats!
Chill out!
What the hell?
What is going on?
What the fuck was that?
What's going on?
What?
Decide well, I guess.
Who are you?
That's me!
Don't do anything!
Yeah, it's me.
Idiot.
It's me!
Is that you?
That's me!
Don't do anything!
It's me!
Uh oh.
I think Fliss might die.
You're the one who's gonna kill.
The game is bugging out, man.
What?
I'm dying?
Why are you dying?
What's going on?
The rats!
There are no rats!
Don't kill me!
Don't you dare!
Come on, Alex.
I'm gonna put you out of your misery, Alex.
I'm gonna put you out of your misery.
Don't do anything to me!
Stop!
It's okay.
There were no rats the whole time!
There were no rats!
Oh my god.
The game is...
The game is bugging out right now.
It's always you that's about to kill me.
I swear to god.
I know!
You were the one holding the knife!
What are you talking about?
You were a monster on my screen.
You were a monster!
What are you talking about?
You had two heads!
Well, you looked like you were getting eaten by rats, but you weren't actually...
Oh, what the hell?
Where the fuck did he come from?
Why are you there?
No way.
Did we survive everybody?
Did we save everybody?
Did we?
Oh my god!
No way!
We're back on the boat!
We saved everybody!
Oh my god!
Let's try it!
Even Conrad!
That's something crazy!
Holy shit!
Are we just gonna forget that everything happened?
We're just gonna leave this ship and just forget anything ever happened?
What about Conrad?
I thought Conrad was gonna come back for us.
I know!
I thought so too!
That fucking bastard!
He just dipped!
Oh my god!
No way!
That actually worked!
Oh there he is!
There's Conrad!
No way!
He came back!
He has a gun!
He's gonna get on the ship!
I think we killed Conrad!
They're gonna kill Conrad in the end!
Oh
shit!
Oh shit!
What the hell is this place?
Oh it's inviting him in!
Oh there he goes!
Oh no!
There he goes in!
Oh my god!
Conrad!
You're gonna die Conrad!
Conrad no!
Is it abandoned?
Do we get a choice?
No.
Just let him die.
No way!
We saved him!
Just for him to go back to the ship!
He has his airpods on!
Where is the ghost guard?
He just got up on the ship!
Where did he get in here?
Oh my god!
The sequel?
The sequel is Man of Conrad!
He was trying to help us to get help but he doesn't know anything about boats or sailing.
Oh it's like the Until Dawn ending!
Yeah!
Or they do the interviews and stuff.
Oh!
It's just her being sad about Conrad!
That's it!
Conrad!
He's just chilling!
No way!
That's the ending!
No fucking way!
We're like where's Conrad?
Technically we saved everybody!
No way!
That's the ending!
Oh my god!
What is he gonna say?
Is he just gonna stare at us?
Come on!
Congratulations!
All your charges are still breathing.
And that's something.
That's really impressive for us I think.
Yeah!
Well it really is!
Things became a little intense but Alex kept his nerve.
We were not trying to save people!
It's all about decisions, isn't it?
Decisions made in a hurry.
In a panic.
Made with the heart instead of the head.
Or vice versa.
Sometimes those decisions take a long time to have repercussions.
But there are repercussions.
There are always repercussions.
Yeah, Conrad's dead now.
We don't know that!
There's no proof!
I think so!
I think he's dead!
Did we get the good ending?
The boat literally invited him in.
Until we meet again.
Maybe in Little Hope.
Oh!
But be certain.
We will meet again.
Whoa!
Inevitable.
Apparently there's a DLC.
I don't know if that guy was baiting us.
I'm skipping.
I'm skipping to the end.
Are you skipping?
Yeah, skip to the end.
There's DLC for real?
Oh, that was a joke.
Okay.
Are they vibrating?
What's going on?
Are we getting a heart attack?
Whoa, they're vibrating?
Whoa, what's going on?
Is it because of the beer?
Is it the beer?
The decompression!
I swear to God!
You killed him because of the decompression!
Oh, my God!
He got into the beer!
She's shaking a lot!
Shit!
This is decompression sickness!
We came out too fast!
Oh, my God!
Get out of here!
Come on!
Come on, Dee!
Why are they vibrating so bad?
Oh, my God!
We almost saved everybody!
We went through the credits!
Oh, my God!
I can't believe it!
Donkey, it was beer o'clock!
Please!
Beer o'clock?
Fucking beer o'clock!
Oh, my God!
We almost had a perfect run!
I can't have this!
Oh, my God!
Fucking beer o'clock!
You have to understand!
Yeah, it was after the credits, so it doesn't count!
Yes, it doesn't count, guys!
It doesn't count, guys!
It was after the credits!
It doesn't count!
What happens after the credits is not our fault!
Oh, my God!
I can't believe it!
She died from beer o'clock!
After everything we've been through!
Fucking beer o'clock got us!
Oh, my God!
Holy shit!
You know, I'm surprised, like, everybody lived.
I'm surprised, too!
Oh, my God!
That's right!
We're special!
No other VTuber plays the game like us!
We stumbled our way into victory!
You can guarantee an original experience here on our channel!
Beers of Medan!
I can't believe beer o'clock!
Are you fucking kidding me?
Why did the decompression take so long?
He said it was like a couple hours, or maybe a couple minutes.
Who knows?
That was good.
Did you like the game?
That was fun.
That was really fun.
We should do the sequel to this next time.
Is the sequel the same where we have to play two different characters?
I think so.
I heard Little Hope's not as good, though.
But I think all of these are all kind of like kusuge a little bit.
It's not the game, you guys.
It's who plays the game.
Yeah, it's who plays the game, guys.
Oh, my God.
As they say, nobody died, okay?
Anything that happens after the credits is not our fault.
Yes, yes.
Anything that happens is not our fault.
Yeah.
It might not be beer o'clock.
It could have been something she felt.
No one important died.
That's true, that's true.
Like, guys, Conrad's alive.
We probably saved Alex, you know?
Is Conrad alive?
I don't know.
Yeah, Conrad's alive, guys.
Conrad's alive.
Like how some people are like, you were supposed to save that one kidnapper.
But, like, he kidnapped us.
He's a pirate.
Yeah, self-defense.
Yeah, it was either us or him.
Yeah.
Someone was like, it's a hallucination, she's alive.
She's still on the trip, or the ship, she's like, Conrad, I waited for you.
It was like time of death beer o'clock.
God, I didn't think that that would be...
I didn't think actions had consequences.
No.
After the doctor boyfriend was like, maybe you shouldn't drink the beer.
People are saying, don't do little hope that it's actually bad.
Oh, is it actually bad?
Wait, how many games are in the anthology?
There's House of Ashes, apparently.
Is House of Ashes good?
Conrad survived up to the credits, therefore it doesn't matter.
So true!
So true.
I would very hard on those quick time events.
House of Ashes is good.
Oh, okay.
We'll do House of Ashes next.
That was really fun.
How bad are we saying, though?
In what way is it bad?
I don't mind bad if it's funny.
Is the story bad, or is it buggy bad?
Yeah.
Like, if it's buggy bad, then maybe not, but if it's story bad, we can make it work.
I thought this one was great.
It was like the perfect... Yeah, this one was good.
This one was pretty good.
The story is terrible?
Oh, okay.
Then that's perfect for us.
Yeah, pretty much.
It's like fucking, I was trying to be a mercier, and then Min here was reading a diary in a British accent, while my when we watch somebody get killed, it's like, and then Min was like, You know, whatever.
Yeah, we'll fix it.
We can fix the story.
Don't worry.
And if the story is boring, we'll just make a podcast.
Again, guys, it's not the game, it's who plays the game.
Yeah, it's who plays it.
Exactly.
What a great time.
We gotta continue the trilogy.
The anthology.
Yeah, we have to continue the Dark Pictures anthology.
Oh, god.
Okay.
Well, thank you.
I can't believe everybody lived, other than Beer O'Clock.
I can't believe it.
It just happened in such a terrible, stupid way.
Like, I thought maybe she would die on the ship and be like, oh my god, it's kicking in, and whatever.
It's the compression.
Yeah, but no.
And that one position you make.
She just collapses on the boat.
She died of cringe.
Oh, man.
Oh, my god.
It just came out of nowhere, too.
We were just like, yay!
We did it!
Also, we weren't intentionally trying to save them.
We were just, we just stumbled upon it.
Yeah.
We just, like, tripped and fell into saving everybody, somehow.
Yeah, somehow.
I mean, we did all the QTE.
Well, I failed the one QTE, the heartbeat one.
We still lived.
Whatever.
One?
The one important one.
The one at the end.
Okay.
I see we're rewriting history right now.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, the one.
I see you're not even paying attention to beer o'clock.
Beer o'clock wouldn't have happened if, I don't know, you exploded the grill.
I'm really young!
Don't do it!
Do not drink the beer!
It was beer o'clock!
The doctor boyfriend was being like, That's a bad idea!
It was fine.
We didn't care about Julia anyway.
Yeah, that's true.
She was kind of stupid.
Yeah, she was pretty much a Karen, to be fair.
She was!
Yeah, so it's like, you know, Alex could have got so much better, you know?
Yeah.
Yeah, he saved him from a marriage.
Now Alex is gonna fall in love with Flix.
Yeah, Flix.
Flix, yeah.
They have to fix him.
Yeah.
Yeah, Flix is so much better.
Yeah, Flix almost got together with Conrad.
Oh my god.
They were making out.
Yeah, yeah.
And then we saved them.
We got Flix for Alex now.
He's a strong woman.
I can't believe Conrad just literally, like, front of the boat, like, barges into the ship.
Yeah, where was the coast guard?
Like, he just went there by himself.
I don't know.
He was clearly not driving the boat.
No!
Yeah, so it makes no sense.
Why was he the only one there?
Yeah, I was like, we're the coast guard.
Where did the coast guard go?
Also, how did he get the coordinates?
Yeah, how did he?
How did he get the coordinates?
Well, we gave the coordinates over the radio, but how did he know to go with, like, what?
Yeah, but then, like, the thing is, they were on the military boat.
Yeah, exactly.
Everybody else was also on the military boat.
Yeah.
So, like, I'm so confused.
Why was there nobody behind him?
Oh my god.
Alright, everybody lived.
Everything that happens after credits was a hallucination.
Someone said if you don't get the distributor cap, you get rescued by the coast guard.
Oh!
So you picked up the cap.
You told us, you told me to pick up the cap!
Okay, but like, if we picked up the cap, then, like...
Doki killed Conrad.
Would Conrad be on the boat?
He'd be on the boat and then be like, oh my god, we're rescuing you guys!
Okay, I think we're getting gaslit.
I think we're supposed to get...
I think we're supposed to pick it up.
I don't know.
I think we're supposed to pick it up, I'm pretty sure.
No, because we called the coast guard.
They were coming.
They were on their way.
This cannot be on me.
I am not.
Wait, so, so like, if we didn't pick up the distributor cap, we would have seen Conrad on the boat?
Yeah, I think so.
I think so.
Yeah, they were on their way.
Someone said not picking up gives you the better ending.
How do I not pick it up?
Do I just, like, not do it?
Like, I don't understand.
How do I not pick up the cap?
Oh, they would have ran into each other.
Guys, I gave you guys a different, I gave you guys a cooler ending.
I think actually the ending we got was so crazy.
Yeah, the ending we got was so much better.
It was actually so much better.
Like, do you guys really want to get rescued by Conrad?
Come on.
Someone was like, you got the better ending.
Now the world is protected from Conrad's frizz.
We took out both of the siblings.
It's fine.
Yeah, we got two for one special.
Great.
Anyway, thank you, Doki.
This was a good time.
That was a good time.
GG.
We'll come back for the next Little Hope.
Whatever one we decide to play, I guess.
Yeah, yeah, we'll come back to that.
GG's.
Alright, we're gonna talk to you in our chats now.
Alright, see you mid.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
Give me one second, you guys.
Give me one second.
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la Da-da-da-da-da-da-da Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da I'm sending you over.
We're going to America.
Bye.
Chup-chup.
Yay!
Let me put on some BGM.
Oh my gosh, I'm so tired.
My brain, once again, is just melted from this.
From this.
What's this?
There we go.
I hope you guys liked it.
I hope you guys had fun.
And stuff that was an experience.
And there you go.
Thanks for the 20 gifted.
Cooper, thanks for the 5 gifted.
Thank you guys so much.
Thank you for all the Super Chats and all the don't-knows and everything.
I've been looking at them.
So sad Julia died of natural cause.
Thanks for the pink.
Watching you two together is my beer o'clock.
Oh my god.
No, don't die.
I hate it.
That was fun.
Anthology was so goofy.
I know.
I kind of love them.
I love them so much.
I think that one's my favorite.
Just because it's like...
It's like my...
I like that it's kind of based...
Well, I guess it's Little Hope also based on a true thing.
I don't know.
But I like that Man of Medan is actually based on a true thing.
It makes it a little bit more interesting for me.
Peak comedy.
Mint Doki Kusage's winning formula.
Oh, that was my controller.
Winning combo.
Glad I caught this.
Thank you!
You guys trolled the narrator guys so hard.
Spoiled my beer o'clock.
Gosh, that was so funny.
I can't believe of all things he just ends up dying.
We Conrads never hear our names said in media so this was an absolute treat hearing y'all say Hi Conrad.
Conrad's gonna die.
For your beer o'clock.
Oh, thank you.
Thanks for the great collab.
Thank you!
That was one of the most hilarious brain rotting collabs of all time.
I'm glad that we were able to get through the whole thing.
I was wondering if...
Because I wasn't sure how long the game was so...
But glad it...
Glad it ended up working out and that we were able to just complete it.
I think it's longer if you do it by yourself because obviously you're going to be going back and forth between people more but...
Yeah.
It's a good length.
I think so too.
That was so fun.
Longer if you're solo and thorough.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Also I was like kind of skimming the notes.
I've been craving for someone new to play this and you guys were so fun.
Thank you!
Yeah, it's like you don't really see it very often played.
I mean, it is kind of kusoge but it's so fun, right?
Thanks for another silly collab.
Also my postcard came in today.
It looked like it was in condition.
Yippee!
I already ordered the new postcard so...
You'll have two of them!
I can't believe we didn't get the death POV.
We did!
Kind of.
I don't know what's up with me and the heartbeat ones though.
They really stress me out.
But um...
You know...
Whatever.
It's fine, everybody lived.
Pre-credits.
Both of you are so cute and silly.
Man, okay.
It's getting late so I'm gonna head out now.
I hope you guys had fun.
I hope you guys have a great night or a great day or whatever.
And um...
Thanks again for watching.
Thanks again for hanging out.
It's been so long since you've had a beating heart.
It freaked you out I guess.
True!
True.
What's the stream tomorrow?
Uh...
I can tell you it will start at the same time as today.
I actually have no idea because I've been so busy getting ready for Anime Expo and stuff.
Oh my gosh.
When I tell you...
So yesterday... Yeah, yesterday was Sunday.
Yesterday, Matara and I recorded um...
recorded...
The collabs between Mint and Doki are some of the best collabs of all time.
Thank you, I'm glad to think so.
Um...
Uh...
She and I recorded Sunday.
We recorded two things on Sunday and then we recorded two things today for the podcast.
So I'm just like...
I have not had a chance to even think about anything.
So um...
Uh...
Like we recorded yesterday's... or today's podcast.
We did it all yesterday basically.
And Saturday night.
No, we did Saturday night.
Then yesterday.
After I did two streams.
And then...
And then we did two more today.
My brain is a little bush so...
It might be pretty chill tomorrow.
Maybe like...
If you'll allow me.
And um...
Then Wednesday will be Metal Gear.
And Thursday is... is Anime Expo.
So...
Did you buy any of those games?
I did actually.
Actually, so it's really funny because I had them all in my cart.
I should have probably just wishlist them.
But they were all in my cart.
And then I had to buy Man of Medan.
So I was just like...
Oh, I'm not gonna remove all of them just to buy...
Buy one.
Thank you!
Thank you, Tri-Princess!
Um, so...
I just bought them all.
I got Bloons from the same sale.
Yeah, it's on like super sale!
And it's so fun.
Hmm...
When you brought up Mata's stream from Friday, I knew you all had recorded it like yesterday.
Yeah, it was like really, really...
She wasn't... She hasn't been feeling well, so...
It's been kind of hard to get our...
I have to change the thing on the menu.
To today's episode.
Wait, I think I have it.
Hold on.
But it's been kind of hard with our schedules lately.
I'll be honest.
So, um...
But, you know, I think that's like the hardest thing about kind of doing the podcast so far has been just kind of being...
Oh, I don't think I have it saved.
Never mind.
Is having our schedules aligned.
So...
She says she's getting better.
Yeah, a little bit.
She still has a cough sometimes, but...
Renski!
Thanks for the 5k!
Thank you!
Um...
Also, Grant...
I see or don't know.
Have you seen Deadly Premonition?
It's 1.24 on Steam.
I did get it, actually.
You need a lot of fan patching.
I got it because...
I want to play Deadly Premonition.
But I know that the Steam one is not very good.
But I got it because, I mean, it was a doll loop.
And I like having options.
If, you know, the Switch version doesn't work out.
So...
MiniSkoda, I saw you!
Thank you for the 5k!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
My birthday is coming up on the 3rd, but I won't be able to be here since I leave for AX.
Oh no!
Can I get a quick happy birthday?
Also, I'm excited to see you this Friday.
You're gonna be there?
Thank you!
Oh my gosh, Friday.
I have to practice my songs.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, dear weeaboo danger.
Happy birthday!
Yeah, um...
What was I gonna say?
Yeah, I have to practice my songs.
For Friday.
Oh my gosh, I'm so nervous.
I'm so nervous!
Alien Isolation is also $10.
Thank you for letting me know!
I'll go at it.
How much is it usually?
That game stresses me out though.
That game stresses me out.
Hmm...
Mmm...
Mmmmm...
Wait, there's a season pass?
What's the season pass for?
Beer O'Clock...
Hey, doggy.
Hahaha
If anyone invites you to explore a giant trending abandon ship.
Just- Fr- Frig... Fridgerate..
What's that mean?
Anyway, okay.
I'm gonna go because I got stuff to do.
So... and I gotta rest.
Thank you guys so much.
I hope you guys had fun.
Thank you as always for hanging out.
And I will see you guys tomorrow for Probably Blues.
Probably Blues.
I managed to get my hands on the MGS vinyl collection.
I'm so hyped.
Yes, me too!
Except it doesn't come out until October.
I'm so sad.
Only caught the last half so I'll have to watch the vibe.
You should give Still Wakes the Deep a try for a whore.
Still Wakes the Deep.
Thank you for letting me know.
Oh, wait a second.
Oh, actually!
This is on my wish list.
This is what Matara and I talked about in the podcast.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thank you for the rest.
Thank you for the stream.
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you.
14 endings?
Wait, what has 14 endings?
There's 14 endings for Man of Medan?
No way.
Good luck everybody.
Holy shit!
Why are there so many endings?
Oh my god.
I mean, I guess there has to be an ending for like...
Each person dying and each person surviving.
I'm looking at the video and it's one hour long of it.
What the hell?
Yeah, because of who lives and dies and if you call the radio or the boat.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh my god.
I guess it's time to watch them all.
I want to see how people die.
Okay.
I'm heading out.
What?
Enjoy!
Thank you for the video!
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Ah, there it is.
Thanks, Grant!
Okay.
Thank you guys!
See you later.
See you tomorrow.
And...
Yeah, I'll probably just play Bloons.
Okay.
Bye!
Have a good night!
Bye bye!