I was in stream... no, the studio mode.
That wouldn't make sense... oh my gosh.
I was just checking the sound.
I was making sure you could hear the...
I was making sure the game volume was on.
Hi everybody!
Welcome to Left 4 Dead 2!
That's how I check the audio.
I'm not in yet with everybody.
Oh, I need to set up probably Fugi too, don't I?
Oh, she's a pervert, you guys.
I saw what she was doing.
I saw.
I saw the pictures that Hanya was taking.
She's playing Bunny Garden.
She just posted in the group that she was like...
She was like, could you guys give me 5 minutes?
I'm so sorry.
8.15?
That's so long.
I'm ready whenever.
Takes 1 to know 1.
Happy Friday.
Happy Friday!
Yippee!
What was that?
Sorry, I'm a little unprepared, I think.
Log in with Discord.
Authorize.
Blah, blah, blah.
Wait, how do I do this?
Oh, group.
And then, don't look.
Don't look.
Said don't look.
Okay.
That should be good.
Whenever I join.
Whenever I join the voice chat.
Happy Friday!
What was that?
It's nothing.
I told you don't look.
I told you.
Let's see what the mods look like.
Not yet.
You must be patient.
Ducky, thank you for the gifted.
Also Spank, thank you for the dono.
And Dragos, thank you for the 10 gifted.
Wandering Taco, thank you for the 10 gifted.
Sukudragon, thank you for the 10 gifted.
Shino, thank you for the 20 gifted.
Hope I got everybody from earlier.
Hope I got everybody.
Blue Archive mods.
Oh my gosh, there were so many Blue Archive mods.
So many.
But unfortunately, I do not have any this time.
Maybe another time.
I think I picked some good ones though this time.
I think.
How are you guys?
How are you?
Good?
How was your week been?
Did you...
Yo man, let me get that Berg, please.
It looks so good, right?
Did you get the Shrek tank at least?
No, I haven't.
But I don't have it enabled.
Because I used the Shrek tank last time.
You know what?
I gotta do stuff that you guys aren't gonna expect.
Okay?
Um...
Prepping the ladies to destroy Bricky.
Who?
What?
Destroy what?
Is that a character in this game?
Hello, welcome to my membership.
Hello, hello.
Hello, happy Friday.
Anyone else watch the amazing Digital Circus?
Oh my gosh.
I was like in the middle of the episode.
And then I was like, oh.
I'm gonna take a shower.
And then I took a shower.
And then I was like, oh.
I haven't watched this week's...
I'm so late.
I didn't watch this week's Blue Archive yet.
So I watched that instead.
I didn't watch that instead.
But yeah, the Digital Circus came out.
Like, oh my gosh.
When I saw it, it was insane.
I was like, it said it had come out 49 minutes ago.
And then it was already at 1 million views.
So I don't even know.
What is it at right now?
Just wanna let you know.
I've started to get more MGS brain rot because of you.
And started streaming Metal Gear recently.
Have fun.
Thank you.
Yippee.
1.5 in 2 hours.
That's crazy.
All the children are probably like...
Digital Circus.
You know?
Probably like, oh.
Um.
Thank you for waiting.
Wait.
Henya.
Who is your favorite girl?
Who is your favorite girl, Henya?
A wonder.
Yeah, today I'm playing with Henya, Matara, and Haruka.
Again, we played last week.
We played Helldivers 2.
Um.
Which.
Oof.
Man.
I'm so.
Oof.
But um.
We are playing Left 4 Dead 2 today.
Yippee.
And I've got some silly mods all set up for you guys.
You guys.
So.
Did you download the Solid Snake mod?
I.
I did.
But um.
I did not have it enabled.
Um.
I know.
Shocking.
I thought you said no mods yet.
When did I ever say that?
Could I get an early happy birthday from Sultry Voice Minto?
Happy birthday, Mic Mac.
This is Sultry.
I was trying
to think of something like... something else to say.
Happy birthday, Mr. President.
Don't look, Haruka.
It's... good.
Don't look.
She was surprised about bunny garden.
Rin-chan, my Oshino waifu.
Rin-chan, so cute.
We have the same bunny girl.
Yes, sir.
No, sir.
Certified Minto Mancini moment.
What do you mean by that?
Do the MGS5 birthday song.
Happy birthday, congratulations.
Happy birthday, salutations.
Happy birthday, may your skies be blue.
Happy birthday to you.
Why are you clapping?
Because it's a song.
You're clapping it, don't you?
Don't you?
I love that.
I love that birthday song so much.
I wonder...
But Tara's not even looking at the chat.
Is it safe to stream this?
Yeah, I streamed on YouTube and they didn't hate me.
I don't even think my stream got demonetized, which is so...
I mean, well, to be honest, I didn't get that bad, that far.
You know, sometimes in bunny girl, the bunny garden game, it gets like kind of, you know, whoo.
But...
I think we were good.
Typical Akiba arcade clapper.
You shut up.
You shut the hell up.
Shut...
How dare you?
How?
That was the most offensive.
That was...
Huh?
Neat, ma'am.
You good in two mins, Henya?
We're all good.
It's you, Metara.
It's you.
I think we're all good, Metara.
Yeah.
Oh my gosh, it's already been almost 15 minutes.
It's already been almost 15 minutes.
That's crazy.
Oh.
She said, I have been ready.
And Metara started the call.
Okay.
I'm going into the call, you guys.
I'll see you guys later, okay?
I'm going in.
Great.
Thank you for coming.
Hello.
Oh, hello.
Hi.
Oh my god, Mint, that is so embarrassing.
What?
That's so embarrassing.
What did I do?
I can't believe you did that.
Oh, sorry.
Am I the cringe?
Oh gosh.
Henya did not like that.
No, it's okay.
I was thinking about Rin-chan.
Me too.
I do, honestly.
Have you all been playing that bunny game that Haruka bought?
Yes.
Sell the game to me.
Okay, you go into debt.
You give all your money to bunny girls and then you can give them gifts.
You give them like, Gucci.
You give them...
Gucci?
Yeah, it's Gucci with a Q.
I gave them panties.
Yeah!
Oh yeah, you can give lingerie.
You can take their picture.
It's like a dating sim.
But they take your money.
Yeah, and you can drink alcohol.
Yeah, you drink alcohol!
And you can take a picture with them.
No, not with them, but you take a picture of a girl.
And you can pick a pose, what pose you want her to do it.
And stuff.
You can go on vacation with them.
Yeah, that's what I'm trying to do.
Are we just gonna glaze over the fact?
Oh, giving underwear to these women who are working?
It's a gift.
You're giving them the gift of lingerie.
They like it.
So my favorite game in Yakuza 0 was the hostess game.
Oh, you'll love this then.
You'll love this.
You'll love it.
But people are gonna know that I'm a pervert.
I don't want them to know that.
That's okay.
I don't want them to know that I'm a pervert.
It's a secret.
You just said you were.
Just now.
No, no, no.
It's a secret.
Nobody's gonna really know.
I'm like, haha, I'm joking on screen.
How would they know?
They're never gonna know.
They won't know.
What?
Did I just buy a game where I can give underwear to women?
Yeah, you're a little pervert.
They'll love it.
Hentai.
No, no, hentai.
It's called socializing.
I think I'm very good at getting good at socializing now.
It's so true.
Before this, I would be too scared to go to a bunny girl bar.
But now, I think I feel very confident.
I live there!
Oh, my God.
So this is the socializing in 2024?
Yes!
Okay.
I think I'm learning a lot now.
Yeah.
Henya and Min, since you played the game, who do you think would be my favorite girl in the game?
Din chan.
I haven't talked to anyone except Din chan.
Din chan bunny garden?
Din chan is best girl.
Yes.
Din chan is my wife.
Yeah.
Wait, she's my wife, Henya.
No, she's my wife.
Henya, I think you need to find...
Henya, she looked at me first, Henya.
Min, I thought we got married and now you say your wife is Min chan?
When did we get married?
When did you guys get married?
What?
Why wasn't I there to help with the marriage?
I know we're married.
But how can I help with this marriage?
I mean, it'd be wise to, Henya.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I now pronounce this marriage hikimori and death.
Hikikomori.
You may now play the game.
Yay!
Because kissing is illegal.
You may now gift lingerie to your girlfriend.
Yay!
Min chan!
Okay, Henya.
Let's go and see Min chan together.
Yay!
Yes, everyone.
Thanks for coming to this collab.
It was very short, sweet.
But everyone, I'm going to play in this bunny game now.
Live reaction.
At the beginning, that's the three girls that you get in the game?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think the little blue haired one seems really cute.
She is very cute, but she's like...
Everybody's cute.
Yeah, they're all cute.
She's like the cool type.
She's like a...
Oh, I love cool women.
Maybe you'll like her then.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, you have her.
We'll have Min chan.
I'm joking.
What about you, Haru?
Of the three girls on the picture, is there one that speaks to you the most?
I think the alcohol is speaking to me a lot.
The one in the middle.
Do they all have breasts that big?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, everybody has a big booboo.
Yeah.
Oh, I didn't even realize about the breasts.
I was staring at the ears.
Look at their panties, too.
When I had my nii-fei sponsor...
You can look at their panties, too.
Don't worry.
Yeah, don't show your panties.
Yeah.
She didn't see any of the women's.
I'd be like, wow, her butt is jiggling while she's shooting the gun.
And Haruka was like, what?
I didn't even notice that.
Look at her butt.
Isn't it huge?
I literally was just staring at the alcohol in their hand, as well.
I was like, oh, that's a nice alcoholic drink.
Yeah, there's a lot of alcohol in there.
I just got an alcohol, actually.
My first alcohol of the week.
Whoa.
They have a wine in the game.
Yeah.
Oh, I love wine.
No, I'm having a little bit of cognac.
I'm going to stop the game.
I like the fact that the short-haired girl has like a gradient black to blue in the tips of her hair.
Oh, yeah.
That's what I like.
That's so cute.
I like her hair a lot.
Yeah.
It's like my hair.
You like my hair?
It is actually kind of like Mint's hair.
Your hair is white to blue, so it's sort of there.
Yeah.
Yeah, sort of, sort of.
But Nichan is the best.
Yeah, Nichan is so cute.
Holy shit, you're getting cocked, you jerk.
She just got married and she's already replacing with a virtual wife.
That's so sad.
That's kind of the reality of things, isn't it?
Yeah.
Nothing can beat two feet.
This is my life now.
Can you girls join off me?
Because I'm trying to invite you on my screen right now.
Oh, it keeps...
Your name keeps like popping up.
It just says Mataraka and over and over and over.
I think it's like the games try to remind you I exist.
It's like...
It keeps just saying Mataraka.
Don't forget about me.
It's like scrolling.
I'm like clicking Henya invite and Mint.
Is it sending you the invite?
Oh, I just got one.
Nice.
Wait a minute.
I'm trying to.
Play a game.
Is normal difficulty okay?
Harder?
I only played this game once for two hours a few years ago.
Yeah, normal is good.
Normal is good.
Yeah.
Good, good, good, good.
Wait, how do I...
I click my name.
Oh.
I go away.
Hold on.
I'm getting rid of Steam.
You guys did get my invite, right?
Because I know Mint is in here.
Yeah, I'm in.
Awesome.
Yay!
I'm excited.
Wait, is that a hiccup?
I was burping This is very cute.
It's not.
Shut the fuck up.
It was so cute.
I will literally strangle you with Rin-chan's bunny ears and you can't do this shit.
Oh my god.
Stop.
You're turning me on.
Wait, what?
I don't think you realize that.
Oh, don't look.
Don't look, everybody.
I'm going to be Nick.
Actually, no.
What people like that?
Hold on.
Yeah.
The game crashed.
Oh, no.
Did the game really crash?
Yeah.
Hold on.
I'm rebooting.
Reloading.
Man, you're laughing.
When I was in the loading screen, I thought that was part of the game and I was severely freaked out.
Scared?
Yeah.
I was a little scared.
I was like...
It's like a little girl laugh.
God, I hate...
I hate it so much.
Oh, god.
Cute.
You guys pick characters.
Oh, my god.
I still have the mons on.
So, this is going to be fun.
I have my mons on, too.
I'm so excited.
I want to see.
That's why I'm laughing.
For me, Fit, you pick Coco Kiru from Hololive on my end.
Oh.
Yeah.
I'm Woody.
Wait.
Like from the Toy Stories?
Yeah.
Nice.
That's so funny.
No.
We basically...
I'm participating in like this little tournament for this game that a friend's organizing.
So, I figure I need to actually play the game before the tournament.
Oh.
Yeah.
I hope you have fun.
Thank you.
So, Hanya is going to be coach.
Who should I be?
Should I be Nick, then?
Yeah.
Whoever you want.
I'm just doing random.
If that's okay.
Whoever it gives me.
I'm going to be...
Hanya wants you to be coach.
Please be coach.
Coach?
Okay.
I'm going to be coach, then.
If there's four characters, I can be the other one.
I'll be Rochelle, then.
Okay.
Coachy.
You're the puffer fish lady from SpongeBob for me.
Hell yeah.
Oh.
The driving school lady?
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm so excited.
Nice.
Let's go.
Prices aren't the only things getting slashed.
Ooh.
All right.
Anything I need to know about the game?
My wallet's getting slashed.
Wait.
Is this your first time playing Matara?
Mm.
Oh, really?
I played, like, one time a few years ago, but I don't know if it was this Left 4 Dead or Left 4 Dead 1.
Because I didn't own this game.
Oh.
So, I don't know if I played this game or if I played the pre...
I own Left 4 Dead 1.
Okay.
Maybe it's a 1.
Just shoot.
Yeah.
I figured.
Is there, like, melee?
Is there anything, like, special that I need to know?
I think this...
Ooh.
The first level will kind of teach you the controls.
Yeah.
Okay.
I played this one.
We're in the hotel.
Yes.
Right?
Yeah.
And then we go to the shopping mall.
Ooh.
You remember.
Nice.
I played...
This is the...
I played this exact, like...
Can this wait?
Just one time.
A one-time night sale.
Is this...
Loud enough?
Because the game is kind of loud for me.
Is it?
Chad, how's the audio?
Is it...
I think I turned mine down.
I feel very loud.
Inside.
I turned mine down, like, so much.
I think those things are down there.
Is audio gone?
Yeah.
Let's see the audio.
How do I switch?
How do I switch from gun to axe?
Or can I only pick one?
You can pick a second weapon.
You have to pick a second weapon.
Oh, wait.
Oh, I guess you can only have the gun or the axe.
Yeah.
It's only, like, gun or the axe.
Or...
I'll pick the gun.
Oh.
I'll pick the gun then.
Yeah.
It's not letting me have both the gun and the...
I guess that's the...
You can pick a better...
You can pick up another gun later, so if you want to get an axe for now...
Yeah.
I think so.
Axe or crowbar is better.
What do y'all think?
I got the axe.
Crowbar!
What was that line?
It's like...
Here comes Johnny!
Here comes...
Hang on!
Oh, my God.
It's so loud.
Oh, we just moved together?
Yeah.
This game is so loud.
I had to turn it down so much.
I know.
Oh, my God.
Yeah!
I think there's no...
We're killing Teletubbies on my screen.
It's funny.
Teletubbies!
Ah!
Is it normal that...
I keep thinking the blood on the screen is mine, but it's the zombies.
It makes it really hard to see.
There's blood on screen?
You might be able to turn it down a little bit, maybe.
I don't know.
I don't see blood on my screen.
You're just getting hurt.
I see so much blood.
I got Katana!
Katana!
Oh!
Sweetie!
Oh, Kari!
Ow!
Oh, wait.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Ow!
Oh, it's not you.
It's the zombie.
Hi!
Oh, woman.
Stop!
Woman.
Go to the side.
Sorry.
Stop!
Sorry!
It was an accident.
Oh!
Oh, yeah.
It was an accident.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm coming to help you.
I'm just flashing.
It might be anyone, to be honest.
It could be anyone.
Where are you guys?
I need...
You guys wait just a minute.
I need to turn off the blood.
Turn off the blood?
Okay.
How do I turn off this blood?
Oh, make sure you don't...
Oh.
Thank you for the magnum.
Me?
Here.
I didn't give that.
This is for you.
Oh, my God.
What's wrong with you?
Oh.
Oh!
Oh, my God.
Are you hurt?
I amex倍 Are you hurt?
There's no escape.
There's meantкі.
No escape?
Is it your job, what about you guys' job?
I'm not 좋아cause you didn't love me!
I love you guys.
WHAT ARE WE DOING THIS TIME?
What is going on?
Hi, Levi!
I'm gonna soi...
What's going on?
What exactly is going on?
M.
I'm coming!
Hold on, I got you!
Behind!
Behind, behind!
Oh!
Oh, sorry!
I keep forgetting, if you get puked on, it will start a horde.
It will come towards you.
Oh no!
Oh my god.
Mint protected Matara-Khan?
That's my girl.
Get out of my way!
I'm not trying to protect you at all.
Wait, I can't hold a katana and gun at the same time?
No, you can only have like one thing.
No way!
Uh oh, it's all fiery down here.
So if I didn't use the axe, would I have less blood?
Because I cannot see anything.
I hate it.
Oh, sorry.
I thought you loved it.
Sorry, I just saw Waluigi.
Waluigi!
Oh my god.
Girls, if you see another weapon on the floor that isn't a gun, can you let me know?
Yeah!
How do I get down there?
Run!
Get adrenaline.
Run, run, run!
Should've grabbed the gun.
Should've could've would've.
What's this?
Am I stuck?
I got you, girl.
Oh, here you go.
Oh, who's getting Henya?
Henya!
Oh my god, Henya.
Henya, do you have a house with her, baby?
No!
Uh oh.
Don't get it!
Haruka behind you!
I don't think you're doing so good, Henya.
Henya, I'm trying.
Henya, I'm gonna scoot close to you.
Oh, wait.
It's okay.
Haruka on me.
Hi, thank you.
Oh, shit.
Riding Haruka.
Uh oh.
No!
There's a big guy coming.
It's okay.
He's on fire.
I need a bigger...
I need a gun.
Oh, I'm on fire now, too.
It's cuffing season.
All the da-da-da-da.
I need a gun.
I need a big boy.
Give me a big boy.
What are you talking about?
Can you...
Oh, it's a song.
Can you pick up...
Henya, there's a health pack here.
Where are you?
Henya's dead.
Yeah, okay.
Wait.
Haru.
Can I give you this health pack?
Oh, fuck.
Face rerun.
Wait.
Sorry.
Haruka!
I almost jumped out the window.
Hold on.
I'm gonna come over that way.
I'm gonna heal you in a second.
I don't know if you...
Can we...
Can we heal Henya?
Henya's dead.
No, we have to get her at the...
We have to get her at the...
The safe house.
Haru, come to me.
And I'm gonna heal you.
Come.
Come here.
Stop.
I'm happy.
Henya happy.
Why is this fire still going?
Henya, I'm so sorry.
Because it hates us.
You know?
Oh my god.
What?
Oh, we can rescue her.
I see her.
Why are they always...
Oh my god.
Help me.
I think this is starting off real nice.
Shove them back.
All right.
Let's stick together.
Maybe.
And also, you know, I lost a lot of health from like, I don't know, it was like PvP, you know, like from team.
Like, you know, like...
Yeah, it's crazy that Henya kept attacking you.
Why did you do that, Henya?
Wait, what?
Why were you attacking Mint?
No, no, no.
You gotta get good.
Not blaming on me.
All right.
Let's try this again.
Let's try this.
Just get good.
Stick together.
I am good.
I am great, actually.
I am the one beside the fire.
Greatest of all time, as they say.
I remember their friendly fire.
I can't remember.
They say that they...
Same thing about me and Mango, actually.
Mango?
Yeah.
He's a Smash player.
Oh, I can't...
And Drinker.
He's a competitive Smash player and Drinker.
He does both.
She's good to go.
Get ready.
I don't want to get a melee weapon.
Also, girls, there's drugs on the bed if you guys want some.
Otherwise, I'm going to do all of them.
Yeah.
Get away.
Oh, shit.
Uh-oh.
Watch out.
I'm coming.
It exploded on me.
I can't see anything.
Oh, I'm icky.
Freaking boomers.
I'm icky.
I'm blind and icky.
I see Garci.
Guys.
I think the whole...
I think the horde is coming.
Are they?
No, we're fine.
We're all good.
I don't know how to tell you all this.
Yeah, we're fine.
I think the horde is coming.
Reload.
Okay, fine.
Just watch this.
All right.
When in doubt, more drugs.
Where's anything?
You better watch out.
Is there anything down here?
No.
Nobody knows what underwear they like.
Lana.
Buy it with your money.
Wait.
Can I not hit him?
Oh, the bat is a little bit weaker.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, I got a defibrillator in case one of you girlies dies.
Oh, you dropped your health kit though, so...
Yeah, I'm gonna use it now and then I'm gonna drop the defibrillator.
Oh, there's a pipe bomb.
How does he want to take it?
Ah!
It's okay.
I just picked up the defibrillator for this exact issue.
Thank you.
I got you.
Thank you, Haru.
You better watch out.
Teamwork.
Tanya is gonna steal your waifu.
So that pipe bomb is actually a TMT Minecraft block for me.
Get the fuck back.
Don't shoot teammates.
I'm not trying to.
Get out of my way.
Oh, shit.
You better watch out.
What's this?
Pills?
Uh-oh.
Oh, shit.
For me, that's the Torah.
Help me.
Here we go.
I got you.
Thank you, Tanya.
My angel.
I shot him too.
Tanya, my love.
My angel.
No, I didn't.
My favorite small woman.
Anytime.
I don't know whether there's a small woman I love than you.
So that's what I saw.
Reloading.
Uh-oh.
The fire is spreading.
Watch out.
Oh, shit.
Smoker.
I'm here.
Oh, thank you.
Fuck you.
Get off my motorcycle.
Ow, John.
You better watch out.
Oh, come on.
Where?
Where's the bullet?
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, God.
Watch out.
More is coming.
Oh, I can't see anything.
I'm sorry if I shoot you.
That's it.
Is this a regular gameplay experience of this game?
Oh, my goodness.
Yeah.
Pretty average.
I can't see anything.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
People are puking.
Yeah, pretty average.
Drugs everywhere.
Pretty average.
If I say so myself.
Oh, my God.
What's a magnum pistol?
Scared the heck out of me.
It's a stronger pistol.
Is it good?
I got a banana.
For me, it's a panana.
Yeah.
Panana.
Banana.
Better watch out.
Toxic acid.
Oh, we've got to keep going.
Yeah.
Okay.
From here?
Yeah, I think so.
I think outside.
Oh, sorry.
I'm burning.
Oh, oh.
You got it?
Yeah, I got it.
Thank you.
You're welcome, Hanya.
I provide.
A room.
Nothing in it.
Min, saving your Kamiyoshi?
Embarrassing.
Um, I am slow to press.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're thinking about other women since you played that bunny garden game.
That's true.
Rin-chan is, you know...
It's not easy, uh...
Oh shit.
Oh my god!
He's on top of me!
Oh, you got him?
Oh!
A pipe bomb!
Oh, nice exploding the boomer.
Good job.
Oh.
Yeah!
Nice, nice!
Good job.
Over here, guys.
Which way?
This way?
Oh.
Beep, beep, beep, beep.
Come in!
Okay, I played, like, the one round of this game.
Is melee or, um...
Zombie Apache.
...weapons better?
Shit, shit, shit.
Depends on, I think, your playstyle, right?
Hmm.
But I think that axe is kind of...
My name's Alice.
Uh-oh, guys.
I can't see well.
I can't believe Amelia is saying that she's coach on my stream.
Guys, I think we're gonna die.
Oh!
What's happening?
I don't know.
Probably the door's open.
Just hold it a little bit.
Oh no.
Uh-oh.
Horde's coming, guys.
Watch out.
Oh my god.
Where are they?
Behind you!
Get out of here, Shrek!
Challenge it!
Oh my god!
A monster!
I'm gonna die.
Take the monster!
We won't die!
We won't...
No, I'm gonna die.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, I can't see!
I can't see it.
Oh my gosh.
Who is who?
I don't know.
Just shoot!
Oh my god.
Keep shooting.
Keep shooting!
Uh-oh.
Uh, you got it?
Oh!
There you go.
Holy cow!
Over here?
I feel like the voices are not loud and then the game is so loud.
Hold on, hold on.
I can hear you, I can hear you, Mata.
Oh, arigato.
Hold on, hold on.
Oh my god, they're all on fire!
Arigato gozaimasu.
Oh my god, Mick, your Kamiyoshi is healing me.
Thank you, Hennia.
A sweet kiss from a maiden has awoken my spirits.
I'm gonna throw this bomb at you.
I feel so awake after a sweet kiss from my love.
Over here, guys.
Thank you, Hennia, for the kiss.
Oh my goodness.
It meant it was the best kiss ever.
Yeah, I bet.
Oh my god!
It was the worst time for me to reload.
Oh my god.
I can't see anything.
I cannot see anything either.
That's okay.
Get over here.
Oh, hey, get off of me.
Uh oh.
This way?
Wait, this way?
Oh my god, how do we play this?
This is so stressful.
I think it's this way, right?
There's a meds over here.
Yeah.
Oh.
It's over here.
Hello.
Oh, hello.
There you go.
Now we're here.
Oh my god.
Okay, we're outside.
Finally.
Going to pipe bomb.
Pipe bomb.
All right, guys, I'm going to throw a big bomb.
Be careful.
Oh, you already did.
Never mind.
You beat me to it.
Oh.
Never mind.
She said...
Oh my gosh.
Over here, guys.
She said I'm throwing a pipe bomb.
The safe room.
Wait, what is the vial?
Safe room.
Oh, come here.
Come here.
Safe room time.
Here they come.
What do you mean, here they come?
Let's go.
Good job, girls.
Yippee.
Oh my gosh.
Look at you, Melee Queen.
I mean, listen.
I do what I do when I do what I do.
I do what I do.
I'm the only one that kills people with a melee weapon.
Yeah.
We'll get better weapons soon, hopefully.
Let's go.
Yeah, I think I'm going to switch to melee back again.
Switch to melee again.
I think that's good.
Also, let's heal, right?
What is this?
No, we can heal here, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll get the shot.
Can we heal it?
Yeah, I'm going to heal.
I'm going to heal.
I'm going to carry a defibrillator just in case one of us dies.
Oh, I already have...
Sorry.
There you go.
You guys are healing.
It does the California girl's dance for me.
Yeah.
Wait.
Are you for real?
Easy.
Yeah.
Is there no melee weapons here, by the way?
No, there is.
They're here.
Do you guys see a melee weapon, by the way?
So, this gun is a cat for me.
Cat?
Oh, you have the cat mod.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Dude, yeah.
It's a cat?
So, what if I shoot it?
Thank you, everybody.
There's a heart.
What?
That's cute.
What about this one?
Wait.
I don't see it.
A shotgun.
It's a regular shotgun.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
I see from my side.
That's cool.
Oh, I should get the mods next time.
I don't know if I should bring the shotgun or the can.
They're really easy to use, too.
Bring whatever you want.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
It's really easy, too.
I'm going to bring the shotty.
Yeah.
I got a shotgun, too.
Ready?
Oh.
Yeah.
Ready?
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Hello?
Oh.
Oh, shit.
I'm ready, bitch.
Oh, sorry.
What's up?
Oh, my God.
Please.
I'm always missing like an inch or two.
I feel like I keep thinking that I'm just like an inch or two longer than I really am.
Jeez.
Get off of me.
I hate that.
Does that ever happen to anybody else?
What is it?
So now your primary gun will have ammo.
I keep thinking I'm a little longer than I am.
But your pistol won't have ammo.
You're pretty long on my screen.
Oh, watch out for it.
Am I a little longer?
Oh, my God.
How do I kill it?
Ow.
Oh, my God.
Please.
Oh, shit.
I'm reloading.
I'm sorry.
Oh, shit.
I need help.
Fuck.
Get it off of me.
Oh, my God.
Thank you, Haruka.
My queen.
All right.
So your primary gun will have ammo, but your secondary gun, like your pistol, will have infinite ammo.
What do you want to do?
I don't want to go.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my God.
This is so jarring, this gameplay.
Why so?
It's like shaking.
What is this?
My whole screen.
Is there something over here?
No?
Am I going crazy?
Thank you for playing this with me.
I am having the time of my life.
It's a little crazy.
It is.
It's fun.
It's a little jarring.
Oh, yeah.
But it's fun.
Oh, there's a grenade launcher here if anyone wants it.
Oh.
Little grenade.
Oh, thank you, somebody.
Thank you.
Not me.
All right.
I can't wait to bring out this Pepsi gun.
Pepsi gun.
The craziest thing is like how much the game shakes when you're trying to do anything.
It's just so fast.
It is very.
It's a super fast, fast paced game.
Feels like so fast.
Yeah.
Which way do we go?
It's like ikuzo, ikuzo.
Here?
I heard a crying.
I don't know.
Oh, no.
That's a witch.
Shoot her.
Uh-oh.
Start over.
Ah!
We don't want to disturb the witch.
Oh.
I'm trying to kill her.
Oh, my God.
Oh, you got her.
I got her.
Oh, sorry.
I didn't realize that.
My turn.
So, the witch, if you wake her up, she'll scream and alert every single zombie around.
Yeah.
It's kind of not great.
So, she's very interesting.
Oh, zombie around too.
Apologize, but I've also never played this before.
Here, hold on.
Oh, gosh.
Wait.
Did you kill him?
Here, hold on.
My turn.
Let me heal you.
Yeah.
Please.
I'm here to let you know what every zombie does.
My maid.
Can I get a moe moe cue?
Oh, my gosh.
It's so funny.
My thing is...
Wow.
Komugi.
Yeah.
Don't worry about it.
I'm here to tell you what zombie does what I think.
Wait.
Let go.
Oh, my God.
This is better.
We're getting it.
Nice.
Didn't even moe moe cue me while she healed me.
What?
Ow.
It's time for the owl.
Unbelievable.
Are you okay, Hanya?
Oh, no.
We need more help.
I think we have to go down here.
Okay.
We'll get more help.
I'm going to go down here.
The hat is so tall.
Haruka, you're Doug Dimadome with a really huge hat.
Oh, sorry.
Doug Dimadome.
Dimadome.
Oh, my gosh.
Did I last time with this hat on?
Yeah.
You got a really tall hat on.
Oh, my God.
I'm not hitting anyone.
Oh, I got to heal myself.
Oh, my gosh.
My aim.
Oh, hunter.
Hunter.
Oh, sorry.
You guys got this.
He's like done.
Thank you.
What is this?
Oh, what is this?
Pills?
I got pills here.
Pills here.
No, that's a grenade.
So, the bio will damage the enemies, right?
Yeah, I'm hitting my teemo if I throw it.
Hold on, I want to...
Oh, yeah.
Well, I think they...
No, they gather to it.
So, they all like...
Oh, perfect.
So, it's easier to...
Oh, nice.
How do you got...
Oh.
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah, they really...
So, it's like...
They're coming from the trees.
I'm coming from the trees.
This is going to be really loud!
It came from above!
Oh my god, a chainsaw?
Where?
Right here, right here!
It can have it.
It has gas though, I'm pretty sure.
Gas, gas, gas!
I'm gonna step on the gas!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Do you like...
my car?
Shit guys, behind, behind, behind!
You got it!
I'm hearing a toad nearby.
What's that?
There's a guy here.
They come from everywhere.
Where do we go?
Oh, up here?
Listen, mothers need love too, sometimes.
Oh my goodness.
Wait, how did I get pushed off?
No
worries!
Meanwhile, getting eaten by a zombie?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Oh, don't blow that up.
Okay, wait, wait.
What if I open it and then I throw that in?
Oh, I hear something.
I hear something icky.
I hear something.
Oh gosh!
I can't see anything!
Oh my gosh.
Oh, oopsies.
Yay!
I can't see!
Oh no!
Up these stairs.
Up the stairs?
Okay.
I got a pipe bomb.
Careful.
Oh, pipe bomb, pipe bomb, pipe bomb.
Watch out.
Good job.
Oh, it's all on fire though.
Here, you go.
It'll pass.
You go.
You go, Matara.
Yeah, you go.
Give me fire!
Ammo!
What is this?
Pills here.
Is this a shotgun?
What's this one?
Oh, sniper!
Sniper.
My beloved.
I have some ammo on my hand as well if you need.
Oh, shit.
Watch out.
The spitter is...
Gross.
I need help.
Please.
My aim.
Oh my god.
Yikes.
Arigato.
God, I love my little gun.
The little gun that could, you know?
Do we go down or do we go up?
I think we go down.
We go down?
Okay.
The little gun that could, you know?
I hear something icky.
Wait, wait.
There's fall damage, by the way.
Do not do what I just did.
Oh, there's fall damage?
No way.
Oh, I didn't know there was fall damage.
Oh, there's a little blower?
Over here, guys.
A little blower.
Well, he like blows bile, you know?
Yeah.
Biohazardo.
Whoa.
Look at you guys.
I'm hearing Peter Griffin.
I think the boomer is nearby.
Peter Griffin?
Wait, we gotta go up, I think, right?
Okay, stop saying the boomer, okay?
I'm old, I know, but I'm really offended.
I can't see it.
Please stop saying the boomer.
A Molotov?
Oh, sorry.
Don't shoot teammates.
Where was that teammate?
Oh, fuck.
Sorry, I just shot a teammate.
I'm sorry.
I'm stuck.
Oh, ouch.
Oh my goodness.
Like a little rag doll.
Maybe the sniper is not so great.
This team is so fast.
I gotta be far away, though.
Girls, how come there's like no medkits anywhere?
Oh, you say?
There's a toad nearby.
I'm hearing a guy who hugs your face.
I got you!
Jockey!
I thought you said toad from Mario.
The jockey is toad for me.
Hold on, girls.
I got a little Molotov cocktail for our enemies.
There's another one in the room if you girls want to throw another one, too.
Oh, I got the Molotov.
Oh.
Oh, that was a little...
Hold on, let me get the other...
Shut up.
Let me get another Molotov.
Oh!
Oh, Chaja!
Oh, you killed it with the fire!
You killed it with the fire!
So, whoever was saying I was anticlimactic, huh?
I was fully climatic.
That was actually pretty good.
I actually hit the climax.
Oh my god!
Oh, what the hell was that?
Oh, oh my god!
I'm slowly dying, by the way, Hina.
Are you okay?
You guys are okay?
Hina's behind us!
I did it!
Why did you set us on fire?
Oh my god!
Fire!
Why did you set us on fire?
Okay, I'm coming.
Did I give you adrenaline?
Into the ring of fire!
I hate you so much!
Down, down, down!
Wait!
I lost my molotov because of you!
No way!
No, you actually hit it on the enemy.
You like hit it on the zombie.
I didn't use it.
Wait, wait, I'll heal you.
I'll heal you, Mint.
I'll heal you.
Mint also has one.
There's a bunch.
I'll give you one.
I'll give you mine.
Hina, you also need one.
I want to heal myself.
I'll hold on.
Alright everybody, I need your help.
Oh wait, Hina, I got you.
Oh, I'm sorry!
What the fuck, bitch!
Come here!
No, come here, come here!
Hold on, hold on, girls.
I need Chad's help for a good gun.
Is this the AK-47?
What's a good gun?
What's this one?
Laser sight.
Okay, perfect.
This gun at the end here...
Oh, AK rifle with the laser sight is really good.
I don't know what this one is, but I'll take it.
Oh, this is ammo.
Ammo.
Which one's the AK?
This one, this one at the end.
Thank you, everybody.
Okay, I'm gonna get a combat shotgun.
Also, is the golf club good?
Or...
Should I switch to the...
I like my grenade launcher so far.
I'll keep it.
I like shotgun.
I want this.
There we go.
I won't let you through the barricade until I get you.
What does he want?
Oh, the snacks.
I want the snacks too.
Corn?
We gotta go to the store and get some snacks for this guy.
Yay, corn!
I love corn.
Wow, she really is your Kamioshi.
Let's get corn!
How much myth do you love?
Okay, wait.
Where are they coming from?
From the store?
Everywhere.
Uh oh.
Oh.
Grenade?
Where?
I got it!
Oh my god.
Yeah, I'm coming.
I'm coming.
Oh my god.
Ah!
I'm on a jockey!
Jockey!
Help me!
Thanks, I guess.
Oh.
We have to bring the cola back to the gun owner.
Ah!
I got you.
Arigato.
Wah!
Got the cola.
I got the cola.
Protect the princess!
Oh my god.
Haruka, are you okay?
I should be fine, yeah.
Oh my god.
Oh,
sorry.
I had a guy overshot you.
I have no idea what's going on, by the way.
Sorry, I'm being quiet.
Oh my god.
I'm dying.
I'm gonna help you up in just one minute.
I got you.
Matara!
Kill the guy that's...
Okay, thank you.
Okay.
Better watch out.
You better watch out.
I'm gonna throw him up.
I think I drank him.
Where did I go?
Did you drink the cola?
I drank him.
We have to help Hanya.
We have to save Hanya.
Hanya!
Oh!
What are you being dragged by?
I don't see him.
Where is the smoker?
Oh, he's up here.
He's on the roof.
I'm gonna die.
I got him.
Someone got him.
What the hell was that?
Thank you.
Arigato.
I'm going into the store to see if there's anything to find, okay?
No, we have to deliver the cola.
Yeah, we gotta deliver the coke.
Was there nothing in the store else?
You can shoot the tongue too?
Oh, okay.
Thank you.
I like how people are saying shoot the tongue.
I've never played the game before, y'all.
I have no idea what to do.
But I'm doing my best.
I'm coming!
Doing my darn best.
I got the cola!
Going!
I
throw the bomb.
I'm throwing the bomb.
Where's the cola?
Careful, girls.
I'm still here!
What the fuck!
Take the cola!
But I saved you, didn't I?
No!
I mean, you did, but no!
But I saved you, didn't I?
But I helped, didn't I?
But you're alive, aren't you?
Woah, what just happened?
You're alive, aren't you?
I've played this so many times now, I can't even remember what's going on.
Have you really?
I thought you'd be a little bit better.
Oh my god!
Oh!
Why did I jump into the...
Help me!
My point's sad!
I wanted to feel alive!
Okay!
I wanted to feel this!
Absolutely sad.
I said what I said.
We're all done.
Okay, I haven't played this in like three years, though.
So you have to give me like a little bit of a...
Actually, no.
It's been less than that.
Just kidding.
There's not enough health packs in this game, y'all.
Oh, here's the ammo.
We need more health packs.
I'm dying.
That's the...
That's the Left 4 Dead feeling.
I am like shocked to play this game.
Always feeling like you're dying.
Watch out!
There's a...
Did I get the spitter?
I got the spitter.
It's her.
I think we have to go back.
I can't remember.
Sorry, I just shot you.
Did you shoot me?
Girl, I'm gonna die!
We're all so close to death, actually.
It's not quite...
Oh, we're going backwards?
Oh, we're going backwards.
Oh, okay.
It's actually concerning how close we are to death.
All four of us.
Honestly, me every day.
Me every day.
I can't even run.
It's me.
It's my tummy.
It's grumbling.
Can we go in?
Let us in.
Oh, guys, guys, guys, guys!
Help me, help me!
Back, back, back!
You got him.
Oh, we're going back to the market?
The market?
What am I hearing?
Oh, ouch.
Nice.
Am I missing these, like, point-blank shots?
What's going on?
What's wrong with ours?
Your age is slowing you down?
I think so, yeah.
Oh my gosh, I can't even...
I can't even run.
I'm so slow.
I only have one HP left.
Me too.
Yeah, we're all, like, right about to die.
Yeah.
We're having a shot.
Uh...
It's over.
Oh, wait.
I have a health kit.
No, I don't have a health kit.
No, no, no, I don't, I don't, I don't.
I thought I did.
My bad.
Jockey!
It's gone.
Sorry, it's because I saw the...
Yeah, I don't have a health kit.
My bad.
You're bad.
Wait, where do we go, you guys?
Haru, we're coming?
We're on normal difficulty.
If anyone's wondering.
If anyone's normal.
Oh man, oh man, oh man.
I'm going to die.
I got you, I got you, I'm right here.
No!
Come here, princess.
Get up.
One kiss from your true love.
I guess I wasn't your true love because you have, like, 4 HP.
I think we go over here.
This way.
Oh!
Okay, okay.
Are we going to make it?
Of course we're going to make it.
We're going to die another day.
As Madonna once said.
I'm going to die another day.
I'm going to die.
I died.
What?
I need a thought.
Okay.
Am I the one growling?
Is it you?
Are you growling?
I don't know, there's like somebody growling.
It's kind of sexy.
I don't know.
If it's you growling, it's definitely not sexy.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Hey, shut up.
Thanos?
Oh, fuck.
Where?
I think the boss is Thanos for me.
And I'm hearing Thanos music.
It's Metal Gear Ray!
It's Metal Gear Ray for you?
I'm constricted.
I'm dying right now.
She's dying, she's dying.
I'm dying.
How am I not able to save you?
Hold on.
I am down.
I saved you, I saved you.
You're fine.
No, I'm not.
I'm dead.
I'm shooting like some mini boss guy.
Oh my god.
Hanya, are you okay?
I'm dead.
Yeah, me too.
Where, where, where?
I have a defibrillator.
Go to the safe house and we'll be revived.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hold on, let's see if there's help here.
You're close.
We're close.
Might as well just go.
Yeah, just go.
Hang in there.
Go, just go.
Just go.
It's almost there, it's almost there.
Okay.
Look at that.
I'm hearing toad.
There's a spider right there.
Nice.
Watch out.
Saw someone jump over.
Nice.
Is this the safe room?
This is the safe room.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Oh, good job.
Amazing.
Let's go.
What is this game?
Left 4 Dead.
Yeah, this is Left 4 Dead.
I don't understand anything.
Yeah.
I think I'm too old.
My brain, I'm like...
I don't understand what's going on.
It's a lot.
It's fun.
It is so fun though.
It is really fun.
I definitely could play this again.
Wait, what's this one?
Gotta be around here somewhere.
This isn't one I had before.
Somebody said I'm pointing and clicking on heads.
I'm not.
I'm just pointing towards where the zombie is, sort of.
I don't think I'm clicking on any heads.
Sort of.
Out of these three, what's the best one?
What's this one?
I'll get this one.
Oh no, I lost my laser pointer.
It looks very cute.
Oh my god.
Is that a scratch mark?
Is that a scratch mark on your chest?
Yeah, it is.
Yummy, yummy, yummy.
I got it from when I was a kid.
I was playing Teletubbies and now I'm here.
Mrs. Puff, get out of my way.
The what?
Teletubbies scratched me when I was a kid.
Oh my god!
Hold on for the door!
Oh my god.
Oh wait, I can use my pipe bomb.
Wait, where did I pipe go?
Oh no, I don't think we need to.
There's not that many.
Oh, maybe there is a lot.
You can use your...
No, we're right here though.
Well, I remember this place.
The scary thing about using a scope in this game is you can't see anything.
Yeah, you can't really, you can't aim in this game.
It's hard to use a scope in this, yeah.
Cause it's too fast.
How do, how do?
Oh, you're fine, you're fine.
Oh.
I'm sorry I'm being kind of quiet.
I really just have to focus.
I can't see anything.
It's okay, it's okay.
I did it by accident.
But you also deserved it, you bitch.
What the?
I'm gonna get you for that with this golf club.
I challenge you.
Punch me in the throat.
Punch me like you mean it.
I'm hearing Toad, I think he's nearby.
Toad!
Toad is the jockey for me.
Oh yeah, jockey, jockey, jockey.
Oh, that's a mannequin.
Get the mannequin.
Good job.
Can I go back in the safe room and reload or is that cheesing?
You can go, I think.
Oh, spinner, spinner, spinner.
Where?
Oh, I see him, I see him, I see him!
Cute girl is yelling.
Oh my god, he's throwing.
Ouch!
I just made that shot.
Why am I taking so long to reload?
Hello?
Might be the gun you have.
Oh boy.
Oh my god.
He's down?
I think I killed him.
Is someone on me?
No?
Is someone shooting me?
I'm so happy I have that as the Thanos.
Because like, when that boss comes in, I'm hearing the Thanos theme.
And he's just running around throwing shit.
It's so epic.
What is the Thanos theme?
Revert to reload.
I think it's also because I switched weapons, so it like restarted the reload animation.
Little baby.
I have Metal Gear Ray as the tank.
Oh, you really?
That's so funny as the tank.
Nice.
I'm the vanilla one.
Metal Gear Ray, my beloved.
I know, me too.
Get the Molotov.
For me, the spinner is Waluigi, which I thought was funny.
And then the fucking, the Waluigi cart song plays when he arrives every time.
That is funny.
I have a pipe bomb.
We can um...
We can coordinate our pipe bombs and stuff, I think.
Another one, another one.
I need help, I need help.
I'm reloading.
I always reload at the worst time.
Big guy, big boy.
The charger is Shrek for me, which is funny.
That is funny.
Oh, they're coming, they're coming.
I should get a mod, I should get a mod.
Yeah, all you have to do is just subscribe.
It's so easy.
Is this like a workshop?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's so easy.
Reloading.
So you're just murdering Teletubbies?
I killed them.
Oh, I hear a voice.
I hear a sound.
I hear a voice.
Take your meds.
Sorry, sorry, I'm hearing voices in my head.
Is it this way?
I don't know actually.
Replace your low ammo.
Oh, it's fully loaded.
It's here, it's here, it's here.
Reloading.
Oh, crying girls around.
They just said.
So there's a witch.
So how does the witch work?
I think you have to kill her before she gets alerted, right?
Can you ignore it?
I think you have to kill her before she gets alerted, or you have to sneak by.
Yeah, you can sneak by.
I don't hear her.
I hear her.
Yeah, I can hear her.
But aren't the bullets going to alert her?
Just sneak around the witch.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I got him.
Oh, ouch!
Guys, I'm going to throw a pipe bomb.
We are running in the middle of this bugger!
Uh-oh.
I got him.
Nice, nice.
Thank you.
Reloading.
If anybody sees ammo, let me know.
Let's look around.
Where is he?
Is he here?
I don't have a pistol.
I have a katana.
Do you want me to heal you?
Please, I am dying.
There's bathrooms and stuff.
I'm going to check in them.
Oh, guys, there's ammo here.
There's ammo in the men's bathroom.
Thank you, Mint.
You're better than Rin-chan any day.
Yippee!
Ammo in the men's bathroom, girls, if you want.
Men's bathroom?
Yeah, men's bathroom ammo.
The other one.
The other men's bathroom.
Is there no one in the ladies' restrooms?
This one?
I can't see in here.
Ammo!
Uh-oh.
I heard something.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Big boy.
Oh, sorry if I shot you.
Happy season.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
The smoker is Ronald McDonald for me.
Oh, is he?
Hold on, hold on.
Can we take like one second before we advance?
Because my eyes in the dark with the light.
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
Are you okay, Mrs. Puff?
She's old, you guys.
I'm so old.
Stop calling me Mrs. Puff.
It's like taking me out, please.
You have to stop.
That's what you are.
You're Mrs. Puff with the skinny legs.
Oh, stop.
What about me?
What am I?
You're Garfield.
Oh, Garfield, the cat.
Yeah.
I still hear her.
Here, come out of the darkness.
Come out of the darkness.
We got to go upstairs anyway, so.
Okay.
Oh, there's the witch.
There's the witch.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
No.
It's so weird.
It's like right here at the elevator.
Even at the elevator.
I'm pinned.
Oh, fuck.
I also am pinned.
Help.
I'm gonna die.
I'm dead.
No.
No, no.
How is this game on normal?
It's so hard on normal.
Please save me.
We gotta go.
Is there no health kit?
Oh, health kit.
Yeah, I think Mint or Haru should take it.
You guys have less HP than me.
I think Haru carries better than I do.
Let me die.
It's okay.
Whatever you want.
Haru, I'm not against you taking it.
Look at her go.
She's healing.
I can tell.
Do you like my dance moves, Mint?
Are you good?
Are you okay?
Oh my god.
Oh, he was right behind me.
??
?
Could you please keep singing?
That is like such a big buff.
I have first aid needed.
Next knock down means death.
Oh f**k.
I'm dead dead dead.
There might be healing kits here girls.
Can you come with me real quick?
There might be healing kits here.
I can't see anything.
Everything's black and white.
I'm like a dog.
Boomer has vomited?
Oh there's a charger coming!
I'll hide it behind you!
Oh thank you.
Oh sorry!
Did I do that?
It's okay.
I had to help so don't worry.
Did I do that?
Hold on I got you.
Behind us!
I got you.
I'm dead, I'm dead.
I'm dead!
I'm so sorry!
I'm dead.
I got killed by Haruka!
I'm so sorry.
This is the worst
game I've ever played.
I'm struggling so much.
You've just been laying here this whole time.
I'm gonna check my music real quick.
I'm back!
Yay, I'm back!
Guys, this was rough.
This was rough.
Yes, it was.
Oh, I tried.
That was hard, but I'm gonna try.
Oh, man.
That was crazy.
You know what else is crazy?
The rats in the room.
Hey, man.
I was crazy once.
The rats.
They locked me in a room.
The rats made me crazy.
Rats.
Me and the rats.
Let's clear some stuff out a little bit before we open the door this time.
You guys are...
Guys, there's a help kit missing, by the way, here.
There's one more help kit if one of you wants to...
Oh, I didn't grab it.
I didn't grab it.
It's fine.
Grab it so we can, like, not...
Let me reload my ammo.
Rats.
Rats It's up there!
Up the stairs!
Come on, my squad!
That's where we had to go.
I'm going around people.
Tinky!
Where's the henna?
La la!
Come on, henna protection squad.
Oh, henna.
Was there Teletubbies in Japan?
No.
I think... I never really watched it.
I don't know, but I think...
But it wasn't that popular, I guess.
Really?
I don't know.
Maybe my chat in JP Bros knows about Teletubbies.
I'm not sure.
The JP Bros?
I love that.
The JP what?
JP Bros.
Like brothers?
Yeah.
I call them JP Bros.
We go downstairs.
JP Bro.
Hold on, I'm going to throw a Molotov there.
Okay.
JP Bro.
That's so funny.
Or Teletubbies.
Teletubbies.
Help me!
There's a snake in my boot.
Oh my god.
I have had it with these motherfucking snakes.
On her motherfucking breast.
There's a snake in my boot.
Oh, you said boots.
I thought you said breasts.
I'm so sorry.
Why would I say breasts?
I genuinely was like, that is so weird that you said breasts.
Why would I do that?
I'm a yes and person.
I'm an improv child.
If that is what Mint decides to be, that is what Mint decides to be.
I know it's a little late, you guys, but how is the audio?
It might be a little late.
Is that audio?
Is it audio?
Is it audience music?
No, I get it.
Thanos is back, guys.
Uh oh.
He's here.
I hear him.
Oh my god.
He's here, Brains.
Ahhh!
Oh my gosh.
Get off of me.
Where is he?
Oh, nice gun.
Oh, I'm out of ammo on, like, all of my guns so I'm going to test all of them.
I'm just gonna die, I guess.
I guess I'll just die.
Where's more ammo?
There was ammo in the bathrooms nearby, remember?
Yeah, was it here?
I think it was this way.
I think it was down here.
I guess I'll just die.
Is it this one?
There's a pipe bomb in here, if anybody wants it.
Guys, they're about to all come in through this side.
There's no ammo in here!
There's just a knife!
There was ammo in the bathroom, in the men's bathroom.
Remember?
Maybe it's in the girl's bathroom this time.
Maybe it's in the girl's bathroom.
Guys, I need help.
There's a charger.
I need ammo.
No!
They don't have it.
I think it's randomly generated where it spawns.
Oh no, I'm so bad.
I guess I'll get the knife since I have nothing else.
I'll die.
Get your knife!
I guess I'll die.
Get your nice, poopy knife!
Stinky.
Poopy.
I like how I just reload the banana every time.
I'm sticking new banana in the peel.
What was that song like all the- Ba ba ba ba.
Wait, who's that?
Well, we go upstairs don't we?
Yeah, I think so.
Upstairs here?
Oh, who's coughing like that?
Me.
Sorry.
I had a cigar.
Okay, I'm also out of ammo.
There is a gun here, Mint, if you need it.
It's a chrome shotgun.
Oh, I'll get the shotgun.
Thank you.
Behind, behind!
Charger!
Fucking trick!
Let's go!
Through here...
We're doing better than previously.
That's good.
Okay, okay.
Through this door.
There might be ammo.
What is it?
Oh, I got a defibrillator.
Oh, another health pack.
I think, Ken, you should have it, because she's dying.
Boomer.
You got him.
Sorry, Peter Griffin, but you have to die.
Oh, go!
Thank you.
Hello!
Let me one-hit these guys.
Guys, there's a little bomb there.
A little bomb.
I got it.
I'll use it.
Guys, a lot of zombies.
A lot of zombies.
Sorry if I shot you.
In here?
Anybody?
Anything?
Oh, ammo!
There's an ammo here!
Oh my god, girlie.
Where is it?
I'm reloading.
Sorry, I didn't notice.
How are you guys with health, by the way?
Because I have one extra health pack.
In my inventory.
I have pills, so I'm going to take them.
I was doing okay.
Take your medication.
I'm taking my medication, and I got the defibrillator.
Is that a katana?
You can go in this door.
Yeah.
No, that's a gun.
Oh, there's a first aid place as well here.
Oh, it's just for pills, though.
No, the pills are good.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I need pills for them.
There's a guy behind the door.
There's a lot.
I'm going to throw a bomb.
Throw a bomb!
It kind of worked, though.
They all came inside.
It kind of worked out.
Alright, guys.
There's another bomb in here.
We have to disarm the...
We have to go to the third floor now.
There's going to be endless horde.
Endless?
Bottom.
Haruka, I'm behind you.
I'm shooting the guys behind you, Haruka.
I'm shooting the guys behind you.
I'm behind.
Oh, whoa!
Haruka, I'm backing you up.
I'm backing you up.
Don't worry about what's behind you, Haruka.
Just keep running.
Just run!
Are we going to go third floor?
I'm backing you from behind, Haru.
Don't worry.
How are you guys already on the third floor?
How the heck are you guys already on the third floor?
Haruka, I got you.
I got you.
I'm behind you.
Keep going.
Oh, there's fire!
There's fire!
Watch out!
Haruka, don't worry.
Don't worry.
Just keep running.
I'm covering you from behind.
I went the wrong way.
I need to cause the fire!
Fire!
Haruka, I'm doing my best.
Oh, my gosh.
Help us!
I'm going to die!
We're coming!
Haruka, I need a second and I can revive you.
I don't know if I can revive you.
We're coming!
Girls, I need one of you to revive Haruka while I'm shooting, please.
Oh, there's vile!
There's vile!
Watch out!
Oh, gosh.
Are you both down?
Wait, what?
Does one of you have the defibrillator?
I have it!
I have the defibrillator!
Saber, Saber, Mint, I'm healing you while this is happening.
Wait, how do I use it?
Oh, I'm using it!
I'm using it!
Get it!
I'm healing you!
Mint, Mint, Mint, stop, stop, stop, Mint.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop moving.
Guys, I need your help!
No, Matara!
Matara, you need more help than I do!
It's okay, it's okay, go, go, go, go, go.
No!
Matara!
Wait, where did my...
Is my gun gone?
Go pick it up, maybe?
There's a med kit here!
I'll take this cap.
Oh, maybe I took your gun by accident.
Shit.
Actually, I think I accidentally took your gun.
That's okay.
Do you want the can back?
No, no.
I want... Can we switch?
Uh, how do I drop the gun?
Charge it around, get ready.
Where's the charger?
How do we drop the gun?
Oh, watch out!
Sorry if I shot you.
I'm assuming you had this gun in my hand, I'm assuming.
Hold on, let me accidentally pick up another gun, let's see if that works.
Is it these ones?
Did I steal your... I didn't pick up a gun.
Oh, I think I accidentally took your gun because I was pressing E.
Wait, how do I... How do I drop it?
How do I drop it?
There's a gun there.
Take the other gun, take the other one.
Where's my gun?
There we go, sorry!
Guys, guys, guys!
Okay, wait.
Did somebody drop my gun?
This wasn't my gun.
I had like a laser scope.
There you go.
That's the laser scope one, there you go.
Guys!
Thank you!
I'm taking everybody's guns, apparently.
It's okay.
Well, I picked up the one that was on the floor.
And it was yours.
I think you dropped it because you thought it was...
Maybe, maybe.
Oh my god.
This fucking hurts.
This game is crazy.
Do you want to stop playing then?
Or do you want to keep going?
Aren't you in a tournament for this?
Yeah!
I am!
Are you going to be okay?
The teams are super unbalanced.
The Flesh team is so strong.
They have people who have been content creators for this game.
But it's also not a real tournament.
It's like a friend tournament.
Oh no!
Oh, she's alive!
Oh, she's dead.
I got you.
I did it!
If you find ammo, let me know.
Sorry, I hit you.
That was my feelings.
I literally revived you.
I think I can get one hit in.
Sorry for being kind of loud, you guys.
I took you into this world.
I can take you out again.
Actually, I think it's the opposite.
Stop doing bomb!
Oh!
There's a molotov here, girls.
Molotov.
I have a bomb in case we ever need it.
Let me throw a bomb there.
Here you go.
I think they're going to explode.
Yeah!
I think I shot to myself.
Sorry.
It's okay.
God dang it.
I'm the one who took it.
At least you tried.
And that is very cute.
Are we going back downstairs?
I think so.
What is this music I'm hearing?
If you guys see ammo on the floor, let me know.
Ammo on the floor.
I think I need a gun so that you guys don't accidentally shoot me.
Yeah, you keep running in front of our shot.
Oh, ducky!
Yeah, I think I need a pistol.
Oh, my mom.
Yeah, I think so.
Over this katana.
Yeah.
The melee is like really strong but it's hard to use sometimes.
What is this music I'm hearing?
It's like an accordion.
Yeah, I think it's one of the mods that I have but I don't know what it means.
Oh, my gosh.
Thank you.
I protected my...
You keep going down!
Come on, Mrs. Coffee.
Take it easy, Mrs. Coffee.
If I die, it's forever.
Yeah, I think melee is like coffee.
I got you.
Where is the safe room?
Oh, is it?
Oh, no.
Not this one.
Oh, what?
Maybe we have to go up?
Maybe.
I'm hearing the smoker.
I'm hearing Ronald McDonald.
Oh, here he is!
I see him!
Watch out!
You got him?
Oh, that was close to my head.
What are you, son of a bitch?
Where do we go from here?
Upstairs?
Oh, people are saying third floor.
Third floor?
I forgot I had a med kit on me.
I'm such an idiot.
Oh, you have one?
Spitter!
Ouchie!
No!
Mrs. Coffee!
Mrs. Puff!
It's okay.
We'll get you.
Oh, thanks, Haruka.
This is it.
Safe room!
Nice!
Nice.
I'm coming.
Come on!
Get in!
Ta-da!
Get in, Haruka!
Get in!
Nice!
Yatta!
Good job!
Yay!
Yatta!
I have no idea what I'm doing.
You got this!
Yeah!
Look at you!
You're the tank slayer!
I'm the tank slayer.
I hit the big man with my gun.
This one is hard to find where to go.
This map is confusing.
Nicely done!
I love this game.
Me too!
It's fun!
It's actually really fun.
It's just a little fast.
I like it, though.
How can you read which one it is?
It's what?
Oh, you can see it says, like, sniper rifle AK-47 combat shotgun.
No, it doesn't say that.
If you right-click, you can shove your enemies away.
Hold on, hold on.
Can I pee super quickly before you open the door?
Yeah, of course!
I'm just gonna go, like, two seconds.
One!
You can right-click to shove as well.
Manta!
If you wanted to shove the zombies away, you could just right-click.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Right-click.
Boom.
Change the knife for a gun?
Oh, but there's no pistols or anything.
Do we get a pistol in the future?
Or is that the only thing we get?
I think there's a pistol in the future, I think.
Oh, okay, okay.
It's this one, right?
I don't see any zombies.
Let's go with AKs.
I'm with you.
Yeah, that's true.
No more knife.
No more kidney fee.
That's what I like to say.
No more kidney.
Kidney?
Kidney fee.
You're looking really dashing, Haruka.
Thanks!
What do I look like?
Can I get a yee-haw?
Yee-haw!
Yeah!
Was that good?
Thanks, thanks.
What is dashing?
You running?
It's like very handsome.
Oh, I see.
It can also mean running, but it can mean handsome too.
What do I look like on your screen, Mint?
You're Doug Dimmadome.
Owner of the Dimmsdale Dimmadome.
But with a really tall hat.
Oh, fuck yeah.
That's what I'm talking about.
Let's go, lady.
Wait, I accidentally switched my gun.
I don't know which gun is which.
Why won't it tell me?
I think I lost my good AK with the sniper scope because I died.
Oh, no!
You'll get another sniper scope.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm not too worried.
Alright, are we ready?
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
Riki is talking shit to me.
He's telling me that Haruka is doing all the objectives and I'm useless.
Oh, thanks, Riki.
Bottom shotgun.
Washing your hands won't help when they attack you.
Who is Seda?
Seda.
Jamie Gibbs Jr. Thanks, Riki.
I haven't played this game in years.
It's been forever.
He's telling me I'm bad and saying that you're good.
Oh, damn.
I don't know about that, Riki.
I got a sniper with a...
Oh, my God.
Is this the same gun I was using?
It barely aims.
As well as my previous gun.
Feels harder to aim this one.
Payout's here.
I don't take drugs.
Drugs take money.
Is it because my previous gun had like the little laser scope so it was easier to aim?
Yeah.
Okay, I remember that this is like as far as I've played.
Not the mall.
We beat this level and it was really tough.
This one is tough, yeah.
In the elevator, gang.
Okay.
So the laser made it easier, damn it.
Any ideas?
We need to fill the car with gas.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
Do you girls think...
Do we think what?
Hear me out.
Strategy.
Maybe one of us carries the gas while the other ones shoot around them?
Or two and two?
What is a better strategy?
I just think we hope for the best.
We don't need no strategy.
You don't want to go in?
No, we absolutely need a strategy, baby.
We don't need no strategy.
I think we absolutely.
I got one, I got one.
Haruka, I'm protecting you.
Okay, Hennia, I'm protecting you.
Oh, never mind.
Hennia, I'm protecting you.
I'm not protecting.
Help me.
Someone help, please.
I'm going to die.
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming.
Oh, God.
What the hell?
What happened to, like, you were protecting her?
I got caught by a smoker and then a jockey, okay?
Guys, there's health kits in the middle of the store.
I'm going to die.
I'm shooting.
Oh, thank you.
Min, there's health kits in the middle, she was saying.
I got a health kit, too.
Oh, my gosh.
Get off of me.
I think we need to be two and two.
I think two and two is the strategy here.
Genuinely.
No one's watching, right?
Hennia, I'll see you by the car, okay?
Okay, I'm at the car, I'm at the car.
Thank you, thank you.
Okay.
If you drop the gas, I'll put it in.
I got you.
Hennia, I'm protecting you, or actually, I can go with Min if you want.
There you go.
Okay, I'll go.
Okay, Min, I'm behind you.
Get the gas.
Let's go get the gas.
I got the gas, I got the gas.
I'm getting the gas, I'm getting the gas.
We can do two and two.
Okay.
If something happens, we can...
Wait, where the hell...
Oh my, oh my.
Oh, oh, I got him.
I got him, yeah, you sure did, girl.
Hey, I took the first...
You got the finishing shot, but I...
Guys, guys!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Where's your partner?
Haruka's right here.
You guys were my partner?
No, Haruka was your partner.
Wait, what?
Haruka, we gotta be two and two.
Guys, guys, guys, guys.
I got three gas on my own.
What are y'all doing?
No, we're supposed to be two and two, Haruka.
I'm dropping gas.
Yeah, yeah, that's good, that's good.
Oh, there's more gas up there.
Wait a minute, let's go get the other one.
That was really smart of you.
No, it's Sumi Mountain.
Wait, Min, Min, Min, I'm gonna go save her.
Yeah, go save her, go save her, go save her, go save her.
Okay, wait, Min, you have to save me now.
Oh, wait, what?
What do you mean?
Wait, what's the music?
I was dropping the gas from the top floor to the ground, so...
I'm coming!
What just happened?
What happened to you?
There's Metal Gear!
I think we have to be two and two together.
Because if we get attacked by the special enemy, we're fucked.
We have to be two and two.
So what I was doing, I was going to the top stairs, and I was standing on the ledge, and I was dropping it down, so it's easier instead of going down the stairs.
That's what I was doing.
Well, can one of us stay with you then, Haru?
Oh, oh, oh gosh.
Please, please!
I got a Jackie!
I'm coming, I'm coming.
Good job, good job.
Shoo, shoo, shoo.
Okay, uh...
Okay, I'm going upstairs.
Oh, there's one up here, there's one up here.
I don't know how to get to this one over here.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Min, Min, Min.
Wait one second, I'm behind, I'm behind.
Ice cream!
Min, Min, Min, do you want to get the ones in the back over there?
Which one?
Okay.
In front of me, in front of where I am.
What do you mean in front of you?
What are we talking about?
Oh, shoot.
I don't know.
Ow, I'm pinned!
Oh, thank you.
I got you, I got you.
Thank you, Haruka.
Min, Min, Min, come with me.
There's two more over here.
Okay.
Oh, over this way.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, they're like over that way.
See?
Let's go over there.
Yeah.
Okay, if you guys drop it, we can put it in.
Oh, sorry.
What the heck?
I couldn't figure out how to... Oh, there's some over here.
Wait, there's some here?
Yeah, there's some over here.
Yeah, throw them around.
Ice cream!
Good girl.
Uh-oh, there's more, there's more, there's more.
I'll shoot some of these guys while...
Oh, there's some over here, over here.
Oh my god, I can't see.
How did you throw?
Uh, I left-clicked.
Oh my god.
Good job, girly.
Okay, I'm getting the ones over here.
Oh, attack!
Oh, oh, I need help, I need help, I need help.
Min, Min, Min, I need help.
I see you!
Wait, I don't see you.
Oh my gosh, where's the... I need help, I'm on the stairs, I'm on the stairs.
I'm trying to get the smoker.
Good girl, good girl.
Hennie, do you have Haruka?
Yeah.
Let's win.
Do you think we have all the gas together?
I'm getting, I'm getting the last two, maybe?
I'm following you, Min.
I think this is the last two.
Every time we fill up the gas, a whore comes in.
So let's wait till all the gas are together.
Wait a minute, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here.
Hold on.
Hold on, Min.
Free ice cream!
I think every time we fill up the car, the whore comes in.
So let's wait till we have all the gas together.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's wait it, let's wait it.
Okay, Min, I'm behind you.
Are you?
I'm far behind you, but I'm behind you.
Are we going down to the girls?
Yeah, because there's ice cream.
Are they actually all ice cream for you?
Is that what it is?
No, I have a, whenever there's a whore, a Spongebob yelling, free ice cream.
There you go.
Okay, how many are we missing?
Oh, sorry.
What's seven plus four?
Eleven?
We need two more.
Is there one over here?
I guess it's gone.
Oh, big guy, big guy.
Where?
All the two are over here.
I don't know how to ping, but it's there.
I'll make it over here.
Oh my god, I can't hit.
I can't hit.
Oh, fuck, I'm conned, I'm conned, I'm conned.
I'm down, I'm down.
I'm down too, I'm down too, I'm down too.
Thank you, Haru.
Help me, please.
I'm coming, Min, I'm coming, Min.
I'm killing my team more than the fucking zombies.
Oh, he's down, he's down.
He's already raising.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, Henya, I'm raising you.
I need a gun.
Reloading.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Girls, there's two health kits right here, Min and Henya, in the back.
Oh, thank you.
Wait, where?
Seven plus one, two, three, four.
Behind the...
Do you see where I'm looking at?
They're over there.
Yeah, I'm coming to see you.
Let's go, let's go.
Wait, Min, I'm still here.
I can't heal myself because of the horde.
How do we get there?
We're gonna find out the hard way.
Ouch.
I can't see, I can't see, I can't see, I can't see.
I'm down, I'm down, I'm down, I'm down, I'm down.
I got you, I got you, I got you.
Hold on, I'm taking care of these guys first.
Then I'll get you, I'll get you.
It looks like it's moving too.
Oh my god, I can't...
I can't get you.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Oh my.
I got you.
I'm good, I'm good.
I got you, I got you.
Yeah, you...
Okay, so...
The gas cans...
get blown up, you guys.
No way.
I swear that's what just happened.
The gas cans are gone.
Wait, but where's...
Wait, there's no more gas.
Nope.
No, they all spawn back.
They do?
Oh, I see, I see.
They're back up there.
Oh my god.
The thing is, I'm pretty sure if you shoot the gas tanks, they'll spawn fire, so don't shoot them.
Let's put... how about this?
Let's put like two more, and then we'll put the rest of like...
Help, please!
Oh, thank you.
No, but the thing is, every time we fill a car, a horde comes in.
Yeah, yeah, so let's do two, and then let's do four.
The ice cream never ends!
That way we don't have a chance to like shoot it and kill it.
I think the one right here is easier.
Or like three and three.
Oh wait, okay, we gotta keep going, never mind.
I went up the wrong stairs.
How does that feel?
Three and three, or like two and four?
What do you mean three and three?
We have to like split up the amount of them that we're doing.
Oh, I'm getting gas right now, so...
Oh, I'm on the wrong floor!
Are you really?
I got you, I got you.
I got you, Henry!
There's also kills here, Mint, if you want, since you might need the extra 100% health.
Yeah, grab him here.
Oh, you killed Peter?
Yay, I killed Peter!
Help!
Oh fuck, I just fell!
Tank is back, Kenya!
Oh my god!
Noooo!
Oh my god, please!
How do you throw the gas, by the way?
Just left click, left click.
It's not letting me.
Really?
It's fine, it's fine, it's fine.
Oh my god.
Yowie paddle time, stop!
What is this?
Oh, I got some...
There's a lot of bombs over here.
Oh, bio bomb, okay.
I grabbed that for something.
I killed him.
Nice!
Gosh.
Okay.
Oh, help me!
Where are you, where are you, where are you, Mint?
I'm on the stairs.
Thank you.
Good job.
Mint, I'm not next to you.
I'm downstairs.
I'm coming upstairs.
I don't know how to get to the other...
Here we go, this is where we need to go.
Where do I go?
Over here?
Oh fuck, I just blew up the other...
I even knew I fucking had to...
I'm so silly.
It's okay.
How do we get to...
Mint, let's get that one on the floor there that they just dropped.
Okay.
Oh my god, oh my god.
Oh my god, charger!
Yeah, fine, fine, fine.
Okay.
This is the most frustrating one I saw, I swear.
Mint, let's get both of these and fill them in at the same time.
Yeah!
Oh my god, I'm so sorry, I just blew it up!
It's okay, I did the same thing.
Don't even sweat it.
I'll fill both of these pretty much at the same time.
I think we have to go this way.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I think so too.
Oh, there you go!
Oh my god.
Bile, bile, bile.
Oh, I'm down!
I'm down, I'm down.
Mint, I'm coming.
I'm kind of far though.
It's okay if I die.
No, it's not.
I'm coming up.
Mint, shut up!
Don't die, you bitch!
You're supposed to haunt me forever, you bitch!
Oh fuck, Mint, no!
No, no, hold on, maybe I can...
I got tongued.
Have I been able to save you?
I don't think so.
Can you go get them?
I can't get the tongued.
Sorry, I fell down, I fell down.
I'm coming back.
I couldn't get the tongued.
But wait a minute, let me save Mata.
Go get Mata.
Okay, I'm gonna go get Mata.
Free ice cream!
Oh no!
Oh my god, no way.
No way, no way, no way, no way!
Ah, ah, ha, ha!
I just...
I just got up, man.
I just got up.
I'm reloading, I'm reloading.
Oh my god.
Matara, you're down!
I am down.
Oh no!
Free ice cream!
Okay, I think...
Strategy time.
Fuck the ball!
Yay!
So, does it actually...
Can I ask our chat, does it actually get harder the more gas you fill in?
Yeah, every time you put the gas in, it makes it work.
So that's why we gotta gather all the gas and then put it in at once.
But if even one of us shoots the gas, it's all gonna blow up.
So I don't think it's a good idea.
Here's an idea, what if we gather two and two and two and two everywhere, like not at the car, but we drop all the gas on the bottom floor.
Yeah.
So that way, even if we blow up a gas, we're only blowing up two gases.
We're not blowing up like a million gases.
Do you know what I mean?
Oh, like leave them where you drop them?
Like it's gonna be two, two, two, two, two, two, instead of like seven gases at the, you know, at the car.
You can just place them behind somewhere else if we don't accidentally shoot them.
Yeah, cause the problem is if we shoot one gas by accident, it's gonna blow up all the gases that are...
And people are saying the spitter can trigger it.
Um, and I also think we should be in teams of two, because if one of us gets like attacked by a spitter or something, the teammate can help.
Okay, okay.
Are we good with like keeping me and Mint, Henya, Haruka, or do you guys wanna change?
I'm good.
Okay.
I just wanna kill things.
Okay, so if you kill things, then Henya, you grab the gas, and Haruka, you kill stuff to protect her.
Okay.
Someone said in my chat like every fourth tank or so is a tank, or sorry, every fourth can.
So that means we should do 5-4-4.
5-4-4, cause it's 13 total.
Okay.
Instead of getting 4-4-1, it's gonna be harder.
We should do 5-4-4.
Is that okay?
I'm confused.
We're killing?
Yeah, we're killing.
Alright, let's go.
Are we going the right way?
Yeah.
Wasn't it the other way?
No, that's the right way.
It's down here.
I hear music.
Again.
Alright, girls.
It's fucking time.
Hi!
Thank you, Mom.
Henya, are you okay?
Sorry, I was fixing my mom!
Your mom!
Oh, wait, I got your wrong gun.
Sorry, Mom, I can't have dinner.
I'm currently trying to save the world.
I got the wrong gun.
Hold on.
Saving what's left of humanity.
Yeah, sorry, Mom.
I gotta save what's left of humanity.
You can have fun in your resort.
Hold on.
Can you wait one second before getting into the elevator?
I wanna switch guns.
Hurry up!
Okay.
I wanna get the AK.
You can't go in the elevator.
You just can't press the button.
They're all coming, though.
No lunch for today.
I'm good.
Thank you.
There they go.
Thanks, Mom!
I'm coming.
Thank you, Mom!
Here they come!
Maybe I need it.
Can you ask Mamanya if there's any delicious Reese's that she wants?
I'll bring them for her.
Oh, they're climbing.
She likes ranch sauce!
Ranch sauce?
Alright, I can bring some ranch.
Do you know her favorite brand?
I like ranch, too.
I'll ask her.
Thank you, though.
Really?
Thank you.
Could you ask your mom what is your favorite Japanese food, too, so I can give it to you?
Um...
My mom likes those little, like, bird-shaped ones.
They're in the shape of a little bird.
It's like a little marshmallow, kind of like a bird.
Oh, look up here.
Ranch sauce, you guys!
Oh, my gosh.
Wait, birds?
Don't you know birds are drones for the government?
Yeah.
They are!
You got it?
Actually, my Oka-san likes pan.
She likes bread.
Did she like Japanese bread?
Alright.
I'm following you.
Yeah.
No, Mint, let's go get the... Oh!
Put it behind the car.
Yeah!
Let's put it behind the car.
Oh, Mint, behind me.
Thank you, girl.
Sorry if I shot you a little bit while that happened.
It's okay.
Spitter, spitter.
Alright, are you ready?
Manta, I need you to come over here.
I'm here.
One second.
I was getting attacked.
Should I shot you, Mint?
You can't go.
Can I shot you many times, too?
Here, bring this health kit with you.
Bring an x-ray with you.
Okay, I'm bringing some gas.
I think I already have one.
I'm following you, Mint.
Then let's just go.
Ice cream!
Here we go.
Oh my gosh.
I never thought I want ice cream this much until now.
I'm helping.
One second.
I'm also...
There's a horde on me, too, girly.
Oh my gosh.
Don't shoot over here.
They're fine.
Oh, I found it.
I found it.
There's two.
Okay.
I think if we have five, we should load it.
Do we have five?
Uh, we have three.
We have three.
Okay.
Hold on, Mint.
Hold on one more.
Let me grab it.
One second, Mint.
I'm behind you.
I'm far behind you.
You're far behind me.
Wait, I did?
I'm far behind you, Mint.
Where are you?
I'm upstairs.
Yeah, throw these two down.
That's perfect.
Good job, girl.
No, I don't have it.
I don't have it.
You got the other one?
Nice.
Throw it down.
Wait, what did I just see?
Perfect.
Good girl.
Let's bring these closer.
I got my banana.
Don't worry.
We can grab these two as well.
I don't know if we can grab them without setting it on fire.
We're done.
I'm far up.
I'm far from you, Mint.
Alright, let's go.
I'm downstairs.
I'm sorry.
I'm upstairs.
Why are you upstairs?
I'm sorry.
Why are you loading them in?
Should I... I mean, there's already a horde.
I think you could.
I think you...
Just be careful that we don't blow them up by accident.
I'm gonna load... Oh!
Oh!
Hey!
B-b-b-back off, buddy!
B-b-b-b-b!
I gotta be careful not to... How do I load it?
How do I load it?
Oh, shit!
I need help!
Mint!
I'm coming!
Behind you!
Oh, my God.
Oh, we're in trouble.
We're in trouble!
Girls, girls, we need your help.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, my God.
We need your help, girls.
There's a tank.
We need your help.
I'm down.
Okay, okay, okay.
We're coming.
I'm down.
Be careful.
Don't blow up the gas canisters.
We got a ton.
We're sold.
It's Jover.
It's not Jover.
It's fine.
La-di-da!
It's up to you, Hanya.
No!
Oh, you were doing so good.
I don't know about that!
Hanya, can you pick me up quickly, if you can?
Okay.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
Mrs. Puff!
I need some help!
Careful.
Oh, for third ball damage!
Yes!
I didn't want to throw the bomb.
I was scared about.
I thought we were doing so good this time around, though.
I think it doesn't matter if you load them or not.
The horde just comes.
I think if you pick them, if you touch them, the horde comes, right?
Really?
I don't know.
So, if you guys want what Hanya and I have been doing, we've been putting the gas behind the car.
Yeah, that's what we did.
That's what we were doing.
But then I tried loading it and then the tank came out.
Well...
Shit.
Let's try it again.
I think we had a good vibe over here.
I think we had a good vibe.
I think maybe what we should do, when we're closer to like loading a bunch of them in, let's all stick together at the end.
For real, for real.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know if they actually heard me.
Sorry guys, I have a cold.
Do you think they heard me or do you think they're just...
I guess we'll find out.
Sorry Hanya, let me wipe my nose.
There you go.
What is happening?
Nice one, nice one.
I was wiping my nose because I clearly sneezed.
Yeah, she sneezed.
Let's go.
How do we start this?
Let's go downstairs.
I have a joke.
Why did the chicken cross the bridge?
Why?
To get to the other side.
Oh, that's a good one.
Oh, sorry.
No.
I was like...
Just pour it in.
Wait, that's not Mitt, that's Hanya.
Mitt, Mitt, Mitt, let's go together.
Oh, I guess let's protect Hanya for like two seconds because she's alone.
Yeah.
I'm pouring in the gas.
Okay, I'm gonna put it right behind it.
Alright, Henry.
I got you, Mitt, Mitt, Mitt.
I got you, I got you, I got you.
Okay, there we go.
Oh, guys, I need help.
Yeah, I got you.
I think I got...
Oh, my God, leave me alone.
Where is it taking you?
Oh, my God.
Here, I'll bring you to the back here.
It was like taking you away.
It really was.
It likes me.
Oh, sorry if I hit you.
Okay, I'm ready.
Alright, Hanya.
Let's go back upstairs where we belong.
Yeah, let's go there.
Where we belong?
I thought you were some asshole chasing me.
Yeah.
Oh, wow, wow, wow.
The Harunia is strong.
The Harunia is stronger than anything.
Watch out, the horse is gonna appear from that back room.
Be prepared.
I'm going upstairs, Matata.
Okay, I'm following you.
I'm gonna put away.
I got you, I got you, I got you.
To the left, Mitt, Mitt, Mitt.
Oh, no, never mind.
I'm so stupid.
I got you, I got you.
Left here.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
Alright, then.
Should we go to the middle stair?
Are they coming through here?
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
I got one.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
Was it you?
I thought it was me.
It was me, it was me.
I'm sorry.
It was all you.
I think we can go up from here.
All you.
Here, I'm just putting the gas tank behind the carpet.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Yeah, maybe we should...
Oh, well, well, well, Panels.
What?
What caught on fire?
Okay, okay.
I remember the day you took my life from me.
Wait, how do we get over there?
It's time to end it, Panels.
What is he?
Go, go, go.
Shoot, shoot, shoot.
Oh, yeah, girls.
There aren't a lot of girls.
There's a couple.
Guys, I need help.
I accidentally fell off the stairs.
Oh, help me, please.
Someone...
Can you please go up?
Go up?
Go up the stairs?
Go up the stairs.
Oh, I see you, I see you, I see you.
I didn't realize that was a thing.
What happened to you?
What did you do?
Don't ask, don't ask, don't ask.
You don't need to know.
Okay.
I think we should load the gas into the car.
I think we should load the current gas into the car, y'all.
Wait, there's a tank!
There's a tank!
After the tank is dead, I think we should load the current gas into the car.
Uh-oh, I'm out of ammo.
There's a bunch of ammo downstairs.
Yeah, I know.
I gotta go get that.
I ain't going down without a fucking piece of shit.
Come at me!
Good job.
Can I reload for you?
Good job, girls.
Oh my gosh.
Alright, I'm gonna start loading the gas in the car.
Okay.
Be careful.
Mint, if you can protect me, Mint.
I'm just a single ghost, you know?
Just a single ghost.
I'm just a single...
You know what, Henry?
Let's go get more gas.
Yeah, let's go.
I think it's up.
You better hurry up, Mata.
I'm only gonna do five.
Gotta reload.
Keep doing it.
I think they're following... I think they're going after...
Henya and Haruka.
Alright, I'm gonna stop at five.
Yeah, yeah.
Keep going.
What was that?
It's fine.
I killed them.
Alright, Mint.
This is kinda peaceful, actually.
Mint, do you wanna get pills for the health?
There's pills here if you want.
Haruka!
I see you.
I got you.
Mint, Mint, I got you.
Thank you.
Mint, do you need drugs?
No, I think I'm good.
You sure?
I'm gonna pick up a med kit anyway, though.
Okay, do it.
Mint, I'm gonna grab this gas over here, okay?
Yep, I'm protecting you.
Wait, Mint, behind...
I'm gonna put it behind the car.
We have four more gases.
We're gonna blow up these gases.
I know we are.
No, we won't.
We won't.
Don't worry.
I'm gonna put it in the car.
Get out of my way.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You can start putting it in the car.
Mint, you're fine.
You're fine.
Don't even sweat it.
Okay.
What was that?
Oh, shit!
Guys, guys, I need your help.
I need your help.
What the fuck just happened?
I got you.
I saw you flying away.
Yeah, I got... I got caught by the guy.
Is there a gas tank on top of here?
I'm loading.
How do we get that?
Oh, no.
Her... Oh, god.
Woody, hello.
How do we get that?
It's okay.
We only got...
After this, we only need four more guys.
We're, like, pretty much almost done.
Let's stick together.
Let's stick together, gamer girls.
Do not blow up the gas tank.
What gas tank?
Where is... Oh, I see it.
I'm gonna get it.
I'm gonna load it.
Good job.
Good job, Haru.
Vile, vile, vile.
Ality.
Alright, I'm gonna stay up here.
I think I have...
Yeah, I do not think it's hot.
Where's all the gas?
Okay, Mint.
Yeah.
Uh...
Uh-oh.
Here it comes.
Metal Gear Ray.
Mint, let's follow Hanya.
Okay.
Right here, right here.
Okay, I'm coming.
Oh, wait.
I gotta heal.
I'm gonna heal.
If you'll cover for me, Mata, I'm gonna heal real quick.
Oh, wait, wait.
Hanya, you're alone.
Be careful.
Okay.
Okay, I'm coming.
We're coming.
Not this way.
This way.
Which way?
Let's help Haru.
Haha.
Solo the tank.
Let me solo the tank.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Ouch.
Oh, fack.
I didn't realized it was a big guy.
I thought he was dead.
He's dead?
Oh, my gosh.
You got her?
Hanya, take the drugs for help.
Wait, she's not up yet.
I'm not up yet.
Guys, we only need 3 more.
How we can
We can try.
Let's go all together.
Where is it?
There's two over there in the back.
Oh, how do we get up there?
I think over here, no?
Wait, wait, somebody's alone.
Yeah, where Haru is.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
We can go there.
Okay, perfect.
I think now if we stay together and use drugs for health, I think we might get it.
I think it's this way, this way, this way.
I think we have to go...
Oh, this way?
This way, this way.
Follow where Hennye is.
They're coming from the stairs behind.
Oh, goodness gracious.
Spooked me.
I'm kind of slow, so I'll guard from the back.
I'm sticking back with Mint.
I'm a little slow.
It's okay, baby.
Guys, there's two tanks over... not two tanks.
Yeah, yeah, we're coming, we're coming, we're coming.
Okay, okay.
I'll grab one of them.
Yeah, since Mint is slow.
Or...
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Guys, there's pills here if anybody needs.
There's a gas!
I got you!
Hennye, I'm gonna give you pills.
Thank you.
No, no, no.
Oh, my God.
Hennye, wait.
Stop for a second.
Okay.
I'm gonna die, but that's okay.
I need help.
Hennye, behind you.
Behind you.
Thank you.
Arigatou gozaimasu.
Oh, my God.
I was so close to...
Did I finish?
I don't even know.
Oh, Mint, Mint, Mint, Mint.
No!
I was so close!
Mint, if you need to ask, then you didn't finish.
That's true.
There's a smoker, by the way.
Be careful.
Guys, I'm running down to get Mint.
I'm trying my best, but I am alone.
Oh, sorry.
That's you.
Oh, fuck.
I got tongue.
Thank you, Haru.
Ice cream.
Ice cream coming in.
Arigatou.
Oh, watch out, watch out, watch out.
I can't get them from behind you.
I'm doing my best, Mint.
I'm doing my best.
I'm leaving them.
Be careful.
Don't shoot the barrel.
I know.
I'm putting it in.
I don't care if I die.
I got it.
Mint, Mint, Mint.
I can give you pills.
I can give you drugs.
I'm stuck.
Oh, my gosh.
I was getting teabagged for real.
Stop it.
It's okay.
We're so close.
There's one more.
Just get it.
Don't even worry about me.
Just put it in.
Shut up, Mint.
We need your extra firepower, you bitch.
Haru, I'm behind you.
I'm behind you.
Let's get the last one.
There's one more?
Yeah.
Let's get one more.
Come on, girls.
Oh, my God.
We literally are about to win.
We're about to win the game.
Oh, big guy.
Big guy.
Get the big guy.
Go, big guy.
Where's the last one?
Oh, my God.
He's going upstairs.
Fuck.
I thought that would avoid the shot.
I went the wrong way.
Fuck.
Oh, no.
Oh, no....
Where's the...?
Where's Rey?
I have a... I have a... bomb!
I'm not afraid to use it!
Is this guy still damaged?
Yes.
HENYA!
HENYA, I'M COMING!
THANK YOU!
I'm a little slow though.
HENYA!
WAIT!
I'M SORRY!
OH MY GOSH!
NO!
IT'S OKAY!
HENYA!
I... I...
I DON'T THINK I CAN...
HENYA!
I'M DOWN TOO!
IT'S FINE!
I'LL GET YOU GUYS!
GIVE ME... OH!
NEVERMIND!
HARU!
YOU'RE THE ONLY HOPE!
HARU WON KANOBI!
YOU'RE THE ONLY HOPE, HARU!
YOU GUYS!
HARU!
YOU GOT THIS!
KILL THE ENEMIES SO HARU IS EASIER FOR HER!
I'M DEAD DEAD!
YOU GOT THIS, HARU!
IT'S ONLY YOU!
IT'S ONLY YOU, MATA!
IT'S ONLY...
NO, IT'S HARU!
NO, AND IF SHE CAN GET YOU...
IF SHE CAN GET YOU OUT...
YOU GOT...
NICE!
OH!
HARU, I CAN'T SEE BEHIND YOU!
OH MY... OH MY...
BEHIND YOU!
OKAY, LET'S SEE WHERE'S THE BOMB.
OH!
HARU, YOU SHOULD HAVE BEEN...
I HAD A BOMB!
I HAD A BOMB, IF YOU NEED IT!
YOU COULD GRAB IT FROM MY DEAD BODY!
PEEL IT FROM MY HANDS!
MY COLD MIND!
I DON'T KNOW WHERE HARU IS.
OKAY, SHE'S BEHIND ME.
I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
OKAY, HARU?
HOW ARE WE DOING THIS?
WE GOTTA GET UP THERE.
GO!
INCOMING!
OH, WATCH OUT!
I DON'T THINK YOU CAN GO FROM THERE.
FUCK!
OH MY GOD.
SHE'S CORNERED.
SHE'S NOT CORNERED.
YOU HAVE TO GO FIRST FLOOR AND TIP THAT OTHER STAGE.
BECAUSE I THINK IT IS UNHURT.
IS THAT A JOCKY?
OH NO.
OH, HARU!
GOOD LUCK!
SHE'S SO STRONG!
I THINK WE'RE ABOUT TO DO IT.
I GENUINELY THINK NEXT ROUND IS THE ROUND, GIRL.
WAIT, WHAT DO YOU MEAN NEXT ROUND?
WE'RE STILL, WE STILL HAVE HERE!
OH GOSH.
YEAH!
WE JUST GOT, UH OH.
THE ICE CREAM.
HARU WITH THE PISTOL, MY QUEEN.
I GENUINELY THINK, LIKE, WE'RE ABOUT TO DO IT.
OH, BEHIND YOU!
WE CAN TAKE, LIKE, A TWO MINUTE BREAK.
RECENTER.
PEACE.
OH MY GIRL.
WHOA!
WHY ARE THEY PURPLE?
NICE!
GOOD JOB, HARU.
MY QUEEN.
SHE IS SO...
IMAGINE SHE CLUTCHES IT.
SHE'S SO GOOD.
OH NO!
NO!
SHE GOT CAUGHT!
OH MY GOSH.
MATARA, WHY DO YOU HAVE TO SAY THAT?
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO SAY THAT?
SHE GOT CAUGHT.
NO!
IMAGINE IF SHE CLUTCHES.
GETS IMMEDIATELY CAUGHT BY THE SOMA.
NO!
I'M DOING SO WELL TOO!
YOU REALLY DID REALLY WELL THAT TIME.
HERE'S AN IDEA.
CAN WE TAKE, LIKE, A TWO MINUTE BREAK?
AND JUST, LIKE, RECENTER OUR CHAKRAS?
BECAUSE I THINK WE'RE GONNA GET THE NEXT ONE.
ARE YOU OKAY?
ARE YOU OKAY, MATARA?
I NEED JUST, LIKE, A TWO MINUTE BREATHER.
AND THEN I THINK WE'RE GONNA DO IT.
OKAY.
TWO MINUTE BREATHER FOR YOU.
YEAH, I'M FINE, I'M FINE.
I JUST NEED, LIKE, TWO MINUTES.
BECAUSE THAT WAS REALLY OVERWHELMING.
OKAY.
THIS STAGE IS SO STINKY.
BUT IT WAS FUN.
I THINK WE'RE JUST ABOUT TO GET IT.
STINKY.
GENUINELY.
I THINK WE HAVE A REALLY GOOD THING GOING WITH, LIKE, THROWING EVERYTHING DOWN IN, LIKE, TWO BIG WAVES.
HAVING TEAMMATES.
LIKE, I THINK THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
I LIKE PUTTING IN THE GAS.
THE BILE REALLY SAVED MY ASS FOR A BIT, BUT THEN THE FUCKING SMOKER GOT ME.
I KNOW!
YOU CAN BLAME MATARA.
IT'S OKAY.
YOU CAN SAY, MATARA, WHY WOULD YOU JINX IT LIKE THAT?
MATARA, THIS IS YOUR FAULT.
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
I'M GONNA SPANK YOU WITH THIS YOWIE PADDLE.
TURN AROUND.
OKAY.
SPANK ME.
THIS IS, LIKE, REMINISCENT OF ANIME CONS.
TURN AROUND.
ARE YOU GONNA GLOMP ME?
I'M TURNING AROUND.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
LET ME LOWER MY SENSITIVITY.
I FEEL LIKE MY SENSITIVITY IS SO HIGH.
OKAY.
JIMMY GIBBS JUNIOR IS THE MAN.
THE MAN.
I DON'T KNOW ANYBODY LIKE THAT, MAN.
MAN.
BIRD TRAX.
THE MAN.
THE LEGEND.
OH, YEAH.
CAN WE PLEASE ADD THE CLASSIC EMOTE IN MY CHANNEL?
WHAT'S THAT?
HAG BANGING TO THE MUSIC.
IT'S LIKE THE LITTLE DUCK SMOKING.
WAIT.
HOW DO YOU DO THE EMOTES IN THIS?
HOW DO YOU DO THE EMOTES?
IN TWITCH, YOU JUST TYPE IN AND THEN IT SHOWS UP.
IN THIS GAME.
NO, I HAVE CLASSIC.
DANCING DA YO.
HOW DO YOU DO THEM, GUYS?
I DID IT WRONG.
YOU SUCK.
THERE'S STILL A MEDPACK HERE IF ANYONE WANTS IT.
I THINK SOMEBODY WITH LOW HEALTH SHOULD USE IT AND THEN GRAB.
OH, WAIT.
I DIDN'T HAVE AN EXTRA MEDPACK.
MY BAD.
I'M STUPID.
I HAVE AN EXTRA.
NO.
WE ALL HAVE ONE MEDPACK, RIGHT?
OKAY.
ZEE?
OH, NO.
HOW DID THEY NOT HAVE IT?
OH, THIS IS IT.
OH.
HOW DID THEY NOT HAVE IT?
HOW DOES THAT FEEL GOOD?
I DON'T HAVE ONE.
Oh, I saw emote.
GRAB THE ONE DOWNSTAIRS, THOUGH.
WE'RE FINE.
NAKE.
ALL RIGHT, GIRLS.
GIRLS.
NAKE.
GRILL.
I NEED YOU ALL TOGETHER.
ENVISION THE WIN.
BE LIKE PROFESSIONAL ATHLETES.
WHAT HAPPENED?
IMAGINE PUTTING IN THE 13TH GAS CAN AND CHEERING.
HOO-RA.
SORRY.
WHOO.
WE DID IT.
13TH GAS CAN.
WHOOPEE.
WE WON.
OH, NAH.
ARE YOU MANIFESTING?
You have to do it.
You have to be happy as if we just won.
Not the Garfield scratch.
Listen, the clutch that I made...
and then you have to jinx it for me.
Sorry, I was sneezing.
Can you just pretend to be so happy that we won?
Just imagine we win.
Yay!
No, more!
Let's go!
Yay!
Alright, let's go.
If we lose, it's because of Hena's power of imagination.
You do not blame Hena for your own skill issue.
Come on!
No, I blame Hena if we lose.
Sorry.
I saw you on the kills board.
Every time.
Yeah?
Don't you skill-issue-dayo me, baby girl.
It's a ping!
I live in Japan!
Wait, Hena, did you just say ping?
It's a ping-dayo!
Real gamers don't blame the ping!
It's a ping-issue-dayo!
It's a ping!
Ping-issue-dayo.
It's a ping-issue-dayo!
I saw you on the scoreboard, Hena.
I know what you do in your spare time.
Why will you move to Japan so we can play with you?
Same thing.
Okay.
Yeah, Hena.
She was talking to me.
She was talking to me!
I mean, too bad, you guys.
I'm already married.
So I technically know you guys from Hawaii.
Don't fill it up now.
We're filling them up after, right?
I'll go get the other two over there.
Alright, Hena.
Yeah.
Let's go.
I got overzealous.
I got overzealous a little bit.
Should we go this way?
Yeah, let's go this way.
Yeah, the other way.
The other way?
Okay.
There's two cans at the end.
Which way?
Oh, down here?
Actually, let's keep the two cans on the floor for the end, actually.
This one will be...
These ones down here?
Keep the two on the floor at the end.
Yeah, yeah.
They're the easiest to get.
Charger!
I'm here.
Oh my gosh, how am I already so close to death?
This is so bad.
Yeah I'm trying...
Let's go up.
Wait, can we get it from here?
Are we here?
We're going.
Uh oh.
What am I hearing?
Bienvenido a Miami.
Oh my gosh!
Okay, I got him.
We're okay.
Oh, sorry.
You scared me, you scared me.
I got him.
Hold on, let me get the pills.
There's always pills upstairs, Mint, if you want some for the extra health.
Did you grab both of them?
No, there's another pill there if you want to grab it.
Nice!
Oh, get off of me.
Grab the pill too.
Yeah, I grabbed it.
Wait, wait.
There's two over here.
Sorry, I'm just so used to going downstairs.
Wait, are there any over here?
I'm not near you.
Are there any over here?
Let's go check.
Oh, I think this is how we get the ones over here.
Oh, let's throw them.
Oh, good girl.
You did find them.
Did you like the 360 roll throw?
Nice!
How did you do that?
There's also bombs over here.
How did you do the 360?
There's bombs over there?
Where?
Down where the gas cans were.
Oh, I see, I see, I see.
Hold on, I just dropped my pistol.
Okay, okay.
I'm here, I'm here.
Watch out, watch out.
Okay.
Sorry, I keep shooting you.
Let's run around.
Yeah, let's run around.
Run back, run back.
Do we?
How many do we have?
Okay.
Oh, wait.
There's just the ones on that story.
And then...
Yeah.
Let's go back down.
Okay.
There's a lot on the floor.
Yeah.
I'm going to start loading.
Maybe let's start blowing some up so we don't accidentally blow them up.
No, there's a tank nearby.
Oopsie.
There's a tank.
Okay.
Let's kill the tank and then...
Careful of the tank.
If you can leave him...
Min, Min, Min, Min.
Get back up.
Back up?
Or wait, wait.
Let's kill the tank with him.
I was trying to get it.
Oh, here.
I see him.
Bomb!
Bomb's away!
Thank you, Manta.
Thank you.
Oh my God.
Welcome.
Get a med kit while you can.
I was reloading fucking forever.
Me?
Oh my God.
Haru?
No, no, no.
Not you.
Haru, Haru, Haru.
Haru, I'm coming in a second.
I have to kill the hunter first.
Oh, God.
I think we're not going to do so well this time.
We're fine.
Stop jinxing it.
Don't jinx it.
Oh my God.
You harlot.
Get him or get Haru.
Thank you.
We're fine.
I think we need to load a few of these in the thingy.
Huh?
Hold on.
I got you.
I got you, Haru.
Come here.
Oh, no.
I can just get this health kit over here.
Oh.
Yeah.
Get the health kit and there's also meds and stuff.
Oh, I actually need one now that I look at it.
Here you go.
Take that.
I'm going to take this one.
And I'm just going to heal real quick while I wait.
Okay.
Watch not to blow them up now.
Don't blow up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Watch out for that one over there.
Reload in here.
Fuck.
I need help with the jumper.
I'm coming.
I got you.
Oh, no.
Good job.
Oh, no, no.
I'm on fire.
Ahhh.
All of them?
Fuck.
Fine.
I got you.
There's still two over here.
Keep the two on the floor for the end because they're the easiest.
Keep those two for the end because they're the easiest.
Okay.
So it's going to be easiest to get them.
I wonder what one's...
Oh, no.
The one's on the...
Reloading.
Oh, shoot.
I didn't even notice.
I should have reloaded earlier.
Wait, who's alone?
Haruka, you're alone.
Don't worry, I'm just throwing this off.
It's fine.
Always try to go with a buddy just in case.
Just in case you get, like, um...
You're such a mom.
I can't hear you, Haru.
Sorry.
It's because I was shooting.
I can't reload.
Gotta get some more.
There's two more in the first floor.
We're saving those, Henya.
We're gonna save them.
Yeah, keep those until the end, Henya, because they're the easiest.
They're the easiest to get, so we should keep them until the end of the game.
I think that one is the one from over here, right?
Okay, I'm gonna try and get this one over here.
You can start bringing those two, Henya, actually, because we're pretty much at the end.
We just need two more.
No, we need four more.
Yeah, and we're getting these four more, so don't worry.
Those two plus these two.
Good job!
I got one.
Uh-oh.
There's only one here?
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
That's what I'm saying!
Wait, there's over here, though.
Over here.
Yeah, let's get the other one.
Bring both of those two, just in case.
Okay, I got it, I got it.
Tank's here.
I hear his music.
He's blasting it again.
Mate.
Was there just one there, Mint, or two?
Yeah, just one.
Just one.
Oh, fuck!
I just dropped.
You're alone.
I accidentally fell through the floor.
It's okay.
I'm far.
I'm trying to kill a jockey.
Oh, gosh.
Okay, there's a guy.
There's a guy.
I'm gonna die, I think.
Mint, I'm so sorry.
I fell through the floor.
How do I... Does it move this way?
Or does it move on the...
Oh, gosh.
Oh, he downed me.
He downed me.
Sorry, Mint.
It's okay.
I fell.
I'm just down, you know.
Oh, you're also down.
Cool.
Mrs. Puff.
Don't worry.
I got you.
Fucking...
What do you think I am?
I'm not a feet man.
I'm gonna go get Mint.
I'm so slow.
Hurry.
I'm back here again.
I'm here, Mint.
Oh, the... What's it called?
Are you sure you're here?
Because I'm literally blacking out.
Can you shoot them?
Yeah, that's what I'm doing.
Okay, good girl.
I think it got blown up, so let's grab the...
Yeah, let's grab the other one.
Oh, I hear him again.
Oh, we just blew them up.
Sorry, I think I just blew them up.
Behind you.
I was taking pills.
My girl.
Mint, there's one back there.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you so much.
Girls, how many...
Oh, shit, you're alone.
How many do we have downstairs?
It's these two that need to go.
Zero down here.
Alright, hold on.
They're gonna come out from here?
Yeah.
Oh, and from here?
Oh, shoot.
Watch out, though.
Okay, I'm gonna throw it overboard.
Yeah, get it, get it, get it.
Throwing gasoline!
Thank you, thank you.
We're gonna get the last one.
We're gonna get the last one and we're done.
We need two more.
Get the one we just threw on the floor.
And we're done.
We beat the game.
Throw the last one and then let's go help them.
We're coming, we're coming.
We're coming, we're coming, we're coming.
Oh, gosh, they're right behind us.
They're right behind us, yeah.
They're behind us, they're behind us.
Oh my goodness.
I'm coming to the car.
How do I get in?
I don't know.
Let me in.
Come on, Matara, you're so slow.
Shut the fuck up!
There we go.
Yippee!
Oh my gosh, Matara, we beat the whole game.
How do you feel?
Let's go!
Isn't this only like round one of the whole game?
Yeah.
Actually...
I'm so sorry for swearing so much.
But that was amazing.
Oh my god.
Let's go!
We did it!
Oh, I used the least amount of first aid kit.
No wonder I died the most.
Oh...
Oh my god.
Dang, Matara.
I was using melee until the beginning of the game.
Yeah.
I killed all them tanks.
All them tanks.
Oh no.
Don't look at that.
We got it baby girl.
Oh I took the least amount of damage?
Let's go.
Let's go friendly fire.
Wait a second.
Revive the most teammates though?
Hello?
Yippee.
Accuracy 19%.
Zombies no harm in the making of this film.
Oh I got the most headshots though.
Nice.
I don't aim for the head ever.
I just aim.
I know it's hard to in the moment right?
Yeah.
That was amazing.
But exhausting.
That's just a taste of how your tournament will be.
How do you feel?
I'm not ready.
Not ready.
When is it?
I feel like I was not prepared.
Like end of May?
Oh.
Yeah.
Good luck.
No.
Oh it's the end of May?
Yeah.
Arigato.
Do we keep going or do we stop here?
Up to you guys.
I feel like I can keep going.
So yeah.
Up to you guys.
I could stop or I could go.
I think it's you know if anybody's too tired.
Is the first mission the hardest?
Does it get easier?
I don't know.
We could also choose like anyone.
We don't have to do like the second one.
We can choose any anyone that we want.
The second one says streets.
Yeah.
Like the carnival one.
Well the carnival one is kind of annoying too.
Oh it's because I have the campaign.
Death center, passing.
They want us to do dark carnival.
How about blood harvest?
Blood harvest?
Or the passing.
Hard rain.
Dead air.
No mercy.
The sacrifice.
There's also the concert.
What sounds interesting?
Dark carnival my beloved.
Is that actually?
I think they don't.
I think it might be smart.
I don't know.
Okay I'll read out a few names and you girls say what you prefer.
The passing.
Dark carnival.
Swamp fever.
Hard rain.
The parish.
The sacrifice.
No mercy.
Crash course.
Death toll.
Dead air.
Blood harvest.
Cold stream.
The last sand.
Dark carnival.
Alright.
Oh people are saying the carnival is hardest.
Why are people saying the carnival is hardest?
Maybe I just saw one person.
Carnival.
Well people are saying no mercy is quick for Alaskan.
Oh is it?
Yeah we can do anything.
I'm fine with anything.
I'm just reading chat.
No mercy or dark carnival?
Oh.
People are saying no mercy and the carnival is a good one.
Yeah that's what I'm saying too.
I don't think I've done no mercy.
I don't know though.
Alright no mercy.
Haruka I see you.
Wait what's she doing?
She's calling me stinky.
Oh no I didn't download anymore.
What do you mean?
The mods.
No.
Aww.
Are you okay?
Yeah oh there's a chat.
Huh?
Yeah there is.
Yeah don't say mean things.
Say nice things.
It says say JP.
What does it mean by that?
Don't say mean things in the chat.
Say JP.
Is it a cheat code?
Oh it's gonna like unlock secret weapons.
Oh oh oh.
It says JP to me too.
Oh.
JP.
Alright I'm starting.
Okay.
I'm gonna need a drink after this game I think.
I didn't think we'd be playing as the Left 4 Dead 1 people.
So I didn't download any of their mods.
The Left 4 Dead 1 guy?
I thought he was from Dead by Daylight.
I didn't realize he was from this game.
Which one?
The one with the hat?
The old one.
Yeah.
He's in Dead by Daylight.
Dead by Daylight?
I think his name is Bill.
Yeah I think so.
That's fun.
Really?
That's cool.
Thank you.
Look at Billy.
Dude.
What?
Sorry we're all humans and then Henya is like Silver the Hedgehog.
I am.
Yeah you.
My brain is fucking up.
It's okay.
Wake up.
Grab a brush and put on a little makeup.
I don't think you trust.
Your money.
That's what my friend wanted to say.
What's here?
I didn't bring a health pack with me.
You know what?
I'm a gamer.
I don't need it.
Go get it.
I don't need one.
Gamer.
Do we go down?
I think we go downstairs.
This kind of reminds me of Half-Life.
There's a Half-Life VR.
I don't know if you saw Henya.
Oh yeah but I get motion sickness.
That's hard.
Wish I could.
What happened over here?
Uh oh.
I can't see anything.
What's the best gun?
Is it still the AK here or is it another gun y'all?
Neighbor.
Oh my god.
Who has such a big mouth?
I thought those were my friends.
Welcome.
This is a gigantic house.
Right?
What?
Oh my goodness.
Those people are alive.
I mean they're dead.
Nope.
Not anymore.
You good?
Thank you.
They just don't stop coming.
And they don't stop coming.
Should we go downstairs?
Sure.
And they don't stop coming.
Oh my god.
Did we get him?
How the heck am I already yellow?
Oh no Hanya.
Oh no.
Use your health pack.
Health pack time.
And they don't stop coming.
I have a molotov in case there's a big gang.
Oh.
Ow.
Sorry I was shooting the other guy.
I'm stoned.
Ow.
Jumpy.
Pecora.
I hate when Pecora swamps me like that.
That's crazy.
Who?
Dakota.
The hunter is Dakota in her jail outfit.
Wait who's Dakota?
Who's Dakota?
Dakota?
Oh Pecora.
I also heard Dakota.
Yeah I thought you were saying Dakota.
I thought you were saying Dakota also.
Dakota.
Haru.
She's all the way in the back.
She's about to die.
Oh no.
Smoker.
Oh it was a smoker.
Should I have done the impression?
Yeah do it.
Do it.
I want to hear it.
Like that?
Oh that's good.
Do you need a health kit Haru?
Yes I am bleeding.
Okay come here.
Come here and I will heal you.
I'm about to lose all my spleens.
Spleens?
Oh her spleens.
Where am I?
I can't see anything.
I guess this is this way.
Yeah.
What music do I hear?
It's this way.
This way?
Oh hello.
Some car set off alarms.
Uh oh.
Guys I'm launching now.
I can't move.
Hey!
What the fuck?
Good girl.
Good job.
You know what Anya?
If you're dying and I don't have a med kit.
I'm going to hesitate giving you my med kit this time.
Why do you love your wife?
The girls are fighting.
Oopsie daisy.
Okay you're all forgiven.
Guys guys I'm getting drunk.
Oh shit sorry Anya.
Why you gotta brag about it huh?
I'm sorry.
Oh my god listen.
Listen.
Is there any...
Is there any ammo anywhere?
Yeah I also would need some ammo.
I have a pistol.
Nice.
Guess we're going into the subway.
Oh what's this?
Oh a chainsaw if anybody wants it.
Me.
A chainsaw.
Where do I buy the bomb?
Let's go down here I think.
Down there?
Not here?
Oh.
Down here okay.
There's a site spot just ahead.
Give me a second.
Oh I found some peace.
Safe room with coins.
Wait that was it?
Good job yeah I mean it was the first mission of the...
Oh yeah.
Uh oh.
Did we?
Oh.
I was like, why did we disconnect?
Alright, mid with the killin'.
That's my girl.
Hanya with the special killin'.
Woah, five!
Oh my gosh.
Yay!
Yatta!
Killin'.
I'm doin' it.
Rip and tear.
Rip and tear, everybody.
Alright, let me see if there's a better...
I'm gonna heal and then I'm gonna grab.
What gun is this?
Nope.
Yeah, does everybody have an extra medpack?
I have.
What's a medpack?
Haru, did you grab your medpack?
I don't need one.
Haru is living on the edge.
Haru, grab one.
Yeah, Haru!
Yeah!
Come on, Haru!
No, no, no, no!
No!
How dare you ruin my edginess.
Mata, that's so fucked.
Yeah, it is.
You don't wanna mess with me with a train saw.
I still hear him.
Oh, I forgot in my mod I gave him a purple neon shirt as well.
Some of the monsters.
That's so funny.
No, what do you mean?
I don't know what he's talking about.
Why you open the door, Hanyar?
Hanyar?
We gonna go kill him.
Noir?
Yeah, time to kill.
Hanyar?
Oh my god, we're in the metro!
Time to kill!
Wait, where are you guys?
What city is this, canonically?
Are we in, like, the United States?
Probably, right?
Reloading!
Take them!
Get them all!
Rip and tear until everything is dead!
Rip and tear!
Why do we need a train saw?
Oh.
This way?
Kill, kill.
I like trains.
Destroy, destroy, destroy.
I love trains.
Uh-oh.
Kill, kill, kill!
Ah!
That's right!
I can't tell if it's dead!
Nice!
Oh, Haruka.
Yay!
Nice!
I did it!
Haruka, are you okay?
Let me patch you up.
Oh my gosh, are you...
Don't, don't help me!
I don't need a med kit!
No!
Take your meds, grandpa!
Take your meds!
Take your meds, Haruka.
Many, many, many time!
They are taking my rage!
Really?
Take your meds, Haruka.
What's this one?
I think I wanna go with this one.
Take your meds, grandma.
Oh, there's my beautiful goon.
Grandma.
Oh, sorry.
Can we not shoot me?
That would be great.
Sorry.
I don't need my meds.
Why are you like this?
I'm like this.
You don't wanna face with me.
Oh.
Steve!
Oh, John.
Leave me alone.
Steve, you've been caught this wrong.
Steve!
Here they come.
Oh my goodness.
I can't see anything.
Right?
My vision is just blinded by everything.
My beauty?
Blinded by my sexiness.
Just say it, Mint.
I don't need no fucking medicine to be able to kick some fucking zombie's ass into the next Tuesday.
There's some Molotov over there.
Molotov?
It's straight stuff for breakfast.
Just drink that.
Three words.
Eight letters.
Hell yeah.
What's the letter?
Do you know how to smell?
I'll tell you what.
Apparently not.
Guys, there's ammo here upstairs and a big gun.
Okay.
Oh yeah, there's ammo.
There's ammo.
And there's stairs.
I think this is where we need to go in the future.
What's the guy in the back?
Oh, what's this?
Oh, big gun.
Yeah.
Big goon.
Big gun?
Yeah.
The boy ammo packs on the ground to share ammo with the team.
Okay, I'm gonna have an extra ammo for us.
Yeah.
For like a big fight if we all run out.
We go up these stairs, I believe.
Okay.
Hell yeah, brother.
Here we go.
I'll grab stairs.
Oh, look at him, girly.
Oh, accidentally took the wrong gun.
Whoopsie.
We gotta flick them door switch.
However, there's gonna be a horde if we do so.
Be careful.
Okay.
Yeah, make sure you grab the little molotov.
Yay!
Yep.
Am I just gonna be talking like this for the rest of the mission?
Are you?
Are you gonna be talking like this, Haruko?
Oh my god.
Hey, everyone.
There's like a big turret.
Oh, Haruka alerted the horde.
Does anybody want to get crazy with the big turret?
Yeah, you got it, girly.
Come on.
Oh, I can't.
It's very limited.
Oh, gosh.
Do your best.
Uh-oh.
Um, yep.
Help me.
Oh, nice.
We got a big boy.
Big boy.
Uh, okay.
Sorry.
Charging.
Oh my god.
You will fuck this shit.
Me, behind you.
Behind me?
How do I get off this thing?
Oh, gosh.
I'm really struggling with this gun.
Why can't I shoot?
Why wouldn't it shoot?
Son of a bitch, I'm down.
You're down?
Oh, where am I?
I'm down.
Oh, are you good?
He's alive.
Ready?
Yeah, I'm not loving this shotgun.
I think it's not my type of gun.
It's hard when you have to shoot fast, you know?
Ready?
Yeah.
I need one of those.
Yeah, that's why I switched to...
I need one of them fast American guns.
You know what I mean?
I'm gonna shoot you.
Whoa.
None of these Russian Kalashnikovs for me.
For me.
All right, queens.
None of them Soviet buildings for me.
Where do we go?
Oh, shit.
I'm getting dunked.
Help me.
Thank you.
Oh, shit.
What?
You got it?
Nice.
Yeah.
Fuck you, young McDonald.
Nice.
I still remember the time you gave me a raw burger, that son of a bitch.
Oh.
That's not very American of him.
I'm good.
Eat a burger.
I tell you what.
I tell you what, Bobby.
Real good American burger made on the propane gas.
Is there any gas for my chainsaw?
Chainsaw.
I hear crying.
Me too.
Oh, there's a shovel here.
I hear crying every day of my life.
That's me when I cry on the plane.
That's the weakness leaving my body.
Oh, I hear a...
What the?
Help us.
It's a YouTuber.
Why won't they help us?
Guys, why won't you help us?
What?
They just left us.
It's a doggy dog world out there.
They just wanted to film the doggy dog.
I used to think that it was doggy dog.
Oh, yeah.
Doggy dog.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know what you mean.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Doggy dog world.
I'll tell you.
I'll tell you what.
Is it down here?
I believe so.
Oh, Haru.
What happened to not needing med kits, huh?
Sae picked up and used that med kit.
Oh, sorry, Haru.
Sorry.
Sorry, Haru.
Oh, jeez.
Oh.
Oh, golly.
Why don't they save us?
I'm able to use med kit to be able to wield my health.
Guys, guys, guys.
I need your help.
I'm getting jockeyed.
Oh, no.
Stop.
Why can't I get out?
Oh, my gosh.
There we go.
Oh, gosh.
Fuck you, wing.
I'm allergic to women.
And off of my body, sick fuck.
I got you.
Oh, that's crazy.
I don't need no medicine.
I can just meditate.
My health will come back.
Oh, that's crazy.
Manifest a healthy lifestyle, and it will come to you.
Honestly, I need nothing but American burgers, then my health will come back.
Well, okay.
Come here, Matara-Khan.
Come here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, I sure do love medicine.
Chow down on that.
Chow down.
I love my prescription medication.
I tell you what.
Oh, sorry.
What have you done?
I thought you were gonna say, go, go, go, go.
This is bad.
I was just testing it.
T Index.
Careful.
I'm gonna put a fire.
Move, move, move.
Could you warn me?
Oh, my God.
I'm setting another fire.
Give me fire.
Oh, my God.
Turning up, baby.
I am the wave of a landslop.
I am the wave of my landslop.
I'm seeing what a dog sees.
No color in my future.
No color in your future.
No color in your future except red wine blue.
See, we handle that.
We say we handle that.
Free ice cream.
Quick, there's a safe room in here.
Oh, nice.
Are the only colors in my life.
But what if I don't want to get in?
What if I like it?
I'll shoot you down, you son of a bitch.
Ah!
How unpatriotic of you to come to.
Almost about to die.
Nice!
Absolutely unpatriotic.
He was about to die.
Yee-haw!
That's the patriotic experience.
Yay!
Talk medicine.
I love the Fourth of July.
Ugh.
Use your health kit.
I'm using my health kit.
You're giving me anxiety.
I'm going to meditate real quick.
Do it.
I am meditating.
Now my ankle has magically fixed itself.
That's crazy.
Crazy.
Is there any gas in my chain muscle?
Crazy?
I don't think there's any gas here.
Ghosting!
Don't talk to me about the rats!
Which way do we go?
I don't know.
Let's go here, I think.
Because this one's bigger.
What is this?
I think we can go either way.
Oh.
Maybe?
Maybe.
There's like a few drugs here and stuff.
Yeah, there's some weapons here and stuff.
And some pills.
What's this one?
Um.
Only freaks climb up ladders.
Oh man, climbing up ladders are bad.
And snakes.
Remember that.
Is that a magnum?
I love my banana.
Which one?
Jockey!
Yee!
What was the gun I like?
Was it this one?
Haunter!
Oh, what do I hear?
Ahhhhh!
Nice.
Little bastard.
AK is better on this map.
Yay!
Wait, pipe bomb.
What do you mean yay?
I got a pipe bomb.
Oh, I got AD!
What?
AD!
I thought you said ADD.
Me too, I thought you said big ADD.
Not AD!
Let's go here.
What do y'all think?
Yeah, this is the way.
If you see zombies, you know you're going the right way.
True.
If you see zombies, better hit them right between the eyes.
Wow!
He's zombies in the Five Nights at Freddy's.
Hit em right between the eyes.
Would you like a Krabby Patty?
No, but I'll take some free ice cream.
Yummy, yummy.
Free ice cream?
Oh!
Free lo...
Oh my gosh.
Leave me alone.
Ugly.
Oh my gosh.
Thank you, ladies.
Yee-haw to you.
Yee-haw to...
What is this accent?
I don't think that was...
I'm Bethany Ann and I lost my left nipple in a hot dog eating contest in Tucson, Arizona.
Yee-haw.
Thank you!
Um.
Was that me?
Everyone.
What?
It wasn't me.
It wasn't me at all.
Wasn't me.
It wasn't me.
Oh no.
Oh no!
Free ice cream!
Where are they gonna be?
I have a molotov.
Me too.
I have a pipe bomb.
I have a molotov!
Oh no, I have a pipe bomb.
I have a pipe bomb.
There's a guy right there.
I'm allergic to teletubbies.
Oh, sorry baby.
I shot you.
Me?
I just shot you in the genitalia.
Honestly, I was just intimidated by how big he is.
I swear to God.
I thought to myself, if I can get him to have a little smaller genitalia, I'll be less intimidated.
What are you talking about?
I don't know how I feel about this.
I'm inside.
Let's see.
I wish I was inside the warmth.
I'm now stuck in here.
Let's go.
Guys, we still need you.
Come right back, you unpatriotic sons of guns.
What are you talking about?
We're killing.
That's the most patriotic thing you could do.
Come back, you unpatriotic girls.
Oh, sorry.
Ow, guys.
Ow.
Hi, Rupo.
Thank you.
Where are you going over there?
I'm drinking beer.
Am I dying?
Don't die.
Oh, there's a tongue man.
Tongue, tongue, tongue.
Tongue, tongue.
Guys, guys, guys.
I need help.
I got you.
Sorry.
He hit me right as I was providing you.
Yeah, I know.
Penny, I need your help.
Okay.
I'm coming.
Oh, wow.
Oh, gosh.
Hello?
Leave me alone.
Hey, what am I?
Oh, my God.
Leave me alone.
You're so sad.
They're obsessed with me.
I know.
Oh, that's a gun.
Down here, you bitches.
I'm seeing like a dog.
I'm coming.
It's Three Dog.
Ow.
What?
This way.
Okay, guys.
There's another health kit here if anybody needs.
Oh, I need if I can have it.
Get it, Mint.
Yeah, yeah.
Have it.
Here.
I'm going to do the other one.
Weak.
Weak as hell.
Me?
Who needs medicine this day and age?
Not me.
I just meditate.
You know what?
I don't think about the consequences I'm already in, so I don't even think about getting hit.
I saw you sneaking medicine, Haruka, earlier.
Yeah, you were sneaking medicine in the middle of the night.
I saw you take them drugs.
It wasn't medicine.
It was a prescribed medication.
That wasn't very American of you.
You brought a medicine.
Guys, I have a pile.
Next time the zombies...
Oh, shit.
Oh, ow.
I got a donkey.
Oh, thank you.
Next time the zombie horde comes...
Yeah?
Oh, fuck.
I need your help.
I...
Oh, sorry.
Oh, shit.
It's okay.
You just...
I'm gonna vile bomb them.
Lucky.
It's a really good...
Weapons over here.
I'm gonna vile bomb them.
Right now?
I did a little close.
I think I did a little too close, but it's okay.
Yeah, you did.
It's fine.
Probably.
Whoopsie daisy.
Whoopsie whoopsie.
Your honor, I plead whoopsie whoopsie.
I cannot even see where I am.
Oh, from up the stairs?
Where do we go?
The stairs?
I got you.
Oh, okay.
No, we go down here.
This way?
I think.
Where do we go now?
This way?
Where do we go?
Where do we go now?
Where do we go down here?
Haruka, I think you had the wrong...
Oh, it's right here.
Oh, please.
Yeah, I'm ready to get stinky smelly.
Oh, wait.
I'm actually stuck.
It's so un-stinky.
Wait, how do I get out?
Oh, there we go.
Where are you?
Wangy wangy.
Nice.
Oh, there's a witch.
There's a witch.
Where?
I hear her crying.
Let's...
If we aggro her, let's be careful.
I think I heard her.
You just had a big fire.
Well, we can just aggro her.
Oh, Charger, where?
I had you.
Okay, I think we found the Charger.
Oh my gosh.
Thank you.
I think we found the Charger.
I don't think we should aggro the witch because then they bring a horde and we'll die.
Oh, I see.
Why don't we just man up?
Wait, where did they come from?
And kill the witch.
Where did they go?
They've been married a long time ago.
Oh, they come inside.
Guys, guys, there's a little secret way here.
Oh, there's a witch.
There's a witch.
Let's kill her.
Oh, there she is.
There she is.
No, don't kill her.
Okay, fine, fine, fine.
Let's go.
Just avoid it.
I think this is going to bite us in the ass.
Yeah, let's go over here.
That guy is dead.
I think this is going to backfire, but you know what?
No.
I don't like the rules.
We're not going back.
It'll be fine.
I'm just a little follower.
I think we just want to kill the witch and then...
Guys, guys, here, here, here.
Ammo, ammo.
I want to kill everything.
I'm ready to kill.
I'm going to kill Bill.
Wait, I'm Bill.
Oh, there's a secret passage over here.
Oh, what's this?
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
Oh.
Guys!
Oh, okay.
Nice.
Molotov.
Thank you.
Wait, is there another witch?
No, I think there's only one.
For me, the witch is the ring.
Like that girl from the movie.
Oh, really?
That's so freaky.
Yeah.
Oh, I see her.
I see her.
She's up there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We went around her.
Smart girls.
I think it's here.
Okay.
Stop crying, you baby.
Oh.
Wait.
No, I think we went around.
I think you went in a circle.
Yeah.
You're not...
You're not this way.
You're not excused.
I don't think it's this way either.
I don't know where to go, actually.
Oh.
Oh, nice.
Nice.
What about...
So, the witch is there.
I think we have to go to the left.
Yeah.
We're higher wind.
We're higher wind?
Okay.
Yeah.
We're higher wind, I think.
Okay.
Ew.
Wait for the bile.
I'm gonna die.
Oh.
There was a guy crawling through it.
That's so freaky.
Oh.
Ew.
It's wet in here.
It's because it's a sewer.
It's so wet.
It's like...
Oh.
Wait.
I can't...
Oh.
I can't see anything.
What happened?
Okay.
The witch is over there.
Be careful.
Yeah.
Come to the...
Where Hena is.
This way.
Okay.
Hena, let me go ahead of you so that I don't accidentally shoot you.
Oh.
You guys are headed towards her, though.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Wait.
Whoa.
Hena.
Come back.
Oh.
Uh-oh.
You guys?
I'm no scared of bitches.
Hell yeah.
I got him.
Reloading.
So not this way.
Do you need ammo, Haruka?
Oh.
Hold on.
Let's come back here.
Wait.
I don't have the ammo.
Okay.
No.
Haruka, throw the witch.
I'm scared no bitches.
You're going to be okay.
Oh my gosh.
All right.
Well, now that the witch is dead, it's up here.
It's up here.
Oh my god.
It was here the whole time.
This one?
What a thrill.
Is that a guy?
No.
That's not a good guy.
There's no good guys in this game.
I could really use this place to meditate.
Wait.
You have to look up.
Oh my god.
Bunch of guns over here.
Yeah.
You just got to...
Bunch of guns over here.
Safe house over there.
Safe house.
Oh.
Safe house over here?
Are you sure that's a safe house?
Well, it says house with a plus sign.
Do you see?
Yeah.
It's right there.
You jerk.
I didn't know.
Yatta.
Are you sure there's a safe house over there?
There's a med kit right here.
Wait.
Oh.
I would love to have it.
Yeah.
I'll get you inside.
Okay.
Thank you.
Let's close the door.
Okay.
I'm gonna watch TV.
Oh my god.
Man.
You're kind of killing it.
You're kind of cracked with it.
Nice.
I like to kill.
What did you say, man?
Come here.
Oh wait.
Are you...
Oh here we go.
Oh thank you.
Girl, don't go.
Girls, girls, girls, there's three medkits over here.
We are not leaving here without you bitches healing.
I'm watching television.
Haruka, you piece of shit.
It's my favorite channel.
Is that a shotgun?
I think that's a shotgun.
I think that would be a good one, right?
Sorry, grandpa.
Grandpa grew up as an iPad kid, clearly.
Guys, there's...
Okay, I'm gonna take it.
Oh, we're in the hospital.
This is so scary.
I am terrified.
We're in the hospital.
Hospital time.
Oh, you guys already went?
I am happy.
Medication time.
In a bag.
Oh, that's a...
Freak me out.
Oh, does this heal you?
It was like an oxygen tank.
Before you go go.
Why are skeletons so funny?
Spooky scary skeletons.
Among Us!
Oh, I see him.
Among Us, Among Us.
Oh, jumper, jumper.
Jockey, jockey.
I'm jockey.
I got him.
Doughy, Tashi, Marsh.
Oh, wait.
Are we got killed?
Oh, watch out, watch out.
Sorry, I was scratching my nose.
Oh my god, now you made my nose itchy.
Scratch, scratch.
How do you say itch, itch or scratch, scratch in Japanese?
They're like...
Itchy you'll be coyote.
Coyote.
Coyote, coyote.
Coyote is itchy.
Oh, wait.
How do I get to you guys?
I'm lost.
So much damage.
Oh, this way.
Thank you.
Coyote, coyote.
Second floor time.
Weapons over here.
Oh, there's a pipe bomb.
Blah, blah, blah.
What does this oxygen do?
Does it just explode?
Yeah, I think it explodes.
I think that's the answer.
I'm hearing a jockey.
It's Toad.
I got him.
Jockey.
Oh.
I thought that was a sparkler.
Reloading.
Bustin' makes her feel good.
Bustin', bustin', bustin'.
Oh.
I got you, princess.
Thank you.
Bustin' made me feel good.
Bustin', bustin', bustin'.
Oh.
I didn't know she was there.
Don't worry.
I think that's the point, girl.
So you're probably wondering how I got here.
Funny story.
This is kind of funny.
Oh, thanks.
You're welcome.
It was like... I actually saved you guys because I took care of her, you know?
Blah, blah, blah.
Is it gonna... Oh!
You son of a gun.
I didn't know you were that close.
This is the infectious air...
Oh, this is so creepy.
It is.
So creepy.
I don't know if we call this elevator.
A whore?
Oh, there it is.
Did I push it?
I'm almost...
Oh my god!
Back up, back up, back up.
I'm all good.
I try to drive on through the night.
Are we good?
Almost.
Oh, whoa.
I believe that hurt me through the door.
Ugh, annoying.
Oh my god.
I got him.
So one more hit and I am dead.
Okay.
Where's the elevator?
Why is it so slow?
It shouldn't be this slow at a hospital.
That's dangerous.
Among Us, Among Us coming.
Among Us.
Oh my god.
There's so many Among Us.
Oh fuck, big guy, big guy, big guy.
Guys, I am dead.
Oh, you guys are dead.
Oh no.
You got him?
I got you.
Thank you.
Oh, watch out for the...
Oh, there we go.
Where's my lucky number?
Where's my favorite number?
Three is my favorite number.
Four is my favorite number.
Really?
Miss, pick your own favorite number.
Oh wait, is that your favorite number?
I got this number first.
It's dead.
Why is everybody picking four?
I liked number four before you were dead.
I liked four forever.
I am old.
Four plus infinity.
It's the day that I was born.
My flesh woman.
It's in your mouth.
Hence, it's mine.
Okay, how about we both like the number four?
How about that?
How about we both can like number four?
If we like 44, we can split the four, you know?
No, I like two.
I like 24.
Oh, sorry.
I keep timing out of my game and then clicking back in.
Just right click back in, that's what I do.
Oh, that's good.
Behind you, Haru.
Oh.
It says stay out of the line of fire.
Wow, this is such a beautiful scene.
Oh, sorry, you scared me.
Don't come running up on me, old man.
I was just looking over.
Wait, did you fall?
Yeah, I did.
Oopsie poopsie.
Oh, there's a smoker nearby.
Help!
Oh, I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming!
Smoker, smoker, smoker, you got her?
Yep.
I got you.
Listen, we both can like the number four.
Good job, girl.
Take your medicine.
Good job!
Wait, what about me?
My brain's not calm enough to meditate right now.
Okay.
So I need to find a nice, calm spot to meditate.
You know what I'm saying?
There's a thing to blow up.
Blow it up, Min.
No!
Listen to the demons in your head.
There's no reason to...
Reloading.
Smoker?
I hardly even know her.
Is it this way?
Careful.
For funsies, what if there was enemies?
What if we had to go that way?
Well, we could wait.
Uh-oh, I hear music.
I hear a little guy.
Nice.
I got the boomer.
This way?
I killed Matarakon.
It's so weird seeing Peter's head being ripped apart.
We're on date.
Honestly, living with you is worse than death.
I don't even live.
You're not living with me at all.
Oh, sorry.
It's okay.
I like to get shot by you.
Oh, nice!
You can shoot me as many times as you want.
Yay!
Is that a spear?
I'm gonna bleed out here soon, guys.
I just wanna let you know.
I'll bleed it out, take it deeper just to throw it away.
Wait, there's a safe house!
Safe house!
I'll bleed out in here.
I'll bleed it out.
Get your bombs and your coffee.
Look at her go.
Silver the hedgehog.
Oh.
Let's go!
Yeah!
I only did the most damage because she was on top of me.
That's the most action you'll ever get.
It's true, actually.
Dang, why'd you have to tell the truth like that?
Why are you such a truther?
Girls, get your health packs.
Get your meds.
Get your medpacks.
That was a good meditation.
There's a molotov and a pipe bomb.
And a pipe dream.
No, it doesn't three days.
What's a better gun, everybody?
This one?
Number one?
Or this one?
It takes four days to change?
No, it doesn't.
It takes two and a half hours.
Number two.
Or this one, number three.
They only come out at night.
That's not true!
They're here all the time!
No zombie is safe.
No zombie.
I'm keeping this gun.
I saw it happen in five minutes.
Let's go!
Two and a half hours.
Did we take all the medkits?
Let's fucking go!
Kill, kill, kill!
Oh, I should've reloaded.
That's embarrassing.
His little butt!
I saw his little butt!
I saw his little buttsy!
That's embarrassing.
So embarrassing.
Oh my god.
Why was your butt out like that?
Are you showing your butt?
So embarrassing.
Hello?
Oh god!
Oh god, oh god, oh god!
Oh my!
There's a boomer up in here!
What the?
My god, I had help and now I don't.
What's going on?
Was it here?
Which one of you non-Americans shot me?
Whoa!
Hi!
No, no, come back!
I got him!
I think the jockey just...
I think he just fell to his death.
That was so funny.
I listened to him scream.
I've heard his final words.
Oh, how do I get up here?
Wait, how do I get up here?
You climb, bitch!
I'm trying!
Oh, this way.
Right here?
Oh, this guy looks like a Batman!
Oh, this is the perfect time for a sniper.
Oh my!
Get away from me!
I'm talking to you!
I'm talking to you, Batara!
You freak!
Get away from me, you freak!
But are you still obsessed with me?
I'm not even listening to you anymore.
I think we have to go down here.
I didn't miss.
I didn't miss at all.
Obviously.
Yeah, that would be crazy if I missed.
Why do I...
Sorry.
Help me, please!
I'm kidding!
I'm in an anime!
Batara, I'm not Batara.
I'm coming.
Okay, never mind.
Did you just talk to yourself in the third frame?
I called you Batara by accident.
Listen, I am all video-gamed out.
I have like...
I am old and this game is a lot for my old woman brain.
It is a lot.
It is so much.
It's okay.
I'm Batara now, everybody.
Hi, honey.
There's a grenade launcher here if anyone wants to...
Wait, there's a medkit over here!
And boobies.
There's a medkit, there's an ammo, and there's a gun.
Why do you say like it's a bad thing that I like boobies, you know?
I love boobies and cute girls and cute girls with boobies.
Hana!
There's a grenade launcher over here.
I like my gun.
I love you.
Take it.
Rescue's coming, girls.
Let's all stand together and then...
Yeah.
Ice cream!
Wait.
I'm throwing...
I'm throwing gasoline if anyone wants to blow it up.
Okay, maybe I like my gun better.
Spitter.
What is a spitter?
I don't know.
Oh my gosh.
Can you?
No!
I got you.
No, no, no, no!
Wait, who did I just see?
I'm here trying to help Hania but I need your guys...
Hania, can you keep shooting the ones in front of you?
I'm trying.
Oh, no!
Oh, I got the jockey.
I got the jockey.
I can't help you.
I'm saving Hania.
It's okay.
I'll just die, I think, actually.
Die.
Yeah, I'm down.
I'm sorry.
I was down.
I wasn't near you.
Hania, are you okay?
Use your med kit.
Okay.
Oh, sorry if I shot you.
Use your med kit, Hania.
There was med kit nearby me, but I don't know if you guys heard me.
I...
Yeah, we're coming.
We're coming.
I have one, so I just gotta get revived and I'll be good.
Mint, I'm coming, you jerk.
Oh, a spitter?
Francis, let's go!
Get up!
He's a quitter.
Francis?
Who's Francis?
Oh, that's me.
Haha, he's showing his butt.
So embarrassing.
Look at me.
Uh, I'm reloading.
I'm reloading.
Oh, you got him, though.
Hehe.
Silly zombies.
What do you think?
Tank?
Oh, it's behind you.
It's behind you.
I got taken.
Thank you, Hadu.
My angel.
Uh-oh.
Metal Gear!
No!
Oh, my gosh.
Throw!
I'm throwing a pipe bomb!
Uh-oh.
Wait.
Oh, oh.
Oh,
my gosh.
Please reload!
What's taking so long?
What was taking so long?
Hadu!
I got you!
Oh, fuck.
I couldn't hide that.
Thank you!
Oh, my gosh.
Get rekt.
Vile spitter down.
I see her.
Oh, Minc.
Minc.
I can heal you.
Oh!
Where are you?
I'll guard.
Thank you!
My angel!
You're such an angel.
You're such a genius!
I'm a genius!
So cute!
Guys, I'm gonna throw a pipe bomb in the middle.
Oh, my God!
I'm not a guy.
Minc, get out of the way.
I'm trying to.
I'm trying!
Is there any ammo anywhere?
Yes.
On a lot of spots.
There is?
Why can't I find anything?
Oh, here.
Here.
Oh, thank God.
Reloading.
Why are you in the hole?
Oh, big guy.
Big guy.
Oh, fuck.
I need help.
I got him.
Thank you, girl.
You're welcome.
See, isn't it a good thing that I reloaded?
Oh, I need to go.
He's gonna die.
Thank you.
Die!
Zombie!
I like when their body parts fly everywhere.
Getting tongue.
Oh, where are you?
Oh, I got you.
I got you.
I'm in a weird spot.
I'm reloading.
Are you good?
Oh,
I can't see.
Uh-oh.
Oh, gosh.
Get off of me.
Get off me, stupid zombie.
Oh, sorry.
That's you.
This is a really long we're coming to save you guys.
I know, right?
Clearly.
Oh, I'm pinned.
I'm pinned.
Oh, thank you.
Minc, there's ammo up here if you come to us.
There's tank here.
I hear Thanos.
I'm coming.
The tank is coming.
Do we have any...
He's here.
I see him.
Oh, wait.
I can't go this way.
Bombs away anywhere?
Any waddle the way.
Waddle, waddle.
Get him.
Metal Gear, I'm sorry.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my gosh.
You scared me.
I'm sorry.
The chopper's here.
Oh, the chopper's here.
Guys, boomer.
And we got a final ward.
Where do we go?
Final ward?
Fuck.
Please don't shoot me up right here.
Oh, guys.
There's a charger behind us.
Guys, guys, guys, guys, guys.
Can you revive me, please?
I don't know about that.
Minc, I'm gonna shoot you.
Oh, there's another tank.
Oh, my God.
Are you coming?
I'm just gonna chill in here, honestly.
Oh, hey, hey, hey, hey.
This is an exclusive club.
Shit.
Oh, my God.
Metal.
Oh, no.
Brax, please.
Haru, Haru, jump, jump, jump, Haru.
Haru, come, come, come.
There we go.
I punched the shit out of that tank.
Good job.
Look at him.
Look, he's so cute down there.
Okay.
No, look at him.
He's so upset.
Yeah, he looks so upset.
Yeah, he looks mad.
He's so cute.
Oh, he just fell down.
Okay.
Yeah, baby.
We did it.
Yeah.
I'm so tired from...
This game is so overwhelming, but it was so much fun.
It was.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Yeah, we can.
We can.
Zero deaths.
Let's go, baby.
We owe zero deaths.
All zero deaths.
Nice.
Drugs used me.
I bombed me.
You have a bit of a problem, baby.
Well, the melee kills.
Nice.
Good job, girl.
That was so much fun.
Yeah.
Nice.
That was so fun.
I'm sorry if I yelled a bit much.
Girl, this is a yelling game.
Don't worry about it.
This is a yelling game.
Okay, I'm sorry for the 51.
It was you last time, too.
Oh, my gosh.
I revived the most.
I protected and I healed the most.
Still getting that head shot, baby.
You're perfect.
Girl, you got 11%.
It's nothing to brag about.
That's still better than you.
That was a lot of fun.
Yeah, thank you for playing.
It was nice to revisit this game again.
I know, right?
It was fun.
I feel like I can only play it once a year.
I know, right?
Oh, man.
It was fun.
It's so overwhelming.
It is very.
Yeah.
Who is still going to stream for a bit?
Me.
Okay.
Mint, we're going to do something fun.
I'm going to try to give you a manual raid on your YouTube.
Okay?
Just act surprised when it happens.
Manual raid.
Bye-bye, everybody.
Bye-bye.
Bye-bye, you smell.
I smell good.
I smell delicious.
Bye, stinky.
Bye.
She said stinky.
She thinks both of us are stinky.
I'm stinky in a good way.
I'm a minty stinky, you know?
God, I love the smell of mint.
I know.
Why did I say it like that?
Bye.
Bye-bye.
Hold on.
Give me a second.
I need to...
I need to actually, like, simmer down from all that craziness.
Every time I play that game, it is so...
Just all yelling, all running, all screaming.
It is just a crazy...
Okay, you guys, let's relax now.
Actually, hold on.
This is called Rain Relax.
What does it sound like?
What's it sound like?
Oh, okay.
This is relaxing.
Yeah, we're relaxed.
Oh.
Ah.
Nice to see you playing it for the first time with Henya.
Yeah.
She's such a gamer.
Thank you.
Fun.
Mint carried not even a little bit.
Not even a fraction.
Well, I guess technically a fraction because I was in the game.
But...
Takizo, thank you for the five gifted.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Oh, why are notives not on here?
Okay, now they're showing up.
Sorry about that.
You were MVP at one point.
Notives are off the screen.
Yeah, I noticed.
Thank you.
Murphy, thanks for the 20.
Oh my gosh, I'm feeling so relaxed right now.
Oh, K4, thanks for the 10.
AKSJF2, thank you for the 10.
Oh, Doug dim a dome carry.
Actually.
Oh my gosh, it was so fun to see Ray and then also Rex.
It was so fun.
So fun, so fun.
Raymac, thank you for the five gifted.
Oh.
Sorry if that was just like...
Everything overload.
I know it was for me.
Holy cow.
But it was... it was fun.
Your mod choices were top tier.
Thanks.
I like looked really hard for some really silly ones.
Thanks for that.
Haven't seen a good elf for D in a long time.
Thanks.
Haru is like really caring.
It was so funny listening to...
listening to...
Mata really trying to like...
ring everybody in.
And everyone's like, nah.
I kind of felt bad though.
Free ice cream!
I'm gonna hear that in my sleep.
Yeah, it did get funnier and funnier.
I was just like...
You know that picture of like...
of one person holding on to three different...
um...
leashes and everyone's going everywhere.
I think that was Matara today.
Oh...
Thanks for the...
for the ten gifted... thank you.
Had a rough day dealing with computer issues.
Glad I could watch...
Oh wait, hold on.
Sorry, my music.
Glad I could watch you girls be goofy.
To keep my mind off things.
Yeah, well it's Friday.
You can also have the weekend.
To just relax.
Cool, thanks for the...
ten gifted...
thank you.
Thank you for the fifty gifted...
Stop!
Why?
Also, if you haven't noticed, I fixed the membership thing.
So the notice won't...
show up a bajillion times.
And clog it up.
I figured it out.
Unfortunately, it won't...
show like if someone joins normally.
But I'll try to keep it.
I'll try to...
notice it when it happens.
It wasn't really a problem.
It was just that if someone gifted...
a lot of...
memberships, it would just be like...
So-and-so became a member.
It made the notice...
really backed up.
What do you guys have planned for the weekend?
Mitros, thanks for the ten!
While the suck things are the five!
Cinco de Mayo this weekend!
Woo!
Uh...
Vamanos!
KBBQ with friends tomorrow?
Oh my god, that sounds so good!
I haven't had KBBQ in so long!
Just chillin'.
Nice.
Zomboid server with friends?
You haven't had enough zombies?
I think I've had... I'm all zommed out.
I'm zommed out.
I'm a ghost, not a zombie.
I'm dead.
Not undead.
Going to a convention next two days.
Sorry if I don't catch the train.
Wait, what con?
What convention is this weekend?
I, um...
Oh, Sawcon!
I think that's every weekend though, actually.
Why can't I remember Sawcon, but I can't remember the names?
Oh well.
Plants vs.
Zombies 15th Anniversary this weekend.
No way!
Really?
Wow.
Meep!
Thanks for the 10!
It's a local convention in Mexico.
Oh!
Awesome.
Wait, they have a convention during Cinco de Mayo?
I guess...
I mean, I guess it's kind of the same when like...
What's it?
Anime Expo does theirs on...
on...
4th of July.
Thanks, Mint.
What did I do?
Hooray!
Thank you!
When I started watching you, I just quit my job.
Leaving was scary, but watching you inspired me to push through the fear.
One day I start my apprenticeship fixing airplanes!
Thank you, Mint, for being my push.
Oh my gosh, Ray.
We need you in the world right now, actually.
Oh my gosh.
I was looking at my flights for some of my upcoming events.
That I'm going to.
You guys...
Two of my flights are Boeing.
If I don't make it, go on without me.
I might be seeing the light this...
Not this weekend.
Thank you for the gift!
Thank you!
But they're not...
Can I call dibs on your stuff?
Sure.
No, it's not the 737 MAX, but it is a 737.
So I'm kind of scared.
Legitimately.
But...
I would say YOLO, but I'm already dead.
And I can't change it, which is the worst part about it.
Don't worry, you'll be safe.
Okay.
What's the worst that could happen?
I'll just make sure my...
Yoda...
You only die once.
Momo raid!
Thank you!
Hi, Motoro.
Hi, Momos.
Hello, hello.
Momo raid!
Manual raid!
What are you guys doing here?
What?
Oh my gosh.
Where did you all come from?
Matara!
Why are you gifting 50?
Stop that.
Matarakan.
I'm gonna tell your mother.
In case anyone is watching, Mint knows information is about to blow the whistle on it.
Get her!
What?
What if the door blows open though?
And I just float away.
I just float.
What if I land in Ohio?
Oh no.
Paperbacks.
Thanks for the 10 gift.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Morris, welcome to Mambooship.
I think you have 5 minute follow mode.
So my take of...
It was so fun.
Matara, good luck with your tournament later this month.
It's probably good that you played this time because imagine not playing before the tournament and seeing how overwhelming and insane it is.
My message doesn't show on the screen.
I see you right there.
Rope wash!
Thanks for the 10 gift.
The game is crazy.
Just like...
Are you gonna be streaming it?
Because if you're not streaming, you can literally put yourself into a trance and not even talk.
You can just...
Like
this.
Also, do you like my...
Do you like my really calming music after all of this?
I'm just playing the bunny game again.
As expected.
I have to continue because I want to get to the parts where you play with the cameras too.
But did I even leave space in my schedule for next week?
Let me see.
I have another collab next week actually.
I'm not gonna say you...
Oh wait, I do.
I do have a room.
Okay, bunny garden.
I can do it.
Hmm...
Uh...
Um...
Matara already said who it's with?
Huh?
How did... I don't think I told her.
No, that's not next week.
They're thinking of Deep Rock Galactic.
Oh yeah, Deep Rock Galactic is not next week.
No, no.
Hippie Kuma!
Thanks for the vibe.
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
But that's eventually.
That's eventually.
Um...
Yeah.
I know that Matara and I have been collabing a lot.
And we also have the podcast.
It's because I'm like...
nervous to talk to people.
So...
She kind of helps facilitate some things sometimes.
Proud of how much you've been networking.
I've been trying!
I've been trying for real.
So...
You know.
I'm trying to talk to people.
Borrowing that extrovert energy.
Yeah.
Prince Wendrew!
Thanks for the vibe!
Gifted!
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Gotta get to the 500k.
First!
I don't even...
What am I even at?
I don't even know.
98!
98.
Crazy.
Did I make it in time for the stream?
I mean it's kind of over.
But not like...
The gameplay is over, you know.
Mm-mm.
You might get them this weekend.
Who knows?
Thank you for the 50!
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you.
Oh, I'm not worrying about it at all.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not just like, why am I not at 200k?
No, I'm just...
I think it's cool that...
When I...
When I left, I was at 10k.
And now I'm almost at 200k.
I think that's a huge accomplishment.
So...
I'm not worried about it at all.
To be honest.
Yeah, I'm just vibing.
I'm having a good time.
Yeah.
Hashtag carried by Matara.
Slash sarcasm.
You have to put the sarcasm in there.
Robo!
Thank you for the 50 gift!
Thank you!
Thank you for the 10 gift!
Thank you so much.
I'm having a good time.
I'm not gonna have a good time next week though.
Because...
I might do an Atlantis no nazo in turn.
So I might have a really bad time next week actually.
Why do I do this?
An accomplishment?
What's so bad about it?
It's like...
Peak kusoge.
The game is just...
It's notoriously difficult and obtuse.
And...
Love the piano in the back.
Yeah, we're calming down after...
A very...
Stressful...
And crazy...
Game of left 4 dead.
Yes.
Trash NES game.
Exactly!
It is a trash NES game.
For real.
Which game?
Atlantis no nazo.
Mhm.
I must try it.
I must play it.
I've been wanting to for so long.
Yeah, we're calm.
We're calm.
If you hear my voice...
You are going into a trance.
And you will...
I love it because it's the first game Arino challenged in Game Center CX.
That's kind of why I want to play it.
I saw...
Him play it.
And...
Korone play it.
And I admire Korone's...
Endurance and...
Skills as a gamer.
It's not that I'm like...
How do I say this?
It's like...
I don't want to copy her.
I'm like...
She did this challenging game.
I want to do it too.
So I'm like...
I will try.
Yeah.
I'm inspired.
I admire her.
Inspired.
Matara told us to give you money.
So we obey.
Why would you listen to anything she ever says ever?
Finally caught you live.
Are you planning on replaying any of the MGS games?
Morky, I'm glad you asked.
I plan on replaying all of them.
Yeah!
Well...
I'm still deciding on MGS5.
But also...
Oh, wait.
I almost said something.
Snappy, thanks for the $10 gift.
Like the...
When I...
Like the last time I played 5...
I was on the fence about playing it before 2.
But I ended up playing it because I was just craving.
I was...
I was starving for the...
For the more Metal Gear content.
So...
Mmm...
I've based my personality on V.
Anthony...
Anthony!
You've based your personality on a silent protagonist!
Um...
But I think...
I think if I play V again...
Maybe um...
I might do something similar to how like with...
April 30th...
I only did the skateboarding game.
Like maybe I'll do certain missions or something.
Like I'll...
Made headband for one year win.
Um...
Didn't I have that?
Uh...
But it...
But YouTube erased it.
I have to re-upload it.
Holy cow!
Oh my gosh.
Sorry.
I just opened up YouTube.
To go check that.
This amazing digital circus is at...
9 million views!
In 5 hours!
Holy cow!
What?
Oh my gosh.
The kitties went crazy.
In 5 hours.
9 million views.
What is like the...
I wonder what like the record is.
For like most views in a certain amount of time.
The episode is good.
Um... I got to the part where like they...
Were riding up on the gators.
And then I went and took a shower.
Yeah there's an episode 2 out.
There's episode 2.
So if you want more...
Pomney action.
Yeah dude.
Us 6 monthers are chomping at the bit.
Oh you have 6 months!
Calm down.
No um...
I tried re-uploading the headband before.
And it said that it was not 1 to 1.
So I have to just...
I just have to... what's the word?
Um...
Resize it.
Yeah it says.
I'm trying to get...
100 million views.
Yeah obviously.
100 million.
I haven't opened a cookie clicker in a long time!
Oh my gosh.
Wait...
Oh...
Cookie...
Cookie clicker.
Play.
Let's see how my cookies are doing.
Happy May the 4th and Revenge of the 5th from Australia!
Is there any clone trooper class type squad or legion that you like as your favorite, both from Legends and Canon?
Oh my gosh, I've harvested 26 sugar lumps while I was away.
I've watched one Star War.
Yay!
Thank you for the reward!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
But I really like the Stormtrooper designs.
A long time ago, I tried to get one printed for myself.
I'm such a fake fan.
I did never even see... I'm such a poser.
I was gonna dress up as a Stormtrooper and I wasn't even going to...
I've never watched Star Wars.
See, every time I think about Star Wars, I just wanna watch Indiana Jones again, you know?
Every time... every time I...
Aren't you a little short to be a Stormtrooper?
What are you talking about?
There's no... there's no height requirement.
Members, watch along of Star Wars, please.
We can only... we can watch just the first three, right?
That was a quote.
That was a line from the movie.
Wait.
I'm gonna guess.
Does Han Solo say that?
That's my guess.
Is he... did he... did he say that?
Oh, no.
Go with Captain Houser.
He's pretty close to your color.
It's funny because I...
He was whispering the Samuel L.
Jackson storytime video.
Did I use this in that video?
I do remember that video though, but I don't remember if I did music in it.
Oh, and welcome to membership.
Um...
No, I meant the first three like the original first three.
But I do kind of want to watch the prequels too.
I do kind of want to watch the prequels also because I...
I don't know.
I want to laugh.
But I've seen... it's so bad.
I've seen Plinkett's reviews on...
from Red Letter Media.
I've seen his reviews about Star Wars, but...
I never watched anything myself.
Oh!
Doki Bird, FPS, Vtuber, Facebook, TTV, YouTube!
Thanks for the five gifted.
Thank you!
In fact, Shepardton Designs, the studio that made the original Stormtrooper suit...
is selling the full suit with the helmet and the blaster.
How much is expensive?
I'm curious.
How much is the...
I clapped when I saw it.
I've never watched them, but I'm watching in chronological order.
Is it one of those... is it a series that you should...
Like, okay, wait.
So it's the prequels?
And then, like, the original three movies that were made?
And then...
What was the recent ones that were made?
Wait, four, five, six, one, two, three, seven, eight, nine.
Seven, eight, nine.
I thought there were just two.
The sequels.
Wait, they're just called...
So it's the prequels, the originals, and the sequels?
It's only six.
And then I have to watch...
The Mandalorian.
When does the Clone Wars happen?
When did I watch that?
I can't believe I'm surrounded by a bunch of fakes.
I'm sorry.
Clone Trooper armor looks cool.
IMO, especially Captain Rex.
I'm like, hold on.
Captain... Rex.
Oh, I do like that.
I do like that.
Wait, you said the... the Clone Troopers?
I don't know.
They just don't look as...
I mean, they look cool.
Don't get me wrong.
But I think Stormtroopers are cuter.
Yeah, I like the Stormtrooper.
I like how his mouth is like a little triangle down.
It's so cute.
Oh wait, it's like that on the Clone Trooper.
But I also like that his head is bigger.
It's really wide.
He's got like a massive chin.
The helmet or the armor in general?
I really like the helmet.
The helmet.
Clone Troopers have collars?
Clone Trooper.
Trooper.
The Clone Trooper armor looks almost the same as the Stormtrooper armor.
I should have them side by side.
Stormtrooper.
You know about the Ewoks?
Are those the ones that go...
Hold on, hold on, I got this.
Hold on, hold on.
Oh, that was pretty good, that was...
That's a Wookiee.
Wookiee.
Wait, so what...
Ewok.
Oh!
Oh my god, they look like my old dog.
What?
I don't know if I like that, because I didn't like that dog.
It was really my mom's dog.
Star Wars only becomes watchable as an adult when you realize that the Jedi are crocked cops and Luke Skywalker was an android slave.
What is going on?
Jawas are cute?
Jawas.
Oh!
Oh my gosh, they look just like...
They just look like...
The Stab Guys!
The Tom... Tom...
Tom...
Tomberry?
Tonberry!
They look just like a Tonberry!
They look so cute, the Jawas.
Oh my gosh, even the plushies of them are so cute!
Oh, they're so, so cute.
Tonberries from Final Fantasy.
I like them.
Wait, what did you say about...
They make a funny noise too?
The Jawas?
What do they sound like?
Jabba the Hutt is really...
I know that guy.
He's the one that enslaves Leia.
Ootini!
Please look...
I know Jabba the Hutt.
I always thought that this guy was...
Was Emperor...
Emperor...
Hold on.
Emperor Palpatine.
I thought it was Emperor...
Stop making fun of me.
Emperor...
Palpatine.
They look kind of similar, I think.
Just kind of...
They're both really wrinkly.
I think that's why it was.
Emperor...
Stop making fun of me!
That's an old man.
One's an old man and one's a slug.
Close enough.
And he talks like this.
I'm Emperor Palpatine.
I said it again.
Stop.
What's wrong with me?
Marrowed, welcome to membership.
I'm Emperor Palpatine.
He says...
Do it.
It's like he's really here.
Palpatine is wife material, to be honest.
Really?
Is it like a gap moe?
Are you okay?
No, I think Left 4 Dead really took a lot out of me.
I think Left 4 Dead really took a chunk out of my brain.
It's okay.
Hold on.
I'm finding a good emote.
There we go.
Cute.
I'm embarrassed.
Okay.
I'm embarrassed that I can't speak properly.
I need to go to enunciation classes.
Actually, I've been thinking recently how much I want to take...
Improv classes.
I've been thinking...
Xeonia, look at the membership!
Thank you!
I've been thinking about how I want to do- I did improv classes as a kid because I took a lot of- I did like acting classes, I did dance..
I went to a school of the arts basically.
And so I um..
I was there for like...
years.
Um...
But I wanna get back into improv For like, you know, sometimes I like This is the first time I've ever watched a video on TikTok, and I'm like, how are they so quick?
How are they so witty, you know, it's like, oh my gosh, I really want to, and I like, try to consume a bunch of different kinds of media and like, you know, I know TikTok gets hated on a bunch, but like, honestly, because of how short form TikTok is, and how much I'm consuming,
like, I'm watching, I'm watching skits, I'm watching facts, I'm watching dumb stuff, like I'm able to to, like, absorb so many different topics within such a short amount of time, that it actually, like, I feel like it helps me.
Dropout TV is the who-whos line.
I've been watching so much Dropout, oh my gosh, Game Changer is like the funniest show, it's so good, like, they, man, they saved college humor, like, dang, Game Changer is so, if you haven't watched it before, it's so funny.
It's really, really good, um, but I've been here the whole time.
It used to be college humor, and then they, um, they changed it, but I watch, I watch, I only watch Game Changer and, um, actually, I only watch those two, Brendan is my wife, they're, they're really good.
Um.
Conan O'Brien recently released a podcast video with Dr. Arroyo.
It's like a whole improv video.
A podcast one?
I will watch it.
Conan O'Brien is also just a comedic genius.
There, I, I, there's so many comedic, so many people that are just so witty, I'm like, man, I need to, I want to study.
But you, it's also like, it's also just like, at the same time, it's, it's, it's, what's the word?
It's like, not overthinking stuff, you know, you have to just be able to, if you overthink it, then you can't pull it out of your, out of your brain so fast.
Sorry if this is talked about before, but I'm curious if you've ever played the early Kojima game, Snatcher.
If not, you play as a police detective.
I know all about Snatcher, dude.
Two, two, zero, seven, two.
Thank you for the super chat, by the way.
Um, actually, I do intend on playing Snatcher.
Um, I, uh, I own Policenauts.
I don't own Snatcher, but I would love to play Snatcher for sure.
But also I would have to get it in English, you know, I want to get it, get it like translated and stuff like that, but I really do want to play it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Conan's an actual genius too.
He graduated from Harvard.
Yeah.
You gotta be smart.
You gotta be quick on your feet.
Hmm.
So, hmm.
Snatcher has an English release?
It does?
Wait, why was I looking for it in Japan every time?
Oh, the Sega...
Yes, the Sega CD.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I...
That's why...
Okay, I do remember.
That's why I was struggling because that's why it's so expensive.
Thanks, Slow Beef.
That guy.
Internet dude, welcome to Bamboo Show.
Which version of Snatcher?
There's several.
They all have meaningful differences.
I recommend SD Snatcher, personally.
Yeah.
Oh, wait, what's the difference?
Also, Skeleton, I love your cat.
Post more of your cat.
Yeah, it's very expensive getting it though.
And I don't have a...
I don't have...
I might actually have to emulate it to be honest.
But I can do that now.
I can...
I can do that.
So, yeah.
Usually, I like to...
I don't know.
I feel more authentic if I play things as they originally were.
Like, you know, how I played Twin Snakes with my actual GameCube and stuff like that.
Thank you for the five gift.
I feel bad calling you that.
Mike Tyson.
Thank you for the five gift.
Thank you.
Mr.
Rats.
But, yeah.
Don't call him that.
I'm sorry.
Sega CD is hard to set up and Sega has been cool with emulation.
Oh, okay.
That's good to know.
Because I don't even have a way to...
I haven't looked into... even a way to port the console onto my computer, you know?
Diver, thank you.
If the notification for this doesn't show, you can call me a simp direct...
Yo, oh wait.
Which one was that?
I think there's more than one.
Wait.
Having a list actually made me think about what I can do and want to do.
A summer list was a good idea.
I'm glad!
Have you watched Very Important People?
So funny.
I have not.
I have not, I have not.
I think actually... wait, are the donuts actually backed up?
I'm confused now.
Maybe they don't show on the screen, but they do actually get backed up.
Interesting.
Interesting, interesting.
They seem to be.
Yeah, because I see yours too, Vera.
Good luck on the karaoke relay.
It's such a stacked event.
Have fun.
Yeah, I'm still... I'll be honest, I'm still trying to...
I'm still trying to think of what songs I want to sing.
But...
Maybe I like Very Important People.
Oh, by Dropout.
Oh, it's by Dropout.
If you want more improv.
Interesting, interesting.
The summer list sent you into an existential crisis?
Why?
It's just thinking of stuff you want to do.
It doesn't have to be like a goal list or anything.
It can be just like, I want to...
I want to... I want to eat a hamburger.
I want to grill my own hamburger.
I think I have an idea for what I want to do for the karaoke.
But...
I'm also kind of like...
Like,
I don't know.
I don't want to be that person.
That's all.
Because I wanted to do like all Metal Gear songs.
And have it like kind of Metal Gear themed, but...
I don't know.
People have asked for like a Metal Gear karaoke.
And I'd totally be down for that.
But...
There's honestly not that many.
Haruka!
Arigato!
Hamburger!
Hehehe.
Hmm.
Do it, do it.
Oh, Metal Gear Rising does have a lot of songs.
I guess that's true.
I was always thinking of Metal Gear Solid.
Instead of...
How long is each person's segment?
About 20 minutes?
So...
Hmm.
That's why I was just like...
Well, you know...
If someone...
If someone's just like...
Wow.
Maybe Mint is kind of cool.
They have to know...
The brain rot that they're getting into as well.
Just a little bit, maybe.
And also...
Even though it's Metal Gear songs...
They're still good songs.
So...
It's not that they're bad songs.
Only Limp Bizkit.
Hahaha.
It's another improv show where they take comedians and put them in costumes and makeup and they improv their way through the interview with Vic Michaelis.
It's so funny to see their improv.
Also, good luck with karaoke.
Thank you!
All the licensed songs...
Oh!
That's kind of fun, right?
Where it's like technically Metal Gear songs.
Have you played Death Stranding?
Actually, I was just thinking about that.
Oh my gosh.
I was just thinking about how I was like...
Man, I think I will start playing more Death Stranding in my off time.
I say more, but like...
I haven't touched it in a long time.
But I've definitely been thinking about it.
Take on me.
Take me home.
I'll be home.
In a day or two.
Death Stranding is an experience.
Wait, it's home?
Well, I don't know.
Take...
Take on me lyrics.
Take on...
Oh!
I'll be gone.
In a day or two.
I need the...
I need water.
I've been out of...
I've been out of water for like...
Two hours now.
I need to get up and I need to...
I don't have to go to...
Take care of my health.
It's slowly going to be dark up again.
But it'll get better back here later.
It does look pretty fine.
from...
the thorns and...
But, you know.
Let me just see if I can catch anything...
in this...
bench...
Stop playing the sad music, I'm gonna cry.
It's not sad, it's relaxing.
It's relaxing time.
In fact, it's making me tired.
It's making me sleepy overall.
Oh wow, oh my gosh, it's almost midnight.
I might actually head out in about 5 minutes.
So that I can get rest for tomorrow.
And um...
Yeah.
Why do I have so many messages?
Oh.
Nice.
Oh my gosh, wait, I have so many messages.
Okay, I have stuff to do tonight.
Mata played Halo recently, fancy trying it.
Oh, yes, actually we talked about that earlier.
And yes, I am interested.
I just have to...
I have to...
Just do it.
I was kind of like...
Halo is one of those series that...
Kind of like...
With Metal Gear, I was overwhelmed by...
I was overwhelmed by...
Where to start and everything.
Now I feel that way with Halo.
You know?
Good night, Mint.
Thanks for the stream today.
Good night!
No, it's not that I dislike FPS.
I actually very much like FPS.
I'm not good at FPS, but I like it.
I like it.
I'm just...
I'm not good at it, but I think it's fine.
Yeah.
Sorry we overwhelmed you.
No, it's not you guys.
It's overwhelming for me to know...
Where do I start, you know?
So, once I'm to that point though, I will ask.
Once I'm to the point of saying like...
Hey, I'm ready to play...
I'm ready to play...
Ready to play...
I almost said Metal Gear.
Halo.
Then I will.
Yeah.
Release order is always a good way.
What?
So just start at Halo 1?
My aim is good?
You think so?
Oh my gosh.
It's like the first time anyone has ever said that to me.
My aim is good?
Do you think I'm a gamer for real?
This is maybe the best day of my life.
Oh my gosh.
I have a good aim.
Yeah, I think I have my aim in mind.
I don't know...
I think I already know how to direct this game.
I know how to make it a little bit better.
Maybe.
If it is working, it will be...
Just continue.
I have used enough aim.
I have to fix it.
He's talking about his overwhelming brain.
I mean... my hands are up!
I have thought about Splinter Cell.
But truly, honestly...
From what I heard...
Like, I don't like stealth games.
I don't like stealth games.
And what kept me going with Metal Gear is the story.
And so, knowing that the story...
I've heard that the story for Splinter...
You can correct me if I'm wrong, but...
I've heard that the story for Splinter Cell is just kind of...
But also, it's like more stealthy than...
Metal Gear.
Right?
Am I wrong?
Metal Gear is a stealth game?
Down to play Devil May Cry?
Yup.
I am.
Tom Clancy.
Who is that guy?
I know it's Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell.
You know what?
You would probably never believe this...
But a long time ago...
I don't remember how I acquired this...
But I used to have a full Splinter Cell...
Standee in my room.
Never having played it...
Not knowing anything about it...
I don't remember how I acquired it...
Let me see if I can find like...
Okay, if I look up...
Splinter Cell...
If I can see like what the image was...
Maybe if I look...
I wonder if I look up Standee...
I wonder if I can even find it from that...
If I can find like a similar one...
What?
What the hell?
Oh my god...
What?
Wait...
I just...
Okay, wait...
What?
I just looked up in Google...
Splinter Cell Standee...
And this is what appeared!
This is what appeared!
Me!
Why am I here?
Oh my gosh, that's so funny!
That is so funny!
I cannot believe that that even showed up!
It was from our virtual YouTubers on Reddit!
Wow...
That's really funny...
I see a Standee that's like on eBay...
But that's not the one I had...
Because the one I had distinctly had the...
It looked...
He was like holding his gun up...
And he had the little goggles on his eyes...
You are more love than you think...
I don't...
I don't know if that's love...
Baby, don't hurt me...
Don't hurt me...
No more...
Hmm...
I may be touching chairs...
That's funny...
That's so silly...
I wonder when that was posted...
Um...
Yeah...
So that's my only exposure...
Okay, no...
No, not my only exposure...
That's one of my exposures with Splinter Cell...
And my other exposure is watching that cutscene where it references Metal Gear...
I just realized I sent the Streamlabs without my name...
So it's from me!
Also, can you sing me a happy birthday?
Of course!
Oh my gosh!
Oh!
Is it the one that's the Akadono?
Oh my gosh...
Haisumi, why?
Why would you send another Super Chat after that?
Can't wait to hear you sing for the Karaoke Relay!
Glad it's happening on my birthday!
Good luck Boss, and have fun!
Thank you!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday dear Haisumi!
Haisumi!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday!
I don't know actually.
I don't know anything about that.
Let me write that down and I will say something on stream.
Don't tell me what to do.
Accepting gifts of Kai.
If I am able to accept gifts, which I don't see why I wouldn't be able to.
I would only ask that they are of a small size because I will be going somewhere else.
I won't be going back home after I cut off Kai.
No bombs.
Yeah, obviously.
So yeah, nothing too big please.
I took the garbage out by myself this week.
So I bought myself the $1600 arcade cabinet as a little treat.
Bringing you a big crapper.
Got it.
If I can find one in Japan, I will maybe get a big crapper.
I will.
And then I will leave it on during streams.
So you can hear it in the background.
All the time.
You'll always hear it.
Smash them on stream.
Ask Gosu.
Thanks for the five gifted.
Thank you.
Set it up to react to Donos.
No one will donate again.
No one will ever want to send anything ever again.
You mean Clapper.
No...
Ah...
No pipe bombs that has off-Kai gifts?
Oh my gosh, you give me a gift and you're like check your inventory.
It's like when Ocelot leaves the bomb in my inventory.
Ghost of Mint!
Thanks for the stream.
Work has been brutal the past few weeks.
No microphones.
So this was my much-needed dopamine to start the weekend.
Full bomb in my pocket.
You hand me a package and it's like beeping and you're just like...
Here you go.
My present to you.
Well, I talked over them what I was initially gonna do.
My bad.
Otsuminto, everybody!
Do a 24-hour Cam of the Clapper when you're on vacation and be like...
You never left!
Exactly!
Thank you, Kato Ruffin.
Thank you.
I will see you guys tomorrow if you come for the karaoke.
Yeah, I think that's all I got.
But yeah, karaoke tomorrow.
So be there or be...
square.
Or something.
I don't know.
No one wants to be a square wisp.
Everyone wants to be a round, plump wisp.
Right?
Fake me, thank you!
Left 4 Dead 2 is such a rush.
Even just as a viewer, I know.
Sorry if it was frustrating.
Or loud.
Or so much.
At any point.
But I hope you guys had fun.
Thanks for watching, and thanks for...
hanging out with me, as always!
Bye-bye!
Otsu Boston!
Good night.