Three, two, one, swap.
Hello, everybody!
Hello!
Buddy!
Welcome!
Oh, welcome!
So, um...
We have a server dedicated to our...
By the way, the sun is setting, by the way.
Oh, I'm going in!
I'm going in!
Oh, God!
Wait, where are you?
Wait, where did you...
Oh, my God.
Why are you out here?
Oh, thank God!
Because there are zombies around me!
What do you mean, why am I out here?
We gotta find our hearts!
I ate some zombie meat, so now I have...
Wait, what do you mean, look at your heart?
I can't see your heart!
Yeah, you're right, you're right.
We're gonna die.
Yeah, so this might be the fastest death, because it's already night.
I mean, we could dig a hole.
In the water?
Literally, right...
Oh, wait, we've got cinematic mode here.
Okay, we gotta find a hole.
Let's just go and find...
We could find a village, I'm sure.
Just avoid the zombies and everything.
We're fine!
Hey, guys, welcome to a hardcore Minecraft preview.
So, Min and I were talking...
Min apparently didn't realize what it meant when I said, like, hardcore Minecraft.
No, no.
We stream until we beat the...
I knew what you meant.
No, no, you were like, so what do we do if we die during the end...
No, no, no, I was just like...
And I was like, we restart.
What do we do?
I was just like...
You know, I was just like, oh, my God.
Oh, my God, I found a village!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, there's a village!
Okay, okay, okay.
I knew we were gonna find a village.
I knew we were gonna find...
No, I had a gamer instinct.
I'm literally leading the way.
No, you were like...
This was literally like 50-50.
It was a life or death.
You were like, when we die, we die.
I know I did not say that.
I'm asleep.
Get your own bed.
Go...
Fuck you.
Get your own bed.
I'm shutting the door.
This is my home and I'm living here.
Okay, okay.
I'm sleeping now, too.
Oh, my God, we already found beds!
Yes!
We did so well.
This is so easy.
We already got our beds for the Minecraft.
Hardcore.
God, easy.
So...
So, we were inspired by...
Oh, shit.
I refreshed my game.
We were inspired...
Well, by the Kai and Spice Show Speed playthrough they did months ago where they...
I don't know.
Have you watched the playthrough, Mint?
No, I just...
I don't even know who those people are.
Oh, okay.
So, I was inspired by them and then I told Mint, let's do it.
Anyway, so, I was inspired.
I was watching a bit of it and it took them like 20 plus days, by the way, Mint.
It took them...
What do you mean?
Like, in real time?
Yes, in real time.
They literally...
Like, they would go to bed, wake up, play Minecraft and then die.
Go to bed, wake up, play Minecraft, die.
And then they kept doing it until they beat the...
I think we're better than them.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking.
I was like, we must be better.
Like, we have to be better than that.
There's no way it's going to take us...
That's why we gave ourselves one extra day.
We...
We gave ourselves one extra day to see if we could beat Minecraft.
I think we could beat...
Okay, like, we're...
Do they even play Minecraft?
Do they even know anything?
Like, I don't...
I don't know.
That's the thing.
I just saw that it took them 20 fucking days to be here.
Wait, I need food.
Is there not food in this village?
Like, where are the food in this village?
Did you take all the food?
I'm looting.
What have you been doing this entire time?
I'm dying.
I'm literally dying right now.
What have you been doing this entire time?
I was trying to introduce the rules.
I was introducing what's going on.
Oh my god, how am I...
I'm dying from fire.
Oh my god, wait.
Oh my god!
You just find some damn food!
You didn't even loot everything.
You're not even that great at looting.
I left you one house.
Oh, thank you.
Wow, I'm so fortunate.
Yeah, I left you a house for you, you know?
Wow.
Do you have any more food?
I only have two potatoes.
Oh, that's all they had?
Yeah, two potatoes and two bread.
Trade me.
What do you have?
I'm gonna go here.
I have 12 emeralds.
I want that now.
I have a pumpkin seed.
How am I missing a health?
How are... because I don't fucking know.
What did you do?
I don't know.
Give me the fucking bread!
I'm eating!
This is a team game!
Get your food!
Oh, okay.
The moment I go kill myself, you have to restart the server.
Look, I'm getting myself berries!
Look, just forage for yourself!
You can't eat the berries!
Yes, you can!
What do you mean you can't eat the berries?
Oh, well you can.
I told you!
I didn't realize I just needed a piece of sky.
Yes!
See?
What are you collecting men in here for?
Collecting men?
What are you doing?
What the fuck are you doing?
Why are you collecting them like that?
People can see my stream and what I was doing.
They know I was not doing any of that.
Wait, can they actually...
Wait, did they do this themselves?
I think so.
Those are some freaky men.
This is a freaky village we came across.
This is a freaky village that you found.
Also, take their torches.
Oh yeah, you're right.
You're right.
Okay, so how do we...
I forgot how to do the Ender Dragon.
It's been a while.
You're like the Minecraft expert.
I've beaten it like twice.
But...
I was there too.
Actually, I watched a guide that was just like...
You watched a guide?
It was like, so you want to survive in Minecraft hardcore.
Kind of guide, and I watched that.
Oh my god, why am I lagging a little?
It's Minecraft.
Oh, it might be my resource packs.
What?
Oh my god.
It could be.
I don't know.
It could be the resource packs.
But...
So I wanted to download...
The reason why we were waiting was because...
I was downloading resource packs.
Yeah, it's always Doki's fault every time we're late.
Okay, that is not true.
When has it not been true in like recent times?
No, no, that is not true.
The last time we had a collab, I knew I wasn't the reason why we're late.
What, like yesterday?
Yeah, yeah, that was not my fault.
I was actually on time.
Why were we late?
I don't even remember.
Because like, some people...
Because of the steam...
Oh wait, it was my fault because I chose the Tuesday.
I...
I chose Tuesday at 3pm.
I'll put the sound...
Is the sound okay now?
How do I sound?
Where are you?
You're over here, okay.
I'm pecking berries.
So what's the plan?
Okay, so...
Can we like start mining for diamonds?
No!
Doki, no!
Why not?
We have to first start...
With iron.
I'm trying to see if there...
Are you lagging that bad?
No, I'm trying...
I'm trying to fucking...
Find a tree so I can get...
Stuff.
Oh my gosh, you should've looted better.
I thought you were a gamer.
Oh, I cared about our fans?
Because I was worried that they were confused.
You have to be able to explain things and game at the same time.
Okay, what happened to multitasking?
Because I wanted to be like...
Oh my god, I didn't even put music on.
That's how angry I am.
That's why I'm angry, there was no BGM.
It was just other silence.
I had to listen to her fucking voice.
Get used to it!
Oh my god, the fucking...
I'm literally gonna see you in like...
Three days.
What do you mean three days?
Well, however many days it is.
Yeah, I was gonna say...
So people thought that like...
You know, you were on your schedule like Saturday.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
People thought that we were actually gonna meet up on Saturday.
And then on my schedule, it's like three different things.
Because she's gonna do it offline.
I know.
I was like, oopsie.
Sorry, everybody.
I made this a little whoopsie-poopsie on my schedule.
Did I grab that?
Alright.
Wait, so what are we supposed to do?
Okay, so first we gotta like get regular iron.
So basically, I think the best bet would be if we go into the mountains...
And we get the iron.
And we like...
Like the ones that aren't in the...
You know how you can find iron not...
Not in the caves?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then...
Oh, so you're...
You're scared then.
I'm not scared.
I'm literally trying to survive.
You don't wanna dig down.
You're scared.
I'm not scared.
We need the...
Then dig down.
Straight down?
Yeah, straight down.
Why don't we find a mountain?
Just dig down.
Okay, I'll dig down right now.
Yeah, do it.
Alright, hold on.
Let me make a little...
Let me make a...
Hold on.
I gotta make a shovel.
Okay, you want me to dig down?
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, dig down.
I'm going.
Hold on.
Come on, you're freaking scared.
I'm not.
I'm trying to...
Let me make a...
Wait, how do I...
Oh, there it is.
Where's my shovel?
Oh, wait.
I need sticks too.
I don't wanna make sticks.
Oh, there we go.
Alright, come on.
You too.
Don't worry, I'm helping you.
Oh.
Hey, what are you doing?
Come on, come on.
Come on.
Dig down, your turn.
We're digging down.
Wait, did you...
Oh, now you need a shovel.
While I was trying to make a shovel, you're like, oh, I'm not gonna let you make a shovel.
Now I have one.
You have a shovel.
Yeah, go.
Yeah, okay, let's go.
Yeah, okay.
While you do that, I'm gonna raise your volume a little bit more.
Okay, okay, I'll talk louder.
Alright.
Keep going.
Alright, alright.
Oh, sorry, accident.
I don't have a pickaxe either because somebody was...
Oh, I have one.
I have one.
I have two actually.
Oh, you think you'll make me a pickaxe and make me one?
No, I don't think so.
Oh, I don't think so.
Okay, so I guess I don't need a digger now.
I guess I'll just use the crafting table.
Use your hands, use your hands.
Yeah, I'll just use my hands.
Yeah, use your hands, use your hands.
Hey, get back in there.
Get back in there.
Oh, that must've been an accident too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, you're so clumsy.
I know, I know.
You're so, so clumsy.
Oh, I can't reach anymore.
I can't reach anymore.
Oh.
I think we're safe down here.
Oh, what the hell?
How'd you get there?
I don't know.
Guess you didn't dig hard enough.
I'm digging down.
You keep digging my blocks and it just shows that you're too afraid to dig down.
No, no, because somebody won't let me fucking make a pickaxe.
Okay, then here.
Come here, come here.
No, I'm making a pickaxe right now.
Oh, you are?
How are you making one?
Come here.
No, I don't remember the recipe!
There you go.
I just gave you one.
I just gave you one, okay?
There you go.
No!
No, you did!
Oh, wait, you did.
Yes, I did!
I'm trying to make a fucking...
I'm trying to make a fucking stone pickaxe.
Why are you giving me a...
Oh, because I didn't have stone because all I had was wood.
Come on, dig down, you baby!
Why aren't you digging down?
Dig down, dig down, dig down.
I'm gonna make a stone pickaxe because I wanna win Minecraft.
Somebody here is playing around.
Wait, how do you make a...
Oh, there it is, okay.
Oh, how do you make what?
A stone pickaxe?
No.
Dig down, come on, keep digging.
I am digging.
I'm literally catching up.
I'm making a stone pickaxe right now.
I'm literally catching up to you.
Okay, I'm already further, way further down than you.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
I hope you drop right into lava.
I hear a zombie.
I think we're gonna drop right into that first.
Oh, we're close, yeah.
Oh, hey.
We literally had like a perfect run set up for us and we're just ruining it.
By the way, we got iron.
I'm done here.
Oh, you got iron?
Oh, me too.
Oh, I got a whole bunch of it.
I'm already done with my job.
We need more iron.
Oh, not diamond.
How do I...
Oh, wait, there's the...
We do need this, though.
We need to eventually be able to craft.
Yeah, I'm making furnaces.
Oh, wait, we need coal.
I forgot.
Yeah, yeah, dummies.
Yeah, idiot.
She doesn't know about logs, you guys.
Oh, my God.
Now I do.
So now I don't need to get coal.
Are you out?
Did you leave?
I had what I needed.
What are you still doing there?
Why are you not digging down with me?
I thought we were gonna go find stuff.
I already got...
Oh, wait, no, that's copper.
You said you wanted to go find diamonds.
You didn't even get iron, you got copper.
Oh, my God.
I'm already, like, ten steps ahead of you.
All right.
Wait, do I need to leave first?
Okay, there it is.
Okay.
No, I just...
I'm restarting this.
I forgot that you were...
You were down there.
Why would you forget?
Because I covered up the hole.
So you tried to kill me.
And then you literally fell into your own trap.
I was trying to make stuff.
I was trying to make something.
So I covered up your hole because I had to make something.
And I forgot you existed.
Can I go in now?
No, I didn't start the server.
Oh, my God.
It's gonna take forever.
No.
Okay, okay.
I'm okay now.
I'm okay.
That was a test run, guys.
Yeah, it was just a test run.
Even though we had a perfect setup, it would have been so good.
I had, like, the starts of iron.
And I had...
We found a village that had everything we needed.
It was just too good.
It was just too easy.
I got...
You can log back in.
I just wanted to make it a little bit more exciting.
Now, where are we?
Oh, I'm in a tree?
What the hell?
We're in a tree.
Where are you?
Oh, I see you.
There's sheep here.
Where are you?
Kill him!
Alright, let's go.
If I fall, I'm afraid of falling.
I'm gonna...
Just fucking fall!
No, I'm gonna jump into the water.
Oh, my God.
I'm a gamer.
I'm gonna eat up the tree real quick.
Oh, my God, you guys.
Oh, my God.
Parkour civilization right here.
I jumped for the beef and I made it.
I'm gaming.
I didn't lose a single heart.
Oh, my God, me too.
I didn't lose a single heart either.
This is our first run, guys.
This is like the actual start of the run, everybody.
Yeah, yeah.
This is where we started.
The last one, we were testing the server out.
Exactly.
She was lagging, you guys.
Like, come on.
Yeah, I was lagging.
I was lagging.
I chose a server that's closer to Mint because I figured she needed more.
So, because of that, I'm tech...
Sadly, I have to...
It's an America server.
It's so far from Canada.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
It's so far.
They're not even connected.
Why is there a skeleton now?
Yeah, there's like an ocean that divides me from America.
That's how far she is from me.
There's a jungle over here.
Wait, where are you?
In the jungle.
The mighty jungle.
The lion sleeps tonight.
Do you know the lyrics?
Yeah, it's from Lion King.
What do you mean?
Why are you just following every time I say it?
Oh, my God.
Where are you?
Wait, Doki, can we get a parrot?
What are you gonna do with the parrot?
It's just gonna die.
No, it's not.
Not if we protect it.
Oh, there's a drown here.
Wait, is this like a monument thing?
Oh, it might be.
Be careful.
There might be guys with...
Wait, what is this?
Where are you?
There's like a thing here.
Oh, I see!
I see a pirate ship.
That's where we can get iron.
What's over here?
Oh, dig for treasure?
Okay.
Wait, you found a map?
No, the people were like, dig for treasure.
I don't think they know what they're talking about.
Oh, I see a drown.
I think he's gonna come and get me.
I might die.
You said this would be possible treasure.
I can't see anything.
Oh my god, wait, maybe I can get diamond before you.
Oh, I found a buried treasure map.
It might be where mine is.
Maybe, actually.
Am I gonna die?
I'm gonna die here.
I'm not gonna do this.
Wait, where even are you?
Where did you go?
I'm in a pirate ship, I just said.
Where is the pirate ship?
Oh, ship, sorry.
Oh, wait, there you are.
I think you were just there.
I'm in the pirate ship.
The pirate trip.
Is there anything here?
Not really.
Did you get anything?
I got some carrots.
That's good, we need food.
Oh, whoops.
I'm gonna die.
I'm dying.
You're fine, don't be a pussy.
I literally lost a heart and a half.
Oh my god, this is literally a chest filled with moss and rotten meat.
I know, it's terrible.
That is terrible.
Look at this bad pirate ship we found.
This pirate ship sucks.
I know, right?
Why did you choose this spawn, Doki?
This is the worst spawn.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You want me to...
Let me Google a seed for us.
I'm gonna die.
Best hardcore Minecraft.
Is that what you want?
I think I'm actually gonna die.
There's a little baby one, an actual...
Wait, how many hearts do you have?
None of your business.
How many hearts do you have?
There's a drow literally next to us, by the way.
Yeah, I know, I saw him.
You're fine.
I'm fine.
You even had carrots.
Punch me, see if I live.
Oh, shit.
I'm gonna die.
Wow,
man.
How could you just die like that?
Wow.
I thought you were a gamer.
I'm a ghost.
I can go down below now.
Now you can check.
Wait, there's bees here.
Wouldn't it be funny if there was a village right next to us?
Oh, my God.
Wait, I'm gonna see.
Wait, is there a natural village anywhere near us?
Not...
Not that I see.
Okay, so this was a bad spot anyway.
Yeah, it was a waste.
You guys, we need a better seed than us.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's why we died.
We were like, you know what?
This seed was pretty bad.
New seed.
New seed, new seed.
We just keep dying until we get some fucking village and those ender portals next to us.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Someone in my chat was just like, VOD gang, you can skip this stream.
On to the next stream, part two.
We're just going to part two at that point.
All right, restarting the server.
All right.
Restarting.
You know, I'm going to put text here.
Wait, how many deaths?
Is that what you're putting?
Yeah.
You're putting how many deaths for each of us, right?
Like, Doki one death, Mint one death.
Yeah.
But my death was caused by you, so...
I guess it was Doki two deaths, honestly.
Oh, my death was caused by you, so technically it's one death.
I literally dug a hole.
I dug a...
You murdered me in cold blood.
Technically, if you think about it, because my death was caused by you.
What are you talking about?
That is the ultimate cope I've ever heard of in my entire life.
Oh, yeah?
Says the person that was like, hit me, see if I die.
Who said that?
I didn't think you'd actually do it.
What do you mean?
You said hit you, so I was like, all right, okay.
Yeah, but like, you were really aggressive.
If Mint says jump, I jump.
If Mint says...
If she tells me to jump off the cliff, I'll jump off the cliff.
If she tells me to hit her, I'll hit her until she dies.
Are we good?
Is it?
Yeah, we're good.
Oh, another similar one.
All right, I need some logs.
Now I understand why it took them 20 days.
Now I...
Wait, I see...
I see a plains, a savanna.
That's a good place to find a village.
A village?
Oh, we can have a desert village.
Okay, I'm grabbing some wood again.
I'm not, I'm going.
How many times will I have to grab wood for us?
For us?
For yourself?
This is a team game.
I am playing Minecraft 2.
Okay.
Where are you?
Oh my god, there's a baby horse.
Wait, where did that sheep go?
Did I not see it?
Where is the savanna?
Over here.
Where's over here?
Use your eyes.
I am literally using my eyes.
I'm climbing up a fucking mountain right now.
Why are you climbing?
That's the opposite direction.
Oh, you could have said that.
You could have actually said that.
I have eyes, so I was able to see it.
That's why...
Well, clearly we weren't spotted in the same... Oh, I see the savanna.
Okay, you know how I saw the savanna?
I climbed the mountain.
Yeah, but I didn't have to climb a mountain because I have better eyes than you.
Well, clearly you spawned in a better location where you could see the savanna because I spawned in a tree where it was covered up by all the other trees.
I spawned in a tree too.
We have equal rights.
I don't think so.
I live in Canada.
In Minecraft, everyone is equal... except the server mod.
Let me get some food for us.
Yeah, I'm killing sheep.
Me too.
I'm killing sheep and pigs.
And pigs.
I just killed a pig.
I'm about to kill a pig.
Oh, there, I killed a pig.
I see you.
That's gonna yoink your crafting table.
No, you won't.
Okay, usually there's villages in this area.
Yeah, I'm killing the sheep now.
I mean, what good does this mean?
We can't cook it.
We're literally... I mean, we can literally burn trees for that.
That's the whole point.
Mr. Beast is now controversial, so we have to burn all the trees that he planted.
Take back what once he planted.
Take it all back.
Oh, I see another portal, actually.
Oh, shit, you see another portal?
Yeah, I'm really good at seeing things.
I'm pretty sure you just have, like, better... Oh, there's chickens.
I literally even told you my FOV.
There's so many chickens.
She asked for my FOV, guys, and I was like, yes.
You guys wanna know what her FOV was?
You guys wanna know?
What?
It was at 75, and that's default.
Is it default?
Yeah, that's default.
Oh, well, that's good.
What is yours at?
No, it's not.
I'm at 85.
I was, like, wondering... I was wondering if I should do it higher or not.
Look, my chat was like, damn, lol.
Wait, does mine look bad?
Guys, what does your chat say about your FOV?
Oh, is mine bad?
90 minimum?
I think I used to have it at that.
I think you just forgot to change it.
I think I forgot to change it when I... Yeah, when you re-bought Minecraft.
Yeah.
Oh, I found an armadillo.
Wait, is this copper?
Yeah, that's copper.
Sorry, guys.
Why didn't you say anything?
That's my chat's fault for not saying that it looked gross.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's your chat's fault.
You're gonna blame your chat?
Yeah.
Of course I would.
That's fucked.
I would never drag goons.
I would never blame you guys.
Uh-oh, there might not be a village here.
Okay, I'm making... Oh, wait, this is not it.
I'm gonna make some sticks.
I'm making progress.
You're making sticks and I'm making progress.
Come on, Doki, we are not the same.
Oh, yeah, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
I'm searching.
I found a village.
I literally just found a village.
Oh, please.
Enlighten me.
I'm stuck in a cave.
Oh, really?
I thought you found a village.
I did.
Okay, I'm good now.
Alright.
I'm not excited.
Look at that.
I made an advancement.
Have you made an advancement?
Okay, caveman.
You're literally the one in the cave.
I have a bed now.
What do you have?
What are beds for?
Sleeping.
You can't respond.
It's the day.
We can sleep through the night.
I accidentally... I lost my stuff because I forgot.
If you mine copper and iron with a wooden pickaxe, you don't get anything.
Are you bragging?
I don't know what you're doing.
No, I'm blaming you for my shortcomings.
Okay, this village actually kind of sucks.
Okay, now I can craft.
Now I got copper.
Why are all the doors open?
This is weird.
Maybe they can open their own doors.
No, they don't do that.
Yes, they do.
They have their own free will.
Are you trying to say the villagers don't have rights?
Yeah.
I need better food.
Oh wait, I have an apple.
I like how you don't even tell me where the village is.
You just left.
Oh yeah, the hay bales.
Yeah, for food.
Yeah, because I told you I made progress.
Yeah, but this is literally a team game.
We have to make progress to get there.
I can't tell anymore.
What do you mean?
We're trying to work together to get to the fucking... What's that?
Oh, I saw the armadillo you found earlier.
Yeah, they're cute.
They're a worthless piece of shit.
What do you mean?
Why are you being mean to them?
What can you do with an armadillo?
You can make dog armor.
Yeah, the dog is still gonna die.
No he's not if he has the armor.
Oh wow, there's also a jungle over there.
I passed your armadillo, but I still don't see you.
Just keep going.
It's pretty far actually.
Oh, I see the village.
I see it.
Oh, my food galore.
There's so many pigs.
There's so many of them.
Alright,
nice.
Well, this village is not great, just because it doesn't have like a...
Fine, I'm just trying to get meat right now.
It doesn't have any stuff like the wood... the stonesmith people.
I'm just gonna grab some wood.
Wait, why do I need stairs for?
I'm just gonna grab wood.
I'm gonna destroy this home.
Where are you?
I'm destroying this one man's house.
He'll never be safe again.
I'm grabbing... I'm stealing their food supply.
This village is literally gonna die out.
Nice.
They deserve it.
Why would you build a village here?
Yeah, this is a terrible location.
Do I flint?
No, I don't.
That was my previous life.
Oh, you do?
I have flint and steel.
You know what to do.
For some reason, I feel like we've done this before.
Death to the village!
Raid the village!
Raid it!
Oh, shit!
I thought it was me inside!
Oh my god, you fucked me up.
I'm gonna die.
I'm actually gonna die, you fucking whore.
Oh my god, I almost died too.
Here, I'll give you some.
Here, here's some bread.
I can't even get up.
I can't even...
Use the pickaxe you made!
I can't even... I can't even get out.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Dig this part.
I just need you to dig...
There you go.
Okay, nice.
You know, you could just...
I don't have any tools.
Oh my god.
Alright, let me fuck you up.
Let me grab some trees and build a furnace real quick.
You can just sleep, it's fine.
What do you mean I can just sleep?
Sleeping doesn't do anything regarding health.
It doesn't... Oh, I thought I gave you food.
Hold on, come here.
Do you have bread?
You can make your own bread, okay?
Oh, wow.
Wow, how fortunate of me.
I gave you half of what I have.
How fortunate that I was given the privilege...
Alright, time to go to sleep.
...to make my own bread.
Time to go to sleep.
Sleep, donkey, so we don't die.
Alright, okay, I'm sleeping.
Yeah.
I'm sleeping now.
Alright, nice.
Nice.
Alright, let me make my bread.
Good morning, Minto.
My... Okay, there you go.
I got 64 bread, let's go.
Wow, see?
It's still burning.
How do you make the bread?
Wait, there's more hay here.
You didn't finish farming all of this.
Oh, whoops.
Oh, it's my bread now.
Yeah, it's your bread now.
Alright, nice.
Okay, we can't die.
This is actually a good run.
We can't die now.
Is it a good run?
This counts as a good run?
Yeah, we have all the bread in the world.
We can't die now.
Food was like the one thing I was most afraid of, so...
So now that we have all the food in the world...
We should be good now.
Okay.
Alright, I'm ready.
I'm ready to find a cave.
I have so much food.
Dig down.
Alright, fine.
I'll dig down.
Yeah.
Where are you?
We're gonna dig down together.
We are?
Yeah.
You said you were going to go explore, and I am the bread winner.
When did I say explore?
Why did I say those exact words?
I am the one who does everything above ground, and you do everything below ground.
You know it'd be faster if we both did stuff together, right?
You know that would be faster, right?
We could protect each other from dying.
Alright, here, let's sit down.
Wait, where are you?
I'm right behind you.
Oh, hello.
I need stone.
Let me get some stone.
Let me... not murder, sorry.
Alright, while you do that, I'm gonna get some cough drops real quick.
I'll be right back.
Are you good?
She's coughing, guys.
Coughing baby.
She's like a freaking coughing baby.
Don't steal this.
What the fuck?
I can't believe she stole that from me.
Wait, I'm literally... she's literally AFK and she's still stealing from me.
This is messed up.
How is that possible?
I'm back.
What were you doing?
Why were you saying it was messed up?
I'm stealing the stone from the people.
It's messed up.
First time?
No.
It's still messed up though.
I'm a criminal.
You literally burned somebody's house down.
And this is your lie.
This is your lie?
You burned someone's house down and this is your lie?
Yeah.
You cared about like somebody's stone.
I'm having a change of heart.
I'm literally having like a... what's it called?
Are you changing?
What's that movie where that guy goes through the Christmas ghosts?
Oh my gosh.
A Christmas story?
A Christmas story.
Yeah, it's happening to me.
Yeah, but these are Scrooge and like the villagers are Little Timmy.
Yeah, the ghosts of Christmas past, present, future are all coming to me.
They're saying you're stealing the stone and Little Timmy's not gonna make it for Christmas.
Oh, it's a Christmas carol.
You were wrong.
You didn't even correct me.
You're like, yeah, it's that.
Well, Christmas people need to be more original then because...
Oh, but Christmas, so like...
Yeah, it's basically the same.
Yeah, it's literally the same thing.
Can I make anything out of the mossy bricks?
A Christmas story is the one with the leg lamp.
What the fuck is... what?
The what?
Someone was like, that's the leg lamp.
I'm like, what the fuck does that mean?
A lick lamp?
Leg, they said leg.
Ligma?
What is that?
Someone was like, why don't you have a mini map mod?
I was like, I'm not making this game easy.
Oh, what are you talking about?
We're gaming.
Yeah, we're gaming.
Alright, I'm ready.
Are you ready now?
Yeah, probably.
Alright, let's go.
I'm gonna actually cut the... get more wood just in case something happens to us.
I wanna go see the jungle.
That's not part of the plan, Mint.
The jungle has nothing to do with the Ender Dragon.
But what if there's pandas?
The jungle has nothing to do with the Ender... Dig, it's time to dig.
You know your place.
Okay, we're digging for real though, right?
Yeah, yeah, for real this time.
But we have to... I think we have to find a way to... we have to dig in like a ladder.
Or like a staircase.
We have to come back out.
We can just... we need to explore.
We're not gonna go back to the same area.
We get our stuff and then fucking dig up.
Oh, typical Mint.
Letting me do all the work.
Hold on, I don't have a shovel.
If I drop, will I die?
We don't need a shovel.
No, we don't.
Just jump down.
Alright, let's go.
You dig mine and I'll dig yours.
Alright.
We're so efficient.
This is teamwork.
This is real teamwork, guys.
Digging our own hole is a lot faster than what we're doing.
Oh, hold on.
Mine just broke.
Do you have another one?
Here, put your crafting table here.
Okay, thank you.
Wow, it feels like...
Oh, hey, coal.
Nice.
Oh, nice, nice.
We got coal.
Okay, we got coal now.
Oh my god, this is a lot of coal.
Nice, you have a... Oh, hey, what about digging my hole?
I'm sorry.
Coal is just much more important.
I'm still digging coal out right now.
Okay, I'm digging coal.
I'm digging coal.
We're digging coal.
We're making progress.
Alright, hole time.
Oh, wait, we're sick.
Oh, never mind.
Why is yours a little faster than mine?
I don't know.
Maybe I'm just more efficient than you.
It's because I'm like...
Oh, it's because I'm clicking it.
I'm clicking it instead of holding.
Yeah, I'm still...
Oh, there we go.
Oh, come on.
Come on.
Dig me.
That's... That's the... What's it called?
That's copy.
Alright.
Hey, don't hop.
Oh yeah, what's going on?
Oh, we're synced up again.
Where's our cave?
Where the fuck is our cave?
There has to be at least one cave.
I hear a zombie.
Oh, we could get the diamond.
I think we might be close to that.
Oh, I hear a zombie to our left.
Yeah, maybe we should dig left.
Our left?
Wait, that's our right?
Are your earbuds on?
No, I think your earbuds is wrong.
This is left.
Kill him!
Where is he?
Oh my god, I can't even tell.
Oh my god, I might die.
I might die.
You gotta kill him.
I actually might die.
You have to kill him.
You have to!
I blame you.
What do you mean you blame me?
You did not get him!
I was literally fighting him.
You were in front of me.
If I hit him, I would have killed you.
No, I didn't.
You were literally on top of me.
I would have attacked you and you would have died faster.
You literally had a chance to fucking hit...
I saw you hesitate.
I did it!
I was attacking!
You looked at him before you attacked him.
I was attacking him.
That was your fault.
I'm blaming that on you.
That's a mid-death number three.
Wait, are you saying mid-death number three?
Why am I at three?
You know why.
Doki two.
Doki is coping.
Baby cough.
Baby cough is getting to her brain.
You go first.
When we are at a cave, you go first.
What are you talking about?
You go first.
You were the one who dug for the zombie.
We didn't even have any iron for a shield.
It's all on you.
How is that on me?
I went first.
And I was like, alright, there's the cave.
I could hear it because I was like, oh, turn left.
There's a cave on the left side.
And I dug the cave hole for us.
And then, I went to explore first.
I went to brave the wild for you.
All I hear is...
Okay, anyway.
You log in now.
Oh, okay.
This is good.
This is a good biome.
Alright, time to hit the trees again.
Hit the trees.
We got this.
Okay.
What if we get a shield before we dig down?
How does that sound?
That sounds like a better idea.
Why didn't you come up with the idea earlier?
I, you know...
My genius hits me in funny ways.
Did chat tell you that?
No, I knew that because I watched the video on how to prepare for...
How to prepare for Minecraft ArcCorp.
Oh, so you cheated.
No, I did research.
How is research cheating?
So you researched...
Oh, no, it is cheating.
You're trying to find the most optimal route instead of letting it happen.
No, because I still have to do it all on my own.
It's still my own skill work.
Yeah, miss...
Let's go to the jungle.
Yeah, the jungle probably wouldn't have killed us like you did.
Hey, did the video tell you to go to the jungle?
Did it tell you to go to the jungle with the most optimal route?
The jungle probably has really great secrets.
I'm just saying.
Like what?
I don't know.
I don't know their secrets.
We could've gotten to see them.
You watch the video.
The video is not gonna tell us everything.
The video does not hold your hand.
Then what the point was the video for?
It's a video guide.
Oh, there you are.
I see you.
This is the first time I saw a cow.
I'm seeing sheep.
Eat up this cow.
With my hands.
I'm so tired of chopping trees.
It's Minecraft.
It's literally Minecraft.
Just get used to it.
This is literally what you do in Minecraft.
I'm so over these fucking trees.
This was your idea.
It's been 4 minutes.
Was Min's volume okay so far?
Okay, I just didn't think that...
Min would cause me to die so many times.
Guys, can you believe this?
Do you hear this?
This coping is absolutely ridiculous.
I think...
The fall really did her in.
She's just...
Oh, I just killed the sheep's...
I just killed the sheep's mom right in front of him.
Oh my god.
Alright.
The little baby sheep just ran up to his dead mom.
It's so sad.
Oh my god, it's like a Disney movie right there.
I know, I just caused...
I just made The Lion King.
You're welcome, everybody.
Oh, The Lion King?
Yeah, because that's a better movie.
Are you trying to say Bambi is not a good movie?
I'm just saying...
Can we agree that The Lion King is a better movie than Bambi?
I guess if you're a furry...
Yeah, Min?
Um...
That's your opinion.
That's a certified Doki Bird opinion.
I wonder if there's any villages.
I'm searching.
I'm getting...
Alright, there has to be another village, right?
Usually this biome is good about having a village.
Yeah.
Oh my gosh, you know about all that too?
I played a lot of Minecraft.
Wow, she's a gamer.
Yeah, she played a lot.
Oh my gosh.
Alright.
I'm killing more pigs.
I'm pushing more trees.
I'm punching so many trees.
Just punch them.
Alright, I'm gonna look for a village too.
I'm running out of...
We need to get food soon too.
I know.
Well, I have some raw meat.
Yeah, I do too.
But I think I'd rather just find a village and like...
Steal their food and pillage them?
Yeah, just steal their food and pillage them.
It's just, why do our own work when we can rob others of their work?
They already did the hard work.
Yeah, exactly.
That's what pillaging is for.
Yeah, for people like us.
Look at the vikings.
There's some coal here.
I think I can grab it.
I mean, the vikings knew what's up.
Let's just ignore all the other bad stuff they've done.
But other than that, they thrived.
They had the right idea, I think.
They had the right idea.
Yeah, exactly.
Oh, I'm advancing.
Hmm, what are you doing?
Are you sure there's...
I'm fucking trying to find a village?
So am I, and I found other things along the way.
And you dug a fucking rock.
Congratulations.
I got coal for us so we could cook our meal.
I mean, we have trees.
So?
Oh, shoot, there's more.
Trees do the same thing.
With less resources.
No, it's actually more resources.
With less effort getting the resources.
We're at the end of the...
There's a really big cave here.
Oh, shoot.
Oh my god.
It's okay, you'll be fine.
I am trying to find a village.
I don't think I'm gonna be fine.
Oh shit.
Okay, Mint, just die now so we can restart.
All I wanted was the coal.
Oh gosh.
Oh my god.
I will know she lives or not while I try to find a village here.
I think I'm good.
Okay, good.
I'm far far.
What is far far?
I kept going forward.
You went into the cave, I went forward.
Wait, did you see me go into the cave?
No.
Then how do you know where I am?
Because I saw you and then you disappeared.
So I assumed...
I assumed something happened to you.
I'm almost out of food.
Or out of... Wait.
Okay, I'm gonna have to eat the raw beef.
Eat it.
Just cook the raw beef.
You have the coal.
We don't...
Where is the... Oh, you're right.
You have... What do you mean?
You literally advanced the stone age.
What do you mean?
Oh my god.
I think I'm the luckiest gamer ever.
Wait, why are we at Terracotta?
Where?
It's Terracotta.
Wait, no.
What is this yellow sand?
Red sand?
Yeah, it's Terracotta sand.
Yeah.
Why is there fucking Terracotta?
I don't know.
That's where we spawned.
Or Mesa.
Or the Mesa biome.
Not ideal.
Because I'm here for the fucking village.
Bad spawn.
Bad seed.
Hate this seed.
If only somebody didn't fucking protect me from the baby zombie.
Did you say didn't protect you?
If only someone did not protect me.
Oh yeah, sorry.
I mean somebody did protect me from the baby...
I'm very delusional.
It's been like an hour already.
I'm already done.
We haven't made...
We've made zero progress.
We haven't even...
We can't get past to the...
To the...
To the cave section yet.
Bro, the seed fucking...
Where is the village?
I don't know.
It's okay.
I found...
I found like a corrupted nether portal.
At least we got that.
That's good.
We're gonna die.
The sun's gonna go down.
We're gonna die for real.
You mean we're gonna die.
Oh, okay.
Actually, I am gonna build my furnace.
And I'm gonna have real food.
I don't...
It's not even... The sun is still up.
Nevermind, I don't have enough stone.
Okay, I found a...
There's stone all around you!
Where are you?
How do you know there's stone all around me?
I thought you said you dropped into a cave.
No, I've got out of there.
I've been searching for a village.
Oh my god, at least I got golden carrots.
How the hell?
Oh, from the...
The corrupted portal, yeah.
Oh my god.
Got my food.
I'm gonna create my house in here.
Maybe.
Okay, furnace time.
Furnace time.
Is that your new house?
Is this where you're gonna live now?
Yeah.
Why do you act like you know where I am?
It's freaking me out.
I mean, I can see you.
Where?
Yeah, I can see you right now.
What am I doing?
You're freaking trying to make a furnace.
No, I made the furnace.
You can't see me.
You're full of shit.
No, I saw you make that furnace.
No, you didn't.
Yes, I did.
Okay, what am I doing right now?
Right now?
Yeah.
You're just walking around.
No, I'm not.
You're so full of shit.
You got paranoid for a second.
You got paranoid.
Yeah, but you are just a liar.
You can't gaslight me for too long.
I call you out.
What are you doing then?
I'm making food.
And I'm preparing for the night.
Oh, it's going down.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's going really way down.
It's going way down.
Oh, this is a little bad.
What do you mean one of us?
What are you doing?
I'm digging.
I'm making a little home.
What are you doing?
I'm doing the same thing.
Uh-huh.
I doubt it for some reason.
It's because I'm in the water.
Now I'm doing the same thing.
I'm just going to spend the night in the hole.
Is that what...
I don't want to.
I think I can make a bed because I got some...
Wait, let's see.
Bed.
I can make a bed.
How many do you need for a bed?
I forgot.
Three wool.
Okay, let's see if I can do this in time before they come in.
I'm asleep.
I'm ready for bed.
Okay, I'm asleep too.
Okay, nice.
Before the zombies get here, do it before the zombies come up.
I'm asleep.
Okay, thank God.
Everything is fine, guys.
Everything is fine.
We know what we're doing.
Yeah, duh.
One of us knows what we're doing.
Guess which one it is.
I made a bed first.
But your initial plan was to dig a fucking hole.
Like that.
I made a hole in the mountain.
In the side of the mountain.
What are you talking about?
What are we gonna do there?
What does it benefit?
I'm finding coal eventually.
I already have coal.
How many?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
It literally has a number.
I'm in front of coal right now.
You can't just count what's in your inventory?
Oh my God.
I'm literally in front of coal right now.
I gotta be in the stone age so I can farm this.
Oh, shoot.
We should probably meet up.
Coal.
Whoa.
Look at all this coal in front of me.
Wow.
Guys.
How do I get out of this?
Alright, first one to find the village...
has to tell the coordinates to the other person.
Okay.
I'm gonna be lazy then.
I'm not gonna do anything.
Oh yeah?
You're gonna have to travel to me.
Yeah, okay.
You'd rather travel?
What if I...
I might find it first.
Oh, shit.
If I find the village first...
you have to fucking find me...
and I can just sit on my ass just waiting for you at the village.
No, you would have to gather everything at the village.
No, I don't have to.
Yeah, you do.
This is a team effort.
Why did you find the village?
What do you mean?
Is it only my job to find villages, huh?
Yes, it's a team...
Oh, what happened?
It's a team game.
We gotta find the village together.
Oh, and now you wanna find it together, huh?
Oh, yeah.
No, I said the first person to find a village...
gets to mix with the other person and travel all the way there.
Okay.
Oh my gosh, I found so much coal.
Me too, I found a lot of coal.
I've just been mining coal.
It would be a shame if one of us dies after all this hard coal I just mined.
We're gonna live, right everybody?
Oh, shit.
Oh my god, I almost died.
What was that sound?
Oh my god.
We're all gonna live, right?
We're all gonna live.
I think if we die...
Someone... We have to have like a chat sacrifice.
We ban one person?
We ban a person, yeah.
For every death.
You can't unban them though.
Oh, shoot.
Eww.
Oh, I found some iron.
Oh my god, please.
My breath meter.
Where am I anymore?
I don't even know where I am anymore.
I don't even know where I am.
Oh, I found iron, but it's in the water.
I'm in the water too.
Hey, come on.
Come on, you gotta put in the effort.
I'm gonna mine something that's not in the water.
Did I get it?
Oh my god, I'm walking backwards now.
I'm back to the Mesa.
The Mesa biome.
Where is the Mesa biome anyway?
Oh my god, I'm gonna die.
Well, guess you'll never know.
Okay, I made it out with one single iron.
Oh, I found a village.
What, really?
I don't believe you.
No, I literally found a village.
I literally see it right... Wait, is that a village?
Or is that a temple?
Oh, it's a temple.
It's a temple, yeah.
Oh, wait.
No, well, I mean...
You can get stuff in there.
Oh wait, there's like traps there.
Yeah, well, there's...
Okay.
I wanna... I have to show you how to do it...
Or else you'll die for real.
Yeah, I think I'm gonna die.
Oh, you are gonna die?
Okay.
I think I'm gonna die from TNT.
Well, I guess...
Good luck trying to find this temple.
I don't even know where you are.
I'm trying to get a sheep.
Exactly.
I think I'm far away from you.
I think you went a different direction than me.
I think so too.
You never saw the Mesa biome.
No.
I'm still in the... What's it called biome?
The what biome?
The sand?
The desert?
I never... Wait, there's a desert biome?
Oh my God, I went too far.
She found a temple, guys.
She found a temple.
Wait, you never... Okay, I definitely went too far.
Where did you go?
I don't know.
I went to a place where there's a desert biome and I never left.
How do I get around this?
Okay.
Over here.
This seed sucks.
Our other seeds were so much better.
We had actual villages like within seconds.
We had an actual good seed and then Mint fucked it up.
What?
Me?
And then she fucked it up for the rest of...
Yeah, you!
Oh, I found a jungle.
Did you ever find a jungle?
No.
I found like an above ground mine shaft.
Oh yeah, you're definitely in the Mesa.
Don't go in there.
Don't go in there, Doki.
Doki, I swear.
Doki, don't go in there.
I found a real village.
I found...
Now I'm actually for real.
I found a village.
It's in front of the...
It's in front of the above ground mine shaft.
Wait, what's the key that you see my spine coordinates?
What?
The show coordinates.
What is it?
Alright, I'll give you my coordinates.
Wait.
Okay, there you go.
But I wanna go in the jungle.
Oh, I got obsidian.
Oh, nice.
Alright, you gotta come over to me.
You gotta leave that jungle.
A deal's a deal.
You gotta leave.
No, I just made it in here.
Don't you want chocolate?
No, I don't want chocolate.
I wanna fucking kill the ender dragon.
What if that includes...
What if that's part of the plan?
Oh yeah, the two-for-one deal.
You get chocolate and an ender dragon.
Yeah, exactly.
Oh, if...
I would be surprised if we would make it to the ender dragon on this seed.
I think we can do it.
Alright, get over here.
Get out of the fucking jungle.
Hold on, and I'm looking around.
Uh-oh, it goes to a dark woods.
Okay, I'm getting out of here.
If you die, like, after I try...
I've worked so hard getting here, I swear to God.
Wait, where are you at?
You didn't even send me your coordinates, you idiot.
My coordinates is...
Type it in the chat.
X-471.3 I'm not gonna pay attention to this.
Alright, someone in the chat is gonna type this out.
X-471.336 X-471.336 X -471.336 X -471.336 X-471.336 X-471.336 X -471.336
X -471.336 X-471.336 Aren't you supposed to help as a teammate?
We have to make shields.
So we gotta get iron.
Okay.
Find iron in the village.
Loot them for all they're worth.
Wait, what was the coordinates, guys?
What was the coordinates?
Oh, wait.
That's not what I meant to do.
Negative 471.
471?!
Seriously?
Oh my God.
4411.
Your chat isn't even typing the right coordinates.
Negative 411.
Oh my God, I took a fucking screenshot.
411.
Oh wait, it was 71 because I moved.
Oh my God.
Oh, and you're calling them dumb!
Negative 410.744.
278.330.
I forgot I can move.
Oh, X is negative?
Oh my God.
Okay, then.
That's only the first coordinate!
How did you get confused with the X?
First thing I read!
You have a bed, right?
You have your bed still?
Yeah, I have several beds.
I'm getting watermelon.
Type in chat, it's easier.
No, she has to work for it.
Oh, there's a cat here.
She doesn't want to work as a team, you guys.
If I die, it's all Doki's fault.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
I fucking found the village for us.
I found the villages before and you blamed me.
So I guess whoever finds the village first is the person who gets the death blamed on them.
Thank you for not fucking protecting me.
No, no, no.
I hope you die in this round.
Why?
I'm gonna fucking jump off the cliff right now and we're gonna restart this.
No!
We have to do it!
We have to win with this seed!
You're gonna get to the village and I'm gonna get that cork gun and...
You'll make it a spectacle.
All the villagers will be watching you like...
No, Doki!
Don't do it!
No!
Wait, you guys, what was the coordinates again?
What were the coordinates again?
I got us a ton of hit.
I'm eating.
I'm having dinner at Twilight.
471304.
Oh.
That's not what I wanted to do.
I have so much worthless shit in my inventory.
Let's sleep.
Can we sleep?
Sleep.
Sleep, please, before the zombies come.
Sleep before the zombies come.
You're not asleep!
You're not asleep?
Oh my god!
Which way was I going?
Maya, I'm working so hard for this group.
I have so much resources right now in my inventory.
Oh yeah, what?
What do you have?
I have meat, I have lots of stone, I have lots of food, I have lots of coal.
Yeah, do you have iron?
I have one iron.
Lots of resources.
Well, how many iron do you have?
I don't need iron.
Wait, what are you talking about?
I literally was just...
You wanted to know the secrets and I said, what are the first secrets?
I have a golden pickaxe.
That's a golden pickaxe.
It sucks.
Golden pickaxes suck.
I have a golden... It's literally the same as iron.
No, it's not.
Golden things are terrible.
It's the same as iron.
It has the same stats as iron.
I have a... No, it doesn't.
It breaks sooner.
Not mine because it has mending on it.
Okay, you're gonna get experience?
Okay, I wanna see that happen.
I bet it's gonna last longer than your fucking iron pickaxe.
It actually will.
I wanna see you dig down with that thing and be like, oh no, it has mending though.
It has mending though!
And then freak out.
It does.
Yeah, the mending doesn't do shit unless you have... Yes, it does.
It doesn't do shit unless you have ways to get an experience bar.
Exactly.
I'll wait till it's night time.
In the cave, huh?
When you dig down?
Yeah, in the cave.
Exactly.
Oh my god, where the fuck are you?
Where are you at?
I'm in the mesa biome.
I'm almost there.
Oh my god.
I'm gonna make sure you get here and then I'm gonna jump off this roof.
Wait, I think I went too far.
You were at 400?
Yeah, negative 410.
But it was like 300.
I think I went too far.
Oh my god, chill out.
If we had just stuck together as a team, like we were supposed to...
You walked away first!
You gotta say that when you literally walked away first.
You literally...
You started off by walking away from me.
No, I'm just... I get things done.
I'm ready to go.
I'm ready to do things.
Oh yeah, you get things done?
Where was the village that you found?
I have found two villages so far and you found literally one, okay?
Get off your high horse.
You didn't find that village.
Yes, I did!
I found all villages so far except this one.
Yeah, the hardest one.
You got the easy... Yeah, because you wandered off first so of course you'd find the easy villages first.
That's like, you know, when you kill a level 1 player, you basically did like a level 1 strat.
And I was doing a level 30 area.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Who told you that this biome would have a village?
Yeah, me.
Oh, every biome has a village.
Except for snow.
That's actually... No, actually, no.
Snow does.
Nevermind.
Every biome has a village.
Yeah, but this one usually has a village.
Yeah, what's the percentage?
What's the percentage?
I don't know.
I just have a magic mind.
Oh, so you're just... You're basing it off of... Not even science, off of magic.
You're basing it off of science.
You're not even basing it off of science.
It's off of belief.
Yeah, my belief is what I know.
You believe in the Minecraft gods.
I believe in magic in a young girl's heart.
She believes in the heart of the cards, guys.
The heart of the cards.
I literally own Exodia, okay?
Oh my god, where the fuck are you?
I'm coming!
I went a little off track.
I'm just waiting here.
I don't even need to do anything.
Did you get everything from the village?
Yeah, I got everything.
Did you get all the torches?
You got all the torches?
Yes, I got all the torches, yes.
What else did you get?
I got all the hay.
What else was there?
What was in the boxes?
In the chests?
It was nothing.
It was books.
It was books and... What's in my inventory?
Oh my god, it's not even this biome.
Oh my god, it's a sand biome.
Alright.
Oh, did you go to that nether thing?
Yeah, I did.
I did.
Okay.
Is she telling the truth, Chad?
I did.
I want a different bed.
I want a green one.
There's greens here.
I know, I'm grabbing them.
Oh, you're here?
Yeah.
Oh my god.
I see you.
Alright, are you ready?
Ready for what?
I left some hay for you.
Oh my god, this guy is fucking a sheep.
What?
Oh, okay, they're done.
Oh, I'm glad I missed it.
I'm glad I wasn't here to witness that.
We're in New Zealand.
What?
Sorry,
New Zealand.
Hey, you didn't get all the torches.
There's literally torches in here.
There's torches all around.
What are you talking about?
I left them for you.
No, oh my god.
I asked, did you get all the torches?
And you said, yep, I got all the torches.
You're a liar.
No, no.
You're lazy.
You were here for so long.
No, I was not lazy.
I left them because I was being a considerate teammate.
And I was like, you know what?
I'm gonna leave these torches for a minute.
I bet she'll need them too.
You didn't get any of them, did you?
No, I did.
I literally have 50 torches in my inventory.
50 torches?
Yeah.
Chat, is this real?
I have 51.
52, 53.
You know what?
Fuck it, you don't deserve any of these torches.
I'm taking them back.
I'm taking all of them back now.
Okay, good.
You can put all of them in the caves then.
We gotta get iron before we go into the caves.
No, we don't.
We just go into the caves to get iron.
Don't we need to get the iron so that... No, we don't.
I believe in us.
I don't.
We died two times.
One time was in the cave.
One time.
The other time, I slipped.
You slipped?
Also, finally, it's her fault.
She finally took the blame.
I slipped because you didn't warn me about the giant.
I think we gotta get some iron.
Alright, where are you?
Where did you go?
Kill the iron golem?
He'll kill us first.
We're too... Wait, wait, no.
Not if we like stand up and kill him.
We need... Is that on these pillars?
Oh, we need a... We need like... What's it called?
What?
We need armor.
No, we don't.
Yes, we do!
We'll find armor in the fucking caves.
Why are you so scared?
Why do you mean we need... We'll find it in the caves.
Do you think armor just grows in caves?
No, we'll find the iron to make the armor in the caves.
Why are you so scared?
Because we died three times.
Yeah, but that's not... That's not my fault.
You guys... I think we... I feel like we need like a poll.
Like a who's in the right here kind of poll.
I feel...
We can't die.
This is... This is the... If we...
This is the run.
This is actually the run.
If we die in this run, everyone will make fun of us.
Everyone will make fun of us.
We... I don't want them to make fun of us.
It will take us 20 days.
Where are you?
Where did you go?
I'm gathering...
I'm gathering torches.
Okay, are you ready?
Um, no.
Okay, we can head straight and see if we bump into a mountain.
Okay, okay, okay.
Does that satisfy you?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Alright, do you need bread?
Um, eventually.
No, just take the bread now.
Here, I'm gonna throw it at you.
I'm gonna make it ring.
Oh, bread!
Make it ring!
Turn around!
Turn around right now!
Make it ring!
Oh, oh, oh, I gotta go back.
Wait, wait, wait, no, that's...
Wait, did you not mean to throw that?
I just hit through like the entire...
It's fine.
I have another stack.
Yeah, don't worry about everybody.
We're good.
Okay.
Alright.
We're adventurers.
This is the run.
I think we can work together.
If we find frogs before we find iron...
If we found frogs...
Wait, oh, is that the...
Oh, that's the temple you were talking about, right?
No, that's a different temple.
Oh.
Oh, yeah, teach me how to do this.
Yeah, yeah, I can teach you, I can teach you.
Okay, it's really delicate though, okay?
Okay.
Do you want me to be in there?
Do you want me to go inside?
You can watch from a distance if you want.
Oh, I can watch from above.
There might be someone in here, so get your stuff out.
Alright, I'll watch from here.
From up here?
I'm in cinematic mode right now.
Alright, hold on, I need my torches.
Okay, I'm gonna torch this up a little bit.
Alright.
I'm watching.
Okay, I like to start from the one over here, can you see?
Yeah, yeah, I can see.
You can?
Okay.
Alright.
Alright, so I like to come in slowly.
Okay, so this is where...
You have to start making your...
Your...
Staircase.
Okay.
And what happens?
And then I get to the bottom and I win.
And I get all the treasure.
But you have to disable the button before you do anything.
Oh my God, that was close.
Did you get the button?
No, I'm making my way to the bottom.
Wait, can you dig some of the parts above us so I can have a better view?
No, I can't do that.
I can't see anything.
You'll see.
Hold on, can you see?
Wait, I'm almost there.
I'm almost there.
No, I can't, there's literally...
Okay!
Oh yeah, you can't see.
Hold on, I'll come back up.
Wait, can you dig like...
Okay, just dig around here so I can have like a view.
You can come in now actually.
Oh wait, did you got it?
Yeah.
Oh, armor trim.
Gold.
Okay, so a zombie might fall here, so I'm gonna...
What do you mean a zombie might fall?
Because there's...
Because it's night time.
Okay, I'm asleep, I'm asleep.
A zombie might have fallen into our heads.
Oh, enchanted.
Oh, a saddle.
Oh, we need gunpowder.
I'm just gonna grab gunpowder for the sake of it.
We need string?
Um, I don't know.
We'll grab some bones.
Actually, we do.
Well, we need to make a bow and arrows probably.
We don't need copper, right?
No.
Okay, I'm getting that out.
I'll take the string.
Alright, I think I have too much stuff.
What is the fire charge for?
Will we need that?
No.
Alright.
Okay, I'm gonna dig my way out of here.
There's stairs.
There's little stairs.
That I've created.
There's actual stairs.
Oh, you did it?
Yes, I did.
Oh, you did it.
We have to keep creating them.
Hey, why'd you hit me?
Exactly.
I'm trying to create the stairs for us!
Just place blocks!
Oh my god.
Like that.
There you go.
I did it.
Yeah, you did it.
Good job.
Thank you.
Taking my torches back.
There's a creeper in front of us, by the way.
No.
And he's like...
Oh, he disappeared.
Oh no, he's over there.
He walked away.
Alright, get over here.
Come on, we gotta find your iron.
Where's the creeper?
Oh, no, that's a cactus.
That's a cactus, idiot!
Look in front of you.
In front of me?
Yeah, you wanna call me an idiot again?
You wanna go up to this cactus?
Go up to the cactus!
Kill him!
Why are you not doing anything, Doki?
He's aggravated!
Wow, good job.
You did nothing.
You did absolutely nothing.
You're a coward, you little chicken.
A coward would've ran away.
I was there.
Yeah, taking two steps back every two seconds.
Yeah.
I was a journalist.
I'm here to record.
I covered wars, you know.
What war?
What was your favorite war?
The war...
The great creeper war of 2024.
Oh, is that another village?
That's my favorite.
No, I think that's a temple.
A mini temple, right?
There's no such thing as a mini temple.
Wait, but you can dig under that.
Oh, that thing.
That is just a water fountain.
I think this is another temple.
Let's see.
You know what would be easier?
We just dig down.
Oh, wait.
What's wrong with this one?
I think that's the door.
I need to spawn in.
Dig down.
Do it.
You're the one who suggested it.
You're the ones like, you know what's easier?
Digging down.
Why don't you go in?
What do you mean?
Do you want to do that?
There's nothing important there.
Yes, there is.
I'm gonna watch you do it now.
From up here, I'll watch you do it now.
Oh, okay.
Alright.
Let's restart the seed.
That's fine.
You have no confidence in yourself.
Come on, Doki.
Doki, you have no confidence in yourself.
You think I saw what you were doing?
What are you talking about?
I was doing the same exact thing you did.
I couldn't see what you were doing.
All I could see was this.
Oh, you said you could see.
I could see until you went down.
Come on, scaredy cat.
Scaredy crow.
Come on.
You know what?
This run was going on for too long anyway.
No, you got this.
Just dig stairs.
Dig stairs and make sure nothing touches the button.
That's all you gotta do.
Are you scared?
No, I'm not scared.
I just think that I know I'm gonna fuck it up.
There might be iron in there.
Come on.
What are you doing?
I'm digging stairs.
What do you think I'm doing?
I couldn't tell.
Oh, yeah.
That was what my perspective was too.
You disappeared.
Oh, there you are.
Now you know how I felt when I...
I'm too far from the hole.
Should it be like here?
Yeah, you gotta like...
Kind of be on the inside of it.
Kind of remember how my stairs were?
No.
Guys, this is what I have to deal with.
My gold pickaxe died.
Okay, come back up, Doki.
It's okay.
Come on, Doki.
Let's just keep going.
How long did it last, Doki?
It last like...
10 rocks.
Yeah, I know.
Come on, let's just go.
It had bending on it.
Wait, the actual village.
Oh, now we found a village.
Yay.
Oh, there's a cave next to it too.
Yeah, I was gonna say, it's right next to a cave.
We could water bucket down there.
Oh my god, we could if we can find some iron.
Yeah.
That's all we need, right?
That's what we need, yep.
These villages suck, man.
I know, these sand villages are so poor.
I know.
No wonder they live in the desert.
I got nothing here.
It's like they're focused more on like survival and water than like actually having anything.
It's like they hate items, but they just, you know, only think about...
Like, you know, the bare necessities to win.
Yeah, exactly.
It's ridiculous.
Oh, I got a lot of bread though.
Yeah, there's a lot of bread in this village.
That's all they do, they just want food.
Yeah, what is up with that?
What's wrong with them and food?
I don't understand.
I don't get it, I don't get it.
It's like they're losing...
Oh wait, there's sheep too.
Okay, there are two sheeps.
There's two sheeps.
We could've gotten the saddle for the camel.
Oh, I didn't think that we would see another camel.
Wait, I have a saddle, I have a saddle.
Oh, you got it, nice, put it on the camel.
Where's the camel?
He's around, there he is.
Put it on him.
Can we both ride it?
Oh my god, we can!
We can, wait!
We have to befriend the camel?
No, we can just ride it.
Are you on?
Oh yeah, look at us!
We're so cute!
Wait, how do we change POV again?
F5.
Oh my god, look at us!
Actually, we don't need...
We don't need a water bucket.
We can just use a boat and drop into the cave.
Oh, that's true.
But what about camel?
He would die.
Wait, jump down the cave with camel, will we die with him?
Okay, this is a science experiment, everybody.
Like, does he act like a boat?
Does he act like a boat?
This is a really important question, everybody.
You guys, this is a really important question.
This is a really important...
Don't land on the lava.
Do not...
Do not land on the lava.
Is this...
You guys, all I see is 07s.
I'm not seeing anybody telling me an answer.
Yeah, we need to know.
Is the camel like a boat?
Is it...
What if we like...
We jump down with the camel and we do like MLG gaming and we get off the camel before it hits.
Do we get the same fault?
Does physics work?
Camel is not a boat.
I repeat, camel is not a boat.
Okay.
They didn't say anything.
No!
They all wanted to watch the science experiment.
Wow.
They were all curious about the science experiment we're doing.
This camel is so fucking slow.
Why did we waste our saddle on this camel?
Because we wouldn't ever get a...
Let's be honest, we would never get a...
Oh wait, I can jump.
Yeah.
They're pretty nifty.
Oh my god, I can jump.
What's the point of having camels in Minecraft?
They're cute, I think.
Like, do they do anything?
No, I don't think so.
Oh, they can swim.
They cannot swim.
No, they cannot.
The camel was gonna drown.
I'm going over to this nether portal.
I'll be back.
I'm taking the camel with me.
To the nether portal?
Yeah.
Camel keeps running away.
He doesn't wanna go.
I'm heading over.
Here I am.
I thought we were trying to find a mountain.
Yeah, we need to find one.
We just need to find iron.
Might as well go this way.
Follow me.
Follow me and the camel.
Wait, hold on.
I'm making bread.
I have so much bread.
Why do you need more bread?
Because I just wanna make bread.
I'm running out of space.
Wait, don't push me.
Don't push me.
I have all the power.
Okay.
Look at this.
I'm looking.
What is that?
I got golden armor now.
I thought you said gold sucks.
It does, but it's all I got.
Let's go onward.
You know you can run.
Just run with the camel.
Okay, you do it.
Come on.
Here we go.
That's running?
Actually, he's pretty fast for a camel.
Yeah, we're running.
Wait, he can't swim.
What do we do?
You can just walk.
And then we just climb back on.
What do you mean climb back on?
Wait, what are you talking about?
Oh my god.
Just keep climbing back on.
Keep going.
We're almost there.
Okay, wait.
We need to sleep.
Time to sleep.
Good night, everybody.
Wait, why is the camel walking back?
He'll be fine.
Oh, he's in the water.
That's right.
You can never leave camel.
You can't leave.
You're part of our gang now.
We stole their camel.
We're still in the desert.
We might find some though.
Let's go check.
In the desert?
Maybe.
I don't know.
I'm not a desert expert.
We're never gonna leave this god forsaken land.
Wait.
What?
There might be.
But there isn't.
It's just sand.
I saw some other stuff in there.
No, you didn't.
I saw.
I really did.
I see it right there.
No, you didn't.
You're just seeing things.
I don't see it.
You gotta take your meds again.
You haven't taken your meds.
I haven't taken my meds.
Wait, we can look at the side of this mountain.
It's not even a mountain.
It's just sand.
I saw a copper.
We gotta get out of sand land.
Well, if you would slow down.
Let me catch up.
You're literally faster than this camel.
Wait, I wonder.
You should run.
Run as the camel and see if I can catch up.
Wait, how do I run?
Do I just press space bar?
No, it's...
You're running.
You're normal running.
What's wrong?
Why can't you run?
Yeah, shift.
No, shift is crouch.
Oh, no, I have my keybinds different.
Oh.
Oh my God, he's sitting down for me.
Are you good?
He's just surfing.
You know, he's like surfing on the land.
Wait, what?
I'm on top of him.
Yeah, no, no, he's like...
He's like sitting down while surfing on the land right now.
What?
Oh my God, it's like we're surfing.
What are you talking about?
I think you're lagging.
No, we're literally...
We're literally surfing.
We're sad surfing.
What are you talking about?
Okay, speaking of someone taking meds...
No, I think I accidentally ate something wrong.
I might have ate some of the wild mushrooms up here.
Uh -oh.
Oh, you ate the beef, but it wasn't cooked.
You have like probably a cow brain disease or something.
Oh, there's coal up there.
Thank God.
We don't need coal.
Yes, we do.
We don't need it.
I'll get it.
Why?
Don't leave me.
We need the coal.
It's a lot of coal.
Oh, it was the rotten meat.
Oh no.
Get back here.
When's the last time you hydrated?
Oh, that's a good question.
Look at her go in the water.
Look at her go.
I'm gonna drink the water in this ocean.
I'm gonna drink all the salt.
You can go crazy with that, you know.
I know.
You wanna try it?
Yeah, sure.
That'd be a fun stream.
We should do that off of collab.
We keep drinking salt water until somebody goes crazy.
Viewer's discretion is advised.
Don't try this at home.
Wait, how do I make this?
Wait, I think we're getting out of the sand land.
Oh, I can only make one?
Why is there more sand in front of me?
Oh, dang it.
How is there more sand?
There's more sand!
Oh my god.
By the way, Min, I went forward.
Yeah, I know.
I saw where you went.
Okay, yeah, I'm just gonna keep going forward until the sand stops.
You could wait like two seconds for me to catch up.
I'm pretty sure the camel is slower than actually walking.
It might be.
Where are you?
Did you go in the water?
Across the ocean.
Wait, how did you do that?
With the camel.
I told you the strat.
We keep walking until...
I'm here, okay.
What do you mean you're here?
Across another area.
Of water?
Wait, I don't think you know where I am.
Am I going the right way, guys?
I am at...
195 and counting.
Negative 195.
Yeah, I'm going up.
I'm a little...
Oh, did you hit a jungle?
Wait, what?
There's a jungle?
You went the wrong way.
No, I'm going towards 195.
I'm at negative 195.
Or almost.
You're at the wrong way.
There is no jungle here.
Why am I always finding jungles?
I'm at negative 20...
20...
04, 350.
But you know what happens when someone is lost?
You literally stop moving, okay?
Why don't you ever stop moving?
You're the one that's lost, not me.
Are you still on the camel?
Yeah.
Okay, I'll find you.
I've never stopped being on the camel.
What's your Z position?
350.
321.
Okay.
Stop moving!
I have to go in like a diagonal.
Oh my god!
Okay, I'm gonna make a peepee tower.
I'm gonna do it.
Okay, make a peepee tower.
Do it.
No, that's a waste of my resources.
You can destroy the peepee tower once you make something.
Okay, I made the peepee tower.
What if I fall from the peepee tower?
Hold on, I'll find you first.
I made a peepee tower.
Where are you?
What's your coordinate?
Over.
I didn't move.
Tell me your coordinate.
Your chat can retell you the coordinates.
Chat, what's the coordinate?
What's the coordinates, chat?
Oh, they said...
My chat says, no, we cannot.
They're not helping me.
Minus...
2003...
And 327.
327?
Oh shoot, okay.
Alright, I'm on my way.
Which side are you on?
Left or right?
I'm coming probably...
Probably from your left.
Okay, I'm looking left.
I'm looking for the peepee tower.
I'm looking left.
I swear, thank god these birds aren't real so they don't swoop in and fucking stab me.
What birds are you talking about?
I have birds in my resource packs.
Oh, what?
What are you playing?
Hold on, I gotta eat.
What do you see around you?
Is it all sand?
I see birds.
Shut up, I don't care.
I don't see the birds.
It's all sand.
You don't see any trees?
No, I see cactuses.
Where the fuck did you go?
Wait, you're at 20... You're at 2000 what?
Dude, negative 2003.
Oh, 2003!
Oh, shoot.
I thought you meant 2300.
Okay.
I see trees here on my right.
Wait, are you still in the forest?
Uh, no.
Wait, what was the other one?
300 and what?
I'm gonna go to the forest.
I went the wrong way.
I got rid of the pee pee tower.
No!
I'm going to the forest.
I'll meet you there.
Wait, oh, the jungle?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
In the jungle...
The mighty jungle...
The lion sleeps tonight...
Oh...
We're not okay anymore.
It hasn't even been two hours.
We made zero progress.
We still don't have iron!
Yeah, we don't have any iron.
I'm at 460, negative 2077 now.
460?
Yeah, negative 20...
Oh, I see you!
Wait, where are you?
I'm swimming.
Hold on.
Oh, I see you.
I'm gonna go to this other side anyway.
Okay.
Go back.
Keep going.
This camel is so fucking slow!
Okay, I'm going.
Get over here, camel.
Alright, let's go.
We're leaving this camel.
We're leaving him.
I'm taking my saddle back.
You can take your saddle back.
He's not in his biome.
He's gonna die.
I took him to the forest and now he's not in the sand anymore.
He's gonna die!
Oh my god, he's gonna be too cold.
He's like...
He's gonna be like, the winter nights are so frigid.
He deserved it.
He should've been faster.
He was pretty fast.
No, he wasn't.
We're literally traveling faster than him.
You just don't know how to run.
I know how to run with him.
I know how to coax him.
Go back, grab the camel.
We're too far gone.
You're just gonna leave him like Mario to his Yoshi?
You're the one who rode him all the way here.
If anything, he thought that you were his mother and you're abandoning him now.
Yeah, because he had daddy issues.
You're the mother!
Who causes the daddy issues?
You literally said I was the mother.
Where are you?
Another thing we can do is...
We can find a pirate.
A sunken ship.
We should sleep.
Oh yeah, maybe let's sleep first.
Where's my...
I'm gonna get rid of this bed.
We just need one bed.
It doesn't matter anyway.
Because we can't respawn.
Yeah, exactly.
Alright, I'm ready.
Let's be on the lookout for sunken ships.
And we can find iron and stuff in there too.
Why don't we just find a mountain?
I feel like a mountain would be easier.
Okay, well we can use the boat to get to the mountain.
I'm looking in the water too for iron.
I'm observing the area.
I feel like a ship, we can see it easily.
Let's just go forward, straight forward.
Forward ho!
We'll find...
We'll find a mountain, right?
Okay, ship or mountain first.
Which do you think will come?
I think a mountain.
I'm ready.
This is peaceful.
You know what?
Maybe we should work together more often.
Somebody here keeps, you know...
Doing it's own thing.
I think honestly...
It's been our chats...
That are pitting us against each other.
That's so true.
Especially like...
Dragoons.
Wow!
Especially...
I don't want to name names.
Dragoons.
I know a couple of wisps.
That were doing some things too.
What does that imply?
Were you wisping like...
I'm not gonna tell you where the coordinates are.
My dragoons will tell me the coordinates if I ask them.
Actually, I think wisps hate me.
Sunken ship!
Wait here.
Is that a sunken ship?
Yeah, but it's not very big, so you don't need to come in.
You just want to keep all the iron to yourself.
There is no iron.
You just want to keep all the iron.
You literally said sunken ships have iron.
Not always, sometimes.
Oh god, I'm gonna die.
Get in here.
Hold on, I'm putting on my new shoes.
Alright, you have to keep on lookout of the sunken ships.
I'm not looking.
I'm on the lookout.
Just go.
There's a drown area here.
Wait, do those areas have...
Yeah, do they have like stuff?
That's like a hidden temple thing.
Oh, there's a drown there though.
I don't think we have enough...
We wouldn't be able to stay under the water for long enough.
It's not worth it.
Oh, okay.
You have to like dig for the chests.
Oh, I see.
It's like treasure hunting and stuff.
I want to give them just dig down.
We could do that.
I feel like...
Oh hey, there's turtles.
Look at the baby turtle!
He's so small!
Oh my god, he's shambling.
Oh my god, seagull's gonna come in and fucking eat him.
Oh no.
Yeah, that's true.
But we can't touch him, it's mother nature.
We can't touch him.
Yeah, we can't touch him.
It's like those like...
Nature documentaries who like...
Let things happen.
Yeah, even if it's a bad thing.
Yeah, cause they're like...
Oh, we can't interfere.
That's us.
We're not bad people, it's literally in the rules.
We're not bad people.
It's called circle of life.
Yeah.
Oh, there's a lot of drowned around here, so just go.
I'm going, I'm going.
Even though we've lost like 70% of like...
Why are you like staying against the...
Cause I'm trying to find a mountain!
We're also trying to find treasure ships, right?
I mean, I guess.
Look, I just had a dragoon come into my chat and said I'm a dragoon and I'm sabotaging Mint.
What do you have to say about that?
I bet he's not even a dragoon.
Who was it?
Call him out.
What's his name?
I remember every dragoon.
You know every single one?
Yeah, I know every single one.
Their name is...
You're just making up a name now.
QuantumTwinSpark.
No, that is definitely a dragoon name.
No, no, no.
QuantumTwoSpark.
Sounds like it.
If they're really a dragoon, they're gonna cry.
Hey, come back.
Oh yeah, QuantumTwinSpark literally came to my chat and said...
And super chatted.
Did he super chat you too?
Yes.
I'm a wisp and I'm sabotaging Doki.
He's playing both teams!
He's playing, he's not even...
He's a...
He's a wisp-goon.
Wispy-goon.
Maybe it's not dragoons or wisps.
It's the wisp-goons.
I wanna watch us both fail.
They want this stream to go on forever.
For two weeks.
They want it to go on for a month.
They want us to break their record.
Of the longest Minecraft.
The longest hardcore Minecraft.
Okay, we have to...
We can't die.
We've been on the seed for way too long.
For how little we've done.
How little progress we've made.
It's time to dig into a mountain.
It's time.
I'm getting off this boat.
What the hell?
Why is my...
Oh, that was weird.
My golden...
Damn, two hours in and still no iron?
That's a record.
Because somebody refused to dig down.
I'm just thinking of our safety.
Someone here doesn't wanna dig down.
I was...
Stop advocating to dig down.
There's a mountain in front of me.
Every time we've dig down, we've died.
I'm just trying to play it safe.
That's two times.
Where'd you go?
I am at...
Minus 33761598.
What the hell did you just say?
Your chat must've heard.
Let's just go to the mountain.
I'm literally at the mountain.
Already?
Yeah, there's a mountain in front of me.
I'm getting there.
I'm walking.
Did you have to...
Oh, I see you.
I hope we're looking at the same mountain right now.
How did that happen?
That's weird.
How is there just coal on the ground?
Oh, because...
I didn't have room in my inventory.
That's the stuff I dug.
I was like, that's weird.
That is weird.
Where are you?
Which way around the mountain did you go?
You're on top of the mountain?
I see you.
Stop.
Freeze.
No,
I know the words, but I don't want to bait people.
Oh, so true.
I know exactly who you're talking about.
You gotta try harder to get that out of me.
Hey, I'm digging a hole.
I'm digging a hole.
Come on.
You're gonna dig a hole?
Yeah, we're digging into the mountain.
Come on.
I thought we're supposed to fucking farm around the mountain.
This isn't the right kind of mountain, but it's okay.
We can dig inside.
Oh my god.
Come on in.
The stone is fine.
Hey, look over here.
Okay, I'm here.
I'm putting a little torch there.
Okay.
Alright.
It's time.
I'm digging this side.
I'm gonna dig the other side.
What side?
This side.
Are we digging down or just digging around?
What is iron usually at, guys?
I don't know.
I'll put torches too.
Oops.
My thing broke.
It's fine.
We're surrounded by stone.
Lower?
We gotta go lower?
Oh, okay.
We gotta go way lower.
Come to my hole.
And we'll start digging the hole.
My head right now.
Can you give me a sec?
I'm trying to remember how to make sticks right now.
Two planks.
I'm struggling at the moment.
Planks on top of each other.
This has been too much Minecraft.
Two planks.
This was your idea.
I'm just reminding you.
This was both our ideas.
You were like, that's a great idea.
That's a great idea, Doki.
Let's do it.
You...
said that you were inspired.
You were the one inspired.
Yeah, and then you were like, wow, that's a great idea.
We should totally do it.
Wait, do we keep going down?
Yeah, keep going down.
What's the coordinates?
We gotta get to five.
Where are we at?
Like 70.
Hold on, I gotta make a new pickaxe.
I'm digging down.
I can't.
You're digging a stair though, right?
Don't fall down.
How do you get back up?
I'm at 50.
We'll find out later.
Okay.
I'm still getting more coal.
I hear...
Is that a creeper sound?
Do you have a...
Creepers don't make a sound.
Creepers don't make a sound though.
Doki, you can't die here.
What's that?
What does that mean?
Oh, it's an Enderman!
We found an Enderman!
Oh, we need those!
We need those!
Oh my god, there's so much coal here.
Do you have a lot of wood?
Uh...
Yeah, I do.
Let's throw this away, we don't need this.
What are you throwing away?
Sandstone.
Oh yeah, we don't need that.
Oh my god, there's...
What'd you find?
Oh, thank god I didn't dig down.
I found a very, very deep cave.
I picked the right...
Oh my god, if I dug down one more time...
Okay, I'm digging the stairs for us.
I'm digging the stairs for us.
My duty is the stairs.
I'm stair duty.
If I dug one more...
This is good enough.
Oh my gosh, I almost just fell into your hole.
Wait, am I...
There's no way, guys.
I'm not...
There's no way.
What biome am I in right now?
No, it's the dripstone cave.
Someone was like, oh my god, you're in the deep dark.
That's the dripstone.
Oh, no, yeah.
You know when you're in the deep dark.
Because it's like...
It's got the glowy stuff.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
I can't believe it.
I literally stopped...
Just at the right time.
You guys, no sabotaging.
My chat is trying to have me sabotage you.
What?
Why did you go silent?
No, I'm just curious on how you're gonna do this.
I'm building stairs.
Yeah?
It's fine.
You messed this up.
Why did you do that?
How did I mess it up?
Oh my god.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
There's literally one more block.
If I did one more block, I would have died.
Oh, it looks so easy.
Oh, no.
What will happen if you just...
Let's keep going and we'll find iron eventually.
Should I cover this up?
Oh, nevermind.
Don't go this way.
Let's go this way.
Why does it keep getting more and more dangerous?
Because we're living on the edge.
I don't like the edge anymore.
I feel like if we dig down...
This is what happens when you dig down.
This is what you wanted.
You wanted to dig in the mountain.
Ignore the copper.
There's so many endermen near us.
Why is there so much copper?
Where are the fucking iron?
Where is the iron?
What are we at?
Oh, we need to go further down.
Yeah, but down is death.
This isn't the right mountain.
We need to go to the mountain.
You know, the snowy peak mountain.
Wait, I can make another stair here.
Oh, okay.
Go, go, go.
Okay, wait.
I need to throw some stuff away.
What do I not have?
Too much copper.
Too much copper?
The thing I told you to do.
Cobble, cobble, cobble.
Okay.
We can't sabotage each other.
No, we can't.
You guys, this is the real thing.
We're not restarting.
This is where we're gonna make it.
Oh my God.
I hear that enderman right next to us.
He's like right here.
He was like literally right here.
Yeah.
Okay.
What corner are we on now?
Don't worry about it.
Just keep going down.
I feel like we're gonna be going down forever.
I told you it's not the right type of mountain, but it's okay.
Why didn't we just find a hole?
Wouldn't a hole be easier?
Maybe, I don't know.
Why didn't we just find a hole?
Why did you make me dig a mountain?
I got an eerie noise.
Yeah, I think that was the enderman.
No, it was Dai.
Okay, we're almost close to where Iron...
Okay, now I think we can...
Just like tunnel.
Okay.
Alright, your turn.
Okay, time to go forward.
Why didn't monsters spawn behind us?
Because we just left it, you know.
Yeah, that's a potential risk.
Okay, you know what?
We like it risky.
Oh, I hear a skelly man right next to me.
Oh, that means we're like...
Okay.
How does that mean we're okay?
That means we're like closer to the ground now.
You know, we won't fall to our deaths.
Okay, I'll go right side.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I hear dripping.
So we're still...
Oh, Iron!
You found Iron?
I found one.
Iron!
Oh, I mean, you know...
One is something, I guess.
Yeah.
I'm tired of these stone pickaxes.
We'll get there soon.
When will we...
When will we hit it big?
When will our streamer luck kick in, man?
When will our streamer luck kick in?
Oh, wait, I already made a furnace.
Okay, well, I have an extra one.
Oh.
For when we wanna cook the Iron.
Actually, I could probably cook the Iron.
What's that?
Nothing.
We'll go this way now.
Why is that boarded up, huh?
Why don't you check it out?
No, Mint, come over here.
Mint, come over here.
You wanna know why it's boarded up?
Alright, come over here.
Dig it.
Oh, there's nothing here.
No, come on, dig another one.
Oh, I see.
Did you...
That's your torch, though.
Your torch.
You see it?
It was your torch.
You're just gonna abandon it?
Oh my god.
Creeper!
Now you know why I abandoned it.
Yeah, but I got your torch back.
You're welcome.
Oh, thank you.
My fifty-third torch is saved.
It's important.
Every torch matters.
This is hardcore.
Every material is precious.
Oh.
I'm in another area.
What do you mean another area?
Oh.
Where are you going?
What does that mean?
Iron!
Just one?
No, I found four.
Yeah.
Four whole irons.
Okay, we're doing it.
And where's your four iron?
I have currently in my inventory...
Oh, I thought I had five.
Five, six...
Seven...
Eight...
Nine...
Ten...
Eleven...
Oh my god, I don't know how to count past ten.
Thanks, Elmo.
Did you see the SesameD Twitter account?
That super...
Like...
Emo?
Like, Elmo, CookieMonster, and like...
Like, all the Sesame Street accounts were like...
Like, it's okay guys, if you're having a bad day...
Like, they were being like those self-help Twitter accounts.
Oh.
I found an area.
Oh, I found Lapis.
Yeah, me too.
Wait, hold on.
Wait.
I'll make sure I don't die.
Okay.
Is Lapis important to us?
Um...
Actually, yeah.
I think we should get it for when we need to enchant stuff.
Okay.
Oh, you're right.
We should get that.
Yeah, they were doing like self-help tweets instead.
And...
And like super encouraging stuff too.
I like Elmo's Twitter though.
He's kinda wholesome.
Yeah, but it was like all the Sesame Street...
All of them?
Yeah, all of them.
It was like Cooking Monster too.
Sesame Street, okay.
Sesame Street is going through it.
Wow!
Did you almost fall?
No.
There's a little zombie heading over.
He's not happy.
Okay, let's see.
Why is there so much copper in here?
Oh, he's blocked by the sword.
He's blocked by my little torch.
Oh, I found a big area.
Oh, no.
I want that.
Nice, okay.
I'm gonna grab lapis.
Oh, look.
I killed my first monster.
I'm gonna get the lapis too.
Can you get it with the stone?
Okay, nice.
I didn't know if you could get lapis with the stone or not.
Yeah, I can.
What do I not need?
No, I can't.
Yes, you can.
I got it.
Oh, wait.
I have too much in my inventory.
We don't need raw rabbit.
Actually, that's food though.
That's true.
I need to clean my inventory.
Should I make a shield?
Can you eat glow berries or no?
Yeah, you can eat them.
Okay, I'll just eat the glow berries.
Where are you?
We don't need copper, right?
No, we don't need copper.
Okay, so I can throw those away.
Alright, I'm gonna start smelting my stuff.
Me too.
I need to start smelting these as well.
I have a lot of iron.
Alright, let's make a shield.
And we'll make a good sword.
Yeah!
And I can make armor.
Wait a second.
I need maybe more...
Okay, there's my chest.
There's my crafting table, furnace.
Get rid of this bamboo.
So sad.
Iron age happening right now.
Oh my god, we're doing it.
We did it!
We're doing it!
I don't need this gravel.
Throw it in the garbage.
Oh my god.
We're actually...
We're actually doing it.
We're gonna make it out of here!
Maybe.
They didn't believe us.
I know.
They thought we were gonna die here.
This is literally the run.
This is the run.
I knew that was gonna happen.
We're safe.
We're still safe.
Okay.
I'm gonna make my shield first.
Where did I put my crafting table?
Did I leave it over there?
I don't know.
Okay, I can fight him.
Shield!
Yeah!
I have my shield too.
We're gonna make it.
Okay, I'm gonna make a sword.
And...
This skeleton needs to be able to aim.
I did it!
Wait, what did you get?
I killed a skelly!
Oh, you got the thingy.
I got the shield, yeah.
Okay, nice.
Okay.
Now I'm gonna make armor.
Oh, I should make armor first.
I want the iron pickaxe.
Actually, I should get iron pickaxe first.
You're right.
No, no.
Get armor first.
No.
No, it's too late.
Okay.
Iron pickaxe.
There we go.
I don't have pants, but I got some stuff.
Wait, what?
Why is it not working?
Do I have too much stuff in my inventory?
I do.
I'm just gonna use my wood ones for now.
Oh my God, I have too much stuff in my inventory.
What do I not want?
What do I not need?
I don't know, but they're all important to me!
Where are you?
Oh, wait.
Why do I have another bed?
Where are you?
I don't know.
You went down here.
Oh, I see your name.
You're very far away.
I don't know where I go to.
I go to too many places.
I don't know.
Oh, I see you.
I'm here.
Oh, no.
Oh, we have the copper.
Okay.
Oh, hey.
I'm gonna throw away the copper.
Oh, look.
There's more lapis here.
Yeah, I'm trying to make armor right now.
Okay.
Okay, I don't need my golden hoe.
I have my hoe here.
Will this kill me?
Yeah.
Okay.
We need all this for when we eventually...
And I'm gonna throw away my stone sword.
Oh, I'm out of space.
And I'll throw this here too.
I don't need the emerald.
And...
Yeah, you don't need that emerald.
There's more to our left.
More over here?
No, I feel like I'm wasting wheat.
Wasting space.
For the wheat?
Yeah, they were saying, oh, you can make wheat off of the hay and stuff, but I waste too much space there already.
Well, if you have the...
If you have it turned into bread, then it's, you know...
Yeah, but...
Then I'll get too much bread.
It's good to have bread.
No, it's too much bread.
There's a limit to how much bread you can have.
There's a limit.
Okay, I need shoes and...
Alright, let's get iron.
Let's get iron.
And shoes and...
And...
I already have a lot of armor.
Let's see, where's my bread?
Wait, where did I put my bread?
Oh, there it is.
Wait, did you go down?
Yeah.
Alright, I'm here.
Wait, what was the purpose?
The dripstone makes it so annoying.
That's true.
What's the purpose of going down here?
I don't know.
To find iron?
Do we need more iron?
Yeah.
We do?
We have to have a plethora of shields and...
And things.
No, you don't.
It'll break.
It will?
Yes.
Oh, I should make a bucket.
Oh yeah, you can.
Oh yeah, I'm gonna make a bucket.
Did you leave all your stuff up there?
Yeah.
I'm gonna come back to it, right?
Are we?
Okay, you're right.
I'll bring it back to me.
It's annoying otherwise.
I'm gonna wait until it cooks.
We also gotta get to the diamond, so I guess we can start diamond hunting from here.
Oh yeah, we might as well start now.
Yeah.
Okay, I'm gonna...
Wait, where are we at?
25.
So if we find iron...
I'm gonna strip mine for iron a little bit more.
And then if we get...
What's the coordinates for diamond?
It's like...
It's like negative...
Alright, let's go.
Let's dig down.
I need more iron.
I gotta mine.
We can get iron while we're digging down.
It stops showing up though.
No, it doesn't.
It shows up with the diamond.
It doesn't?
When did it change that?
It used to.
It didn't?
No, stuff stops showing up, right?
No, it doesn't.
No.
Alright, let's start digging down.
Alright.
Where are you at?
Also, I don't know why you're listening to me.
I know less about Minecraft than you.
I don't know, I'm just...
I'm just gullible maybe.
Wait, where did...
Where did you go from?
I'm trying to find where you are.
I started to strip mine.
Wait, where are you?
Did you keep going forward?
Where did you go?
Where are you?
Did you go down?
Oh wait, I see you.
I see you.
I'm heading back to you.
Oh, I see you.
Why did you go all the way over there?
Why would I go there?
Where did your name go?
Oh, nevermind.
I'm here.
We can go down and then we can just start digging down.
Alright.
Oh, there's more.
Hold on.
They said it was less of a chance, but that doesn't mean we won't get it.
We might as well.
Okay.
Hold on, I'm grabbing coal.
Alright, I'm digging down.
Oh my gosh.
I forgot to look at my computer yesterday and it's starting to rattle again.
Wait.
Wait, what?
My fan is like all messed up.
Oh look, see?
I told you.
I am right here.
Where?
Where are you?
I just dug down.
Are you like actually digging down?
Yeah.
I dug down.
I dug down next to you.
I didn't know.
I dug down right next to you.
Okay, I'm digging down again.
Okay, I'm digging down.
I'm digging down.
What's the coordinates for diamond?
Like negative 50.
Okay.
You're at...
We're at 14.
Yeah, we gotta go.
Oh, we gotta dig.
Alright, how bad would it be if I...
If I just dug straight down?
Like, is it worth the risk?
Is it worth it?
A seasoned Minecraft person would probably say don't do it.
But...
Are we seasoned?
No.
Get over here.
Are you willing to risk this run?
You know what that means.
Alright.
You dig mine, I dig yours.
Wait, that's an Enderman next to us.
I think that is like an actual death pit.
Wait, let's...
Okay, let me double check.
Wait, I think there's lava next to us.
I don't hear lava.
I think I heard lava.
I think I heard...
No, I hear the Enderman.
No, no.
It's...
This is my music?
Is it my music?
I can't tell.
There's no lava.
Okay, it might be my music.
Okay, are you ready then?
Okay.
To risk this entire run?
I dig yours, you dig mine?
Okay.
Alright, ready?
Wait, I need a head start, because I don't have iron.
Wait a second.
My pickaxe is gonna die.
No, I'm gonna be the one who dies first.
It'll be your fault though, if I die.
You're the one who's digging mine.
You're the one who's digging my block.
You said...
You said alright, you wanna just do it?
Wait, hold on.
Yeah, I need to make...
Can I have some iron?
Do you not have any iron blocks?
I have one left.
Go make your own iron.
I have none, I only have one iron ingot.
Go burn your iron ingot!
It's already burned!
How much do you need?
How much is a pickaxe?
It's like two.
Okay, then give me one more.
Alright, that's an I.O.U.
right there.
Yeah, give me two more.
Oh my God.
That's an I.O.U.
right there.
Sure, yeah.
Alright.
Okay, one second.
It's almost done.
We are at...
Minus ten.
We still have 40 more.
Okay, I'm making my pickaxe.
I'm gonna eat real fast.
Yum, yum, yum, yum.
Oh yeah, me too.
What if a creeper just falls on our head because we didn't put any torches above us?
I don't think they...I think they're smarter.
I don't think they fall like that, right?
I don't know anymore.
I don't know.
We're at negative 11.
What if we just strip mine from here?
No, it has to be negative 50.
It said negative 50, right?
I think so.
They do fall in harder difficulties, but we're at hardcore.
Hey, what the hell?
You're trying to sabotage me.
No, I'm not.
I'm literally trying to fucking dig.
You literally attacked me.
No, I didn't.
I just stood in front of the hitbox.
That's why I...
I didn't move.
I literally just left click.
That's why I didn't attack the zombie at that one time.
I didn't move.
Where are we at?
We're at negative 29.
Hey.
You don't get an extra one?
Why are you so scared?
Jump down.
Come on.
What are you doing?
What happened?
I thought you wanted to...
You're such a fucker.
You're actually such a fucker.
Such a fucker.
I hope it is a hole and we have to do this all over again.
I hope...
I hope it's a hole.
I hope it's a fucking hole.
You just couldn't... Come on.
It's all good.
Whatever.
I hope it's a hole and we actually dig to lava.
We're at negative 50.
Oh shit, are we?
Yeah.
Oh shit, we went too far.
No, we're good.
We're good.
No, now I'm at negative 50.
It doesn't...
It's not exactly negative 50.
It is.
Yes, it is.
That's the whole point.
Oh, no.
What happened?
There might...
I can't tell if this is a good thing.
We need to do this one together.
Why?
It's a mine shaft.
Oh.
Oh my god, okay.
Let me make staircases real fast.
Yeah.
We gotta actually work together here.
Oh my god, okay.
We're gonna die in that mine shaft.
No, we're not.
No, I believe.
Come on.
We're gonna die in this mine shaft.
I fucking believe in our deaths.
No, we have... Do you have a...
We need redstone?
No, no.
Okay.
Do you have...
Do you have a good sword?
Do you have an iron sword?
I have an iron sword, yeah.
Alright, let's go.
And let's loot.
Alright.
Yeah, no, we gotta stick together, yeah.
We gotta watch each other's backs.
You're scared.
Maybe.
I like how you're saying, yeah, we gotta work together, and then you disappeared.
Come on, you gotta keep up with me.
I'm trying to put torches for us.
Oh, I got a lot of that.
Oh, there's some iron.
Nice.
Yeah, there's iron right here.
Oh, I'll get rid of that.
I'll keep the blueberries for food.
I can get a name tag.
I'm putting some stuff away from this area.
You know what?
Since we're here, we have to go back to the same area anyway.
I'm gonna put a furnace here.
Okay.
And start making some stuff.
Alright.
Oh, hey.
Nice.
Iron.
Oh, wait, gold.
We don't need gold.
Wait, we do need gold.
No, we don't.
For the piggies.
Oh, I guess that's true.
Wait, why do people give gold to the piggies again?
What do you get?
You can trade with them, and sometimes they give you potions.
We need, like, potions of fire resistance.
Potions?
Can't they give, like, ender pearls and stuff?
Yeah, they give pearls.
They can give pearls, they can give potions, and then they can give...
What's it called?
Wait, did we come this way?
Oh, this is the way we came from.
They can also give... Wait, there's one over here.
There's what?
Right here.
Yeah, we gotta get down here.
Oh.
Okay.
You could make a staircase.
Yeah, but...
But what?
Yeah?
Why didn't you?
I wanted to do it the cool way.
The harder way?
Oh, there's an iron pickaxe in here.
You mean the harder way?
The cool way?
The harder way.
The cool way.
Where I look cool, like I'm fearless.
Chat, did you think she looked cool?
Yeah!
Did she look cool just jumping down?
She looked so awesome.
Oh no, there's a spider!
So cool!
Wait, where are you, Doki?
I'm... I went up.
I think this is the entrance to the mineshaft.
The coolest.
Yeah, see?
I think I look cool.
Oh, maybe that's the spider I'm hearing.
Diamond!
Let's see if there's more...
Congratulations on your one diamond.
You needed that.
Oh wait, I ran out of torches.
Two diamonds, actually.
Wait, why do I have two chests?
Did I accidentally grab your chest?
You grabbed my chest?
Yeah.
Oh sorry, there's none.
I forgot.
I forgot you got nerfed.
Says you!
Oh my god!
Pot calling the kettle black!
For real!
Says you!
I remember when somebody was spamming Doki...
laughing at Doki board.
I fucking remember.
You know, someone at a fan meet gave me a cutting board literally with your face drawn on it.
Wait, what?!
And the letter said, don't tell Doki, but you know what?
I think I will!
But you told!
You told!
Yeah, I think I will because it's my ammunition now.
You can't trust her, guys.
Where'd you go?
I don't fucking know!
Says the guy who owns an actual...
Why did you give it to Mint and not me?!
That's like...
That's the thing I'm wondering about.
Why did you give it to her?
If it has my face on it?
I don't know!
Control your words, your goons!
Was that a mending book?
Oh yeah, we need...
Actual things, don't we?
No, sweeping it.
Actually, this might be good to have.
Where'd you go?
I'm scared!
I'm all by myself!
Actually, I'm...
I think I fucked up.
What do you mean you fucked up?!
I don't know where I am!
Where I can go even deeper?
No, don't go deeper!
I'm scared!
What happened to sticking together?
I don't know, you walked off the other way.
No, you're just too slow!
Oh, hi.
Oh, let's go down here then.
No, I went there.
I went all the way... I explored all of that.
Oh, all of it?
Okay.
Did you explore all of this way?
No, this way.
I didn't go any further than this though.
Okay.
We gotta find our original way back, because I put a furnace there.
Oh wait, I know where to go.
Just let's go.
I would like to have my furnace back.
I have another furnace.
I have two furnaces.
I know, but I put furnaces.
I was making stuff from there.
There's a spider in here.
I can hear him.
Alright, let's go.
There must be like a...
What is it called?
A spawner then.
Oh my god, that's a bat.
Oh my god, he scared me.
Oh, I'm out of torches.
I've been out of torches for a while.
What?
Why did you say something?
Yeah, but I've been...
I've been using my one torch to light my way.
I have more torches.
Where are you?
Where am I?
Oh, a diamond.
Actually, where am I?
What is this role reversal here?
I've waited for this moment for a long time.
Oh, there's a creeper over here.
You wanna get him?
Sure.
Hit and run.
I like how you ran so far.
Well, I'm giving you extra room.
Duh.
Yeah, sure, sure.
Oh, I'm stuck.
I can't...
I hear a spider.
I thought he was down here.
I hear him.
I think he's like somewhere in here.
Here, hold on.
Watch my back and I'll make more torches.
I'll give you some.
Oh, nice.
Okay.
Where'd you go?
What happened to watching my back?
Take some torches.
I was.
Take these.
Alright, nice.
Put that here.
What was in here?
Oh, what was in here?
Oh, okay.
I feel like we don't really need a torch or anything.
No.
Oh my god, where the fuck...
I have five whole diamonds.
Only five?
Well, we don't have...
fortune pickaxes anymore.
This is bad.
I think if we...
Go to the left, we'll find the spawn.
Maybe it's here.
Maybe that's where the spiders are spawning.
The spawner is...
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that's where I found diamonds.
Down here?
No, we have gone down here.
See, there's a torch.
Wait, hold on.
Have we gone across before?
No, it doesn't look like it, but I want to check the...
Oh, hey, wait.
Look.
I don't know if we have...
Hey, that's where the spiders are.
I don't know if we have gone down here.
I'm sure we have, but...
No, look over here.
Oh, yeah, we have.
Look over here where I am.
Oh my god.
Where did he come from?
Over here.
What the fuck?
I didn't kill him, though.
He's still down there.
That's fine.
Get your shields up.
What is he gonna do?
Climb up?
Uh, true.
I'll be very impressed if he does that.
I'll be very impressed.
I still hear the spider, but I don't...
There's nothing here.
I'm pretty sure the spider is like...
Oh, there's a zombie here.
I hear a zombie too, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I just killed him.
No, there's a different one.
Wait, I can actually go down?
Did he climb up?
Oh my god.
Where did he come from?
Why are you laughing like...
Oh, I found the spider.
He was guarding the diamonds.
All I'm saying is...
I have four now too.
What?
Oh my god.
I have five.
I have five, not four.
Just letting you know.
Yeah, but you had to mine several times for five.
Hey, this is a team effort.
It doesn't matter how many we have as long as we...
I have mined one square for that diamond.
I think there's more spider here.
Or... Oh yeah, there is.
Spider!
There's nothing here.
I got him.
Is this where the zombie was?
Alright, I think we got all the mines...
I think we explored the mineshaft fully.
No, we have not.
Oh shit!
Wait, where are you?
I'm exploring the mineshaft.
Wait, where did you go?
Where are you?
I don't know.
Well, find me.
Oh, I see you.
I was gonna say, how do I find you?
Oh my god.
Are you sure?
Oh yeah, we haven't gotten here.
I'm gonna die.
Hold on, I gotta eat.
How are you so close to dying?
We don't need gold.
No!
We can get ender pearls!
I swear to god, if we like...
If this clutches our run, I'm gonna remember this.
I'm gonna remember this if this fucking clutches our run.
You're gonna remember this?
Yeah, I'm gonna remember this.
English is not my first language.
It's not a first language thing, it's literally a mumbling thing!
You're mumbling this?
There's more over here by the way too.
English is my first language by the way.
But it made you feel bad.
Not even a little bit, because it's you.
Should we just strip mine here then?
No, I need to go back to the furnace.
Oh my god, forget about your furnace, I have two furnaces!
No!
But it had meat in it!
It had all my coal!
I had 50 coal in there!
Why did you put all of it in there?
Okay, fine, let's go back.
Because I thought we were gonna go back!
You said you knew how to go back!
Not from here, shit, I don't know.
Okay, hold on.
Wait, I think I do know.
Okay, from down here.
You said we were gonna go back, and I believed in you.
I don't actually know where you left it though.
I don't know either.
What do you mean you don't know either?
Was it before the mineshaft?
Yeah, it was the mineshaft, but it was the first mineshaft area.
Oh, there it is!
See, I told you!
Okay, now we can...
Where are these zombie noises coming from?
Oh yeah, two, right?
Okay, I'll just wait for you two.
Yeah, you don't need to bring your...
Actually, I'm gonna bring it anyway.
We don't need gunpowder, because then we don't need TNT, right?
I mean, I guess technically not, unless we want to get netherite, but...
No, that's too much work.
Do we need netherite to fucking fight the ender dragon?
Well...
We can just fight them with diamond.
Yeah, I guess so.
Like, we could just do it with diamond.
How do you open a book?
What do you mean?
You need a thingy for it.
You need a thingy?
Yeah, like a library thing.
So you have to have a thingy to open to write in it too?
Yeah, you can't open it and do anything with it.
Oh my God, I knew I can't read.
I'll never be able to read.
Okay, let's go back downstairs.
Oh my God, you scared me.
Oh,
this is where you got your diamond.
Well, let's go keep... This is a good diamond area then.
Yeah, yeah, so we just trip mine.
Trip mine.
Alright, nice.
This is it.
This is where we're gonna find all the diamonds.
We're gonna find diamond, we're gonna be so dripped out.
We're gonna be so rich and everything.
You know what?
I'm gonna use that diamond I have now...
And craft a diamond pickaxe.
What?
I'm gonna do it.
That's such a waste.
I have... What do you mean?
We literally... That's the whole point.
The point is to have the diamond armor.
Why don't we just keep using the iron?
You crafted it, didn't you?
It's important!
It's gonna do so well.
I'm gonna find the remaining diamonds for you.
You'll see.
You're gonna see.
You'll all see.
You'll see.
You're gonna see.
I'm gonna prove you wrong.
Do it!
Prove me wrong!
You'll see.
I'm gonna show you all.
Show you all.
Didn't they add a new enemy to the caves?
They did?
No, they didn't.
I thought they did.
What did they add?
I don't remember what it's called.
I don't... Chat, what was it called?
Oh, it's a new biome?
I thought there was a... Yeah, like a Slenderman thing, right?
What?
What the fuck are you talking about?
Not the warden.
The creaking?
Yeah.
Is it in this?
Only a certain cave biome.
Wait, is it in this one?
What's this one?
Isn't this snapshot?
Or like...
Deep dark!
You got the deep dark?
I'm in the deep dark!
How the fuck did you find...
Well, I don't know.
It might not be a...
It might not be a city.
Wait, no.
You can tell if it's a city.
F3.
It tells you the biome.
No, it says my biome is deep dark.
Oh, if you dig down, that means we're in it.
Are you gonna dig down?
Should I dig down?
Okay.
Are you gonna do it?
If we find a warden, we are actually for sure dead.
What do you mean, we?
Oh, wait.
I'm at bedrock when I dig down.
Wait, I'm at bedrock too.
I've been digging bedrock.
I was trying to dig bedrock.
I couldn't tell.
I couldn't tell that I was bedrock.
Toki.
I was like, wow, this is some hard-ass rock right here.
You're wasting your newly diamond pickaxe.
I was like, whoa, this rock is so hard to dig.
Is this really deep dark?
There's no skulk at all.
Maybe I dig down or above.
Maybe it's above us.
Yeah, I think it is because we're too far deep for...
We're too far deep for it to be.
Yeah, it doesn't matter for us.
Yeah, we don't need...
I don't think we need it, so...
I don't think there was anything there that requires us to...
To... What was it?
Nah, it would probably just be a flex to say that we survived the deep dark.
I mean, technically, I'm surviving the deep dark right now.
In hardcore.
I'm surviving... Oh, diamond.
Oh, diamond.
Whoa!
Hey, I got diamond too.
See, I told you it was an investment.
One.
Two.
Yeah, two.
Okay.
Yeah, how many did you get?
I got like five.
Oh, okay.
I'm at eleven now.
I have eleven diamonds.
Oh, okay.
I mean, I got my diamond pickaxe.
Actually, I think we do need that for like obsidian.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah?
Oh, so my investment was like corrected.
Barely.
I mean, we could've found obsidian.
We could've also like made it without the obsidian, you know?
Sure, sure, sure.
Yeah.
Are you crying?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Why would I be crying?
I have my diamond pickaxe.
My good investment.
Your good investment.
Wait, we could just use the bucket.
Wait, that's actually...
That's what I'm saying.
You use the bucket to like make it without the...
Yeah, do you know how to do it?
Do you know how to do it?
I actually don't know how.
Yeah, exactly.
Exactly.
I actually think I'm stupid with that.
I never looked it up.
Wait, your video tutorial didn't tell you how to?
No.
I told you, they don't hold your hand.
They're like, you're gonna figure this out.
We'll just give you hints on what to do.
Wait, I need to go up.
Let's see.
How the turns of tables, right everybody?
I feel like we need to be at... Isn't 54 like the optimal?
I don't know.
I'm at negative 58.
You're at 58?
Is that almost bedrock?
Yeah.
This sounds like cope, huh?
Oh, I don't think I'm at the right level for me to be getting diamond, you know?
I'm gonna remember this.
Oh, I have!
Toki, I have remembered it!
At least people are gonna remember what you...
I have remembered it!
Through the afterlife, I have literally remembered this.
People always remember the first time, not the second.
It is my first time.
How many diamonds do we need, guys, for a full armor set?
How many?
I'm surprised I haven't hit anything.
Oh, I hate this eerie sound.
It's so creepy.
33?
I feel like I've been digging for the rest of my life.
We need 30?
Someone says 24.
24.
Okay, people are gaslighting me.
24 for armor.
Your whisper gaslighting you, but my dragoons instantly told me the correct amount.
Oh, but we also need a sword.
I think they meant it with also the sword.
Right?
We need the sword too.
Uh-oh, I hear lava.
You hear lava?
That was one guy doki as well.
No, that was several people!
There were several dragoons that said it!
Oh, you don't even see my chat.
Like, how are you gaslighting me when you don't even see my chat?
Oh no!
Wait, do you have a crafting table?
Yeah, I do.
I have two.
Can I have one?
Oh, I think you stole mine.
I didn't steal it.
You lost yours.
I'm running back to you.
How far are you?
You're going down one hole, right?
You're just going down a single hole?
Oh my gosh, you switched directions.
Did you not hear when I said I hit bedrock?
You can keep going!
No, you can't!
I'm just going straight!
Is that incapable of you?
Are you incapable of going straight?
Oh hey, look, I found...
Give me my crafting table.
I found five diamonds.
That's right.
Give me my crafting table.
Yes.
No, you gotta find me first.
I'm literally right behind you.
Oh hey.
Stupid crafting table.
Look at that.
Okay, thank you.
That was a stack of six diamonds?
Look at that.
How many do you have?
Um, seven.
And if I include the, you know, the two diamonds, the three diamonds I used to make my diamond pickaxe...
That would be like ten.
Yeah, that's rookies numbers.
Yeah, well you have eleven, like the plus one that's apparently better.
Yeah, eleven.
I didn't take it?
Oh, I didn't take it.
Oops.
Yeah, see, you lost yours and you're like...
You stole my crafting table when you didn't even take your crafting table in the first place.
I can't see.
You don't put any torches down.
It's pitch black down here.
Yeah, I don't need torches.
I literally have a torch in my hand to light the way.
Why waste resources when I can just light the way with my torches in my hand?
I can't wait for a creeper to spawn right up behind you.
And I want you to eat those words.
Do it!
Do it now!
Spawn in now.
I ain't scared.
I ain't afraid of no ghost.
Yeah, I ain't afraid of no ghost.
There's literally a ghost right beside me.
I'm gone.
I'm long gone.
She's not scared.
She's not scary.
I am scary.
What are you talking about?
You're not.
You're not fucking scary.
You've never scared anybody in your life.
Yes, I have!
You have.
Name one.
You wanna watch me scare them right now?
Yeah.
I'm graduating.
We've already done worse.
That's it?
It's a joke, guys.
It's a joke.
They're all sad now.
They're all really spooked right now.
They're like...
They're like PTSD.
Too far.
It's a joke.
JK.
She's a monster.
I scared you guys.
Halloween's over.
Oh my God.
Why am I getting redstone?
Okay.
When you get redstone, does it give you experience?
Yeah, it does.
Oh, yeah.
Then mine it.
You don't have to take it.
Just mine it.
Why should I?
I'm already level 11.
Because we need it to enchant our stuff.
We need more experience.
Fine.
God!
I guess I'll do it.
Can I do anything with this bamboo?
You can make sugar.
I can only make one block.
That's sugar cane.
You can make paper.
I'm making sticks.
Making sticks.
Nice.
I'm making...
I'm strip mining.
I'm stripping.
You're stripping?
She's stripping?
I'm stripping.
That's like the short form for strip mining, right?
Yeah.
We're all stripping.
We're stripping.
You're stripping.
I'm stripping.
Will that be enough?
I wonder.
Let's strip mining.
Is that what it means?
We're stripping.
We're doing it.
We're stripping so fast.
I'm cooking now.
If we die during this run, I swear to god.
I don't think I can do this again.
What are you talking about?
We're so much more experienced now.
We could do it in like half the time.
I don't think I can start stripping again, man.
I hate this.
Actually, I don't mind the stripping because it's kind of relaxing.
You don't mind the stripping?
It's kind of relaxing to just, you know, not worry about...
Especially when they give you superchats while you're stripping.
They don't do that.
They don't do that?
Are you stripping for free?
I mean, it's like a hobby.
It's just a stress reliever.
It's like a hobby.
I'm just like, you know...
Do it for experience, you know?
I lose myself in the strip, you know?
I don't think about it.
My mind just goes like blank.
And I just say, I'm gonna keep stripping.
Before I know it, I've...
Mint, I swear to god.
Mint, please.
I swear to god.
I can't keep stripping, Mint.
I'm okay.
I've hit lava, but I'm okay.
Thanks guys for the dollar bills while I'm stripping.
Yeah, where's your dollar bills?
Oh, hey, hey.
Have you hit diamond, Mint?
Have you hit diamond?
No one remembers the first time.
Nobody remembers the second time, okay?
Yeah, and that's why people always remember our first experience.
It wasn't my experience.
This is all original right here.
This never happened before.
Actually, you know, I never played Minecraft before.
Yeah, you never played Minecraft before, then how come you knew so much about stripping?
Thanks for the dollar bills, guys.
I really appreciate it.
I worked so hard.
Oh my gosh, thanks for the dollar bills.
Thank you, guys.
Thank you for the dollar bills.
Thank you.
I'm stripping.
Well, it's not a hobby anymore.
They're paying you.
No, it's...
What is it called then?
It's called... I don't know.
Do I need to get... Oh no, do I need to LLC this strip?
Oh no, now you gotta make sure it's taxed properly.
Gotta add the GMT taxes, guys.
That's a Canadian tax.
YouTube's not gonna like this.
YouTube, they're already thinking of... They're already pressing the button on banning our accounts at this very moment.
Banning accounts?
What did we do wrong?
We're just stripping.
Yeah, but YouTube... For money.
For money.
Yeah, for money, guys.
Not legal.
We're just strip mining.
It's not legal, guys.
It's not against your TOS.
Did you just say it's not legal?
That's... That means...
It's not illegal.
Oh, not illegal.
Yeah, yeah.
We're just strip mining.
Oh my gosh.
Did you see like the Twitch TOS about like VTuber hips?
Yeah.
I thought that was funny.
Well, I mean, it's fucking sucks, but like... I thought that was funny because like...
I played like Nikkei.
I got sponsored for Nikkei.
And then I was like, you know, the girls.
But it doesn't... It's fine.
The TOS is... If it's like a game character or something.
Oh my God.
But we're not real, though.
We're not real.
I'm... What if we were in a game?
I made a game.
And you were in the game, too.
Technically, we're video game characters.
Yeah, we are video game characters.
I mean, we're not Twitch streamers, but like, technically, like...
If we were, we'd be fine.
Yeah, we'd be fine.
We'll be within TOS.
Yeah.
Someone was just like, my mom asked me what I am watching.
Because we keep saying we're stripping.
We're Minecraft friendly VTubers.
We're playing Minecraft.
Don't worry, mom.
Mom, it's okay.
Don't worry.
Just say like... Just say it's like the new name for mining.
They don't know what strip mining is?
Oh wait, they do.
That's like a not a Minecraft thing.
Yeah.
It's not a Minecraft exclusive.
Like, it's not... Yeah!
Do you think mining was invented in Minecraft?
Yeah.
I can't believe it, guys.
Mining was invented in Minecraft.
JohnMinecraft invented mining, obviously.
Oh my God, you're right.
Oh my God, someone was saying I'm watching miners.
No, guys, don't say that.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Donkey, the bit is getting too dangerous.
Oh no, okay.
Alright, guys.
Alright, show's over.
Show's over, we're closing down.
The bit is getting too dangerous.
We're changing businesses and hobbies.
Yeah.
Oh my God, there's so much redstone.
Wait, how much do we need again?
For redstone?
No, like, no, like diamond.
Diamond was, uh, twenty...
I hear zombies next to me.
Twenty-seven?
I think?
Well, twenty-four is for the armor, and then it's three for...
For, uh...
Oh my gosh, I hate...
Twenty-four for armor.
Okay, I already have the boots.
You made boots?
Yeah, I already made the boots.
Okay.
I'm almost done.
That's a bit of a stretch.
Well, I'm almost... That's like one out of four!
That's twenty-five percent.
It's not even fifty.
That's almost... Okay, do you have any boots?
I don't think so.
I don't think you have diamond boots.
I haven't made diamond anything.
Exactly.
I'm saving until I have the full...
Full set, baby.
The full set.
Yep, and then a zombie is gonna fucking get you.
Why are you wishing death upon me?
No, I'm not wishing death upon you.
I'm trying to tell you that you're not playing it safe.
I don't even have pants on right now.
In public?
Well, I'm in a cave.
Is this truly public?
I mean, your wisp is here, surrounding you.
Are they?
Where are you guys?
Guys?
I mean, they're ghosts, so you can't see them.
I'm a ghost too.
You think ghosts can see other ghosts?
Yes, we can.
How do you know that?
Because I can see other ghosts.
Have you seen another ghost?
Yeah.
Who?
Yes, I have.
Yes.
I've seen many ghosts.
Who?
I met George Washington.
And what the... Oh, yeah?
What does he look like?
He has...
What's his middle name?
I don't know.
How... What do we... Wait.
Oh, so you didn't actually, like, meet him.
What's my... OK, Doki, what's my middle name, huh?
I don't know.
I haven't met you.
You literally...
What do you call this?
I'll know your middle name next week.
This is a phone call.
It's not like I actually met you.
It's like... It's like a seance, you know?
Like...
Good amount of diamond and redstone all together.
Oh, my God.
I hit level 15.
Let's go.
Just level 15?
What level are you?
16.
Wow.
I remember when you were saying that about my...
OK, but that's levels.
That's levels.
OK, fine then.
Yeah.
Now I'm level 16.
Wow, now I'm level 17.
No, you're not.
I'm level 16 plus infinity.
Oh, yeah?
I'm level 18 and my dad works at Nintendo.
This is Minecraft.
Who cares if your dad works at Nintendo?
I care.
Minecraft is on the Switch.
Your dad doesn't do anything with Minecraft.
Ma'am, this is a Wendy's.
You don't know that.
What if he works in the Minecraft division for this?
You're saying he works in the mines at Nintendo?
Yeah.
It must feel like it.
We know how JP companies are like.
I think Nintendo is alright though, comparatively speaking.
Yeah.
No, wasn't there...
Wasn't Nintendo...
Wasn't there an article of like one of the...
Wait, we need Lapis, right?
Yeah, and we also need sponsorship, so...
OK, yeah, you're right.
I love Nintendo.
Let's go, Nintendo.
I have like more than a stack of Lapis.
Do we need more than one stack of Lapis?
I have almost two stacks.
OK, I have almost two stacks as well.
Yeah, so I think...
It really depends on our RNG.
I love Nintendo, guys.
Clip it and ship it.
Oh my gosh, I don't wanna do this again.
Doki, we can't die.
We have to make it.
Why are you saying that to me?
Are you trying to imply something?
We have to make it to the Ender Dragon.
I don't think I can strip mine again.
I can't strip mine again.
I can't do this.
I can't go back to stripping, man.
How did the other streamers that you were inspired by...
How did they do this?
Uh-oh, wait.
It took them...
It took them 20 days, man.
I don't think that they are the...
I don't think they are like the goal of like...
Are we doing it right, chat?
Are we doing this right?
I don't think we are.
I don't think we're meant to even have diamond.
I think they're like...
Yes, we are.
Are we, though?
Are we?
We could do this with iron.
Wait, what if we build snowmen?
Like, you remember?
Oh, yeah.
We need to find the ice biome and just farm snow.
Okay.
But that will kill the Enderman, I think.
It won't kill anything else.
Yeah, no, it would hit the Ender Dragon as well.
Does it?
Yeah.
Make an army of snowmen?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm pretty sure that works.
Snowballs don't do damage.
Wait, what the point was to make snowmen?
Why did we do that?
Yeah, why did we do that?
Why did we do that, though?
Yeah, why did...
I think you're the one that suggested it to me.
No, it's not me!
Don't put this on me!
Why did we do that?
Oh, it was to stagger?
Stagger what?
Blazes, but we didn't even do that for the blazes.
Oh my God, we gotta find the fucking fortress.
I just remembered.
No, we don't need to...
We need blaze rods.
It's fine, we get a fire resistance potions, we'll be fine.
Will we, though?
Probably.
Will we be fine?
Where's your name?
I don't even see your name anymore.
I don't know anymore.
I've been stripping for...
She's stripping.
I don't wanna go back to stripping, guys.
I can't do it again.
I need to turn down the music a little.
I'm going a little crazy.
What's your music?
It's just like a free BGM channel called BGM President or some shit.
Oh, I think I ran into your strip.
Into my...
It makes the fight easier.
Oh, so we weren't crazy.
We weren't crazy then.
I was crazy once.
They locked me in a strip mine.
A mine full of...
A mine full of strippers.
I wish.
Oh my gosh, what if we find the... What's that thing?
That new thing...
The torture room.
The crippling?
No, I mean that.
The crinkler?
What's that...
What's that thing that...
The trials!
Yeah, the trials.
The trials?
The fuck is that?
How many things did they add since I last played?
It's crazy.
Minecraft is crazy now.
The scruggly?
Oh, I hear a skelly.
Where am I?
No skelly, please.
What if I like...
What if like...
I grab that moment again and then re-dub it to like...
Change...
What?
You know the first moment?
Oh, yeah.
I re-dub the name so the moment can live on.
What if we... Okay, hold on.
We dub over the names and then we also re-film it because...
Because our skins would be different.
Or mine.
No, we re-animate it.
No, we can just do it in... We can make the whole environment look the exact same.
Oh my god, you're right.
We can.
We can just do it in creative mode.
Yeah, just react and...
We can do it.
It's... What is it called?
Like when...
The react videos when they...
It's fair use, guys.
Fair use?
We could just... We're just like...
It's like a very famous moment that happened in Minecraft.
Yeah, it's like a parody.
Yeah, a parody.
A parody.
We're not claiming we own it.
We're just trying to parody it.
It's such a famous moment.
Famous moment in Minecraft that happened.
Everybody knows about that moment.
It's transformative, exactly.
Like even...
What's it?
Squackity knows about that moment.
Yeah, yeah.
Everyone who plays Minecraft knows that moment.
What was it called?
Even ThomasInnit knows about it.
ThomasInnit knows that moment.
Yeah, it was TommyInnit.
Oh.
TommyInnit.
It's YouTube history.
It's a tribute we'd be making.
A tribute.
Yeah, we're making a tribute.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Oh my god, I'm going crazy.
I have 23.
I'm almost there.
Wait, seriously?
I have it.
I should be able to make a full army.
Wait, how many do you have?
I only have 15.
You only have...
What the hell is this?
Nothing's changed.
Clearly nothing has changed.
At least finding more iron.
I didn't even acknowledge it because I was like, surely she's finding stuff, right?
I'm not finding anything.
That's unfortunate for you.
I was finding it at first this whole time.
Okay, to be fair, you mine faster because you have a diamond pickaxe.
Oh yeah, are you trying to say that was a good investment?
I'm just saying it was.
Is that what you're trying to say?
I'm saying you invested.
Are you trying to say what I did there where I got a diamond pickaxe and you're like, no, don't do it.
Good is subjective, okay?
Good is subjective.
I'm just slow because I have just only iron.
Are you calling me?
You're saying, okay, now you're making fun of me for being poor?
That's so messed up.
I'm trying to make my way through this world.
I'm just trying to make my way through this damn cruel world.
The rich gets richer!
That's why you gotta learn now.
I can't believe you still don't have... I can't believe you have 15.
Okay, well, you know what?
Doki, you're just gonna have to keep digging because you're gonna wait for me.
And I'm gonna keep strip mining for you.
I'll just keep going forever and ever and then I'll die.
And then you won't... Oh my god, it died.
Oh, shoot.
I swear to god, if you die after everything, I'm mine all the way till...
I will.
I'll die.
Because you spite me and I will die.
Do it!
No, do it.
Do it.
We'll do this at the end.
No, I'm fine.
I'm working.
I doubt that.
I really doubt that.
Alright, go kill yourself right now in Minecraft.
I'm gonna use the bathtub.
Oh, you really had to add that in Minecraft in there real fast, huh, girl?
Yeah, you had to add that.
You had to add that real fast in there.
I'm gonna use the bathtub.
Okay.
And I'll come back and you're still alive.
I don't know.
Okay.
Is she gone?
What was that?
Guys, did you hear that running?
It was like a...
Wait, what was that?
Doki?
It wasn't me mining the lapis.
Was it me mining the lapis?
Actually, I don't know.
Guys, I almost have enough.
I almost have enough diamond.
The crinkler.
That wasn't...
That sounded different.
No, there's a skeleton right there.
I think he's on the other side.
Are you actually gonna die?
I heard running.
Running?
Wait, that's not in the game.
I don't know.
I think Karol Bryant is coming for me.
Oh, thank God.
I think Karol Bryant is here for me.
It's all... It's so over.
It's so over for me.
You just had like a Halloween mod on the entire time.
Yeah.
Oh, skellies?
Okay, I think I'm about to hit a...
Are you got any new diamonds since... Since then?
Since 15?
Are you still at 15?
I'm... Yes.
You're still at 15?
What happened?
I've been... I'm strapping and also there's someone running after me.
Oh my God, what's that sound?
Eerie cave.
Eerie cave, eerie cave.
Scary, spooky cave.
Where the fuck did I put my crafting table?
Oh, right here.
I didn't pick it up.
Scary!
Scary cave.
Spooky, scary.
Wait, I wanna make... Wait, I wanna make an iron pickaxe.
My other pickaxe is almost dead.
How do we get to the crinkler?
What biome is he in?
Yeah, what is the... What is the crinkler?
I don't even know.
Yeah, I don't know.
The only thing I know about the crinkler is what you just told me.
He crinkles.
He just crinkles.
He's behind you, don't say that.
Wait, do I have one rail?
Oh, I do.
I have one singular rail track.
I'm gonna go crazy.
I'm so mining because somebody still doesn't have 24.
I'm trying!
Are you though?
Are you really trying?
I'm mining!
Oh, I'm gonna find your... Okay, I'm gonna find where your hole is.
What?
Then you what?
You're gonna steal my diamonds from me?
No, I'm gonna help you!
You'll steal my diamonds from me and then you'll be like...
I have all the diamonds.
Beg me for more.
That's what you'll say.
I don't wanna be stuck in these mines anymore.
You're not welcome into my hole.
You're not consenting?
Stay out!
I better not see you.
I better not see your name.
I don't know where you are actually.
I don't know either.
I don't know...
I've been in this one area.
If you just keep going forever you'll eventually get good.
My great-great grandchildren are gonna be in this one mine.
Okay, but we gotta get more levels too.
I'm at level 18.
How many more levels do we need?
Do you know how much it costs to level up stuff?
I don't remember how much.
No, I don't.
Do you remember?
It costs a lot.
How much is a lot?
Like 50.
There's no way it's 50.
It's a lot, I promise.
There's no way.
It's not 50.
I'm having backseaters in my chat telling me how to dig.
Oh my god, good.
I don't know, mid, you're at 15.
I don't have these backseaters, that's all I'm saying.
I got to 24 and I don't have these backseaters right now.
We need more than 24, Doki!
Oh my god, I want it.
I have three extra.
What more do we need?
Wait, what do you mean you have three extra?
I have three more.
I have three.
I made all my... I have more than 24.
Oh, wait, how much is a sword then?
Wait, I can make a sword right now.
I can literally make a sword right now.
You didn't say that!
I'm digging.
I'm digging too.
I might as well make another diamond pickaxe.
Oh, can I have it?
Might as well use the last three to make a diamond pickaxe.
Oh, fuck it, I'm going to do it.
I don't know how long I'm going to be trapped in this mine.
I like my boots.
I don't know how long I'm going to be trapped in here.
I might as well make another diamond pickaxe.
I'm going to go mad.
I'm going to get mad trip disease.
Are you done?
Yeah.
I'm done.
Guys, I know it's been like three hours, but Hope Mint was not too quiet.
Sometimes she hits the green instead of the yellow, so I got a little worried.
What do you mean?
Now what?
Now you finally made armor?
Yeah.
I like my boots and stuff though.
I'm going to miss them.
Oh my gosh, I keep clicking the wrong thing.
Like auto...
Thank god I didn't know.
Don't die!
That was lava.
Wait, how many shots?
Okay.
I'm just going to leave it here.
It could be a little louder.
It's been three hours.
She could have been a little louder three hours ago.
I don't know what's wrong with my Discord.
I really don't.
Yeah, like I have you like...
You apparently could have been a little louder.
That's not my fault.
Oh no!
There's something wrong with your Discord.
You changed the setting.
I didn't change anything though.
Oh no, I have to buy... I have to get the diamond pickaxe.
I'm going fast now.
Okay, I upped her a bit more guys.
So I hope it's a lot better now.
Am I loud?
No, you're like barely loud.
Am I like quiet on my stream?
Yeah, because on my stream...
No, you're not.
You're not quiet on your stream.
It's just...
You did something to your Discord that like made it so that it's...
Like I don't know what you're... Something with your setup.
But all my settings are... I've sent you my settings.
They're all normal.
Yeah, but like...
Because like there was a time where like suddenly it was just different.
Where like you're like super quiet for everybody on Discord.
And I don't know what you did.
I don't know what... I didn't do anything!
Discord's trying to sabotage me!
I don't know what you did.
I didn't do anything.
That's what they all say.
Okay, I'm gonna go this way now.
I'm changing directions.
My diamond pickaxe is about to break.
This is how long we've been trip mining for.
Wow, finally?
My diamond pick... yeah.
Yes, finally.
We've been mining for like an hour plus, I'm pretty sure.
I'm pretty sure I've been stuck in the... I haven't seen daylight in like 20 years, man.
Wait, how do we get out of this?
We just make a fucking ladder staircase.
Remember how to take up?
We've always done that before.
Okay.
I wish we had fortune.
Me too.
I wish a lot of things, man.
I wish... I wish you'd get more diamonds.
Like at this point, now it's just sad.
This is just sad now.
Hey, I'm doing my best, okay?
I'm doing my best.
Are you?
I'm digging!
If you were doing your best, you could've made a diamond pickaxe.
I made one!
Now, after an hour and a half!
It doesn't matter how long it took me.
Yes it does!
This could've been over!
We would've been out of the mining stages!
Don't you want this to go?
How long do you want this stream to last?
I will cancel my other streams if you're gonna do this.
That pickaxe is about to die?
Well, good thing I have enough for another pickaxe!
Lucky you!
Oh my god, that was lava.
Okay...
YouTube streams can only go up to 12 hours.
That's why we'll make a part 2!
Do you have a lot of iron?
I have... 20.
Okay, we might need more for shields.
Shields.
Okay, that's 5.
Part 2 is still in the mine!
At one point, it doesn't turn into a joke.
It's not my fault that my luck is very bad!
If not luck, you could've made a diamond!
At that point, it's not luck, it's a skill issue.
Oh my god...
Okay, time to make my fucking...
Another diamond pickaxe!
Let's fucking go!
I don't even have fucking...
I need to make another stick.
Alright, here we go.
I'm going down a different direction now.
I feel promised in this way.
Good for you.
We don't need redstones, right?
No, we don't need a redstone.
Okay, I've been in the mines for so long, I keep forgetting what we need and what we don't need now.
All I see is just cobblestone.
What if this was beating Minecraft?
Like, what if the mine... It's Minecraft, technically we're beating it.
Do you know the worst part, Mint?
Yeah?
The nether is supposed to be the hardest part out of this.
The nether is supposed to be the hardest part.
It's supposed to be.
All we need are... We need some green mushrooms to get rid of the hogs.
We need some...
We need some lava to kill hogs.
Oh, we're good.
We need some potions.
We just gotta go find a village with a potion plate thing.
And we're good.
Yeah, and what if a ghastly comes up to us while we're crossing the...
A ghastly?
What game are we...
What game are we playing now?
Oh, sorry, I have a Cobblemon mod on.
What if, you know, the ghast comes in and goes...
And then, like, we fall into the lava.
That's what shields are for.
What if we don't do the shields in time?
You run around with your shield.
What are you talking about?
What if I don't do it in time?
What if I don't do this in time?
I mean, I can't... I don't know what's gonna happen if we die on this run.
I don't know what's gonna become of me.
It's only, like, the first run that we've gotten this far, but...
I don't know what's gonna happen to me because then we have to do this all over again.
This specific part of the run.
At that point, I'm not even gonna... I don't even wanna...
At a point, we might as well just do it with Iron.
I don't care anymore.
She's really losing it, you guys.
She's so weak.
It's only been hour three.
You're literally a ghost.
You're dead already.
Like, you don't know...
You're weak.
You're... You're dead.
You're literally a ghost.
So what does that have to do with it?
You don't care about dying because you're already dead.
Join me.
I don't know.
What do you want me to say?
The strip madness is getting to me.
The strip madness madness.
How much more can you take?
Like, how much more can I...
Are you still at 15?
You're still at 15, aren't you?
I just found three more diamonds and you're still...
I'm doing my best!
I'm gonna find your hole.
I'm gonna find your hole and dig that hole.
I'm freaking coming back.
Let me dig this.
Alright.
Okay, give me your coordinates.
No, find my hole!
Give me your coordinates!
I'm coming over.
I'm running over.
You don't even know where I am.
I've been digging so many holes.
There's so many holes.
I'm surprised no monsters spawn into any of these holes that we've created.
Honestly, I'm surprised too.
Wait, but seriously, how much more can you take?
I think this is your hole.
I didn't dig... No, this is my hole?
Oh wait, this is the hole I dug with lava.
Okay.
Unless that's my hole with lava.
How many holes with lava did you find?
Wait, did you leave a... I just need to know.
Did you leave a hole unattended with like lava?
Yeah.
Wait, what do you mean by that?
Like, did you leave a hole where like...
I could accidentally walk into where there's... where it's a pit?
Uh... I don't think so.
Okay, alright.
Alright, that's good to know.
I think I wanna just find one more.
Okay, I'm gonna try and find you right now.
Oh my god, how long have I been digging?
This does not stop.
What?
This... This doesn't stop.
Holy shit.
I dug a lot.
I'm still... No, I'm still at my hole.
Damn, Doki, okay.
Okay, they found your hole.
Did you?
You have torches, okay.
Oh, you left this.
What did I leave?
You left the redstone.
You don't need the redstone.
Precious experience.
You need the experience.
Oh, the experience, yeah.
Okay, you put torches in your hole, right?
Not all of them.
Alright, this has to be your hole.
I didn't put any torches in mine.
Okay.
Oh my god, this is a long asshole.
Okay, you must have...
Go into the right one.
I've changed a couple of times.
Okay, which one?
This is the one with lava.
What the fuck is this?
It's what?
What?
Mine is so much more straightforward.
Like, what are these?
Oh my god.
Oh, did you find my...
Wait, how are you so far...
I found your...
I found your cross section.
Oh, no, no.
I ran into your hole.
Ran into my hole?
Yeah, at one point I ran into your hole.
Yeah, but you're in the cross section.
Wait, why did you stop here?
Why did you go back here?
I just wasn't feeling it.
I don't know.
Oh my god, you stopped before you hit it big.
You're like those gamblers.
What?
Keep going then.
Did I hit it big there?
Did I miss out?
Alright, alright.
I'm gonna do it.
It wouldn't be funny if you missed out.
Maybe I did.
I don't know.
It would be so funny if you missed out.
We'll keep digging.
I'm gonna dig this hole and see if you missed out.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm digging.
I'm digging your hole.
I'm digging the hole you fucking stopped at.
I mean, if you eventually get to something...
It has to be within like 5 hits.
5 hits?
Yeah.
5 hits.
So you're like, you know...
You're like changing the rules then.
What?
No, because it's...
That's the meme.
You hit it big right before you get to it.
It's not like you hit it big after like 50 hits.
That's just...anybody could do that.
No, no, no.
It means you gave up too early.
You just gave up so easily.
No, no.
That's not the meme.
The meme is literally he gave up right before he hit it big.
It doesn't matter because you're the one that gave up.
But anybody...you could give up literally any way.
Okay, you stop digging.
If I go to your...
If you go...if I go to your hole...
I stopped digging because I finished my task.
Oh, what is this?
Among Us now?
Okay.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
At least I finished it.
I finished my goal.
Somebody hasn't finished their fucking goal.
I just wanna find one more stack, okay?
God.
Hello, Redstone-do.
I'm almost at level 20.
Me too.
Oh, yeah?
What's your level?
19.
Just like you said, I'm almost at level 20.
Me too.
I don't know.
It could be level 18.
Oh, so you're at level 18, huh?
Yeah, okay.
No, no.
I'm level 19.
I just thought you weren't good enough to be level 19.
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh my gosh.
How much more do I have to dig?
I don't know.
I'm digging your hole right now.
Why is it that I'm the one that's more sane than you?
Because I know we're gonna die.
No, we have to beat this eventually.
No, I know this is not the run.
I know I'm...
What do you mean this is not the run?
You're still the young optimistic...
You're still young and optimistic, but I know...
I know we're gonna be doing this all over again.
I know this isn't it.
Is it because I only have 15 diamonds?
I know that I have to repeat this all over again.
Well, then you can find all the diamonds and...
Just give them to me.
Since you have better luck, right?
I thought this is a team game.
I thought...
Well, clearly I'm not doing well enough.
Mint!
I found diamonds.
I found diamonds in your hole.
Okay, but that was like 20 minutes later!
Oh my God!
It doesn't matter!
It was so long ago!
You had to dig for so long!
You had to dig!
It was not right there.
Six!
Six diamonds in the hole you gave up on!
Six diamonds!
Well, then give them to me!
Then give them to me!
No!
This is to teach you a lesson to never give up.
You gave up.
I'm still going.
I didn't give up because I'm still here and I'm still digging.
I'm still digging.
Yeah!
I'm gonna go find another one of your pathways that you fucking gave up on.
Okay, do it.
Come find me.
You'll never find me.
I'll never find you.
I'm so fucking lost.
I don't even know which one was the hole I dug.
That could have even been your hole then!
It could have even been your hole!
No, it's your hole.
Hey Min!
Why do I have some wisps writing you out in my chat?
You guys!
I'm gonna dig up.
I'm gonna start digging up.
Somebody has a full set.
You motherfuckers!
I'm gonna meet you at the fucking surface you fucking whore!
Help!
Oh yeah!
So loyal!
No, no.
It has to be the dragoons coming over to see how much I had left.
You mean the dragoons?
I'm fucking going.
I'll see you up in the surface.
I'll see you up on the surface.
Where are you?
Wait, I don't know where my... What's it called?
Crafting table.
Dragoons would never...
No, the dragoons are the ones that ratted me out.
No, dragoons would never...
How dare you guys.
How dare.
Dragoons would fucking never do that.
Who snitched?
Give me names.
Give me names right now.
I know all my wisps.
I'll be able to know.
I'll be able to...
Oh yeah?
Alright, alright, alright.
Let's see.
Who was it?
Who was it that snitched?
Aragon Battleborn.
That's a dragoon.
That is a dragoon.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You know what?
I bet it's even a wisp-goon.
Oh, they're the worst.
You know what?
This person...
They're not even... They're not even a member.
But I bet they're a member in your chat.
Check if they're a member in your chat.
Check, check.
Where are you?
Show up on Ms. Chat right now.
I wanna see if you're a member.
I wanna see.
I mean, my...
No, no, no.
They were probably gifted a member if so.
They're a gifted...
Are they calling him a gifted member?
Show yourself, Aragon.
I can't see though.
Oh my god, no.
Stop gifting memberships.
Stop it.
Stop.
They said, I'm an SSRB.
What is that?
What is SSRB?
Are they a member?
No, they're not a member.
Okay, okay.
So...
They're like an inside job.
Oh, they're a fan of Botan.
You're not even watching.
This is...
We're indies.
Get out of here.
It was a psychops.
It was a psychops all along.
What's so sad is that they wouldn't even say like, yeah, I'm a fan of you.
Not even for the bit.
Oh my gosh.
Oh my god, we're at minus 26 right now.
You're at minus 26?
I think the worst part... Oh my god, I hope we dig up to the fucking... Not to the mountain.
I hope we got out of the mountain area.
Well, once you get to something, just dig over.
Okay, I don't know if I'm in the mountain though.
Oh wait, I'm gonna start taking my torches back.
Are you not digging up?
No, I had to... I guess I could get some.
I could've done everything.
I'll dig eventually.
I'm waiting for you in the surface.
You're only prolonging your torture.
Your torture?
I'm fine.
You're only prolonged.
You think you're gonna be fine, Tia.
You think.
What do you mean by that?
You think you're gonna be fine and then we're gonna do like 20 more of this and then you're gonna be like, oh my god, Doki, why did I...
Okay, I'm getting to a safe spot.
What did they say?
Why are you saying LOL at them?
Wait, what?
I don't know, my chat.
No, like where did I dig to?
Is this another cave?
Uh-oh, don't die.
You better not die.
You have golden armor, I mean diamond armor.
You're good.
Oh, now you don't want to prolong this to another... You don't want to prolong this?
What happened, man?
I thought you wanted to do more of mining.
No, we're still playing.
I thought you loved mining.
Oh, you left some sweet, sweet experience.
Oh, wow, there's a lot here, actually.
You left all the redstone.
Oh, no, not the fucking redstone.
Oh, no.
Doki, you're still alive.
Okay, diamond armor.
You're alive.
I just took a creeper hit in the face, but like I'm...
You have a shield?
You also have a shield?
Yeah, but I have my pickaxe and torches out, but it's okay.
Oh, gosh, I'm scared to go up like this, man.
It's okay.
Everything is fine.
I took a creeper shot to the face, but it's okay.
You're fine.
Probably, it's fine.
It's probably fine.
I took two creeper hits in the face, by the way.
Why don't you use your shield?
You know what?
I'm not scared anymore.
I literally took two creeper...
I took two creeper hits in the face and I'm okay.
That's why we get the armor.
See, you were like, oh, I want to do this with iron.
No, no, no.
Look at that.
Yeah, this is why we do things with diamond armor, duh.
Yeah, but like... Oh, my God, I thought that was a creeper again.
I don't know.
I'm fucking seeing things now.
I'm seeing things, guys.
When I leave here, I'm sick of mining.
Oh, now you're sick of mining.
Maya, you're so sick of mining now.
I hate mining up.
It's boring.
Oh, my God.
I don't even know where I am.
Oh...
Witch giggles?
Oh, shit.
Okay, I might be in trouble.
Uh-oh.
Wait, are you... Do you have subtitles on?
Yeah, of course.
Oh, I should have that.
I should have that too.
Yeah, you should have that.
Where's the subtitles at?
Chat settings?
No.
I don't remember.
I don't remember, guys.
Accessibility?
Oh, there you go.
Uh-oh.
Oh, shit.
I'm in trouble.
That's a good idea.
Okay, I gotta get out of here.
Okay.
I'm at negative 42.
You're at negative 42?
I'm at 33.
I'm in a bad spot.
I'm like...
Oh, my God.
There's a witch right next to me.
Oh, shit.
Okay, am I like...
Shouldn't I be in the surface now?
I'm at 33.
You're probably... We're in the mountain.
We're still in the fucking mountain?
Probably.
Just dig to the side.
Actually, 33 is not very high.
Okay, maybe, you know...
Wait, I found... Wait, there's like...
Not found.
There's like dirt in front of me.
Oh, see?
Then you might be good.
Might be close, then.
Never mind, the dirt stopped.
The dirt stopped.
Oh, surface is at 60+.
Keep going.
Oh, God.
Fucking... Okay.
Okay, maybe I'm good.
Maybe I'm okay.
Oh, my God.
You're gonna what?
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna cry.
You won't like it when I cry.
What does that mean?
It'll be too real.
It'll be too real?
Oh, cry.
Oh, shit.
That's another room.
Oh, my God.
No.
Get me out of these stupid ass rooms.
Oh, my God.
I hear the witch still.
No!
How do you still hear the witch?
I'm trying to get out of here.
I'm like digging around.
I'm strip mining again.
Oh, diamond.
I'm trying to get out of here.
I'm trying!
Your grandchildren will live in these mines.
It's okay.
I got a lot of diamond here.
It would be a shame if you died.
You know what?
I'm just gonna build a staircase.
That'll be easier.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
Never mind.
Oh, look at that.
I see you on the surface.
I'm almost there.
I am at...
62.
Shit.
I don't want to be in here by myself.
Maybe you shouldn't have been...
Maybe you shouldn't have fucked with me, man.
Maybe you should pretend that you didn't have any diamonds on you.
You should have come found me.
You said you were going to happen.
You lied.
I keep hitting... I just keep hitting cave.
Cave, stop!
That's karma.
That's actually karma.
Little by little.
I can't always hit a cave.
Right, guys?
Little by little.
It'll be a shame.
What?
You want me to die?
I will.
Do it.
Do you want me to?
I asked you.
Do it.
No, no, no.
Come on.
I don't want to.
Oh, yeah.
See?
I fucking knew you wouldn't.
I'm a ghost.
I'm already dead.
I want to appreciate life.
You don't appreciate life.
You just want me to waste my...
Oh, I don't appreciate life.
I'm almost there.
Like, calm down.
I'm at like 20.
What number?
20.
I'm at level 20.
What?
Why are you at 20?
No, I'm at level.
I'm talking about leveling.
No, I was talking about...
I know.
I'm at level 21.
Oh my god.
Well, I was testing you.
I was actually level 22.
Okay, let's from now on...
No lying.
We're teamwork, okay?
That's a fucking lie already.
What do you mean?
No, we're teamwork.
We're teamwork.
Make the dream work.
Let's not lie, guys.
And I didn't lie.
I just didn't tell you...
how much I had.
You assumed every time.
I asked you.
I literally asked you.
You would ask me and I wouldn't say anything.
And then you would say, you still have 15.
And you're like, yeah.
And I was like, oh my god.
Okay, I think at the time though, I did have 15.
I'm at the surface.
I'm literally... I'm here.
I'm almost there.
Oh my gosh.
No, you're not.
Yes, I am.
What number?
I'm at 2.
What are you at?
Didn't you say you were at 20 earlier?
Didn't you tell me?
So you lied and...
No, I said negative 20.
Oh, I hit not big rock.
Okay, yay.
Or the regular rocks.
I still go so much faster now.
Do you have a bed on you?
A bed?
Yeah.
Okay, it's almost night.
It's night.
Yeah, you gotta sleep now.
Okay, I'll sleep.
I'll sleep.
I'm sleeping.
Why aren't you sleeping?
Oh, there you go.
I'm sleeping.
Sleep.
Also, you didn't say negative 20, by the way.
You said 20.
Doki, may I remind you, you wanted to do this collab with me.
Might I remind you, this was...
Might I remind you that you were very excited to do this.
I am.
I'm still excited.
Are you not excited?
I'm so...
You're the one who's crying.
I'm so... I'm so excited.
I'm so excited.
Let's see.
I'm at... 11.
I'm almost there.
I'm at... I was at 101 to get here.
Oh, shit.
We're on a mountain.
I'm digging probably...
You might not be, actually.
You might not be.
You might have dug further away from me.
I think... Oh, oh, wait.
What's your... What's your other... Wait.
I don't wanna go through.
What's your X and Z?
Hold on.
I think... Oh, that was water dripping.
I'm at...
Negative 3558 and 1771, but I'm having to change it.
3558.
Guys, remember that for me.
Well, I'm digging, like, not up up.
I'm digging through... I'm digging, like, what's it called?
A staircase.
Wait, what's your Z again?
No!
Guys, what's your Z, guys?
What's your Z?
My Z?
Yeah.
I don't know.
Hold on.
Uh, 1771.
Okay.
I need to go this way, then.
Yeah, you're far.
Oh, hey, there's...
No!
I threw away my bombs!
Could've grabbed a dog.
You could've grabbed a dog.
Oh, I don't... I'm afraid of towering from here.
What if there's someone up there?
Oh my God.
Oh my God, you're so far.
I'm scared.
Okay, I'll do a little bit.
Oh, I hit...
Yeah, you might not hit the mountain, because you're really far.
I am?
Yeah, you're far from where I dug up.
Okay.
Do it before they spawn?
Oh, God.
I'm trying.
I'm getting more... You know what?
I'm just gonna... It's fine.
We can do here.
First, I'll grab the iron.
I can staircase from here.
I'm heading over.
I'm heading over to where you're gonna show up.
I might be different, though, because I'm staircasing.
Are you not staircasing, like, the same direction?
I have to switch, because I just hit a big cave.
Okay, what's your number now?
I'm heading towards...
1767.
No, I'm still heading the right way.
I'm like 1767.
Okay.
Okay, you might actually dig a mountain.
Oh, you're on top of a mountain.
Am I in the mountain?
You're in the mountain.
You're in the big ass mountain.
I'm at 34.
I'm climbing.
It's 99.
You might need to get out of that.
I'm climbing.
I'm climbing, too.
Oh, shit.
Goddammit, this stupid ass cave.
You're actually...
Wait.
Oh, I see the surface, kind of.
Okay, yeah, you're literally on top of a mountain.
On top of a mountain.
All covered in cheese.
By the way, you have to dig 133 if you want to get out.
I'm at 47.
I'm close.
I'll wait for you at the top of the mountain.
Okay.
Wait, where are you at?
I'm at 1757.
Oh, my God.
1757.
Let's see.
17... Yeah, I'm at 17... What's your X again?
Negative 3579.
Are you right there?
Guys, what was the Z again?
What's the Z?
What?
Are you right on top of me?
Oh, it's okay.
I'm at 60.
I'm almost there.
I'm almost there!
Yeah, you're definitely almost there.
I'm playing the game.
Why?
Does it get higher?
Wait, what's your X and Y?
I'm not telling you anymore.
What do you mean?
You're gonna make fun of me.
I'm almost there!
I can feel it.
Yeah, you can feel it.
I'm over halfway.
What's your Y?
If I keep stopping to tell you, I won't keep digging.
Nice.
I got lots of coal.
Oh my God, this is a lot of coal.
Holy moly.
Holy coley.
Oh my gosh, there's so much coal here!
Oh my God.
There's so much coal.
Okay, I'm level 50 now.
What?
I'll give up.
Why are you giving up?
What?
I don't even need to do what I was doing.
I still have a long way to go.
I'm almost there!
Oh yeah, that's why I'm not telling you my location.
Because that's what you'll fucking do.
You'll sabotage me!
How would I sabotage you?
You already sabotaged yourself!
How did I sabotage myself?
You already sabotaged... You'll find out.
You'll find out when you get to the top.
Oh, is it night time?
No, that's not it.
That's not it.
What?
Am I underwater?
No, you'll find out.
You'll find out when you get to the top.
How much are you adding to the top of the mountain?
I don't need to.
What do you mean?
You don't even know where I am!
Yes, I do.
No, you don't!
I don't need to.
You don't even know where I am!
Alright, what's your why?
What's your why?
I'm not telling you anything because you have...
I can't do anything with the why.
You have sneaky people who are telling me...
Telling you where I'm at.
I need you to tell me where your why is.
I just need to know your why.
The why is different.
The why is what level you are at.
I'm at 90.
Alright.
Gosh, I thought I was about to fall.
What trap have you set up for me?
I have no trap!
I don't need to do any trap with what you are doing right now!
Someone came and snitched!
It's the Eragon guy again!
I have done nothing!
I'm merely just standing there!
I don't believe your lies.
I don't need to do any tricks!
Yes, you do!
No, I don't!
Do you want to know why?
I thought it would be funny if I placed more blocks above.
And then you told me you were at 30.
And do you know how high this mountain is?
It's a lot more than 30.
It's like 130.
And I didn't even say I was at 30.
Yes, you did.
And that's when I knew I didn't even have to do anything.
I'm gonna come out and you won't know where I am.
You're gonna be... Oh, I know where you are.
How do you know where I am?
I know where you are.
This entire mountain fucking covers a lot of blocks.
Yeah, but you don't know exactly where I'm gonna come out on the mountain.
Yes, I do.
Do you see my name?
I don't see you.
I don't even see your name.
Because you still have to dig!
I'm digging!
You still have a long way to go.
Guys, how much do I have to go?
How much do I... What's the top?
Where are you at?
You're the one who's just like...
I'm so tired of digging.
Please, why won't you just dig out?
Oh, and now look at you.
Look at you.
Oh, you're not even that high.
Oh my gosh.
You're so dramatic.
Yeah?
140 is not that...
It's not even that high!
I'm at 66.
I have to climb up this mountain to get to where you are.
Okay, we have an actual problem.
What's the problem?
Sleep.
So, my pickaxe just broke and I don't have a crafting table.
Do you have a bed?
Yeah, I have a bed.
Okay, put that bed down.
We have to sleep anyway.
Oh, I can only sleep at night.
Yeah, the sun is setting.
It won't let me sleep.
Not yet, it's setting!
Oh, it's not that high, she says.
By the way, I'm sleeping.
I did too.
Yeah, so I guess I'm stuck here.
Oh my god, give me your coordinates.
Oh, we're stuck here?
That's fine.
Hold on.
Saving private mint.
Wait, hold on.
I'm pretty close.
I could punch my way to freedom.
Okay, do it.
There we go, guys.
Yeah, I don't have a crafting table.
Oh, I could've just put that in there.
Oh my gosh.
TNT?
Okay, I'm gonna do the TNT method.
No!
Uh-oh.
Spooky sound.
Oh, wait.
How do I... Oh, I have the flint.
I have the flint that will make it go explode.
I swear to god.
I swear to god, if you blow up and get knocked back into your fucking hole...
I might die, but probably not.
Alright, 07s, get ready, guys.
07s.
This might end up being her fucking gravestone at this rate.
How do I... Wait, it didn't make me go up.
Oh, this sucks.
Hold on, I have to punch it into the wall.
Do you need me to save you?
I have to punch into the wall.
Do you need me to dig down?
Yeah.
Alright, what are the coordinates?
Negative 3587.
And then 1693.
Why did you...
I'll wait here.
1693.
Yeah, I went a little further.
Okay, okay, and then negative 35...
Oh my god, okay.
It's just a couple blocks.
Okay, what's your Y?
I see you.
I literally see your name.
Oh my god.
What's your Y?
Just look down, you'll see me.
I can hear you digging.
You can literally punch this dirt.
It's stone where I am.
Oh my god.
It's literally stone here.
Oh shit, oh shit.
There you go, dig up, dig up once.
Wait, can you come get me?
Can you come get me?
I made a deep hole, dig up once.
No, I'm stuck here.
How are you stuck?
Just use your hands!
Use your hands and climb up.
I digged a hole.
I can't hold on.
I was gonna explode it so that I could get through.
Hold on, hold on.
I'm coming through.
Oh, I see you, hi!
Dig up, dig up.
Hold on, I'm going up.
Oh wait, hold on.
I guess I'll leave him.
Where is it?
Is it night time?
No.
It's just dark.
I'm going, I'm going.
I'm going, oh my gosh.
This hole sucks.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Do you want me to make a better hole?
I'm sorry, but my rescue mission is not good enough for you.
Do you want to see how high this mountain is?
Look down here!
Hey, you know what?
It's good that we dug a lot.
What if we found the place that we have to put the enderpearls in?
Now we gotta get to the nether.
Yeah, now we gotta get to the nether.
I have lots of gold too.
Alright.
Oh wait, hold on.
I'm gonna burn my stuff.
I'm gonna cook my gold.
Do you have any obsidian?
I have three on me.
No, I don't have any.
Okay.
Actually, I really need to punch trees.
I'm gonna go punch this tree over here.
I'm gonna get my furnace too.
I'm gonna make some gold as well.
I'm gonna punch this tree over here.
The single tree on this mountain.
I feel like we should make like a mini house.
Like a little...
Yeah, when we find lava, we should make a mini house.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna make more than one furnace.
Fuck it.
Wait, no.
Why do I have cobbled pieces?
Oh wait, I'm so stupid.
Wait, what happened to my crafting table?
Oh, I fucking broke it.
Oh, I have another one.
I never picked it up.
I'm about to make one.
Yeah, I made another one.
I just wanted to make another furnace.
Oh, why?
Because I have a lot of stuff to burn.
Ah, me too.
I want to get rid of all of it now.
Alright, let's see.
I'm gonna throw away my iron stuff.
No, we need the iron stuff.
Yeah, you can throw away your stuff.
But we need the...
Yeah, I need my iron sword.
We need the actual iron though.
Why?
For shields.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And water buckets.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm planning on doing that.
Wow, the daylight.
Smells good, Aria.
Wow.
I forgot what that looked like for a sec.
Someone just said, set a spawn point.
That's so funny.
I think they forgot what hardcore meant.
Yeah.
We're never coming back here.
I guess I can make this.
I think I can make this.
Well, I can make a lapis blocker, right, guys?
I would actually have enough for a lapis.
I have two stacks though, so it's not like...
Of lapis?
I have three stacks.
I have tons of lapis.
How much is a block?
Lapis block.
It still takes two.
Okay, I don't need these two lapis.
Here, give me the lapis.
Here, here, have the two.
Oh wait, I still don't have enough either.
Yeah, that's why I was thinking like, oh, it's no point.
Are you okay?
No.
What else is around here?
I'm not okay.
Did you find any villages while you were waiting?
No, I just waited on the mountain.
No, I didn't see any villages while I was waiting for you.
Oh, this isn't a house.
This is you trying to trap me in the mountain.
Yeah, and then I gave up because I realized how high up you were.
I was like, there's no point.
There's no point doing this.
There's a point to everything.
No, there's not.
Minecraft.
Oh my gosh.
I almost fell in lava.
Oh wait, we need that.
Okay, I'm gonna make a bucket then.
Oh yeah, yeah.
There's some lava here.
Wait, actually, no, we don't need...
Do we... I mean, we can do it in the ocean.
Do what in the ocean?
Actually, no.
Actually, I'll grab water.
Wouldn't it be easier to just get water?
Well, you have to... So you have to make it... It's like...
You have to make it a certain way so that it actually turns into obsidian and not into cobblestone.
Well, if it's like lava itself...
Wait, where are you?
Are you gonna make the lava?
We need a lava pool.
So like, I can get water and then...
But we still need lava regardless.
We need to make like... Yeah, no, we can use the lava pool to do it.
Here, I'll get this lava.
So I just need the water.
Yeah, but we need lava for protection in the nether.
What?
Why don't we just mine the obsidian?
I mean, if we get the pool, then we can mine the obsidian.
No, it'd be easier to just...
Yeah.
Make it... We just pour water to get the bottom first.
And then mine and create the...
What?
Okay, let me grab water first.
And then I'll just pour water in it...
And then mine it and then we just build off the three blocks...
To make the thing.
Okay, you'll understand when I do it.
We need water first.
Yeah, that's kinda hard to get on top of a mountain.
Yeah, but the lava pool is... I can just climb back up.
What else do I need?
Oh, let me just get the...
I'll just burn the rabbit meat now.
You know that if... Okay, so...
You know how to make it stop being flowing lava?
Well, if it's... The lava block itself.
If the lava is like the main source, then it should be fine.
Why don't we just find a lava pool and then mine from it then?
Isn't that the lava pool?
Didn't you say there's a lava pool back there?
No, it was like a little tiny thing of lava.
That's it.
Oh, okay, nevermind.
Oh my gosh, you may have seen like...
No!
I didn't see anything!
See, I just said, oh!
Yo, this is miscommunication from somebody.
Somebody?
I wonder who.
Yeah, I wonder who.
I wonder who's fucking gave me the wrong information.
I don't know, buddy.
Who could it be?
I mean, we could go back into the mines and then we'd...
No, we're not going... No.
We're not going back into the mines.
Oh, let's sleep.
Oh, that's my bed!
That's my bed!
No, it's not!
I don't have a bed now!
Get out of my bed!
There we go.
Oh my God.
Why do you have a blue bed?
Because I wanted a blue bed.
Well, I called dibs on this color for...
I saw you take it.
I literally saw you take it.
This is why we can't have nice things.
This is exactly why we can't have nice things.
Okay, we're gonna go find...
We're gonna go find a lava pit.
There's tons of them in this forest.
In these types of forests.
There should be.
Yeah.
Alright.
Oh, look!
That looks like lava down there.
Where?
In that big, big cave.
I'm not gonna go to the cave to make the fucking nether stuff.
Why not?
My God, do you wanna die?
What do you mean, why not?
Oh, don't go that way.
That's how you die!
Hold on.
Oh my God, you're...
Just fall down.
We literally have diamond armor.
I don't wanna take any damage.
I don't wanna damage my armor at all.
Just fall down.
We have...
We can repair it.
We have so much diamonds to repair it.
No, I'm not wasting my diamonds to repair it.
We gotta get mending, maybe.
We're not gonna have time to get mending!
Why not?
Oh my God, we're gonna have to find books!
Yeah, that's the point.
We gotta...
That's the point of the lapis!
Okay, alright.
We gotta get at least, like, the projectile stuff.
And we gotta also get...
Slow falling potions...
And we gotta get here.
Oh, I left my bow.
Aw, man.
Oh my God, there's trees everywhere.
There's trees everywhere.
There weren't trees in the caves!
There's trees everywhere right now.
I'm literally farming trees now.
I'm still in the caves, mentally.
No, the cave madness.
She's just standing there.
Why is she just standing there?
I'm mentally in the caves.
I was switching my items, my God!
Oh, there's pillagers here.
What?
Where?
Right behind me.
Where are you?
Wait, where did you go?
I'm literally...
Where are you?
Wait, where are you?
See?
This is why we can't make a good team!
There you go.
Okay, here we go.
Watch out, he's right behind you.
Just come at me here.
Just run!
It doesn't matter!
Don't kill him!
Run, run, run, run!
Run away!
Don't kill him!
I know, he'll start the raid.
Yeah, we have to not have a raid happen.
Okay, wait.
Give me a second.
I need to put my shield on.
Oh my God, he's coming for me.
Oh my God, they're coming for me!
Wait, where did my...
Where did my diamond sword go?
Where did your diamond sword...
Did you not make one?
No, I did.
Oh my God, they're still coming for me.
Wait...
Did I throw it away?
Did you throw it away?
Okay.
I think I...
Oh, I never made one because I made my pickaxe.
I'm just gonna kill him.
I'll drink milk!
I'll drink milk.
He dropped something.
Wait, what was the potion he dropped?
Bad Omen 3, you can drink that.
Bad Omen 3?
You have more experience with that.
Wait, you have a bad omen now?
No, I gave it to you.
Wait, you drink it?
Oh, it's not like automatic now?
Interesting.
You don't get bad omen from killing anymore.
What?
That's crazy.
Yeah, you dropped it as a potion.
You're the one that killed it.
No, I saw that.
No, but you picked up the potion.
That's why I asked you what did he drop.
What the heck?
Oh, interesting.
Wait, what was your plan again?
Oh yeah, to find lava pool.
Yeah.
Where's your fucking cocoa beans?
I'm gonna go this way.
I feel like...
Wait, we should... Where are you?
I'm in the water.
Wait, where did you go?
Did you go in the jungle?
I'm not in the jungle!
Oh, there I see you.
I was gonna go that way too.
That's why I was like, wait a second.
Apparently, it's for use in the tricky trial dungeon.
Whatever that means.
That's the trial dungeon, right?
The thing I talked about before?
Oh, it's that?
Wait, what is that?
You have to make the sword.
Well, how do we use it in that?
Yeah, what does that even mean?
Oh my god, rip everybody's farms.
I see a village!
We don't need a village anymore, right?
Oh wait, nevermind, it's not a village.
It's a nether portal!
Oh, we can use that!
We can use that to make it!
Use that to make the thing.
Just take away the corrupted areas.
Yeah, yeah.
And you have your flint, right?
Yeah.
Okay, alright, we can do this.
Oh wow, it's almost nearly complete too.
Okay, we can do this.
Get the corrupted... Oh wait, we just need one!
We just need one!
Wait, I...
Wait, I have one, I have one, I have one.
There you go.
Oh my god.
I don't think there's any corrupted areas too.
Wait, I think it's not corrupted!
Yeah, I think we're good.
Okay, lighting up.
Okay, let's put... I'm gonna make another chest.
I feel like, just put away stuff we don't wanna take to the nether.
Uh, I don't know.
I'm gonna put a crafting table here, chest.
I'm gonna make another chest for us.
Get rid of this.
Um, I don't think... Okay, I'm gonna make some...
Make a gold helmet?
Yeah, yeah, that's what I'm gonna make, but I wanna make some...
I'm gonna make some bread.
And then...
There we go.
I still have a name tag.
I wanna name something.
You can just put it in the chest.
Okay.
I'll put the stuff I don't need in the chest.
We don't need all that coal.
We don't need all this flint.
We don't need the lapis.
I don't trust you with my diamonds, so I'm gonna put it in my inventory.
Hey!
I mean, what?
What's gonna happen if we die?
We're not... Don't say that.
That's what I'm saying, though.
You were like, oh, I'm just gonna put my diamond in my chest.
Why?
Because if we die, we die.
Because if we come back and then my diamond is gone, then I know why.
No, but the only reason you put your diamond away is if you die.
No, the only reason I put my diamond away is because I don't want you to fucking take it from this random chest.
Oh my god, you're dying...
Doki comprehension is not comprehending.
Oh my god.
Alright, are you ready to go into the nether?
Yeah, I'm ready.
Get a pickaxe?
Wait, why?
Hi, we didn't have a pickaxe.
I don't have one, actually.
What happened to your...
Mine died, remember?
Oh yeah, because you broke it.
Hey, I was using that!
Oh.
Whoops.
Okay.
Alright, so from here, now we have to...
We find...
We survive.
We have to get blazer arms.
Oh gosh.
Yeah, we gotta survive and...
Alright, I have some...
Wait, we gotta feed pigs too for enderpearls.
Yeah.
How many enderpearls do we need?
Um, we can...
It really depends on how many you need.
Chat, how many enderpearls do we need?
We need 12, but how many is it 14 safe?
14, okay.
At least 12.
Take a diamond one?
Okay.
Diamond pickaxe.
Oh, wait, hold on.
Stop pushing me!
I didn't know that.
I literally can see you pushing me.
Stop...
Alright, are you ready?
Yeah.
Here I go.
I'm going in.
Alright, I'm going in too.
Please don't be a jungle.
Okay, could be worse.
It's not that bad.
This could be worse.
I see chicken.
How did you get a chicken in here?
How did a chicken get in here?
Are you taking the court?
Yeah, I want the experience.
True.
Okay, be careful.
Oh my god.
How did he get the chicken in here?
I know, I'm like thinking...
Wait, there's blue fires now?
Yeah.
What does blue fire mean?
That's like a different biome.
That's the soul fire.
On the soul sand.
Okay.
There's no hoglins around here.
But we maybe should...
I don't know what to do first.
I'm just gonna go this way.
Where did you go?
Up?
Up!
Oh, you're going up that way?
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know, I just feel safer going up.
Wait, that's the chicken.
Where are you?
Oh, no, I see you.
Yeah, I'm here.
I guess chickens were originally in hell.
Sounds about right.
Yeah.
Birds are from hell.
That's a fellow bird.
I agree.
I know.
Alright, I got the nug... Oh, there's a strider down there.
We don't need him.
He can live here for all I care.
Yeah.
I'm sure he wants to, otherwise.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like, when you take him out...
Oh, there he is!
There's a pig, pig!
It's time to feed you.
Okay, take...
Take the gold!
Let him observe, let him observe.
Observe?
Oh, no, the guy's over there.
Oh, oh, oh, what did I get?
I got obsidian.
I got three obsidian.
That's cool.
It's not like we don't need that anymore.
Oh, he's taking it, he's taking it, he's taking it.
There's another guy up there.
I'll go to him with mine.
Yeah, you go to him.
I'll feed this guy.
Yeah.
Oh, my gosh.
He gave me... What the fuck did he... He gave me gravel?
I gave you gold, sir!
And you gave me gravel?
I'm scared.
He gave me fire... Oh, my God, he's useless.
Oh, my God, I hear a ghast.
No, no, no, Doki, I hear a ghast!
Oh, he's right near me, he's next to me, he's next to me, he's next to me.
I try to ping, I try to ping.
I press middle mouse button.
Oh, he's looking at me.
Oh, God, what do we do?
Oh, he's right by this... by our... by our...
portal, even.
What an asshole.
What the hell did he give me?
He gave me leather?
Your guy sucks.
I'm gonna go talk to this...
Oh, did he give you anything good?
I haven't talked to him yet because of the... the ghast.
Okay, come here.
Hey, come here.
Oh, my God, ghast.
He keeps giving me blackstone.
What are you gonna give me?
I keep getting gravel and blackstone.
Oh, he gave me boots.
Enchanted boots.
I don't... Oh, whoops.
Please!
I don't need this.
I need this.
Oh, what the hell?
He just took my... the boots and put them on.
He stole your...
He stole the boots.
Oh, I got nether... Oh, you don't need nether bricks either.
Hey, hey, hey, come here, come here.
Yeah, yeah, take that.
I got fucking... Oh, my God, give me something good.
I don't need blackstone.
How is this big?
Spectral arrows!
I got that too.
That should be...
This is the worst gacha I ever had.
Oh, I got iron boots.
He gave me fucking iron boots.
Soul speed, okay.
I'm just gonna give him the whole thing.
Here you go.
Here, take it, take it, take it.
I'm losing the gacha right now.
I'm not doing well with this gacha.
I'm not...
I'm ditching this one.
I'll give it...
Do you have better gacha?
What did he just give me?
I can't tell.
My inventory is full.
Oh, golden axe.
Do you have better gacha?
You gave me string?!
Here's my last gold.
What is he looking at?
Oh, I gave him a gold!
Oh, my gosh.
Did he just drop it?
What did he do?
What did he give me?
I gave him...
He gave me another stack of string.
He's giving me corpse.
This is kind of bad, Doki.
I think we're in trouble.
I got some soul sand.
Come here, come here.
I didn't get anything.
Oh, God.
Oh, shit!
He came out of nowhere!
I see him.
Oh, my God.
Oh, there's two of them!
There's two of them!
They're looking at you.
Sir, I have one more gold.
Sir, please.
Oh, my God.
Please, please.
I have one more gold.
The spectral arrows!
Please, just one ender pearl, please.
I have my last...
I don't have any...
Why gravel?
I don't have a bow.
Why?
Do you think he'll see me if I go down there?
Oh, my God.
Wait, where are you?
I'm afraid to deflect.
I'm afraid to deflect it.
OK, come here.
What's the status?
Come here.
I'm a little scared.
Of what?
Of dying.
Oh, me too.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna die.
Toki.
Toki, I think I'm dead.
I think I'm dead, boy.
OK.
I'm just on fire a little bit.
Oh, God.
I'm OK.
I would be so sad.
How do we deflect them again?
You just hit it with your sword.
OK.
Like you're playing b-ball.
I mean, baseball, not b-ball.
I can do this.
Alright.
Why are you scared of deflecting?
Because I'm not good at it.
I've only done it once.
OK, I'm ready.
Look at me.
Why is he always looking at you and not me?
Where are you?
Oh, I see him.
Yeah, he's right there, but he's not looking at me.
Because... I don't know.
Wait, we didn't get the portal... OK, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
Portal coordinates.
No, I got the portal coordinates.
Yeah, I screenshoted it.
How do we want to go?
Where do we go?
It's literally right down there.
No, no, no.
I meant like where do we go to try to find the fortress?
Wherever we can... I don't know.
Fortresses are random.
We just got... Wait, I think I see one right over there.
Wait, really?
Unless that's just built strangely.
Let's just go.
Let's just check it out.
Yeah, let's go.
Also get magma cubes because we need...
We need magma stuff for...
For what?
For potions.
Oh my gosh.
Get out of the way, Piggy.
Get out of the way.
I have a fire charge.
How many fire charges do we need?
No, it's magma.
It's not fire charge.
It's a magma slime.
Ouch!
Who hit me?
Not me.
Ouch!
I think it's the... I think it's the little... It's the magma.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They hit you back.
OK, I give up.
The guy is too close.
Alright, so if we go over this way...
Where did you go?
Follow me.
Oh, up here, up here.
We're going around.
We're going around this lava.
Alright.
We're going around it.
Just go up it.
Be careful of the other lava, though.
Here we go.
Why are we so close to that lava?
Why do we have to...
be right next to it?
I don't know.
We don't have to be next to it, so why are we doing that?
I don't think it's fine.
You're getting closer to the lava than me.
Oh my god, this pig is right on you.
Oh my god, leave us alone!
He's our biggest fan.
Where are you going?
You're supposed to...
No, we're going up.
I am already up.
What do you mean?
I'm up.
What are you doing?
Where are you?
Just kidding.
So I'm doing the wrong thing, I guess.
My fire texture looks really weird.
Oh, I guess I was doing the wrong thing.
You were doing the wrong thing.
Oh, I think I didn't actually see one.
Maybe it was just a strange texture.
No, I thought it was one in the distance.
Is that not it?
What is that over there?
What?
Oh, it's just like little trees.
Yeah, we don't wanna go in there, though.
Why?
Oh, that's where the big pigs are, right?
Yeah, we hate those guys.
Okay, okay, okay.
We'll just go back here.
Okay.
We might as well.
Yeah.
Like, there's no other way to go.
We'll grab some mushrooms in case.
Is there any pigs around?
I'm gonna grab this gold.
And we can do more mining.
I'm checking.
Watch my back.
I'm watching.
There's nothing here.
Okay.
There's literally nobody next to you.
You're so safe.
Okay.
You're so safe right now.
Alright.
Cool.
What can I throw away?
Soul speed, go away.
Do we need soul sand?
We don't, right?
Okay, I'm gonna throw away the gravel...
and the crying obsidian.
Hey, why were you so far away?
What the hell, man?
What do you mean?
I was scouting you out.
I had to be high ground.
Oh, there's gold right here.
Nice.
Watch out!
No, no, no.
Oh, okay.
What?
It's not the... Okay.
The zombie guys are safe.
It's just the normal guys.
Wait, do they get mad if I farm their gold?
Yeah, they get jealous.
Wait, they do?
No, they don't.
Oh, we can get...
Hey, what the fuck, man?
Grab a blue mushroom.
Wait, what for?
We can also probably... They scare away the big hogs.
Oh, they do?
Yeah.
See?
You're a Minecraft expert.
We can also probably...
How do they scare them away?
Do we just take it out and be like...
Yeah, you like put it on the ground.
Oh, really?
But Warp Forest is good.
This is where all the Endermen are.
We can just farm Endermen here.
Where are they?
I see one.
Look at it.
Look at it right now.
But he's gonna come for me.
He's gonna come for me.
Where is he?
I'm gonna look at him.
Do you see him?
How can you not see him?
I'm literally looking at him.
He's not angry.
Look at him closer.
Okay.
Maybe let's build a little house.
Hold on.
He's not angry.
Hold on, I'm gonna build something.
I'm gonna build something for us to...
Look at me!
Look at me right now!
Yeah, I'm looking at you.
Do you think this is good enough?
Oh my god.
Get under here, Doki!
Get under here!
Yeah, now we kill.
Now we kill.
Oh, I looked it in his eyes.
He was not happy.
You guys, I got the portal coordinates.
I don't know why you guys are like...
Oh, rip the portal coordinates.
I literally got them.
Alright, we did it.
See, I ain't no coward.
Did you grab the...
No, he didn't drop any.
Oh, shit.
I wish we had fortune.
He didn't drop any.
Don't fall.
Don't fall here.
Oh, there was a hole right there.
I know.
This is kind of a bad spot.
Hold on, I'm gonna pick up shop.
Pick up shop?
We're gonna move shop.
Yeah, we're gonna move shop.
I'm gonna go this way.
Maybe we should have got fire resistance before we did this.
Oh, yeah.
I told you.
Where did you go?
Make a shop.
There's so many Endermen here.
Shop where?
I see two.
It's shop time.
Shop time.
This is it.
This is where we set up the family business.
Let me know when to look.
Don't look yet.
I'm gonna look.
That's your... If you feel safe.
Where's the second one?
Oh, there he is.
Oh, I see one.
Oh, my God.
We're so...
Oh, God.
Doki?
Where did he go?
He's dead.
He killed him.
Okay.
I got a little worried.
Now we have to worry about a ghast too.
This is not the place to set up shop.
Oh, my God.
I hear him crying.
Why did you do it again?
But there's literally a ghast on the run.
I'm gonna look at him.
I'm gonna do it.
Where is the ghast?
He's like all the way over there.
How do we make a bow?
Do we have enough stuff for it?
I have string.
Hold on.
A boat or a bow?
A bow.
I can!
Oh, my gosh.
I can.
Oh, my God!
Yes!
Okay.
Am I looking at him?
Oh, I have no arrows though.
Okay.
Do something about it.
I don't know.
Where did he go?
Oh, he's not happy.
Kill him.
Just stay under the rocks.
He'll come back.
He's just staring at me.
Oh, my spectral arrows.
That's right.
Oh, I have so many.
Hello.
You guys are so smart.
What you gonna do?
Pussy?
Yeah, that's right.
What you gonna do?
Nothing.
Yeah, that's right.
He's stuck there.
Was he actually stuck?
Yeah, he's stuck down there.
Oh, dummy.
Wow.
Yeah, stupid.
Where did he go?
Wait, wait.
Uh-oh.
I hear the gas again.
I don't see him.
I don't either.
The guy has 20-20 vision.
Oh, my God.
He's right here.
Get him, Ducky!
That's spooky.
What you gonna do?
Nothing.
Why aren't you under the 2x2?
Say under the 2x2.
Oh, he's right here.
He's on it!
Fill in the hole!
I thought you said you were safe!
You liar!
No, you were leaving the hole!
I got in your prayer.
Okay, nice.
Our first ender pearl, everybody!
We got our first ender pearl!
Our first ender pearl!
Oh, my God.
How do people make this look so easy?
Let's figure this out.
Okay.
I don't know where that ghastly is and it's scaring me.
Stop calling it ghastly.
I like ghastlies.
I don't like these guys.
You see the Minecraft movie version of them?
No.
Oh, wait.
Maybe I did.
I don't remember.
They have, like, hair.
Ew!
They're, like, made out of skin and stuff.
Shut up, guys.
Okay, you wanna see?
Wait, let me...
Yeah.
You can't pause the game in Minecraft.
Don't use these blocks.
They suck.
Why not?
Because if a ghast gets us, they can blow them up.
They can't blow up other things.
They can't blow up clobble.
Yeah, clobble.
Okay, look.
I have one.
Okay.
Hey, what the hell?
What about me?
I'm trying to find the ghast.
Oh, my God.
Minecraft movie ghast.
Ghast.
This is what they look like.
They look so ugly.
They're, like...
Oh, my God.
I hear another one.
Skin and, like, hair.
And it looks so weird.
Did you send it to me?
No, not yet.
I'm trying to find Discord.
Oh, my God.
Where did my Discord go?
He sounds so close.
Oh, wait.
Here it is.
Oh, my God.
I see him.
He's really close.
Oh, my God.
If we were still over there, we would be dead-dead.
Alright, this is what they look like.
Hold on.
I'm trying to fight this guy.
Wait, you're fighting?
Oh, he's too far.
What the hell?
Wait, where are you?
I'm right here.
I'm right next to you.
You're not.
Ew!
Wait.
Oh, my God.
Why'd they make them look like that?
They're made of skin.
Skin.
It's skin and there's, like, a little bit of hair on it.
Okay, so the gas is, like, where I'm looking.
It's, like, that direction.
Oh, we don't have to look there.
We can just go forward.
He might have despawned.
He made the bridge.
We might as well just go forward.
We'll find more Endermen.
Where are the Endermen?
Oh, I see one.
I see one.
We're setting up shop.
Set up shop.
Set up the shop.
Wait, where did you see him?
Where is he?
They're all over there.
I'm looking.
Do you see him?
Disappeared.
Oh, no.
He's right there.
I'm looking.
I'm looking right at him.
I think I got him.
Alright, nice.
This is so dumb.
Another one!
Nice!
Nice.
You said there's another one here?
I thought I saw one.
I thought I saw two.
No, there's one.
Oh, you guys wanna see the ugly thing?
Hold on.
Just Google Minecraft movie gas.
Yeah, I'll save it.
I'll risk my life for you guys.
My life in Minecraft.
Okay, I'm gonna go find another Enderman.
What?
Setting up shop.
Oh, the shop is set up?
The shop is set up.
I found two.
I'm gonna eat meat before I look.
Gotta be hungry first.
Yeah, I'm looking at you.
Yeah, that's right.
I'm looking at you.
What you gonna do?
Yeah, what you gonna do?
I ain't scared.
I'm gonna look into your eyes.
Why isn't it aggroing?
Alright guys, this is what they look like in the movie.
Wait.
Nasty.
I'm looking.
You.
Nasty.
Yeah, I'm looking at you.
I think you're ugly.
That's right.
Oh, oh, I see you.
He baited me!
There you go.
He ran away and then ran.
Oh, ouch, ouch.
He baited a 360 at me.
Oh, he dropped one too.
He dropped one.
I got three.
Nice.
Okay.
I can't tell if I aggroed that one or if she did.
I can't tell either.
Wait, there was two.
The other guy despawned.
No.
I'll look around too.
There's two here.
Nice.
Okay, I'm gonna keep that shop.
Keep the shop is set up.
Shop is set up.
Let's keep it.
It's like our little food truck.
Yeah.
As soon as you see one, just run.
Look and run back to shop.
Is he following me?
I turned around!
Oh my God.
Oh, I almost ran the wrong way.
Oh my God, is he chasing me?
Never look back.
Did he drop one?
He got four.
Yeah, he dropped one.
We're getting lucky.
Nice.
Oh, I see one.
Oh my God.
Run!
Come here.
Drop your goods.
Run by!
I don't know if...
He didn't.
Oh, come on.
It's just me.
Oh my God.
That guy looked at me and then he like...
Oh, it's probably because he was aggroed on me.
The other guy.
I found another Enderman.
So far, not so bad though.
Don't look back.
Oh, I see him.
I see him.
He's coming.
Don't look back.
Oh, he's going.
Yeah!
Get his ass!
You're in the wrong neighborhood!
Yeah!
We'll take you out.
Nothing?
Oh, come on.
No, he was broke.
Okay, I need to stop attacking him because clearly...
He was fucking broke.
Watch out because there's a really big drop here.
Look in the trees too, but...
Oh, yeah.
I'm way too confident with jumping around.
I know.
I'm like, whoa, there's no holes here.
Oh, I think that's just a normal Skelly.
Oh, wait.
Or is that an Enderman up there?
Oh, that's an Enderman.
Do you think... Is it too far?
Look at him.
Look him in the eye and ask if it's too far.
Oh, he disappeared.
Oh, maybe it was too far.
He was really far away.
It's a 50% chance to drop.
Oh, wait.
I see him.
Where?
Oh, I see him too.
He's really far.
I see all the way over there.
I think it's too far for me.
I don't think he wants to play with us.
No.
What is that?
What?
Was that ambiance or is that an Enderman?
I don't see any near us.
I heard something.
Let's just move on from here and see if we can find a fortress.
But we need the Enderpearls.
Yeah, but we're gonna find more.
We'll find more Endermans later.
This is the Enderman place.
The fortress is more harder.
Like, if we survive the fortress, then it's fine.
Like, if we spend all our time trying to get...
No, wait.
I think we actually...
No, I think we need to leave and get the fire potions before we go to the fortress.
Okay.
I think that's our best plan of action.
You're right.
No, you're 100% right there.
I thought about it.
I was like, no, I think we're gonna fall into...
I think we're gonna fall in that lava.
And what do we need for fire potions?
We need the magma cubes, but we might be able to, like...
Oh, we can leave that.
Wait, but how do we find the magma cubes?
Oh my God, there's a ghast.
Be careful.
I'm gonna deflect him.
Watch this.
Okay, do it.
I'm gonna watch this.
But if he hits you and, like, you don't deflect...
And, like, it explodes around you, you might fall into the lava.
Oh, shit.
I won't watch this.
Do it.
Okay, um...
I thought you said just hit it!
You do!
I don't think so.
Okay, why don't we stand together and maybe one of us will hit it.
I don't wanna try that.
I wanna go.
You know what?
I think I can do it.
Just trade with the pigs.
Have you... Oh wait, I actually still have more gold.
Hold on, let me try trading.
Wait, I do too.
I do too.
Yeah, let's keep trading.
I can craft.
Come here.
I'm gonna craft my gold.
Oh yeah, here.
I have 50.
Take these.
Take those.
Yeah, I have some too.
I'm crafting too.
What did he give me?
I don't even know.
Oh, I think he gave me soul sand.
Here, take that.
Take that.
Mister.
Blackstone.
I'm crafting.
Wait, did he steal the nuggets?
Or did you get them?
No, I got them.
I got them.
Okay, okay, okay.
Alright, gotcha time.
Wait, why didn't he... He didn't give me anything.
Unless you took it.
Did I take it?
I don't know.
I don't know what I have in here.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't think it was that.
Okay, he's giving me gravel.
Gravel?
He's giving me fucking gravel.
What else?
Wait, wait, wait.
I got soul speed 3.
What the fuck am I gonna do with soul speed 3?
Yeah, he gave me that too.
This sucks.
Hey, throw them over here mister.
Don't look that way.
Oh my god, I hear another... I hear another gas.
He got me... He gave me more...
Oh shit!
Oh,
you did it!
I did it!
Was that cool or not?
That was pretty cool.
Gosh, I can do it again.
Hold on, there's two of them.
There's two of them.
Do it!
Yeah, that's fucking right.
Oh, he can't aim.
He can't aim.
Oh, he can aim.
He can aim.
Oh, he's aiming at you.
Oh shit!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
What if I try?
I'm gonna gotcha.
Did you hit it?
No.
I don't think you hit it.
I didn't.
I wasn't ready for it.
What did he give me?
I can't see.
Oh, this is like all destroyed.
What is that?
Oh, it's iron nuggets.
That's fine.
Oh, wait, is that netherite bricks?
No, is it iron bricks?
Or the...
Just the...
What is that?
Oh, it's nether brick!
Wait, that's good!
Wait, he actually gave you nether brick?
Yeah!
Oh, nice call.
I hit him big!
I gotcha!
Isn't nether bricks good?
Yeah, that's what you need to make the netherite.
Yeah, isn't it?
Yeah!
Oh, no, it's not.
You're fucking with me.
Oh, it's not.
It's nether brick.
Oh, I thought you meant it was netherite brick.
Oh, I thought it was nether... I thought that meant netherite because it says nether in it.
So I was like, oh, that's cool.
You wanna find another guy?
Yeah.
Let's go find another guy.
His payout, his gotcha rates were a little too high.
Yeah, a little too high.
A little too low.
Oh, there's a guy over here.
There's a guy here.
Hey, hey, hey!
Come here!
Hey!
Yeah, that's right.
Come down here.
Go buy gravel.
Yeah, work for us.
Go, take the gold.
Yeah, take that.
Take that gold.
What'd he give?
What'd he give me?
Sometimes I don't know.
I know.
Sometimes I can't tell what I'm already holding.
That's gravel?
I don't want that.
Oh, I got the nether brick.
The elusive nether brick.
Yeah, that's the one I threw away.
Yeah.
I got more gold here though.
Gold nuggets.
Oh, don't do it in front of him!
Don't do it in front of him, he'll get angry.
No, he didn't.
He didn't look.
Oh, I think it's because he's busy with the...
Yeah, as long as I throw it in front of...
Come on.
I wanna kill him so bad.
Oh, I got...
It's a fire potion!
Yeah, fire resistance!
I got fire resistance!
Nice!
What'd he give you?
Obsidian.
Okay.
That's more gravel.
Alright, we got fire resistance.
Oh my God.
Alright, let's head back.
Okay, yeah.
So we need to kill magma cubes, but we can't kill them though.
Like, we need to find magma cubes for more fire resistance.
Unless we find for more gold.
And just keep gacha-ing.
That might be an option, yeah.
I feel like magma cubes are harder for fire resistance.
For where we spawned in?
Yeah, maybe.
Might just be easier.
Time to just gacha.
I love gacha.
I love...
Wait, where did I leave my chest?
Oh, over here.
We need the warts too.
The blue ones?
The blue mushrooms, we need those.
I threw away my mushrooms.
We need a lot of blaze rods.
Wait, why did you throw away your mushrooms?
Because I didn't know we needed it.
Yeah!
We need them!
Okay, I'll go back in.
It's right there.
It's right there, I'll go in.
I'll go in, it's right there.
Chill out.
I might be able to kill some more endermen on the way.
Like that guy.
Come here.
Come here, stupid.
Wait, did you get trapped down there?
Oh no, he's not.
What about you?
I'm just throwing away stuff right now.
We don't need obsidian anymore, right?
I don't think so.
Okay, goodbye obsidian.
Wait, chat, we don't need obsidian anymore, right?
I don't know why I asked you.
Nether warts are from the fortress.
Oh my gosh, I'm not doing very well with these.
Oh, enchanting tables.
Wait, we need an enchanting table for obsidian?
Oh yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
I should listen to you.
Listening to chat was a good idea.
I can't English anymore.
Every single enderman I've killed has not dropped anything!
My mind is mush right now.
Alright, picky.
It's time to let's go gambling!
Let's go gambling!
I don't know where it's at.
Where, where, where?
Don't do this to me.
Why are you still pondering?
Oh my God, he's right there!
Are you kidding me?
Grab the gold.
Oh, what the fuck?
Oh my God, he just fucking keeled over in front of me.
I kill him.
Dang it.
Oh, I got a tear.
I don't think so, do we guys?
Another guy?
I hate...
Ghasts.
I hate them.
Where'd that guy go?
Goodbye.
He gave me two stacks of gravel?
That fucking bitch.
He sucks, he sucks.
Oh, I'm out of space.
Oh, okay.
There we go.
What if I just take this gold in front of you?
Oh, come here, come here, come here.
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
Oh my God, you do get mad.
You do get mad when you take gold in front of them.
I told you!
I know, but I didn't believe you!
Oh my God, they're all gonna keep attacking us now.
No!
Just this one guy.
I think if you kill them in front, or not in front of other guys, then they don't notice.
No, I didn't touch him, I didn't touch him.
Okay, okay.
We should be good then.
I called your bluff and I was wrong.
Why would I be wrong?
I don't know.
Sometimes you're wrong.
Yeah, I'm never wrong.
Oh, that's a lie right there.
Oh wait, these are the wrong ones.
Okay, I need...
It's these guys?
Actually, it doesn't hurt to have more of them, I suppose.
Let's go gambling!
Okay, I'm gonna give it to that one guy that didn't like me.
Because I'm gonna bribe him, so he'll like me.
Yeah, yeah.
Alright, here you go.
Do you like me now?
See, he likes me now.
I see a magma cube!
If I can get down there...
Hey, come here.
Oh no, he stopped...
Oh no, I'm sorry, I'm so sorry!
I didn't know!
I knew, I did it again, I did it again, I did it again!
What the hell?!
I went gambling!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Gambling with your life...
Oh, I got an ender pearl!
Yay!
I don't know why I keep gambling.
I have a problem.
You're addicted to the thrill.
Okay, there's a bunch of little endermen around here now, so...
I'll keep getting them.
Yeah, yeah, while you keep doing that, I'm gonna keep gambling.
Okay, I have some more gold.
I have a problem now.
I have enough.
Come here, come here.
You too.
Yeah, yeah.
Both of you.
Oh no!
Wait, what happened?
I knocked the enderman off the side and I think you fell into the lava.
You did this.
You killed somebody today.
Wait, it says enderman screams.
He's still around somewhere.
Enderman?
Let's go gambling!
Let's go gambling.
Oh, he's down there yelling at me.
Oh my god.
He's alive.
He knows what you did last summer.
Come on, what else do you have?
What do I have?
Oh, it teleports before it hits lava.
Oh, okay.
Alright, well, come here.
I want more gold piece.
Come on, I know you're rich.
I see what you're wearing.
I know you have the money.
Don't be... Don't be holding out on me.
Goddammit, he gave me fucking leather.
He held out on me.
Both of our gotcha luck is so bad.
Mine is usually this bad.
Well, I did get fire... Well, I did get fire resistance, so...
I don't know.
I got one pearl.
Here, I'm gonna give it to you.
Hold on to it.
Where are you?
Okay, we have five now.
Yeah.
Five out of how many?
And here is more gold.
Oh, we don't need books.
Guys, we can just get it by farming the...
the fortress.
The big fortress.
What are you talking about?
They're saying we need books for enchanting table, but we don't need it.
Yes, actually, we kind of do.
Okay, well, I dropped like seven stacks of...
I think like a stack of leather.
Whatever.
Into the flames.
So, we don't anymore.
We don't need them anymore.
I got another enderman.
I baited you.
I baited you into my trap.
Oh my god.
Why did you have to fall?
Goodbye, soul sand.
I don't need you.
Stronghold library?
Oh yeah, well...
Yeah, that's what I mean.
That's what I mean.
We'll make strong...
We'll get the books from the stronghold.
True, true, true.
We don't need the leather for it.
Strongholds are not scary.
How long is your potion for?
Three minutes.
Okay.
That should be enough.
Well, we still need...
What do we need for the slow falling, everybody?
What do we need for the slow falling?
Oh, that guy disappeared.
For real.
What happened to him?
He gave me another bricks again.
Oh, phantom!
Phantom!
Okay, so we have to not sleep, okay.
Oh, okay.
That's fine.
Yeah, that's fine.
And we stay up for the endermen too.
Maybe we'll buy more endermen.
Maybe, yeah.
Or we die by skelly or creeper or...
There's no way we die.
We have like...
We have...
We're full diamond...
Oh my god.
I'm sorry, my brain is not working.
We're full diamond armor.
You okay?
You're losing it, you're losing it.
I'm not losing it.
You're really losing it.
I'm fucking losing it.
I'm gonna jump into the lava.
Someone stop me.
I'm fucking heading straight to the lava.
I'm gonna take the jump.
Don't do it!
I'm gonna take the jump!
I'm fighting endermen!
For us!
Why can't I get any pearls?
How do we get home?
Pearls here.
Guys, why is my luck so bad?
This is why I don't gamble.
Let's go gambling.
Doki, it's been four...
Oh, okay, five hours.
But, like, come on.
That's five hours too many for Minecraft, that's...
What do you want me to do?
I'm waiting for you right now.
I'm waiting for this enderman to come get me.
Alright, I'm heading over.
I'll fucking...
I'll help you.
All in all, this isn't the worst spawn, I suppose.
Okay, come up here, buddy.
Come up here.
He's like...
He's fallen.
Where is he?
He's down there.
What are you looking at?
He's down here.
Where?
Literally down here.
Oh my god.
I swear, if he comes back up and he fucking smacks me into this lava pool...
No, he's aggroed on me.
I'm looking at him too.
Just use your arrow.
He'll dodge it.
You can't shoot an enderman with an arrow.
I'm not gonna waste my arrow.
You don't know that.
How do you know that?
I've done it before.
Yeah, maybe...
Maybe it's just that one guy.
That guy was, like, super good.
He'll dodge and TP up.
Do it.
Wait, what?
He'll TP up.
Yeah.
What?
Up?
Yeah, he'll dodge, but he'll TP.
But it's a waste of a spectral arrow.
Oh, there he is.
Nevermind.
We didn't have to do it.
There he is.
Ouch!
Stop!
You were hitting me instead!
No, I didn't!
Yes, you were!
You were hitting me instead!
It was the ender...
It was the enderman!
It was the end...
I literally...
My thing was on the enderman right here.
This is what I did.
I was like...
That wasn't me.
That was not me.
I don't think so.
That wasn't me.
Alright.
Pull up the VOD!
We need the receipts!
After this stream is over, pull up the receipts right now!
Timestamp this moment!
And we'll know...
We'll know in 12 more hours.
We'll know in 12 hours if that happened.
It's gotta be...
Okay, be careful.
Don't go that way.
It's gotta be this way.
Because...
We didn't go to the crimson forest.
We came from the side.
Yeah.
Do you remember which side it was?
Because I don't.
I have the coordinates in case we need it.
I think this is the moment where we need it.
No, no, I know.
I remember that sand over there.
Why don't we not put any torches to tell us where we went?
I did a little over...
Over there.
Uh-oh.
There's a gas.
Be careful.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god!
No, don't say that.
Now I'm freaking out.
Now I'm panicking.
Oh my god, he can see me.
Now I'm panicking, Min.
I'm panicking right now.
Oh my god.
I'm freaking out.
Shit, shit, shit, shit.
I'm freaking out right now, Min.
I don't know.
I'm freaking out.
He's aggroed on me.
You have no reason to freak out.
What if he looks at me?
Okay, I think he despawned.
Yeah, he definitely did.
He just disappeared on my screen.
Okay, cool.
Oh shit, where are we?
Oh no.
Oh, you have the coordinates.
I do.
Okay, I'll get the coordinates.
It's on the other side from here, I think.
Oh yeah, it's over there.
Yeah, past the lava.
Yeah, it's past this lava.
Yeah, yeah.
Is there any piggies around here?
It's here, he's here.
I'm mining, I'm mining.
I found the hole we made.
I'm not scouting, by the way.
I'm literally in our hole.
Alright, I'm going back to the portal.
Hold on.
I'm getting more gold.
This is for us.
I'm heading over.
I only got 17.
Oh my God, how do we...
How do we jump down from here?
How does this work?
I'm so...
I'm coming.
Where's the hole we made?
There's too many holes.
There's so many holes.
Alright, this is the right hole.
I'm just gonna fall.
I think I found it.
If I get out of the nether and like...
And then I see...
Made Mint dies.
Are you out of the nether?
Are you out?
Yeah, I'm out.
Okay, I'm almost there.
I'm out, but it's night time and I'm gonna sleep.
Oh, I can't sleep, so...
Good luck with that.
You might...
You actually would be safer probably in here.
Yeah, that's true.
Maybe it would be safer.
Until I'm out.
Back to the portal I go!
Oh shit!
Doki doki!
Where are you?
I'm okay.
Everything's fine.
Where are you?
Where are you, Mint?
Everything's fine.
Why does it not sound fine?
I'm okay.
Things were not okay for like a good 30 seconds, but I'm okay.
What happened?
I was doing my job as the gold collector.
Yeah?
Oh, so you were being greedy.
What the heck?
What do you mean greedy?
This is for the gacha.
You were being greedy.
What happened?
Oh shit.
I heard that.
It's fine.
Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay.
I can't do baseball.
I told you not to try the baseball.
Where's the...
Is that the portal over there?
Oh, I see it.
I thought it'd be...
Bam!
No!
How did I miss?
I'm gonna try for this one.
Bam!
What?
How?
Oh!
He got his ball!
He got it!
Go, go, go!
It's okay.
I'm okay.
Nothing bad happened.
That was literally what happened to me.
I'm not playing baseball again.
I'm not.
See?
Oh, so you got greedy with the baseball.
You got greedy trying to play baseball.
How do I get over...
Oh, I'm on the wrong side.
Are you still not here?
I'm over...
I literally saw you bouncing around.
Is it...
Oh, shit.
He's on you.
Oh, thank God.
I had PTSD right there.
Oh my God.
I might die.
Or maybe not.
Maybe not.
Oh, he's still on me.
He's still on me.
Where is he?
I can't get him!
All I have is this sword!
I know.
Try to aggro him and I'll try to shoot him.
I'm looking at him.
I'm literally looking at him and he's not looking back.
That's not how it works.
He's not an Enderman.
How do I aggro him?
I don't know!
Okay, he's not looking at either of us now.
He's just chilling.
It doesn't matter.
He's just waving his little feetsies.
He's waving his feetsies.
Where are you?
I like your arrow.
I took one of it.
You did?
Why am I...
What the fuck am I missing, man?
Okay, I'm running.
I'm coming over.
Yeah, yeah.
No, come over here.
Come over here right now.
We're not fucking around no more.
We're not fucking around.
Alright.
Is it daytime?
It's nighttime.
Okay.
We'll just...
He's like right behind us, by the way.
He's literally right there.
The gas.
Oh, I'm out of the nether.
I'm out too.
Okay, I'm sleeping.
I mean, we want it to be night anyway, right?
Oh, well...
For the phantoms, right?
Yeah, but ideally, we would have like a place to, you know, be safe at.
Like, there's skellies everywhere.
Alright, pussy, let's do it.
Alright.
Good morning.
Someone's a coward, so...
Someone's a little coward.
Do you guys hear this?
That's all I'm saying.
As she was like...
Okay, we gotta do a marker.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Okay, we'll make a peepee tower here.
Okay.
So we'll remember...
We have to...
Okay, mark this coordinate, because we have to come back here.
You mark it.
What?
You...
Okay, I won't...
Chat, mark it.
Oh my god.
Okay, I marked it.
I marked it.
Why didn't you jump into the water?
I'm scared.
Okay.
Who's the baby now?
What am I...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I just didn't want to fucking die by fall damage.
That's even labor than wanting to not die by skeleton and creeper and enderman and literally everything.
Witches that come after us.
Literally, majority of our deaths was from fall damage.
Literally, that's the majority of our deaths.
Majority?
That's just you.
No, no, no, no.
No, no.
Our deaths, guys.
Majority of...
Wait, where are we trying to find again?
I don't know.
I'm just walking.
Ideally, we want to find a village.
Oh, it's a...
Wait, for what?
Armadillo.
He's so cute, isn't he?
What?
You hit me.
No, I didn't.
Yes, you did.
The VOD.
Check the VOD in 10 hours.
What?
I wish there was one close to you.
Wait, why do we need to find a village?
What was the point?
Well...
For...
Yeah?
What's it called?
The brewing thing.
I don't know how to make it.
Oh, the brewing sound?
Yeah, how do we make that?
Where did you go?
I'm where the armadillo...
Oh, you went far.
Okay.
Wait, I didn't even go anywhere.
Why did you...
Why are you just taking off on your own?
I thought you were beside me.
Why aren't you moving?
I am moving.
What are you talking about?
Why were you still at the armadillo place?
No, I was...
I was looking at something in my inventory.
Stone and blaze rod.
Yeah, see?
I don't want to waste a blaze rod on the...
The potion stand.
Why do we need blaze rods again?
For the things to activate the...
The end portal.
Like, we actually do need them.
Let's go straight.
Straight?
Yeah.
Here, I'm gonna make a boat.
Alright.
Hold on.
I have crafting table.
Oh, I just made one.
Okay.
Oh, you could have asked.
You could have spoken up and said you have one.
You could have asked.
Come on.
Oh, you're not gonna bring the crafting table you made?
No, I'll just make another.
There's trees everywhere.
Oh yeah, then you're gonna be like...
Oh, Doki, I broke my pickaxe.
I need somebody to help me.
I don't have any wood.
That's gonna happen.
Maybe.
That might happen.
If that happens, I'll just die and then we'll restart.
What if we did a run where it was not only hardcore, but you could only make one of...
What the hell?
Oh wait, wait.
Does he have anything?
Yeah, he might have stuff.
He might have trading stuff.
No, he doesn't have anything.
Oh my god, you're actually worthless.
They're gonna spit on us now.
It's fine.
Now you have no owner.
Now they'll just die here.
Yeah, they'll die here.
Yeah, they're domesticated so they can't live in the wild.
They're gonna come back like Alan Wake.
You killed my owner.
Oh yeah, this is a hidden run.
That's right.
What are you gonna do?
Fucking kill us?
They could.
If they really spat enough, maybe.
Oh, my chat is just so sad, making me so sad right now.
Wait, why?
They just keep saying of Hawk Tua.
Yeah, they said that too and I ignored them.
I know.
I'm not here to encourage this behavior.
I don't understand why that meme is so popular.
I don't either.
I don't think it's funny.
I think it's one of those things where it's like easy to get people to say it, you know, like...
Like, you can kind of like with the mic memes and all, you can get people to say them easily.
Yeah, but that's clever.
The other one's not as clever.
Like, it's just...
And then, like...
Okay, like, I admire the girl for milking that shit so hard.
Oh, my God.
She went crazy with it.
She was like...
There's Halloween costumes.
I was like, how do you make Halloween...
You saw the Halloween costume.
I was like, how the fuck do you make a Halloween costume?
You don't.
Yeah, but it's in spirit Halloween.
I know.
I saw, like, pictures of it.
And then there's, like, podcasts.
There's videos.
There's, like...
She got signed a million dollar kick contract and everything.
What?
Yeah, she signed a contract to stream exclusively on kick.
And, like, it was, like, you know...
A lot of the contracts are a million dollars and stuff.
And, like...
She is a business woman.
Yeah, she's...
Honestly, if that's...
I need to know who her agent is.
I want a Halloween costume at spirit Halloween.
Yeah, but you have to lose all your dignity to get it.
Okay, like, not like that, though.
You have to lose your dignity to gain the spirit Halloween costume.
Is it worth it?
I'm gonna email spirit Halloween and be like, hey...
Do you wanna make me a Halloween costume?
I'll say something dumb.
All you have to do is open your mouth, doki.
That's every day.
Yeah, it's every day.
Do you think we'll ever go back to our coordinates or what?
I have the coordinates, we're fine.
I didn't get so far.
Hmm...
It's a $5,000,000 kick contract, not even a million dollars.
$5,000,000?
I've never, like, I've never... I don't think I even...
Oh, no, I did watch the original video, but...
No, I watched the original, how she got popular.
I've never seen anything else about her, like, is she actually funny?
Like, is the podcast any good?
I think she's just... she just has a country accent.
That's when she's like...
Hey, y'all.
Like, sorry.
Yeah, she has, like, a very heavy southern...
Did we make that?
What is that?
Did you make that?
Did I make that?
No, no, no, I didn't.
I broke my peepee tower.
Oh, no, I think it's just...
What the fuck is that?
It's a false peepee tower.
Ignore, ignore.
Wait, what?
What is this spot?
It's a false peepee tower.
Don't go towards the jungle.
I think there's not really villages in the jungle.
I feel like she's just, like, an inside job.
Oh, one of those...
Like, an industry plant?
Yeah, she has to be an industry plant.
I don't think so.
Like, I don't understand.
She's, like, mainstream.
So, it's like... I don't understand.
Am I not normie enough?
Wait, what is... Oh, no, that's a tree.
Just kidding.
Don't go towards the jungle.
Turn around.
Where do I go?
Here, let me... Yeah, my turn.
Yeah, your turn.
Oh, uh... Wait, hold on.
Hold on.
I was... Oh.
You were literally in the front seat.
They made a change where if somebody gets off, you're pushed to the front.
Oh, okay, okay.
Yeah, yeah.
I have no idea who you're talking about.
Google...
What's it?
It sounds French.
Not gonna lie.
You make it sound like a grandpa explaining it.
Like, we're gonna get that.
It's actually quite elegant.
What was that?
Oh, just a fish.
Anyway, Google that.
She's everywhere.
Oh, yeah, you can't miss her.
Yeah.
There's a savanna.
Yeah, maybe there'll be a place... But usually it's the plains ones that have the...
The brewing... Actually, no, I...
Oh, village!
Village!
I knew it!
Someone's like, wait, I get it now.
It is funny.
No, it's not.
It's cause we made an actual funny joke over it.
We fixed the joke, everybody.
We fixed it.
That's why you guys find it funny now.
It's not our fault that we're so funny.
Oh, there's another saddle here.
We're just natural comedians.
Oh, this village kind of sucks.
Yeah, this village does suck.
Oh my gosh, the people in the savanna don't know how to fucking cook.
I got some bread and that's it.
I don't think they have it in the savanna.
Well, we have to sleep in this village anyway.
Yeah.
There's melons.
Melons!
Oh, I see you're going over there.
Yeah, I'm just trying to see if there's any more chest.
There's bread, but that's it.
I'm in the bed now.
You can sleep now.
Okay, I'm getting in the bed.
Get up, mister.
Too small, too small of a village.
My 5 million dollar contract.
I won't take it.
I just like to have it offered.
Really?
Yeah.
I don't know, actually.
I won't... I don't know.
5 million dollars is a lot.
It is a lot.
I don't think, though, I would want a contract to exclusively stream on one place.
Yeah, I feel like... No, I'd be like, I'll take it, but like...
You know the xQc contract where he sometimes streams on kick, but not exclusively?
Oh, I know.
That's what he does.
But he got paid more than 5 million dollars.
He got paid like...
Like 50 million dollars or something.
I think we can leave this place.
Yeah, we can leave this.
Back to the boat.
Yeah, boat time.
I don't know.
I know, like...
Oh, my God.
I don't know if you got this offer on your YouTube channel, but like...
My YouTube partner manager was like emailing me and calling me, asking me if I want...
Calling you?
Yeah, no, they called me on my phone, too.
Oh, my God.
And they were asking me if I wanted to...
Oh, yeah.
No, xQc was a hundred million.
Yeah.
What?
That's insane.
He got a hundred million dollars to stream not exclusively on Twitch.
I mean Kick.
Basically, he can stream on Kick sometimes.
Not all the time.
Oh, my God.
He can keep his Twitch account.
Wait, am I going the right way?
I don't know, but like...
They called me and was like...
Oh, like for your VODs that got restricted to R18, which was my one VOD, which was the FNAF VOD.
Because I was like...
Apparently, I swore too much in that video and it got R18 gated.
Wow, good job.
That's because I was like...
Oh, I heard about that.
They were like...
You can't say...
Yeah, they thought you were saying, you know...
They saw I was saying whore.
So like...
And I was saying it a lot.
Let's just watch.
Yeah, I'll grab the boat.
Okay.
And so they were calling me.
They're like...
Because, you know, they're like...
Oh, hey.
We were wondering like for your VODs that got R18, we're trying this new thing.
And basically, it's like we're gonna...
Since R18 are like limited ads.
Yeah.
They're like...
Oh, can we put gambling and smoking and drinking ads on your videos?
What?
R18 videos.
I was like...
No.
There's another village.
Oh my god.
Because apparently, you can get a lot of money from that.
Because like it's...
You know, casinos pay so much.
And I was like...
No, I...
No, that's okay.
Do you get that money though?
No, I think you don't get the money to...
Like, it doesn't matter what ad.
It's ad revenue.
It's ad...
But then you get ad revenue from...
Yeah, but like...
Because like when it's restricted, you get...
You don't...
You tend to like not get ads and stuff.
But...
Oh, there's a prize!
There's a prize!
Oh, nice!
Oh my god.
We did it.
Chat.
Oh my god.
Reddit, we did it.
We did it.
This is the...
This might be the shortest hardcore session that streamers have ever done.
Right here.
Right here, right now.
Okay, we still need the blaze rods, yeah.
Okay, um...
Anything else they got here?
Just pillage them.
Loot them.
Loot them for all they're worth.
Why is there...
They already looted everything.
Their villages are so terrible.
I don't know.
It's maybe because they're poor, man.
Maybe...
Oh, they have a better furnace here.
Oh, that furnace?
Nice.
How did you get inside?
Oh, there you are.
How...
What do I not need?
You wanna grab it?
Do you have room?
I do.
I can get rid of that one iron nugget or...
And the sweet seed.
Yeah.
Okay, what else can I get rid of?
Um...
Okay, I'm gonna get rid of the nether break.
And...
This.
Okay.
All we need now is we need an enchanting table.
Oh, we need a bunch of books.
I mean, I have obsidian for enchanting.
Yeah, we need books, but...
We need a lot of books.
Why did...
I should have kept the leather.
I should have...
Wait, no, no.
It doesn't matter because we don't have paper.
Yeah.
How do we wanna do this?
Do we go back into the nether and risk it now?
We have to find a...
I feel like...
I think at this point, we got...
Wait, how many...
How many enderpearls do we have?
I have six enderpearls.
I think...
I was gonna say it would be maybe more worth it to just go find a new enderpearl, but...
Or make a new one.
We left all our stuff back there.
I didn't leave my stuff.
I left a lot of my stuff in that chest.
Wait, I don't even know what I left there.
Then you won't miss it.
You won't even know.
I mean...
What did we deported?
We can go back.
Where was the boat?
Chat, chat, was it important?
Chat... No, I have the boat.
Chat, was it important?
Because I don't remember if it was important.
The sugarcane?
Do we need paper?
Yeah, that makes paper.
The sugarcane.
But we need a lot of it.
We're gonna need a ton of it.
Okay, yeah.
Then it's easier for us to just find bookcases.
I think so.
More pillaging, maybe.
Alright.
Here we go.
Why are you swimming?
I literally put the boat down.
I didn't know!
I didn't see!
Oh my gosh!
Oh, it's lapis blocks!
I left all the lapis blocks there.
Oh, okay.
We do need those.
Yeah, we do need those.
It was like a stack of lapis.
Okay.
How do we get back?
You fucking had the coordinates.
Doki, I'm gonna give you the coordinates and you're gonna guide us, okay?
Okay.
Okay, I gotta get the boulder.
Hold on.
Okay.
Alright, so the first part, we weren't able to get that done.
It's, um...
Okay, it's negative four, one, one, six...
Negative four, one, one, six...
Oh, why can't I...
Write that down.
Chat, write that down.
Why can't I send a message?
Why don't you just look at chat?
Why can't I send a chat message?
I don't fucking know.
This is your server!
Oh, maybe I didn't give you permission.
Lol.
Wait, what does it say when you try to send it?
It says, cannot send chat message.
Lol.
Bad.
Muted.
Wait, why can't I send chat message?
Oh, I think you have to...
Your account might be like...
It's like...
It's not the server.
It's like your account got marked...
Am I marked as a baby?
Yeah, you're marked as a baby.
No!
Oh, why did that happen?
I think I'm marked as a baby.
I don't know.
Wait, how are we gonna do this?
You have the coordinates, I gave them to you.
Alright.
Yeah, chat, chat.
What was the coordinates, chat?
Yeah, chat.
Doki's chat never lies to her, apparently.
So, you know.
Yeah.
Chat, what was it?
I'm just gonna keep going.
Negative 4116, negative 4116.
And?
You never gave me the Z.
Yes, I did!
No, you didn't!
You really just...
No, I remember you said the X only.
And then you're like, oh, why can't I write it down?
Oh, because I was typing it.
Okay, it's negative 4116 and then 1576.
1576.
Okay, negative 4116.
Keep going.
Okay, I'm going.
I'm going.
Negative 4116.
Okay, you're the one navigating.
Oh wait, that's the false peepee tower.
1576.
Oh yeah, that's the fake one.
Yeah, we're close.
We didn't go that far at all.
Okay, what do you need?
Is there anything else you need?
Okay, while you roll that boat, I'm gonna feed my dog.
What?
I gave you those coordinates so that you would...
I gave you the coordinates so that you would guide me.
I'm not gonna look at it.
You're fine, you're fine.
I'll be right back.
This is...
Who is pulling all the weight here, everybody?
I want everybody to remember that it is I, Mint Phantom...
that has been pulling all the weight in this collab.
I'm getting us back to that.
I've been telling her all the information.
I'm getting us back to our tower.
I'm doing all of this.
Should I break the boat?
Let her drown?
I don't think she'll be back in time to save herself.
Guys, if we...
There's enough sabotage.
If we die, we die...
natural causes.
Natural causes being...
like a ghast.
Though I will...
build a...
a thing for me and have her face the consequences of...
I think I'm going the right way.
She will have to fight for herself...
against the night time terrors.
Drowning is natural.
It's beer o'clock.
It's starting to get real dark.
I don't know if I'm going the right way.
I haven't checked even a single one time.
Oh, so you're gonna try and kill me, huh?
I didn't say that.
Why are you gonna try and kill me?
I said that I will leave you to yourself...
when the night time comes.
Oh, you're not even gonna try and protect me.
I see.
When the night comes...
Am I in the right direction?
Negative 4116?
Yeah, maybe.
What do you mean maybe?
Is that what it is?
Okay, get off the boat.
We need to sleep.
Okay.
Who's a baby now about wanting to sleep, huh?
Oh, okay.
We don't need to sleep then.
I'm sleeping.
Negative 41161576.
I'm asleep.
And you still slept.
Alright, get over here.
Come on.
Hop on my boat.
Alright.
So which way do I need to go?
1576 is the negative 4116.
Do you think we can ask this guy for directions?
Sure.
Hello sir, do you...
Yes, Min was gonna drown you by breaking the boat.
I didn't say that.
My chat suggested that.
You know who said that?
What?
Your favorite guy, Eragon.
Eragon?
This guy has no loyalty to anybody.
Oh my god!
He has no loyalty!
He's a professional snitch.
I'm starting to get hungry.
That's not even a wisp goon!
I know.
What was it?
An SSR?
Yeah.
SSRP.
What does that mean?
Super-sized roleplay?
Am I going the right way?
Negative 144...
What?
Stop telling me numbers and tell me directions!
I don't...
I thought you were okay!
Oh my god, okay.
We're negative 49?!
I thought you had your coordinates out.
No, that's why I gave them to you to be the navigator.
I thought you had
your boat.
Get off the boat.
You're not allowed.
Okay, while you direct, I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Oh my god, where did you end up going?!
Oh my god, what was the coordinates?
Negative 4116...
Oh my god, where did she end up going?!
Like, we're at 700!
Oh my god, how did we get to 700?!
How do I get out of here?!
Okay, it's this one.
Try to reduce the numbers.
Oh my god.
Okay, this...
How did she fucking get 600 coordinates away?!
She just followed the coast...
What if I let her drown here?!
What if I let her drown?!
How's my GPU hitting 100 too?!
Like, what is wrong with this?!
Oh, this Minecraft is too beautiful.
I think it's my resource pack.
Alright.
No, it's the right way.
Oh, 1-5...
Oh my god, it's 1-5-7-6.
Oh my god, I'm fucking...
I'm losing it right now.
I'm reading numbers wrong too.
I'm fucking... Guys, no, you don't understand.
I'm losing it as well.
She took us so far that I fucking... I didn't even know where I was going at that point.
I've lost track as well.
Okay, does this go down?
Which way goes down?
This way?
This way.
This goes down.
This way goes down.
Okay.
Okay, that way.
Okay, we figured it out.
Sorry, I got very lost.
She was getting further and further away from our destination.
Oh my god, what did I end up getting in my fucking inventory?
Oh my god, where did she take us?
Where the fuck did she take us?
I'm back.
Oh my god, where did you take us?
I don't know.
I just was following the edge of the world.
I thought I... I thought me saying the numbers was like 3-0.
No, that's why I gave you the numbers.
What do you want me to do?
Left?
Right?
Yeah, basically.
Oh my god.
I could hear you screaming while I was walking away.
From my headphones.
I don't even know where you took us anymore.
I'm trying to figure out this pathway.
Okay, I remember this savanna.
What were the coordinates?
It's not the wrong way.
It's not the wrong way, guys.
I'm just trying to navigate this fucking hellhole that Mint took us through.
What were the coordinates again?
Negative 4-1-1-6.
Because we're close to that.
We're close to that.
Get off the boat.
We're fucking... We're gonna walk now.
We've lost your...
Alright, here we go.
Negative 4-1-1-6 and...
What's the Z?
1-4-something... 1-5-7-6.
Oh, we're going the wrong way then.
Oh, this way.
This way.
Yeah.
We're not.
Yeah, now it's right.
I was going the right way.
This way.
Yeah, my way.
Oh my god, there's so many bunnies here.
My way.
No, my way.
Where are you?
I don't know.
I'm going my way.
We're both going the same direction, I assume.
Because we're both at the same coordinates.
Yeah.
Oh my god, are those cows on trees?
What are they doing up there?
No.
I see you.
No, they're cows on the cliff.
They're cows on the cliff.
We're just having a good time.
Yeah.
Just like us.
You guys, she's gonna try and strangle me in a couple days when I say it.
Oh shit, I'm going the wrong way.
I'm supposed to go this way.
Are you going the wrong way?
Oh my god, that was close!
I gamed over that?
I thought I was going the right way and then I went the wrong way.
Okay.
That's probably how I got lost in the first place.
Probably.
Oh, now you have your F3 open.
Wow, when we're not using the boat, you have your F3 open.
Well, I can't drive and look at the F3 at the same time.
Oh yeah, guys, remember, don't Minecraft and drive at the same time.
Guys, don't read and drive.
Aragon gave you a good report.
Oh yeah, what did he say?
He said you were good.
You were a good girl.
Yeah?
That's what he said.
The boat.
Was I not a good girl?
What was your death threat against me?
I'm fucking taking the boat out.
I don't think you should phrase it like that.
What was your death threat against me?
I'm taking the boat, goodbye.
Wait, what do you mean you're taking the boat?
Why are you taking the boat?
Where are you?
We're gonna both be... make it to the same place anyway.
Okay, I'll just be a little longer.
I'm gonna get lost.
Look at the coordinates again.
4-1-1-6.
And?
1-5-7-6, so it's here.
1-5-7-6?
1-5-7-6.
I thought it was 106.
I was gonna...
Oh, we know.
Okay.
Oh my god, can I take this bird home?
Oh my god.
Did you go to the jungle?
Are you at the jungle?
I'm about to leave the jungle.
I literally pulled a Patrick Starr.
Why don't you guys say something sooner?
I bet they were.
I see the doggos again.
What was the coordinate?
1-0-4-1-1-6.
I found the portal.
1-5-7-6.
Oh, I'm a little far.
Okay.
I'll be there eventually.
Can I have the boat?
There's trees everywhere.
Was that something you said to me?
I was like, oh, you didn't get the boat.
Oh, there's trees everywhere.
That's literally what you told me.
I'm getting stuff to make books, just in case.
I'm doing my part.
I got my boat.
I was hungry.
I haven't had dinner.
I'm hungry.
We gotta sleep soon.
Okay.
Alright, do we need to go back to the nether?
Probably to find a fortress.
Alright, I'm gonna put my stuff away then in this thing.
I'm gonna give you the spectral arrow.
I'm putting it in the chest so you can take it.
Okay, yeah, I'll use it.
It's like, you have the bow anyway.
Why don't you make a bow?
Just make one.
I don't wanna.
It becomes apex then.
Okay, I'm gonna sleep.
Oh my god.
Wait, okay.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to sleep too.
I'll go sleep.
Sleep.
Now.
Alright.
Where's my string?
Bow time.
Alright, I made my bow.
Nice.
And I'm gonna put away...
I'm gonna put away some stuff.
Put away sugar cane, dirt.
Cut my water.
I don't need the water yet because the enderman...
Like, it's the nether.
Yeah, we only need it for the fight.
Yeah.
And then...
Put the string away.
I'll put the soul speed.
I'm taking a bite.
Do we need the boat?
Do we need it?
I'll put the boat.
Oh yeah, bring the boat.
Yeah, in case we fall.
Just in case we fall.
Put the charge.
I put the blast furnace.
I put away the obsidian.
I'm having mac and cheese.
Oh, that sounds nice.
I haven't had dinner yet.
No.
Let's have it later.
It's kind of late for dinner for me.
Oh yeah, you're not west coast.
Yeah.
What did I want to...
Oh, my brain is short circuiting.
Oh, I see the BB tower.
My brain isn't working anymore.
What did I want to make?
What did I want to make again?
Arrows?
No, I have the spectral arrows.
What did I...
What did I want to make?
Guys...
Guys, what was it?
I don't remember.
There's a lot of sheep around here.
So, I'm gonna murder them and make more food.
Oh, wait.
Gold, gold, gold bars.
Let's murder sheep.
Hippie...
Down with sheep.
Why are you already dying?
I'm ready.
What do you mean already dying?
Hold on.
I'm gonna put my stuff away first.
Alright.
You're not even here.
I am.
No, you're not.
I see you.
I don't see you.
Well, use your eyes.
Oh, I thought you meant like next to me.
Because you're like, I'm gonna put my stuff away.
I thought you're like at the chest.
Yeah, I'm here.
Okay, I'm putting my...
Wait, we're putting the lapis away, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We don't need it now.
Oh, I guess I could've thrown that out.
Dang it.
Let's get some... Let's grab some food.
How much food do you have?
I have 30... I have a lot of hay.
But bread is not fast.
I think we need something faster than hay.
We're fine.
We need some...
Fine.
No!
It's fine.
I have golden carrots.
There's a bunch of sheep right here.
I have golden carrots!
How many?
Enough for me.
Okay, that's you.
I only have...
I have lots of bread, but...
I need more substance.
I'm a growing girl.
I'm pretty sure you stopped growing.
Oh my God, I almost fell into this hole.
Be careful of holes.
Oh no, I'm gonna...
No response to that?
I'm taking my aggressions out on these sheep.
I'm gonna get a mod.
I'm gonna get my own resource pack where every sheep has a doki bird face on it.
There's a fucking Napoleon complex right there.
What?
Sorry, some of us are not born to be stretched out, you know?
Some of us...
Some of us had short moms and dads.
I'm 5'2".
What do you mean?
Wait, you're only 5'2".
And you're giving me shit.
I remember looking down.
I remember looking down, that's all I'm gonna say.
I won't stand this cylinder.
I'm gonna wear my tallest shoes when I see you.
Do you have the furnace?
Yeah, the blast furnace.
You want me to put it up now?
No, the blast furnace only works for...
It only works for...
What's it called?
I have leather too.
Put it in there.
Wanna use it?
For what?
Blast furnace.
I'm putting a blast furnace here just in case.
Okay.
Wait, does it not work on meat?
No, it only works on stuff.
Look, I took all... both...
Oh wait, no, there's another furnace here, I was gonna say.
I only took one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll put the meat in here too.
Oh, the furnace is so slow.
Is that furnace...
You can... Guys, this is not about how perfect the stacking is.
Like, you already saw my inventory, it's not great.
Yeah, we're here for survival, not style.
Yeah, this is survival.
I put the enderpearl away too.
Okay.
Oh, it bothers you?
Don't worry, I'll make it worse.
Yeah, you will.
I can make it... I can make it worse.
Oh my... Oh yeah, my gold.
Gold.
More gold.
Nice.
Gold, gold, gold.
How many gold nuggies do you have?
I have eight.
You have more?
I can make another gold bar.
There you go.
Okay, I have four bars now.
Okay.
Nice.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry, guys.
Oh my God, that sounded like... That sounded like the experience.
When you get the experience.
Alright.
One last meat.
Alright, nice.
Alright, I'm ready.
I'm ready to go to hell.
I'm ready.
Okay.
Oh my God, my... My helmet's not doing so hot, but...
What are we doing again?
Find the fortress, right?
Right?
Is that our goal?
Yes.
Alright.
I'm gonna make another shield.
Okay, what's the... Oh, my shield's okay.
I have not used it.
I'm just having one just in case.
Because, you know, it'll be a lot of blocking from the... What's it called as well?
And I'm gonna get some...
The gas?
Not the gas.
The blazes.
Oh, you're right.
You're right.
And I'm also gonna get some more...
Are you farming trees?
Yeah, I'm gonna get another tree so I can...
Alright.
I'm gonna wait here.
Yeah.
And contemplate my life.
Goodnight.
How did I get here?
Alright.
Alright, I'm ready.
You don't get burned if you block it with a shield?
I think so.
Yeah.
Unless they changed that in the update, but it didn't used to be that case.
That way?
I don't know.
It's been a while since we fought blazes.
I know.
Apparently, they've changed so much.
Yeah, I mean, they have camels now.
That's fucking wild.
Okay, well, I played during camels.
Oh, okay.
So you have no excuse.
What's some potions for the fire...
You have gold helmet?
Yes.
Nice.
Okay.
Fire resistance or what?
Gacha time!
Here's some gacha!
This is a dangerous area to do gacha.
What are you gonna do?
Kill me?
Oh my god.
Here, gacha!
Gacha!
Got more arrows.
Nether wart?
Oh, I have a nether wart.
Oh no, sorry, I have wart fungus.
Oh, what's the nether wart?
Is that the brown ones?
Oh my god.
What did I get?
Is it soul speed again?
It's soul speed again.
God damn it.
What did he give me?
It's soul speed again.
Oh, what the hell?
He gave me a water bottle.
This guy sucks.
Oh, it's the red ones.
Stay hydrated!
Stay hydrated, guys!
Go ahead.
Thanks, guys.
And string!
He gave you string.
Yeah, and you're giving me string?
Okay, I'll take it.
That's literally the string he gave you.
Oh my god.
He gave you gravel.
Yeah.
Hold on, I have more.
Come on.
Wait, did I take it?
Let's go gambling.
Did you take it or did I take it?
No, you took it.
Let's go gambling.
Pig snorts enviously.
Well, yeah, to be fair, water is rare in the nether.
That's like his diamond.
Oh, true.
There's two.
You can give both of them.
Come here, guys.
At the same time.
Come on.
Oh, he gave me a fire charge.
A double whammy.
Oh my god.
I got leather at least.
Oh, that's good.
Come here.
You have more gold?
Oh, that's not what I meant.
Yeah, I have three more.
Come here.
Throw another one.
They're greedy.
Oh my god.
Oh sh...
I missed.
I know, it's really easy to miss.
Oh my god.
What the fuck?
What's the drop off?
Oh my god.
What's the drop?
Okay, there you go.
I got it.
Okay, I figured out the drop off.
I figured it out.
I don't even know what they gave us.
I figured out the drop off.
Blackstone and gravel.
Oh, okay.
Because I got it.
I'm throwing it away.
Okay.
Let's find this fucking stupid fortress.
Alright, you lead.
Me?
Yes.
Okay, hold on.
Yes, because if we die, I can blame it on you.
Sure, I knew that would be the case.
Yeah.
It's good that you know.
Wait, so these are the ones that we need, right?
Are these the ones?
They are red mushrooms.
No, they're not.
They're red mushrooms.
He's shooting at us.
Where?
I don't even see the guy.
Just go up.
He's right behind you.
It's fine.
Let's just go.
Oh my god.
This area sucks.
Alright, I'm climbing up.
Me too.
What about these ones?
Those are the mushrooms?
Oh, they're not the mushrooms.
I'm confused.
What the?
I fucked up.
I can't help you.
Is he following me?
Yes, he is.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
He stopped.
Let's just keep going, I guess.
It was just a prank, bro.
I'm sorry, bro.
This is so bad.
What's the easiest way to find a fortress, you guys?
There's no easy way.
No!
We just go.
Wait, is he still angry?
What did I do to you?
Did you take his gold?
No.
Let's just dig through here.
You get lucky.
This sucks.
It's all about luck, isn't it?
I think so.
I'm putting a thing here.
Oh my god.
I hear him.
Yeah, go in.
Go in.
Dig into lava.
We don't do that.
We be very careful.
We keep our distance.
But what if I'm not lucky?
Where are you going?
Gold.
Oh my god.
He doesn't know.
Well, he's already aggroed, so even if he didn't know...
How does he know?
Do I have to go up?
Go up?
Yeah, because it's a mountain.
Wait, what's first?
It's a mountain.
I saw it.
We have to go up.
I don't think we have to go up.
I just went across.
I'm digging up.
You can go across.
I dig up.
Don't dig up.
It's a full lava.
It's full.
Wow.
What a thunk.
I thought it was...
I don't know.
I thought it was a mountain.
I thought it was a...
Why are you down here?
Because we're going through.
Okay.
Hold on.
I learned my lesson from before.
I learned my lesson.
Hold on.
Wait.
Do you have...
Do you have nuggies?
You grab them.
I learned my lesson.
Okay.
Let's just keep going this way.
Because we're about to get to another soul area.
So it might be in here.
I heard like gas.
Hold on.
I'm gonna put...
some torches down.
As a way to find our way home.
What's that sound?
Is that gas?
The meowing?
Yeah, it's a gas.
Yeah, that's what he does.
Nasty.
Imagine him being all filled with skin.
The skin and like...
little hairs coming out too.
Wait.
Where is my...
Where is my hole?
How did you get over there?
This is where my hole is at.
Hold on.
Don't follow me.
It's too late.
I'm gonna not listen.
We're going down through here.
We're going through here.
What if I dig up again?
You could die.
Do you want to try?
Wouldn't that be a shame?
It sounds like...
you want to not do this.
Or rather, you want to do this forever.
Nooooo.
Look at that.
It took us 5 hours to get to this point.
I don't know how many hours it's gonna take us.
This is why it took other people literally...
20 days.
Oh, I'm in the soul sand.
This might be good.
Oh, I hear a gas.
Nevermind, that's not good.
We can fight him.
He'll disappear eventually.
Oh my god.
I hate them.
Where is he?
Oh, there's the bones.
Look at all these bones.
Yeah, we're in the bone zone.
Who the fuck is this guy?
I don't know.
I hear him, but I don't see him anyway.
He might be above us.
I don't want to leave until he's gone though.
I don't think he's gonna go away.
Alright, my shield.
We're in the bone zone.
I don't hear them anymore.
I don't either.
I think we're good.
Can we go down?
Yeah.
Oh god.
No.
We can build a ladder.
Staircase.
I'm gonna try.
Hold on.
There we go.
Okay, we can start from here.
Oh, okay.
We'll start from here.
I was already making my own, but okay.
Just kidding.
Alright, that's fine.
Don't you know what?
This is why you don't dig underneath you.
Did you see the gas?
No.
Just have your shield ready.
I don't see him.
Have your shield ready for bone zones as well.
For bony fellas.
I learn sometimes, chat.
Bony fellas are on the...
I think he's actually above us.
Because I don't see him anywhere.
Hold on.
I want to put another torch here.
Oh!
Oh my god, double.
That's double?
That's so messed up.
Oh, I see him.
He's above us.
I knew it.
Oh, are these the...
Where are these?
I don't know where you are.
What are what?
Oh, they're the crimson roots.
Where are they?
There's so many white stuff above us.
I can't tell what is actually...
How do you not see them?
I don't see them.
I don't know where you are.
Where'd you go?
I went straight.
I see you.
Look, I'm here.
I'm here.
We can't run in this area.
That's right.
I'm better.
I know the drop off.
I know the drop off now.
That's fucking right, guys.
I know the drop off.
It only took me...
A little bit.
It took me a little bit to learn.
The sand sucks.
Yeah, it does.
I'm gonna get the gold here though.
Get over here.
Run, run, run, run, run.
Oh my God.
That didn't help much.
That's a lot of lava.
It just keeps going.
You literally find one single thing.
That was such bait.
Yay, gold time.
I put one block in attempt to help.
Oh yeah, I can see that one block helping.
I was gonna do more, but it started coming out.
It started flowing faster than I expected.
What am I doing?
I just wanted the gold.
Be careful.
Let's go back up.
Oh, there's one more gold here.
I made a ladder over here.
We can go from here.
We don't need the bones for anything, right?
I don't think so.
I wanna see if I can get a dog.
I'll grab one.
Oh wait, I already have... I'll grab one.
Oh no, that's for bone meal.
I don't fucking need that.
Oh yeah, you can't turn the big bones into bone bone.
But what about bone town?
Hold on, I need that.
How am I gonna get to bone town?
Wait, how do we get down?
I don't know.
Wait, there's a fortress?
Where?
Is that it?
Is that a fortress?
Oh, you could use the bow.
Wait, we have the bow.
Oh, you're right.
Use the bow, use the bow.
It won't sing, I'm blind.
Where below is this fire?
Can you check?
Wait, is...
We're good, we're good, we're good.
Alright, nice.
Oh, we got one guy, nevermind.
Oh, come on!
Nevermind, I just saw somebody be like...
Can't believe she's blind.
And then another guy was like, there's a fortress!
So I was like, oh, what?
Did we get one guy?
Oh, I see this magma cube that's just stuck floating in space.
Yeah, but it's so far.
I'm just gonna head straight.
Just gotta get lucky.
Wouldn't be fucked up if like...
Uh...
The fortress was like literally the other direction.
Yeah, that'd be kinda messed up.
That'd be so messed up.
Yeah, that would kinda suck.
Yeah, that would really suck, guys.
Oh, there's a Ghastly.
No, why are they...
Why do they spawn everywhere?
I feel like the new update made them spawn...
Wait, what?
That should've hit.
Sometimes it's...
Oh, yeah, it's hidden.
Oh, shoot.
Why?
Oh my God.
You got him?
Oh, you got him.
Oh my God, I almost fell in there too.
Holy...
Oh my God.
Oh, I almost went back.
Don't do it.
I almost jumped back in there.
There's a Skelly in there too.
I felt extra wild today.
Only today.
Hold on, I'm gonna go check this area.
I'm gonna see if there's like...
Maybe a fortress.
I don't see it.
I could've closed that hole up, but I decided not to.
You're living on the edge.
I feel extra crazy.
Oh my God, she's crazy.
She's wild.
She's gonna do something wild, guys.
I think this is the worst part.
Trying to find...
The fortress?
Yeah.
How do people... How do speedrunners do it?
They just get lucky, I think.
Are you firing?
Oh, I see what you're going for.
Yeah, because I didn't want him to fucking shoot his arrow and I go...
Set C.
No, that's so boring.
Yeah.
Some of them don't do set C.
I think they like reset over and over again until like...
Oh, they know what they're getting.
Or like, they get a good thing.
Yeah.
I'm good.
I mean, that's what speedrunners do.
They do it like a million different times until it works.
Yeah.
Do you have more arrows?
Yeah, I have spectral arrows.
Do you want them?
Yeah, I'll take some.
Oh, there's another ghast over there?
Yeah, that's why...
Come here.
Right there.
Yeah.
Alright.
I'm gonna eat some food.
Oh, IRL?
Yeah.
Holy shit, there's so many soul sand.
Oh my god, how are we gonna get it?
Oh, this is so scary to get across.
It's literally lava.
Straight up lava on the other side.
Oh.
I don't know if we should cross that.
I don't know, it's a little dangerous.
With ghasts spawning, I wouldn't.
Yeah, so where should we go then?
I don't know.
Oh, I think we...
Through the walls.
I feel like maybe that direction, the right side?
That's the way we came from.
Isn't that?
I thought we came from the back.
I don't remember where we came from.
Like, I think if we just dig this way...
Alright.
We can just dig on through.
I was like, it would be silly to make a bridge across.
Yeah, it would be pretty silly.
It would be so silly if we did that.
Yeah.
Let's just dig.
Stand far away.
As you do.
We're never making it back?
Oh yeah, that's probably a problem, right?
No, we'll get back.
We have the coordinates.
Yeah.
We're fine.
We've got the coordinates.
Alright.
You want me to do it?
Yeah, you can do it.
Switch.
Wait,
hold on.
Let me set up my setup for optimal.
There we go.
You just built another one?
We don't have obsidian.
Oh my god, this gas is a pain.
There's so many.
I know, we're getting really...
Oh shit, watch out!
Watch out!
Nevermind, I didn't even need to warn you.
Okay.
What do we do?
What do you mean?
Oh, okay.
I continue onward.
So brave.
She's so brave, guys.
I'm so brave.
Oh my god.
She knows what she's doing.
I'm tabbing out.
You're tabbing out?
I realized there hasn't been music for an hour.
I just realized music stopped for an hour.
Okay, I'm back.
Welcome back.
Where are my torches?
Oh, there it is.
You've been using the same song for...
Yeah, sorry guys.
You want a different song?
Sorry, too late.
They've already...
They've already Stockholm Syndrome themselves with this song.
Probably.
Oh, this is very dangerous.
Oh, skele-man.
And ghast.
Where?
Oh, that's a bastion.
That's not a skele-man.
Wait, that means we're close.
That's the fortress enemy.
Does it mean we're close to one?
Isn't that a fortress enemy?
I don't think we're going into the bastion.
I don't think it would be wise.
They will actually kick our asses.
What?
They don't care that we're wearing gold.
Wait, aren't they the black skellies?
No, no, no.
Wait, what's a bastion?
That's like the stronger piggies.
Oh my god.
Oh, I thought you were talking about the black skellies.
No, please, not me.
Please, not me.
Oh, fuck.
Doki, I'm in trouble.
Oh, wait, that's not my thing.
Oh my god.
I'm trying to figure out the drop-off.
Why is that my...
I gave all my arrows to you.
I was like, why isn't it shooting?
I'll give you some arrows.
Okay, let's split them.
Oh my gosh.
I didn't even realize you didn't have any arrows left.
I thought you were talking about the black skellies.
No, I thought...
No, I wish that that was them.
Where'd you go?
Right here, but I need to grab my sword.
Behind you?
Oh, shit.
That's right, shoot that arrow.
That's fucking right, you stupid idiot.
Where are you at?
Right here.
Oh my god, again?
Look up!
Hold on!
Oh my god.
I got you.
Did you hit any?
Is that the arrows you shot?
Are those the gold arrows you shot right there?
Yeah, I'm gonna take them.
Oh, there you are.
You were closer.
Oh, it left a tear!
Oh, that's good.
What are the tears for again?
Potions, right?
Maybe, I don't remember actually.
Some sort of potion thing, yeah.
That was a scary sound.
Where did we go?
Oh, regen potion.
That's good.
That's a good thing to have.
Yeah, that's a good thing.
Do we need soul soil?
Do we need that?
No, I don't think so.
So many things I don't know we need.
Where do we go, guys?
Where do we go?
Oh no, we're unlucky!
We're in the fortress!
I don't even know where we are!
I'm gonna kill the skeleton.
This guy looked at me funny.
Yeah, kill his ass.
It's okay, you can go get it again.
Yeah.
Just block on over.
There it goes!
Why did it fall?
Oh my god.
I think they...
Wait, what is...
What is that coming up?
You shot the pig!
Oh god, Doki!
They're all coming for you!
Oh my god, there's another ghast.
There's another ghast.
Watch out!
No, this can't be it.
There's two of them!
Oh my god.
This is so bad.
Just run.
I'll try and take care of the ghasts.
I got one.
Okay.
Where are you?
I'm trying to kill the other ghasts.
Oh, you got him?
You're running?
Oh my god!
I'm okay.
Are you really?
No, I'm not.
I'm not okay.
I think all we have to do is kill these guys...
away from other pigs...
and we'll be fine.
I don't know.
Oh my god.
I don't know how I got him.
No!
There's another ghast.
There's a ghast in front of me!
I don't know if I can take them all.
Can I get them?
I'm gonna start shooting them.
I'm gonna use up all my spectral arrow.
I'm just letting you know that.
Wait!
Don't do that!
I have 15 left.
Here I'll start attacking too.
Use your shield!
I am!
I'm coming!
Oh my god, there's the ghast still.
There's the ghast.
There's the ghast still.
Oh my god.
We did it!
Oh my gosh.
Eat, eat, eat.
Oh, there's two ghasts.
There's two ghasts.
Oh my god, please.
Why are there so many ghasts?
What did they do?
Why did they up the nether so much?
This is so messed up!
Oh my god, watch out Doki.
He's like literally right behind you.
Oh my god, there's another one?
He's still spawning!
We need more arrows.
We don't have enough arrows.
Try to figure out the drop off for this guy.
Oh my god, I can't either.
I can't.
Oh, I got him once.
Oh my god, is he closer than I expected?
Ah!
Oh my god.
Let's just get out of here.
Let's just leave.
This area sucks.
It sucks, it sucks, it sucks.
Oh my god, get his ass.
What?
Why?
I thought it was...
They were like, get out of there.
Gastly loves this place.
But I thought they loved the red area.
Okay, we can't go that way because that's to the bastion and they will like...
Mog us.
It'll be so bad.
Oh my god, no please.
Oh my god, another one!
We need to get out.
We need to get out of the soul sand!
How do we get out of the soul sand?
I don't know how to get out of here in the first place!
There he is, the pigs!
I killed him.
Okay, okay, okay.
Alright.
We just gotta get out.
Just gotta get out.
Oh my god, another one spawned in.
Do you have the coordinates?
How do we get here?
Okay, hold on.
Just run this way!
I don't know, I think a bridge would be...
Maybe the easiest way, I don't know.
A bridge in this area!
I don't know!
Wait, we are in the red area!
Okay.
Let's just explore the red area.
Yeah, let's explore the red area.
Let's never go back.
Never go back.
I don't wanna go there.
The red area is better.
Oh my god!
Just leave, just leave!
Oh my gosh.
Wait, I can trade.
Trade...
Oh thank god, spectral arrows.
Oh thank god.
Maybe he'll give you more.
I have leather right here, you have leather, right?
Oh yeah, yeah, I'll take it.
Did he give you anything else?
No, they gave me spectral arrows.
Wait, there's more right here.
That they didn't pick up.
I like to only give them one at a time, because they just...
They end up missing a bunch.
Oh my god, I would make him a whole...
Stop running away, you bitch!
I know, like, he takes it and then runs off.
I know!
Like, he's stupid.
Oh, they gave me more arrows!
Nice, we both need that.
This ghast, I'm going to become the joker.
Leave us alone!
It only takes one bad day.
Fire resistance!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Okay, nice, nice, nice.
How much is that?
How many minutes?
Three minutes, three minutes.
You got it, right?
He gave another one!
Oh, nice, nice, nice.
This is a lucky gacha.
I can only carry one fire resistance.
I can't stack up.
No, no, they don't stack up.
Unless that was the one he...
The one that you...
No, no, no, I got the second one already.
He gave bricks.
Where did he go?
He's here.
I think he's all out.
Oh, nevermind.
No, I have more.
Okay.
What's that sound?
That's the...
The ghast?
No, you hear the sparkle sound?
Oh my god!
Are you fucking serious?
I hate them.
I hate these guys so...
With every fiber of my being.
I hate them so much.
Oh my god.
This letter.
Let's just leave.
I don't wanna deal with them.
They can have...
They can have this area.
They live here.
I don't care anymore.
I don't wanna deal with them anymore.
It's a tactical retreat.
It's so tactical.
I don't see a fortress anymore.
Oh, this is a different biome though.
Nice.
This is...
This one's not as bad.
There's just a lot of lava...
And sometimes magma cubes.
Yeah.
That's not that bad.
I hear him.
You always hear them.
You close your eyes, and he's there.
You close your eyes, and he'll always be there.
You guys hate the bustled ones?
Why?
Is it because they're annoying to get through?
But we need to go.
We need to venture forward.
Where do we go?
We need to find the fortress!
But where...
Which way?
Don't dig up!
What is wrong with you?!
But there's gold!
Yeah, it's there.
It's there.
Someone's like, basalt equals parkour nether.
That's true, yes.
I don't think so.
I mean, we got the boat.
I think we gotta go through the basalt.
Or something.
Or we gotta... Maybe we go down.
I'm drinking my lava resistance.
No!
Don't do it!
Not yet!
Okay, why don't we get boat and row down?
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Boat and row down.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Alright, my life is in your hands.
Wait, are we good?
Is there anything down there?
I don't know.
Oh shit, that's really close.
Wait!
I don't know if...
I'm drinking my fire resistance.
No!
Don't do it!
I don't think we should do it.
Do it?
No balls?
Okay, someone told me...
I'm drinking it all.
Doki, we would've made it.
Doki, look at this!
You fucking idiot!
I didn't drink it!
Okay, then we're fine.
I take it back.
I retract my statement.
Does the baby give you gold?
Oh, does he?
Oh, he does!
What do you give us, baby?
What if he's like stupid and gives us really great stuff?
Oh, he just took it!
Kill him!
No, don't kill him!
There's no other guys around.
We can kill him.
You do it.
Kill the child.
There's a guy right next to you.
He's a zombie.
I got it back.
There you go.
You killed a child.
I don't care.
It's about survival in this mode.
Why did you kill him?
We got scammed!
I took it and just looked at me.
He was like, yeah.
Thanks for that.
Neat present.
I thought he was gonna be like, I don't know what's worth good stuff since I'm a baby.
I thought that's what he was gonna do.
I was like, wow, these nice ladies gave me some money.
So sweet.
And then you just killed him.
Yeah, and I'll do it again if he steals our stuff.
Watch out.
Watch out, children!
She's gonna do it.
She ain't afraid.
There's a hole here.
Okay, I thought there was a...
I keep getting tricked and thinking I see a fortress.
We'll never find the fortress.
We have to or else we don't beat the game.
This is our personal hell.
This is our nether.
We have to or else...
This is our silent hill.
No!
I'm just looking for my wife.
I'm just looking for the fortress.
The fortress for my wife.
What's that?
What is that in front of me?
No.
How many fortresses are in the nether?
I don't know.
Alright, I'm going up.
Maybe we should go to the right to avoid the...
Avoid what?
The basalt area.
There's only basalt here.
No, I mean to the other direction.
Like this way.
This way?
Yeah, that way.
Alright, let's do it.
I'm building up.
I think bad happens when you build up.
I don't know if that's true or not.
I like how everyone in my chat was like, I suggest you avoid Basalt.
Oh, he has all gold.
Surely he's rich.
Oh my gosh, royalty!
He's so fucking rich.
He gave me blackstone.
He gave me gravel.
There's more.
Oh, he gave me arrows.
Oh, okay.
Wait, me?
I took them?
Yeah, it's fine.
Uh, iron chunks.
Yeah, that's fine.
I'll take it.
Oh, I got an obsidian.
I took the obsidian just in case.
Oh, yeah, we need obsidian.
And there's more obsidian here.
Oh, okay.
I'll take it.
Almost went through that.
It's not deep.
It's okay.
Okay, where do we go?
Okay, uh...
Take the lead.
Oh, hold on.
Can we go down here?
I think we might be able to boat this one.
Oh, maybe not.
Here's the boat.
No, no, not yet.
No, no.
Here it is.
No, I think... I don't think we can.
I don't think we can.
Let's dig through here and then we can probably dig out on the other side.
I think I need some gamer subs.
Guys, can you use my gamer sub code, DokiBird, to get...
Stop digging!
Stop it, please!
...to get 15% off of your next order.
Or is it 10%?
I don't remember.
You remember it, right?
It's either 10% or 15%, but it works.
Do you still get sent stuff by them?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh my god.
I get so much stuff.
So...
Yeah, yeah.
Like, every promotion they do.
I think that's like for all creators, too.
We get, like, everything.
Okay, I'm gonna do this from far away and then you grab it.
Okay.
The clothes and, like, the gamer subs.
Everything.
Yeah.
Oh no, I haven't withdrawn my money.
I have to do that.
Guys, use the creator code, DokiBird, to get 10% off.
Boomer, Boomer, Boomer.
But you guys know what we both have?
That's the same thing.
Our Phantom Thief concert!
Yeah!
We have...
I almost said it.
Did you almost say that person?
We have some special guests that are still unannounced.
Uh...
Special guests that are unannounced.
They are definitely unannounced.
Very unannounced.
Very secretive.
I can't say.
Oh my god, please.
I'm like the Tom Holland.
But it'll be fun.
We'll be in full 3D.
Oh my god, how did you know I was gonna say Jerma?
Oh my god.
No.
Isn't this the big picky area?
Yes.
This is the big picky area.
I don't see any of them.
I do.
I see one right there and one right there.
Oh, I see him.
Wait, maybe that's not one.
I don't know.
No, I see him.
He's on the far right.
I saw him.
Oh my god.
I looked him in the eye.
Maybe the fortress is across that.
Oh, we're gonna be really...
Our shields will be super needy here.
Necessary.
Okay, I believe in us.
Let's go in.
We gotta make sacrifices.
And I have warped fungus.
Okay, I'm just saying that there's a lot of lava over there.
What if it's above us?
We're at 91.
That's kind of high, right?
Oh, that is high.
I don't know.
Oh, we climbed the trees.
Parkour.
Wait, we can just go around it, right?
I'm on the tree.
Can't jump.
Oh, why are you going inside?
Oh, you left a bunch of...
You left so much gold here.
Did I?
Yeah.
Oh, I have 64.
That's why.
Okay, I'm grabbing it.
I'm gonna make some gold then.
Okay, I grabbed it.
Come back.
Okay.
Give me a sec.
I'm making gold.
I don't see anyone around.
Alright.
Is there anyone up here?
Hello?
No?
Okay.
Alright.
Where are we going?
I think we can go around it.
Alright.
Where are the fortresses across at?
Well, we'll go around it eventually.
Here, hold on.
I have more gold nuggies for you.
Oh my god.
Yeah, I need some.
Oh my god, that guy.
You didn't notice, right?
You didn't see anything?
Well, does he... No, he's okay.
Can we give him the gold now?
Yeah, give him the gold now.
Let's see what he gives us.
Over there.
Give us stuff, please.
This is a safe-ish area, so...
What?
Crystal?
That guy is snorting enviously.
Piglet snorts and the child is jealous.
Why did he make all those noises?
What is that?
Oh, he got the leather.
I was like, that happens?
What was that?
That was impressive.
That was... I've never heard that sound before.
Oh, he gave me more arrows.
So if you need some, let me know.
Oh my god, only... Does the nether bring us together?
We're finally... We're working together in the nether.
We've never worked together until now.
We have one common enemy and it's the nether.
Oh my god.
I just realized my game volume might have been really loud.
Guys, has my game volume been very loud?
I don't know.
You have any more?
Oh, there's end...
She gave us two enderpearls!
Let's go!
Three enderpearls!
Oh my god, let's go.
Oh, it was okay?
Okay, that's good to know.
I was scared there.
I saw it, I was like, wait, that's a lot.
How's my audio been?
Is it quiet?
Is it loud?
I don't know anyway.
Is this obsidian over there?
Or blackstone?
Where?
Oh, I picked up something.
I don't know what I picked up.
I don't know anymore.
Okay.
No, I don't want blackstone.
Oh, they're freaking out again.
They're freaking out.
They're jealous again.
Oh, what are they?
What the hell?
They're dropping like...
What is this?
Soul speed?
We don't need that.
Oh, we don't need that.
What's the other one?
That's iron.
Oh, that's my iron.
Are they both soul speed?
I think so.
I think they always bring out soul speed.
Is this also soul speed?
Yeah, it's both soul speed.
Okay.
Alright.
I'm ready to leave.
Onwards, this way.
Onwards.
Alright, let's try and go around this...
heckin' forest.
I hate this thing.
Okay.
What's the song that they've been listening to 24-7?
It's my original song, so they better like it.
Actually, we can probably build a bridge over this way.
Oh, never mind.
I just heard a ghast.
Never mind, I thought we were safe!
They're to our left.
The ghast is above us to the left.
Oh, you know what that means.
It's time to go through your favorite forest.
Where is it?
It's behind us.
He literally spawned inside.
He's right there.
He's right there in the cubbyhole.
In the cubbyhole?
There's a cubbyhole?
What are you talking about?
He's right there.
If you go straight you'll see him.
You wanna look at him?
Come on, I'll show you.
I'll show you.
Go in straight.
Straight?
Here?
Yeah, just go straight.
There he is.
There he is!
In the cubbyhole!
I told you.
You didn't believe me.
Oh, I flung it back at him!
No!
I told you.
It was in the cubbyhole.
Oh my god, I can't stop moving!
Oh my god, I'm stuck!
I'm stuck!
I got you.
My turn.
Ok, nice.
Did you drop anything?
No.
I don't know, I'm taking your arrows though.
Yeah, go take my arrows.
Alright, it's time to go through the forest.
I kept hitting the things!
No, not the forest!
It's time to go through the forest!
Oh my god.
Into the thick of it!
Hey, what are you doing?
Why are you going up?
I'm going to climb the trees.
Oh, ok.
We're climbing the trees.
You can't climb the trees.
Yes, they actually can spawn up here.
Yeah, they can spawn here.
No, don't say that.
Don't say that.
I will say it.
I will say it because it's true.
Because then they'll start spawning in the trees and then it's your fault.
Have your shield up.
Where are you?
I'm in the trees.
I'm in your walls.
I mean, you're right below me.
Oh, you're actually that high?
Oh, I see one.
Where at?
Oh, I see you.
If I stay high ground, they can't get me.
If I stay up here, they can't get me.
I'm trying to save you.
Cinematic mode!
Let's go!
If we die in this run, we have to do all of this again.
All of this again.
Just every single seed.
But what if we get like the best seed, you know?
And it's like super lucky.
All of this again.
What if we get like a seed that like...
Is that the fortress over there?
Where?
Over there!
What is those vine things?
Vine things?
Did you see that?
That's the blue area with all the endermen.
That's the blue area.
I thought they were like, I don't know, chains or something.
Chains from the fortress.
I don't know.
I'm just...
I'm just trying to be...
Have like some optimism these days.
But now I'm just...
I'm a soulless husk right now.
Now I know why there's so many ghasts here.
They're all people who are trying to play hardcore Minecraft.
But they couldn't find the fucking...
They couldn't find...
The fucking...
The fortress.
I'm gonna...
Excuse me, sir.
Should we take a boat down here?
Oh, um...
Wait, I'm just checking out the area first.
Right here.
Right here where I'm standing.
I think this is the perfect boat area.
Might be.
I'm gonna come with you.
Oh, God.
For anyone going to bed, good night.
Good night.
You can check the VOD time in the morning.
Oh, there you are.
I went the wrong way.
Wait, how do I get up to you?
Oh, nevermind.
Alright, ready?
No, I'm not even by you.
I know.
Oh, my God.
Why did you position it like this?
Are you ready?
This is our only boat.
Come on in.
Are you in?
I know.
Wait, let me double check.
Okay, this is actually...
This is gonna be crazy if we make it.
I can't see very well, so...
Here we go.
This is a 50-50.
If we make it, it'll be fucking wild.
Oh, my God.
Thank God.
Anyway, turn around.
Oh, my God.
Well, we could've landed down there.
Anyway, there's two pigs in our boat now.
So, I'm scared.
Oh, what the hell?
These guys are such freeloaders.
I don't know.
I don't know if I wanna hit that.
No, we need this boat.
We need it.
Okay, okay.
I already experienced my first pig invasion.
Use the pig.
Wait, am I getting...
No, I don't wanna get one guy.
Should the pig be good?
Oh, I have a lot of wood.
We can make another...
Do you have a crafting table?
Okay, we can just make another one.
It's fine.
Abandon ship.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
A boat.
Okay, I threw it.
It's yours?
Grab it.
There you go.
Hold on, I gotta eat.
Okay, what's the plan?
I think the...
We can go through this forest.
This is just the one with all the endermen.
Yeah.
We go to the right.
Don't look at them.
Oh, watch out because there is a guy down there.
Hold on.
Oh my god, another ghast?
Are you kidding me?
Why are they all here?
Why are they here?
This is so unfair.
They literally spawn in every biome.
Give us a break.
Why did they make this biome harder?
Why did they make nether harder?
I don't understand.
What?
What happened?
There is a hole.
There is multiple holes.
There is a lot of holes.
I think I just aggroed a guy.
Wait, maybe not.
Maybe I am safe.
I thought I aggroed him.
There is multiple holes.
Watch out not to aggro a guy.
Or be ready to build your own shop.
Why is there so many?
Where are you?
Oh, there you are.
Don't be careful when you are looking down.
You could accidentally look at you.
I know.
Oh my god.
I don't want to accidentally look at you.
You are so ugly.
Boy, I think the Endermen are cute.
They are literally on this Tumblr sexy man list.
Wait, are they really?
I think so, aren't they?
How do you know?
How do you know that?
I don't know.
I have heard it before.
Oh, you heard it?
From who?
I don't know.
Someone who is an expert at it.
I thought they were.
Aren't they?
You don't know.
Aren't they on there with like...
What's his name?
Slenderman?
They are basically Slenderman.
I mean, I guess you are right.
My back is actually starting to hurt.
They are close.
There is a fortress over there.
Wait, is that a fortress over there?
No, I can't see.
Where?
I don't know.
Everything looks like a fortress to me.
Everything looks like a fortress.
I can't distinguish between what is a fortress and what isn't.
They all look like ones to me.
Yes, I think it is.
Where?
Where are you?
Just follow me.
Oh, there you are.
Do you actually think?
I don't know.
I don't know what I saw.
What did I see that I thought was a fortress?
I don't know.
I don't see one.
I see a... I saw a gas.
I don't think it was.
I don't think so.
I think even...
I don't think it was.
The chat's eyes were freaking out too.
I think even chat was seeing things.
It was like we are in the Sahara Desert.
I saw a mirage.
A mirage.
Um...
This is the freakiest bridge I've ever built.
Because it's next to a gas.
A gas?
Yeah, there was a gas in front of us.
Where are you?
Wait, where did you go?
I don't know.
I was looking for the fortress and you disappeared.
No, where did you go?
Wait, wait.
Up, up, up, up, up.
Pulled up, pulled up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna build the freakiest bridge.
Oh, uh...
I'm gonna build the most freaky bridge.
I don't... I don't... I look up and I see a tree.
Just go up.
You see my name tag, just go up.
I don't see your name tag.
So go up.
You look...
Oh, I see you.
Are you sure this is a good idea?
It's not.
I'm fucking...
I'm seeing things now.
It's not a good idea.
Are you sure this is a good idea?
You know what I think is even a worse idea?
What?
Okay.
Get in.
I'm getting in.
I'm in.
I trust you.
I really don't trust you, but I'm trusting you.
Okay.
There we go.
Get that boat.
Look to your right.
I can't get out of it.
I have no more room.
Look to your right.
Yeah, that would've been...
Yeah.
Everything could've went wrong.
Yeah, probably.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
I'm living life by the edge now.
I don't...
We need to make progress.
And to make progress, we have to take risks.
I'm going through another sickness now.
I'm going through another sickness.
This is just...
This is the minds all over again.
Doki is so weak-minded.
She breaks so easily.
Take that.
Write that down in your notes, everybody.
I'm gonna mind break.
She mind breaks easily.
Okay.
Oh, that's not good.
I need... I don't have any more bricks.
I have some.
There we go.
Alright, it's your turn to make bridges.
This is your job now.
We'll just start mining some because I'm almost out too.
I mean, I do have other blocks but I was gonna save them.
I went to the right.
I see it.
Just mine some random ones.
Just get like a full stack.
I'm gonna get...
Truly, this is...
We're not going back home.
Well, I have two obsidian.
So if we get however many we need more, then...
We're never going.
We're never making our way home.
We're never making back home.
We never had a home.
Doki, we never had a home.
Yes, we did.
We had that lapis blocks.
Think about our lapis blocks.
We can get back to those.
Once we're on the surface, we can get anywhere we want to.
So far.
It's okay.
This is so unlucky.
Why have we not found a single fortress?
No!
We'll have to get all the diamond over again.
Please god, no.
This is the easy part at this rate.
I know you're behind me, okay?
Yeah, I'm behind you.
This is a cursed seed.
We should have known when we couldn't find a village.
No, I found villages.
Oh my gosh, imagine the first one we got was like, oh no, no, we're back in the blue area.
Doki, we're back in the blue area.
No, no, I see the bones.
If we go left, it'll be fine.
It's the forest!
Oh god!
If we go left, it'll be fine.
Where'd you go?
I'm in the forest, I'm in your favorite place.
How'd you get in there?
Which way did you go?
Oh!
Oh my god.
I'm okay.
I'm right here.
I'm down.
Nevermind.
Oh, I see you.
I'm right here.
Hi.
You're so funny.
We get pushed off the edge right here.
By some pigs, yeah.
We have our potions.
I'm gonna drink it.
Don't do it right now.
I'm gonna fucking drink it.
Don't do it!
Why are you gonna do it?
We're gonna die anyway!
No we're not!
I'm doing real parkour-sive...
Moves in here.
Come on.
Don't you wanna be a parkour master?
Okay, nevermind.
Don't go this way.
Don't follow me.
Where did you go?
I'm here, I'm down.
But we can't...
We have to make a bridge.
I have two blocks for this bridge.
Did you not mine more?
Mine 20.
I thought that was okay.
I told you to get a whole stack!
We've been in the desert for three hours!
Has it actually been three hours?
I don't know.
It feels like three hours at this point.
We were in the mines for two, I feel like.
It's been a six hour stream.
How long?
Oh god, six and a half!
We're not making any progress!
Oh my god!
I don't understand!
Uh oh, there's big piggies here.
Oh, he's angry.
Oh shit, he's here.
He's actually coming up.
They try.
Where are you?
Are you behind me?
Oh, I see you.
I'm down here with the piggies.
I thought you were scared of the piggies.
Yeah, I hate them.
They're fine with shields, honestly.
Oh, here he comes.
I'll put the mushroom down.
Oh yeah, nice, nice, nice!
Put the mushroom down!
Yeah!
Yeah, get scared dummy!
Scared of a little mushroom!
Yeah, stupid!
You're so stupid.
There you go, here's another one.
Yeah, take it, take it.
That's right, eat your veggies!
Okay, I have more mushrooms for us.
Oh my god.
This is just hellish.
This is actual hell.
This is the real hell.
Who invented Minecraft hell?
Who invented this?
I'm gonna go back in time.
I will prevent...
I will prevent the nether ever being created.
I will prevent Notch from telling Minecraft to Microsoft so the nether would have never been created.
I don't think...
Wait, was Minecraft...
Was the nether from Notch or from Microsoft?
I don't know actually, that's what I was gonna say.
I don't know if this was Microsoft's idea.
I don't think they have any ideas.
Who is it?
Oh, it was Notch.
Notch would do this to us, of course.
Oh my god!
Okay, we're fine.
I got the boat.
Yeah, it'll be fine.
Yeah.
Oh my god, of course you make me do it.
Are you in?
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh my god.
I have the mushroom too, in case things go wrong.
Grab the boat!
I don't have any room.
Okay, we go... I feel like we should go forward.
Okay, what's forward?
It's like here.
There's no other way.
There's no other way in this hell.
It's literally hell.
Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay.
No, me too.
Oh my god, don't fall.
Actually, come down this way.
I think this way is easier.
Parkour.
Oh my god.
Why can't we find one?
Just...
And then we have to...
Survive in the fortress.
I feel like at that point...
We'll be okay.
Watch out, there's pig.
We were ready.
Oh wait, these are...
There's already some here.
There's some pink ones...
Or blue ones here.
I can't even get colors right.
We can kill him.
No, we're running.
No, I don't.
No.
To our left.
Oh my god.
Are you a Costco guy?
What is this?
That's a...
I don't remember what they say anymore.
I don't know.
Where'd you go?
I'm over here.
Where did you go?
I went left.
I see you, I see you.
Boom, baby!
Bring in the boom!
Oh, I see you, I see you.
Cause the other end is a dead end.
Nothing's a dead end when you can...
Oh shit!
Thank you for the 10 gifted.
Boom!
I got him.
Nice.
Yeah, nothing's a dead end...
when you can mine pick through it.
It's fine.
Okay, okay, okay.
That's what you say.
Boom!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh my god.
No, don't come here.
Yeah.
Wait, does he not...
hit you even if there's a mushroom there?
He's too afraid.
Okay, nice.
Alright.
Okay, this is a dead end too.
We have to mine, Doki!
There's no such thing as a dead end!
Boom, baby!
We have to mine through!
10 gifted!
That's a 5 out of 5 boom!
Boom!
5 out of 5 booms!
Booms!
Come down this way.
See?
Look, you've conquered your fear...
No, I just hate this area.
I just hate everything!
I had no fear!
You conquered it!
I just have only hate!
There was no fear!
You did it!
Oh my god.
That's a 5 out of 5 booms, baby!
Boom!
Minecraft guys!
Of course!
Of course we trade with...
What happened, Doki?
That was so scary.
They almost knocked us into the lava.
I just need you to know, they almost knocked you into the lava.
I saved us!
Boom, baby!
Bring in the boom!
Hoglin growling!
Wait, he comes back!
We need to leave at least one.
More fortress spawns on the positive side of the exit.
Did we go the wrong way?
What are you talking about?
I think that's cap.
We're at negative 1,000.
No, I think they're being stupid.
That's not true!
That can't be true!
Don't say that!
Because we're at negative 1,500.
We have gone so far.
We've definitely been in the positive.
Oh my God!
They almost knocked you into that lava.
I'm just saying.
I had my shield up.
Boom, baby!
Oh my God, and a ghast.
It is true.
Speedrunners don't use that.
Okay, guys.
Don't...
Why didn't anybody tell us this at the very beginning?
Guys, look.
This is not...
This is not our fault.
You guys could've told us that.
We're going west.
People were like, just go east-west.
We're going west, so...
Just mine on through.
Of course we're Minecraft guys.
We love trying to find the fortress in the nether.
Oh my God.
If it was just a stream that was just like...
Don't give in trying to find the fortress.
That's one thing.
But no, we have to find the fortress.
We have to survive the fortress.
We have to leave the fortress.
We have to go to the end.
We have to fight the Ender Dragon!
Boom, baby.
Five out of five, boom!
No, apparently Google says it's true.
I don't... Google says that you can...
That like...
Oh my God.
You're like, you filled that hole.
I know.
Because Google says what?
Google says that like...
What was it?
That's the thing that says you can eat it, but it's like a bandage or whatever.
Oh yeah, because of the AI.
The Google AI shit is so wrong.
Yeah, glue!
Put glue on your pizza!
I don't feel so good about this area.
Oh, the dressing!
Yeah, it says the dressing you can put in your salad.
And then there's also a bandage.
Like...
I think we can make a bridge here.
Alright.
Or we could go up.
Do you want to go up?
But we're at 47.
47 where the fortress is?
I don't know where the fortress is!
Guys, is 47 a good for a fortress?
Fortress?
Double choc-chocolate cookie!
Boo!
Now I can see why hawk tool is funny.
We failed up.
You want to build up?
I don't know.
What do you want to do?
Build up or go straight?
I think we go straight.
Alright, let's do it.
We gotta keep going west.
Keep going west, eventually we'll hit it.
We either fall to our deaths or we fucking hit the jackpot.
Oh my god, the lava is glowing so much.
It's so beautiful, Doki.
I'm like a...
I'm like a moth to a flame.
It's calling to us.
Let's go this way.
Take the jump.
Do it.
Your chat will think it's so funny.
Don't you guys want to make content?
You know you love content.
Take the jump.
Oh my god.
I'm getting sleepy.
Just give up right now.
Just give up.
Start a new seed.
A new seed will surely be easier than this one.
The next seed will be easier.
Start over.
Start over again.
Go through the mine.
Strip mining was so much easier than the nether.
Don't you just want to do it over and over again?
Keep doing it.
Keep dying, restart.
Oh my god.
Why is the forest so far?
I don't know.
That's why I hate this area.
Because it's hard to navigate and it's huge.
Last time we were here, it wasn't this big.
We're in unknown territory.
We've been in unknown territory forever.
When does it start becoming known?
I don't know.
Where did you go?
I'm in front of you.
What's in front of me?
Just go forward.
Oh, I see you.
I did the bridge.
This is the most painful.
This will...
Nothing ever would turn me off of Minecraft before now.
Oh my god.
Why is there so many?
It's the worst biome, I'm telling you.
You can't see shit.
And also, it goes on forever.
I didn't know.
You were like, let's go through the forest.
You hate the forest.
It's so fun.
This is why I hate the forest.
I was thinking like, what if...
There's a baby in front of you.
Baby is gonna be scared.
I got the mushrooms.
I'll kill him.
Did you kill the baby?
No, I didn't.
That's fucking right.
Look at that.
He's running.
That's fucking right.
You're scared of your vegetables?
That's right.
Get scared.
Your mother is dead.
We killed her.
Alright, where do we go?
Onward.
Go away, little baby.
We're gonna fucking kick the baby again.
We're still headed west.
We're still west.
What's the worst that can happen?
Are you okay?
I don't think okay is the right word.
Go west.
Eventually, if we keep going west, something will hit.
Why would they make it so that...
more fortresses spawn in the positive?
When does it circle back?
It has to circle back eventually.
I don't think you can circle back.
So we just turn around?
We gotta get obsidian.
Make another obsidian.
I don't know anymore.
Apparently, the x-axis thing was...
before 1.16.
So it's old news.
Wait,
hold on.
He said something else.
One fortress can spawn every 432x432 chunks.
Okay, we're fine then.
We can just keep going.
Your chat was trying to feed us wrong information, Doki.
They were trying to sabotage us for real.
Yes!
Your chat was saying the same thing!
No, it wasn't!
Wait,
what's this?
You give us the seed so we can look it for you?
No!
We're not cheaters!
Come on, this way.
Come on, I'm here.
I'm here.
We're not cheaters.
We're here.
Yippee!
We have integrity!
Take that, take that.
Oh wait, be careful.
Actually, maybe don't.
Too risky.
Wait, did you see the piglin snorted angrily?
He didn't notice though.
We're inside.
Yeah, we're inside.
I think we'll be fine.
Don't get tired.
I'm tired.
No, you're not.
If we die, you gotta stay up.
If we die, you gotta keep going.
Oh my gosh.
Hold on, I'm gonna go to the side and see if there's any...
any fortresses over yonder.
There's another...
There's another forest.
Let's see if there's any fortresses yonder.
Oh my gosh.
Fortress blaze!
How the fuck did a chicken get here?
What the hell?
How is there another chicken guy here?
Is that fortress over there?
Where?
Over there.
Is this another mirage?
Am I looking at a mirage right now?
Everything looks like a fortress.
Is this a mirage?
I don't know.
I'm gonna keep my render distance the way it is because...
What is that?
Let's start selecting him.
What's what?
It's just land.
What's that over there?
It's more land.
There's a ghast behind us.
Oh, I see him.
I'm not ready to deal with his bullshit today.
Oh my god.
I got him.
You got him?
Nice.
I locked in.
I got him.
Can you believe Doki wanted to start this later in the day?
I didn't realize.
Wait, is that...
Is that the fortress over there?
Stop!
Do you wanna go?
We can just build a bridge.
We can just build a bridge all the way there.
Come on.
We can build a bridge at sea.
Is it that over there?
Oh, it definitely is not, but we can go check.
I'm just trying something here.
I'm trying.
I'm trying something.
I'm like, somebody wants to just give up.
How are we doing?
I'm saying we build a...
Dude!
It's midnight for me, you west coaster!
You're a west coaster!
This is my first breakdown, okay?
Okay, I actually think we should build over there though.
Okay.
Because going over lava, it's high risk but high reward.
Oh, it's true.
You're so right.
We build a double bridge.
Wait, do you have enough things?
Yeah.
You do?
Where should we go?
I'm drinking fire resistance.
No, you're not.
Only drink it if you start falling.
I'm not gonna get it off in time!
Here I go.
Here you go.
Into the thick of it!
My fingers get sweaty.
Okay, you have to tell me if I'm gonna back into a lava thing though.
Just say stop.
Yeah, just tell me though.
Don't tell me to stop.
If I start going.
Looks like a bastion?
Oh my god!
Oh, it is!
No, I literally told you that earlier.
No way, there's a freaking...
We found two bastions but not a fortress!
This is so unfair!
I thought the bastions were the big piggies.
They're the most dangerous part.
All those guys in there?
Yeah, all those guys will kill you.
They don't care if you're wearing gold.
Yeah, they just attack.
I guess we go left.
You think it's the same one?
I don't think so.
There's no way.
No way, I think it is.
Do you see those blue flames?
Is that the bones?
We've gone too far for us to have made a circle.
Okay, turn around.
Turn around.
No.
I didn't think of it.
I thought you were going left and right.
Oh my god.
We made out just in time.
Holy shoot.
Oh my god.
Let's just keep going through the wood.
I don't care anymore.
I got the mushrooms.
I have nine mushrooms.
I didn't think of it.
Why is he chasing after you?
Okay, that was weird.
Okay.
We're still going west everybody.
Turn it to the west.
See this?
Be thwarted fool.
Now we have to get past him still though.
Boom!
Double chonky mushroom.
What?
Where'd you go?
Oh, you're up there.
I'm gonna crack.
It's okay.
Everything will be fine.
I got him.
I think.
Where'd you go?
Where are you?
I'm here.
Keep going straight.
I'm seeing...
All I see is red.
Red everywhere.
I don't understand.
I don't even know what fortresses look like anymore.
They're just really big red structures.
It's just a myth.
They aren't even real.
They were invented by a big crafter.
A big crafter.
Wait, I think we should stick to...
We should stick to the edge where we see the big pool of lava.
Okay.
What?
What are you even saying?
I know!
That's why I hate this bio!
I hate this bio so much!
Oh my god.
A bastion is tempting, but...
It is not our goal.
It's not our goal.
Oh my god, please.
If there...
I went to heaven, but if there is a god...
Oh my gosh.
Oh, please.
What the hell?
Who just yelled at me?
Where are you?
I'm over there.
Oh, I see you.
I'm checking.
I'm being on the lookout for...
For vortices!
Into the thick of it.
Where are we?
We're in the thick of it.
The music is gone.
Just like my sanity.
Why is your music disappearing?
It's like a YouTube playlist.
Oh, did you put on like Minecraft music or something?
No, it's like the thing where like...
If you leave it on...
If you leave your playlist on unintended, it like pauses it.
Because they're like, are you alive?
Oh, it does the Netflix thing?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It does that.
I don't know where I should...
I'm running out of blocks.
It's so shiny.
I just want to jump into it.
It would be so funny though.
I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna...
You could continue on without me.
I'm gonna do it.
No, you're not.
Wait, why are you going that way?
I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna...
Do you believe?
I can't see your POV.
I don't believe, honestly.
I don't know your POV.
Don't take it!
Here we go.
Oh, you made it.
I thought you said you didn't see me.
No, I see you.
I don't see where you... I didn't see where you were gonna land.
It looked like...
It looked like you were gonna land into a lava.
Oh, yeah.
No, there was...
There was a chance.
Wait, okay, let's split up, gang.
We've already split up.
Let's split up.
No, that's the worst idea.
One of us will die.
Okay, then we'll...
Blame the other.
We'll do this all over again.
We're gonna do this all over again.
How much...
Probability is me.
If we...
Okay, how much do you think we would owe chat if we told them that we didn't want to do this anymore?
No, we have to, Mint!
We can't just give up!
We're not quitters!
Mint.
You got this.
You knew!
You knew the time commitment!
Okay, where are you?
I'm coming back to you.
I'm in the air.
You probably could see my little bridge.
My sky bridge.
My god, you made a fucking sky bridge.
Mint, it's time to get the gamer soaps out.
It's time.
It's time to get the gamer soaps out.
Are you actually?
I will drink the gamer soaps if you drink the gamer soaps.
I have so much gamer soaps.
I think I will actually have gamer soaps for like 5 years.
Exactly, it's time.
Are you gonna go get some?
I'll get some when we meet up.
When we...
Okay, well come to me then.
Where are you?
I'm in the thick of it.
Then come to...
I told you to stay along the edge so we could see if we see any...
I don't know.
You know I don't know anymore.
I'm just...
I'm trying to not die.
I see you.
You do?
Okay, I'm gonna go get something to drink actually.
Because I'm dehydrated.
Okay.
I'll make gamer soaps later.
No, no, make it.
We can take a break.
No, no, no.
I'm in the thick of it.
I'm panning over to you.
Wait, what's your name?
I'm in a fortress.
Not a real one.
I said the wrong one.
Don't say that.
You gave me hope for a second.
You gave me...
You gave me hope for...
Okay, while I...
You go make your drink.
And then after you make your drink...
You come back.
I entertain chat while you make drink.
Okay.
And then after you make drink, you come back.
And then I need to...
And then I need to walk my dog.
And then...
And then we go on.
Wait, how long is a dog walk?
It's like 10 minutes.
He just needs to pee and poop.
Oh my God.
You never had a dog before?
I have, but like...
I just would...
My mom took care of him.
Oh, you're not responsible.
We would just let her out and...
And they'd run around.
Okay.
Go make your tea.
Gotta pee and poop.
Okay, I'm going.
Okay,
guys.
Guys, how...
Oh my God, please.
Please stop.
Get away from...
Oh, he's gonna hit him.
He's gonna kill him.
Oh, thank God.
Please kill that stupid pig.
He stopped killing him.
Why did you stop?
Wait, I lost her.
Oh, there she is.
Okay.
Alright, I gotta grab more of these.
And then grab my...
Where's the piggies?
Wait, is that...
Is that the...
Oh no, that's the gas.
When...
When will I find a fortress?
I'm gonna make my own house.
I'm gonna make...
my own little house.
I gotta make my house.
Gotta...
No!
No, I'm not a cheater!
Alright, I got my safe house.
Never give up.
Never back down.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm sorry.
I know you wanna pee and poop.
Give me a sec.
I can walk you soon.
Are fortresses normally this hard?
Are they normally this hard to find?
I don't understand.
Are they normally this difficult?
No!
What's wrong with us?
I don't know.
I don't...
I don't know why we can't...
We can't do...
We can't find a single fortress.
It's like the frog's all over again.
Look in open areas.
Okay.
There's so many people fighting.
Alright.
Okay.
Oh, we're going...
Okay, we just gotta go in the open area.
We just...
We just need to go...
Okay, alright.
Now it's your turn to talk to the chat.
I'm gonna go walk him.
And then make my gamer subs.
I'll be right back.
Alright.
Oh my god!
A guy spawned on my...
My bridge!
My sky bridge!
I got some more mac and cheese, guys.
I'm...
I've come to the...
What's the word?
Not the realization.
I've come with peace that this might ruin my sleep schedule.
I want to stream tomorrow, but...
It might be more Minecraft.
Give us the seed.
No!
I refuse to give you the seed!
I refuse.
When Doki proposed this, I thought we were gonna start in like the morning.
What was he thinking?
Doki, I wake up at 10am every morning!
My sleep schedule is not broken like yours!
She had too much confidence.
Yeah, I think so.
I'm just eating my dinner.
Where even is she?
Like, where did she...
Look at this guy taking over my bridge.
I don't mind a second stream.
If it comes down to it, we have to.
She's in the ground.
What is this hobbit...
What is she doing?
She's a groundhog now?
I'm gonna keep going.
But I need more...
I'm gonna waste all my deep slate.
For these, you know?
These are good against like...
I can get more, I guess.
She's six feet under.
I wish that were me.
Actually, can she and I trade places?
Can she and I trade places?
I guess I can drop here.
Did she go further than me?
I don't know.
Oh wait!
Oh my gosh, there she is!
Doki Birdo.
I found her.
That's so funny.
Oh my gosh.
More...
Okay, blue forest is fine.
We don't mind the blue forest.
Here, I'll even make the bridge over there.
That'll be productive.
While we wait.
Oh my god.
I'll be productive, everybody.
Doki stream, you may not be able to see.
But trust.
Trust in me.
That I'm making a bridge.
Across the sea.
I'm...
Almost there.
We'll find the fortress and we'll live.
We'll survive.
If it's the two of us, we can do it.
If it's the two of us.
If it's the two of us, we have to be able to.
Oh my god, no.
Ghast.
I swear, go away.
Oh my god, I hear him.
He's like right next to me.
No.
Oh my gosh.
Believe.
Believe in magic.
Guys.
Okay, I'm just gonna say it.
I'm just gonna say it.
We've gone through every biome but the basalt.
We have to go through the basalt.
We've gone through every...
Oh my god.
I thought that was a...
I thought that was a fortress.
Oh my god.
I literally...
This I thought was the top of...
Oh my god.
I thought we had made it.
I made it myself so much.
We've gone through every biome but the basalt.
We...
This is what we have to do.
See, check that out.
Come here.
Give me magma cubes.
Why do they hurt so much?
Did they not give me anything?
Oh my gosh, everything is so stingy in this game.
No nether fortress November?
Yeah, maybe.
If we never find one, just what do we do?
I think we should give ourselves a time limit.
And if we don't find it within the time...
I told you it was in the basalt!
Don't give up!
I literally was gonna say if we don't find one in the next 30 minutes we do a new seed.
But then I literally just saw it right there!
Sorry, I need to drink so much more water.
I sent that before...
Oh, the funny and sad thing was that you two were making really good progress but the nether said no.
Oh, and then you sent that before.
That's so silly.
I know how to get to here so I didn't really need to save the cords but I guess it's good to have it too.
Alright.
Oh my god.
It was right here!
Oh my gosh.
See, she just has to cross from here.
She just crosses.
She's right up there, she crosses and then we just run right into it.
Oh my god.
What if I don't tell her that I found one?
What if I just didn't tell her that I found it?
I'm just kidding.
Dragoons, I'm gonna tell her, don't worry.
We've been through enough.
We've been through enough, I'm gonna tell her, don't worry.
Loot it and then don't tell her?
I'm not going in there by myself.
I hate fortresses.
I'm gonna make a little hideaway for me.
Don't go into the bath salt, they said.
Oh my...
Doki's chat, all the dragoons said don't go into the bath salt.
You didn't have to prove me wrong that fast.
What did you do?
What did you say?
Thank you guys for all the donos and memberships and gifted and everything.
Really appreciate it, both of us.
Sorry we can't really acknowledge all of them on stream.
While we're losing our brain cells.
But we are seeing As a dragoon, please don't tell her.
That other guy would just snitch.
Yeah, he would.
Eragon, where are you?
Eragon the snitcher.
You gotta change your name, man.
Say you found it, but like Doki guess.
This guy is really trying hard to get those.
I wanna get these.
This is perfect too.
We can get lots of magma cubes.
Actually, I feel like this is a good...
Magma cubes are annoying, but they're not so bad, you know?
This is a good biome for it to spawn in.
Why'd I say all of this?
It's like a broken fortress and we don't get any blazes.
I think Doki stole one O from your name.
Oh, the bird O?
Doki bird O?
Yeah, she saw how popular Minto is and she's like, oh yeah, I'll be Doki bird O.
Or she's trying to be bird O from...
From...
Mario, but who would wanna be that loser?
Don't jinx it.
I don't know, guys.
I'm feeling...
I don't know.
I'm gonna hide in this cubby hole while I eat.
I always believed in you, especially you.
Thanks, Aizy.
Oh.
Bird O is so scary looking.
And I like kimo kawaii things.
I keep seeing these things called labubus.
Have you guys ever heard of it?
You know how like...
These like...
These blind boxes of like these random characters have gotten really popular?
You've never seen a labubu?
I don't know how to spell it, but I keep just seeing people being like, who would wanna buy a labubu?
Why are they so popular?
They're so ugly.
But they're kinda...
I like them.
I think they're cute.
They look like little gremlins.
Labubu craze even in the west?
I think less so, but it's still popular.
People will line up at stores at like 5am for new labubus.
I don't understand it.
Got popular thanks to Lisa.
Like...
Blackpink Lisa?
Is she Blackpink?
They're cute though.
I like them.
Labubu.
It's fun to say.
Oh yeah, Lisa Blackpink.
Okay.
Yeah.
And like...
I don't know.
Recently, like the weirdest things are popping off.
Where people will like... Okay, have you guys heard about the ladies that like stalk TJ Maxx for Hello Kitty goods?
If you don't live in the US, there's a store called TJ Maxx that like sells kind of discounted items and stuff.
It's like...
Not... It's not Walmart, but it's like sometimes you can find designer brands in there that are a little like less expensive and stuff.
And so... But recently Hello Kitty blankets and like mugs and things have become like the it item.
And so...
These ladies are going to TJ Maxx and like scalping these Hello Kitty products.
They're not even that cute.
I don't understand.
It's like a discount store.
Yeah, it's like...
I don't know how to describe it, honestly.
It's like if Target was a thrift store.
Yeah, I guess that makes sense.
But they'll go to TJ Maxx like in the early mornings and like fill their carts with all the restocked Hello Kitty goods and then...
And then...
Oh, hello.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
So did you get...
Did you...
Did you get any intel?
Yeah.
Did you cheat?
No.
No, I didn't cheat.
Did you cheat?
No, no, no.
Doki.
Did you cheat?
No, I didn't.
Doki.
There's a guy...
There's a... Oh, he's getting beat up.
Doki?
Yeah?
I found it.
You...
I found one.
I built a bridge.
Come over here.
Hello?
Why did you leave?
Oh.
What?
Come here!
Get out of your hole.
I saw your hole.
I built a bridge.
Why is our chat...
Why is our chat saying many different things?
What?
Because they're not watching me.
They didn't see me discover it.
What?
Dragoons!
Dragoons, why are you being like this?
Dragoons said you were cheating.
What?
Oh my god.
No, literally when I came back...
The first super chat I saw was someone being like...
Give me the seed.
And I was like, no!
Here, come over this way.
You can't even find the seed.
Yeah, I don't even have the commands probably.
Did you see me?
Yes, there's a pig in front of me!
Put down a mushroom!
I only have one!
That's all you need!
Come on!
But what if he hits me?
Put it down!
I have ten.
Put it down and then...
This is a block!
It's not...
It's not grass!
What are you talking about?
What?
This is another block.
It's not the grass.
Oh, hold on.
Oh shit.
Don't come for me.
Oh my god.
Use your shield.
They can't hit you if you have your shield up...
when they try to knock you back.
Oh, see?
You got him.
Easy.
Oh my god.
There's a ghast!
There's so many things going on.
Oh my god.
Okay,
come on, come on.
I'm heading over.
How did you find this fortress?
Because I...
said, I was literally to my chat...
I was like, guys, the one...
the one...
biome we haven't been to is the basalt biome...
and that's where we have to go.
And then it was...
Why did everybody think you cheated?
Because they're assholes.
They hate me and they're trying to sabotage me.
Fine, you know what?
You can find it then.
You can find it.
No, no, no.
I believe you.
I'll just check the bot later.
Then you don't believe me!
No, no.
I believe you.
What's Hot Tourist Destination?
Did we just go through every single biome?
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
We didn't go through all the biomes.
Okay, come here.
We're going.
How did you go so...
I only went to here.
And there it is.
You see it over there?
You see that?
You don't see that?
What do you mean you don't see that?
My render doesn't go that far.
Oh my God.
I need to get closer.
There's nothing there on my screen.
What?
Oh my God.
No wonder you wouldn't see anything then.
No wonder you thought everything was...
Square in the ground?
What's square in the ground?
I've never seen a fortress before, so I actually don't know what it looks like.
It's like just a bunch of brick.
You see that big chunk of brick?
That?
Yeah.
Oh shoot, I'm almost there.
Oh, that!
Wait, that's a fortress?
A fortress is just brick.
That's what I said!
It's just in front of us.
I know!
Oh my God, I hear a gasp.
That's what it was supposed to look like?
Yes, what did you expect?
I thought it would be like a fortress.
No, they're really lame.
Maybe we pass by a lot of these.
No, I don't think so.
They do not look very easy to see.
Oh, apparently it's very rare for it to spawn like that.
Well, we're in it.
We're in it.
There's the blazes!
Alright, time to dig down.
Are you ready?
Oh gosh.
We might actually fall in though.
This is it!
This is what we've been working for!
We worked so hard for this.
For this.
We have to live.
Yeah, see?
That's what I was afraid would happen.
Hey, move!
Move!
Oh my God.
We can maybe build a staircase like this.
I thought we did it.
We actually did it.
All it took was a bathroom, but we did it.
I fell down.
Okay, that's fine.
We do need a way out though.
Okay,
is that enough?
No.
Oh, that's not good.
What happened?
Wait, I don't like the sound of that.
Why did you say that?
No, I'm just trying to figure out a way out.
But it was like lava.
Lava.
I'm just gonna...
Do you hear the blazes?
No.
Try to get them up close.
Don't get them from far away.
What if there's Wither Skellies?
Put down torches.
What does the torches do?
They stop the Wither Skellies from spawning.
No, I'm not talking about that.
I'm just talking about what if I just encounter one?
Then don't fight it!
Don't fight it.
Because if it hits you, it'll like...
Oh my god, it's breathing.
Oh, I see one.
He's right there.
Oh no, the Wither Skelly!
Oh shoot.
Yeah, this is a good spot.
This is a good spot.
Nice.
Wait, what's that in front of us?
This is just basalt.
Oh my god, there's a bunch of Wither Skellies.
Yeah, I see them.
We don't want them.
Not this time.
That's not our goal.
Wither Skellies, you are not our goal this time.
Like, don't let them touch you.
Oh wait, we got the wards!
Oh yes, these!
We need these!
Some of them are...
Not grown though.
Oh, maybe they are.
Yeah, yeah.
This is what we need.
But I think the blazes are here.
No, that's a Wither Skelly.
Oh, where?
Over there.
No, I think I hear blazes to my left.
Hold on, I'm trying to make more...
I'm making more...
Okay, I see them.
I'm making more torches.
Yeah, bitch.
Yeah, they're right here.
In front of me.
They're not our goal.
Like the...
Oh, diamond!
Oh, I think I...
Ah!
What, what, what?
It was just a normal Skelly, but I ran.
Okay, I thought it was...
He freaked me out.
Oh my god.
I got freaked out a little.
But the blazes are here, I hear them.
Yeah, I do.
They're everywhere.
Oh god, they're breathing.
Why do they sound so scary?
Breathing really hard.
I think they're upstairs.
Are they upstairs?
Maybe.
I hear a Wither Skelly.
Oh shit!
You can block them.
I have a lot of experience with these guys.
Oh my god, you're gaming?
I got nothing though.
No!
Next up.
Oh, nothing here.
Nothing.
I'm just...
Are you sure?
You can go forward.
Oh, didn't trust me.
That's cool, that's fine.
Yeah, I'm just saying.
I was just double checking.
That's okay, that's okay.
It's fine.
Some people just don't trust others.
Where did he go?
I'm trying to see where they are.
I think they're all above us.
How do we get above?
We probably have to dig up.
Okay.
But we found this!
Oh my gosh, oh my gosh.
You guys.
This is where the real grind comes.
We don't even have enough for like...
Did we go here?
Where?
Here.
I don't see you.
The other exit.
Below the stairs.
Here, here, here.
No, we didn't go this way.
I'm grabbing the rest of the warts.
Did I grab some warts accidentally?
Oh, I did here.
Here's some nether warts too.
Alright, we didn't go here.
Oh, this is scary.
Okay, we didn't go here.
And I hear Wither Skelly.
Be careful.
Oh, there's more places here!
Okay.
Watch me.
I'll get the blaze.
You get the Wither Skelly.
If you can find him.
I heard him.
I got obsidian too.
I got rib armor trim.
Do we want that?
No, we don't need it.
Oh shit.
Is that netherite?
Are armor trims netherite?
No.
Come here, come here.
There's more warts here too.
Got him.
I don't see...
Okay, run, run, run!
No!
I got hit!
They're on the side.
To the right.
Oh, there they are.
Oh my god.
I don't see...
the other skeleton.
That's okay.
He might be up.
I see magma cube.
Oh my god.
This is so confusing.
I told you, never give up.
Never give up.
Someone almost gave up.
I found it.
Before they found it, they almost gave up.
I remember.
We're like locked in now.
We're so...
If we can, we can.
Oh, there's a magma cube here.
Kill him!
Oh, I see him.
I think this is not a bad spawn though, because...
Honestly...
Like...
Okay.
I don't have any more torches, by the way.
Oh, there's another blaze.
Oh my god!
I don't know where he was.
I don't know.
Shoot me!
Oh my god.
Kill him!
I got blaze rod!
Get a blaze rod!
How many blaze rods do we need?
I don't know.
That's a dead end.
That's a dead end right there.
Did you get the warts?
Yeah, I got them.
Oh, is this one of those that like drops off?
Okay, yeah.
That's what I was like.
We can do that.
There we go.
Oh, there's another wither skillie.
Oh, he dropped off.
Oh yeah, the rib armor trim would be so cool again if only we did it.
There's so many rib armor trim.
Yeah.
Ten rods is...
Okay, we need at least ten rods.
We gotta get the spawner then.
Do you have any more torches?
Yeah, I have some.
Where are you?
Upstairs?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm here.
I guess I'll throw away the bone.
You're a single bone?
No, I have six bones.
I guess I'll get rid of it.
Oh, there's diamond horse armor.
I wish they would come closer.
I have arrows.
Yeah, but then we can't get the blaze rod.
They're all the way over there.
I think that's where the...
Okay, do you... Oh, you're...
You're what's it called?
Yeah.
Can you see where it looks like a jungle gym?
That's where the spawner is.
How do we get there?
Maybe it's like over here to our left?
Maybe, but it'll be really risky running over there.
Oh, there should be a guy here.
Oh, there he is!
Get his ass!
Oh, why did I get hit?
How did he hit you?
I don't know!
Did you kill him?
I killed one of them.
Ignore that guy.
Ask me this way then.
If we can even get to it.
Actually, maybe we can.
Oh, hello.
I looted that, I think.
No, not this way.
The hardest part is like...
avoiding them when they're...
Oh, come here.
Because they like to fly away.
He's not above...
How did we get there?
I feel like we already went through all the entrances.
Sometimes it's not connected.
Sometimes it's like blocked off.
Okay, watch out for him.
Watch out for him.
Do we go drop down from here?
Oh, maybe.
It's like here, right?
We went down here though.
Oh my god, I hear him.
He's breathing in my ear.
Come on.
It's like around this general area.
No, it's not connected.
I don't think it's connected.
Oh wait, it's probably down this way.
Oh shit!
Oh no, Doki!
Doki, I'm not okay.
I'm not okay.
There's another one!
Okay, I got one of them.
Are you okay?
There's a blaze.
Yeah, I'm okay.
I just heard Dad howling.
I heard you howling...
Oh shit, oh shit, shit, shit, shit!
Um, I might not be okay.
Hold on, I'm retreating.
Tactical retreat!
Okay.
Oh my god.
Got him.
Yeah, there were two of them, there were two of them.
Okay.
You got it, you got it.
Oh my god.
We're okay!
Because my dog was also howling.
He was, I don't know, I think he heard us yelling and he's like, I wanna get in there.
He was like, howl!
I was like freaking out.
I was like, why is he howling?
Everything was happening.
Oh, there's magmas.
Oops, that's not what I meant to do.
Grabbing the magma.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Oh my god!
I think that was a good idea.
Why did they come at me like that?
Oh my gosh.
Because you're literally killing them, what do you mean?
No.
No, I would never, no.
What can I get rid of?
What?
Oh my god.
Yeah.
Yeah, you got it.
Good job.
I hate weather skellies.
Oh, there's a, there's a blast, there's a, there's a blaze, blaze, blaze.
Yeah, fine.
Wait, which one was the spawner again?
Are we lost?
No, no, I know, I know where it was.
I don't wanna get rid of the string, what if I need to make a new bow?
Well, I guess I don't need the bow.
Oh, the quartz!
Thank you, I don't need the quartz.
What do I need to get rid of?
There we go, ok.
I need to keep my gold chest plate.
What if my gold helmet breaks, guys?
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
I think I heard a guy.
Nevermind.
Ok, we're good.
I think it's just the magma cubes.
Wait, so where was it?
Ok, this way?
But it's gonna be really dangerous going over there, I think.
I think we gotta take the sip.
I think we gotta take...
I don't know.
I think it's safer to just let them spawn where, when we...
Ok, there's a, yeah, get him.
I don't know why he's howling.
I don't know why he's howling right now.
Is your dog howling?
Yeah, my dog is howling.
Yeah, see, we have to, like, go down here.
He never howls.
I think it's just safer to...
To...
You can block the skellies in the hallways because they're three blocks tall.
Oh, really?
Ok, good to know.
I don't know.
I just wanna eat my dinner.
I'm making a wall.
I need to check on my dog.
I need to know why he's howling.
We're back.
He's like...
I don't know, check in here.
And I was like, oh my god, why are you howling up your back?
Oh my god.
I got hit by a skelly.
I'm also gonna block this up.
Why do they keep spawning even though I put...
Maybe it's too dark here.
Oh, I thought that was one.
Oh my gosh.
Hey, you.
Come here.
Blaze, blaze, blaze, blaze, blaze.
How many magma cubes we got?
Only one?
We have the one magma cream?
Torches don't work?
No, they usually work for the skellies.
Why do I hear so many things?
I hear blaze, breeze, blaze, crackle, wither, skeleton, crackles.
What's going on?
I don't know.
Is anything bad happening outside?
Okay.
I thought they worked in here for the skellies at least.
I thought the torches worked.
My dog's okay, he's just...
He's being a dog?
Yeah, he's being a little freaky today.
Usually never... I think this is the second time I've ever heard him howl.
Oh my god.
Hello.
Yeah, there's a big guy right here.
He's just like on his pillow.
Just chilling.
Get him, get him so we can get magma cream.
But watch out for the size.
Don't go so far out.
That's what...
Oh wait, I forgot they like multiply.
Yeah.
And then again.
Yep, keep going.
Did they give any magma cream?
They got me one.
Got rid of the bones again.
Okay.
You can hand it to me, I have the magma cream.
Do we need soul sand or soul soil?
None of... We don't need either.
Don't you need to plant the warts in the soul soil?
No, we have plenty.
Okay, so I'll get rid of that.
Okay.
Okay, here we go.
Come here.
Come here!
Come over here!
What if I kill him with my bow and arrow and then you...
Why did you just stand there?
I just wanted to look at him.
I'm gonna kill him and then you parkour.
No!
How was our parkour?
He's too far.
No, he's not.
He's literally right there.
There wasn't any rods anyway.
It doesn't matter.
It would've been eaten by the lava probably.
No, it didn't!
There was no lava over there!
Yeah, yeah.
Likely story.
Oh my gosh, there's so many Wither Skellies here.
This is crazy.
Just keep spawning, I think.
Wait, there's a Blaze Rod right in front of me.
I'm gonna do it.
Blaze Rod?
I mean Blaze.
Blaze.
No, you're not gonna be able to get...
Oh my god, Doki no, please.
I'm gonna do it.
Doki no.
Doki.
I'm gonna do it.
I'm coming back.
I realized there was a mistake.
It was so fast.
Wait, hold on.
I gotta build a wall because...
That's it?
That's all I got?
That's it.
That's your wall.
You're here.
Thanks.
I gotta check if my YouTube keeps freezing.
Chat's frozen, guys.
I'm sorry.
One second.
Just in case.
Just in case, like, I get fucked over too.
I gotta make sure that I'm also safe.
Okay.
Oh, I hear so many noises.
I hear so many noises around us.
Okay.
Okay, are we safe?
Doki's counter says mint death 3.
No, it doesn't.
Gaslighting.
Why are you in here?
What the hell?
I was scared!
Oh my god, you have to be able to handle yourself.
Wait, how do I get out of here?
Which is...
Oh, okay.
I couldn't see.
Wait, how do we get out of here?
I couldn't tell!
It was dark!
Okay.
There must be a Blaze right above us.
We should go get him.
Yeah, I hear him.
You see him?
There's a lot of things right above us.
What the hell is going on up here?
It's a party!
Yeah, I wouldn't do that.
I think I'm gonna go look... I'm gonna look for Blazes in other areas.
What are you gonna do?
Slam me?
Oh my god, don't give me a good time.
Other Blazes in your area.
Don't give me a good time.
We'll get the magma cube.
Magma cream, whatever.
Yeah, I'm getting the magma now.
Wait, did we ever go upstairs like this?
No, because it's scary.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, please.
I'm just...
Please get closer.
There's another magma cream right here.
Oh my god.
It's all right here.
Did you grab the magma cream?
Hold on.
Where is it?
Oh my god.
Oh my god, there's so many.
Yeah, I'm here.
I know, I know, I know.
That's what...
They're multiplying.
I like how this one pig is just watching us.
At least there's no Blazes up here.
We also have to get rid of these guys because then it'll spawn like other mobs.
Oh, we have been here.
Yeah, we've been up this way, yeah.
Yeah, you said we haven't.
No, I thought you meant like on... in that little area room.
There we go.
How many... Oh, I have only two.
I have one of them.
You got the other one.
This sucks.
They're not dropping anything.
They're so far away.
Why can't they spawn faster?
Put out some torches, Mint, so mobs spawn inside.
Which is it?
Do they... Do the torches work?
Do the torches not work?
I was just... You guys just said that the torches don't work.
What is it?
I got... I got fucking sniped.
He's like all the way over there.
I'm telling you, that's why... That's why you don't go out there.
We know... We know there's a spawner, but the spawner is danger zone.
The spawner is really far, guys.
We can't get there.
It's like separated.
We can't cross.
Right below where you were is a spawner thing?
Below us?
Below?
I think maybe they mean... Oh my God!
Oh my God, hello.
Wait, how did he get here?
He spawned.
Oh, blaze rod!
Nice.
We got two.
Okay, we got two.
Okay.
There's a much closer spawner?
Where?
There is?
I feel like we walked everywhere.
I feel like we walked everywhere too.
Yeah.
We went down here, yeah?
Okay.
We're getting one guide?
I can't tell.
There's one guide that said we're getting one guide, but there's three people said that...
I know, sometimes people will say one guide, but multiple people will say the same thing.
So I don't know.
Oh, hello.
Regular skelly.
I'm trying.
Stupid regular skelly.
Is next to the broken bridge?
There's a broken bridge?
Next to a broken bridge.
Are you okay?
I'm not okay.
Oh God, there's two of them!
Holy shit.
Remember when I said I wasn't okay?
I got one.
I got hit.
I got hit too.
Who's hitting us?
I got you.
It's a bow.
It's a skelly.
Regular skelly.
Regular old Joe Skelly.
Come on.
Watch out.
On the top floor right below the broken bridge?
What the fuck does any of those words mean?
On the top floor right below a broken bridge, there is a blaze spawner.
This floor?
The floor I'm on right now?
The scary floor?
Right here?
Right before a broken bridge?
Oh my God.
Huh?
In the middle of summer?
Make shops?
I just started spamming.
I forget to make the shops.
This is the top floor.
This is the very top.
Here?
This is a broken bridge?
That broken bridge?
Watch out.
There's a guy who's going to start shooting.
There's 200 fucking things here.
I just left it right here to my left?
This one?
Where?
The War of Borealis?
Right here?
In the middle of the fortress?
Oh, there it is.
Yeah, there it is.
Wait, where?
Oh, I see you.
Yeah, there it is.
It's right there.
Look at the corner to your left.
I think it's the wither spawner.
There is no wither spawner.
Oh, wait.
Maybe it is.
Yeah, I think this is the wither spawner.
Oh my god.
It's just a wither... Wait, is that a thing?
A wither spawner?
Oh my god.
The one thing we... I didn't even know wither...
It's a blaze!
Oh shit.
I was gonna say, I don't think blaze spawners exist.
I'm trying to get rid of the skellies.
Get rid of everything.
Oh my god.
We gotta build a bridge.
I know.
Okay, one of us has to build and one of us has to take out the guys.
Okay, I got you.
I got the arrows.
Okay.
You can actually... Oh my god.
You need to defend yourself too though.
Okay, I'm gonna eat.
I'm running out of arrows.
I just need you to know that.
Oh, that's not good.
That's not great.
Oh shit.
Don't do it.
Don't cross.
I have my shield up.
I need to make bread.
I ran out of food.
Okay, there's three guys now, so...
That's not good.
I'm making bread.
Just calm down.
Calm down.
I'm calm.
Oh my god.
Why is there a gas?
There's a gas?
I don't think I will be able to make it enough, everybody.
I got... I got one.
Where's our gas from?
I don't know.
Stop getting hit.
I killed two.
Oh my god.
You're gaming.
You're gaming right now.
I ran out of arrows, so it's up to you.
I killed three.
Alright, you did it.
You did it.
You should be able to go now.
Okay, but... Help me.
Help me.
Here.
Half.
I give you half.
Okay.
How?
I...
Take it.
Okay, I need to know there's a gas somewhere.
There's a gas somewhere.
Somewhere.
Okay, I'm gonna speed this.
Oh my god.
You don't come back.
Come back.
I heard a blaze.
I hear him.
He's right here.
Build a wall.
Here.
You keep building the bridge.
Build the bridge.
Oh, he came back.
He came back.
Oh shit!
Ah, shit!
I gotta eat, I gotta eat.
I'm gonna drink it!
I'm gonna drink the fire resistance!
No!
Actually, that might be the good...
Actually, this might be the good time to do it.
I'm gonna do it.
Okay.
Keep building, keep building!
I need you to build for me.
What do you...
What do you mean?
You have the fire resistance!
Why did you...
Can I still get hit?
Yes, you can get hit!
Would I die?
Oh, I missed him.
No!
Just spam attack!
The fire can't hurt you right now!
Okay, okay!
Oh shit, oh shit.
Where are they?
Oh my god.
Okay, I gotta drink my potion.
I gotta drink my potion.
I'm hitting them.
Where's my potion?
Okay, I'm coming in!
Oh my god, they're still hitting me!
It doesn't hurt me, but why am I still getting hit?
Why am I still getting hit?
Wait, really?
With the fire even?
Yeah.
Wait, do you have torches?
Do you have extra torches?
Someone said she has full HP.
Oh, hey, I have six.
What the fuck, man?
Okay, I'm out of torches.
I'm out of torches?
I have torches.
I'm okay now.
Okay, we need to get these guys.
Oh my god.
Please, come over here and die.
I'm just gonna put this here for now.
I can't.
Regular-ass Skelly, get out of the way!
I need these guys to get out first.
Okay, hold on.
We'll let them spawn in when things start calming down.
He's on me!
Oh my god.
Who is... There's 20 things on me too!
Oh, they can do melee damage?
Wow.
Give them more stuff to do, I guess.
I got it.
Blaze rod, blaze rod, blaze rod, blaze rod.
I have... I have four blaze rods.
I can't pick it up.
I need you to pick it up.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
It's up here, it's up here, it's up here.
Up here.
What's the point of attacking these bozos?
Okay.
Oh my god, I'm getting a stomachache from all this.
Oh my god, I'm gonna freak out soon.
How much is left?
It's gonna be like...
Okay, a minute and a half left on my thing.
You probably have less than.
It's gonna be my fifth freakout right here.
Oh, I just fell inside.
Oh my god.
No.
Oh no.
Alright, they're gonna spawn in again.
Okay.
I'm building our escape route.
I'm building our escape route while it's calm.
I don't have arrows.
Do you have?
Oh, I do.
Try and kill them.
Try and kill them here though.
How many do I have left?
I can't see.
Use your shield!
One... One... One second is gone.
I don't have fire resistance.
I'm waiting for the spawner.
I got another.
Nice, nice.
I got five.
You have six, right?
You have one, right?
I have one.
Oh shit.
Okay.
Oh, you're fine.
You're fine.
Sure.
Sure, sure.
There's another arrow.
There's another one.
Oh my god.
These guys... I'm gonna murder them.
I'm gonna murder them.
These stupid skellies.
I hate them so much.
Oh, there's another spawner in front of us!
Yes!
There's another... That's the one that I was looking at!
I'm gonna block... I'm gonna block this area.
I'm gonna block this area.
I need to heal before we go in.
I can.
Okay, I can.
Okay.
Okay, I have six.
I have six.
We need... Oh, I need ten.
Okay.
Yeah, we need several more.
I'll break the torches again.
I needed it to calm down.
I needed things to calm down...
Okay, I'm blocking these walls.
I'm blocking these walls.
Okay, I'm blocking...
Actually... Yeah, like, make it so that when they spawn in...
They can't leave.
Oh my god.
No!
Are you okay?
No.
Oh my god.
Hello.
I'm not okay.
I need to heal.
I'm not okay anymore.
Get behind me.
Okay, I need to heal.
I need to heal.
Go heal.
I'm not okay.
I'm actually... I'm gonna fucking collapse.
Okay, I killed him.
Okay.
I got two.
I got two rounds.
Okay, we have A.
We have A.
Oh, your helmet broke.
Your helmet broke.
Oh, is that why?
Okay, that makes more sense.
That's why I was taking so much fucking damage.
Oh my god!
Oh my god.
Go back!
Throw a grenade!
Oh my god.
When they're on... Oh my god.
When they're on fire, they're about to, like, attack.
So, like, attack when they're not on fire, and then, like, shield up when they get on fire.
Oh my god!
How did that still hit me?
I'm backing up.
Don't be a hero, Mint.
Don't be a hero.
Okay, I gotta heal.
I gotta heal.
Don't be a hero.
Oh my god!
I don't have arrows, guys!
Oh, I do.
Oh my god.
Do you have arrows?
Yes, here.
Spectral arrows.
There you go.
Give me all of it.
Give me all your arrows.
I gave you all.
Oh my god.
They're still spawning.
Oh shit!
Shit!
I killed three.
I don't have any more torches!
I have torches.
Okay.
Oh my god!
How is it still hitting me?
I don't have any more arrows.
I don't have any more.
I don't have any.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm going in.
Get out!
I can't risk it!
I can't!
We can't get out!
We can't!
The thing is, we have to return home, but this is the only way we can go home!
Oh my god.
This is the only...
I know.
I'm drinking the other potion.
You have another potion?!
I'm drinking one more potion.
I'm going in.
I'm going in with these potions.
Okay, okay.
I've got it.
I'm going in.
I can't leave!
I got another rod though.
That's cool.
How many do we need?
I don't know.
I went in.
Oh my god.
We have ten!
I have ten!
We made it!
Get this guy!
Okay, I think we can leave then, right?
I made an escape route.
Do you have enough food?
Are you good?
Yeah, I'm good.
Oh my god.
Now we go home.
Going home!
Alright, do you have obsidian?
I have two obsidian!
Alright, time to walk over.
Wait, is it really ten is enough?
We have thirteen.
With you, we have thirteen.
Oh, okay.
I'm going to give you my other three.
There we go.
We'll just keep them all together.
Ten is minimal.
We have thirteen.
That's good.
Thirteen is good.
People were saying fourteen is like the absolute safe, so thirteen is good.
Watch out!
What are you looking at?
Why are you wearing a gold...
Because my helmet is broken!
I don't want to get beat up by the pigs!
No!
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
I got you.
Okay, how do we get out of here?
There's a gold chestplate if you need this.
Oh, okay.
I'll take it.
Just in case your helmet breaks.
Oh my god, it's almost dead.
Alright, how do we go home?
How do we get out of here?
What would be the easiest way?
We traveled very far.
Very far.
Let's just get out of the fortress first so that we don't die.
Someone said trade for more obsidian.
We should.
I left my crafting table, so I gotta make another one.
Oh, I can make one.
I just made it.
Okay, nevermind.
Okay, so I'm gonna make the...
I'm watching out for any guys to attack.
Alright, do you have any nuggies or no?
No nuggies.
Alright, so I have... I have 16 gold for obsidian.
How many obsidian do we need?
We need 10.
We have...
Okay, we have 4.
Yeah, we have 4.
Give me your obsidian.
Okay.
That's fine.
We're so paranoid.
I know.
We are paranoid.
Alright, we gotta figure out... How do we get here?
Okay, now we just have to...
We gotta go back to...
How do we... How did we get in here?
How did we get here?
Did you go down here?
I didn't open that up.
No, I did.
I did.
We gotta find the other assault place.
No.
No, not here.
Not here.
Oh my god.
I can't believe we did it.
We actually did it.
We didn't get one guide.
I know.
I can't believe there's a horrible realis right here in the kitchen.
It was right here.
It was actually right here.
Oh my god.
I have such a bad stomachache right now.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna puke up all my mac and cheese.
From the stress?
Yeah, from the stress of it all.
How did we get out in here?
How did we get here?
I don't understand.
Oh, is it here?
Where?
No, I'm just seeing things.
I'm just...
Watch out for Wither Skelly.
I'm just seeing things now.
I don't know anymore.
Everything looks the same.
Every...
How did we get in here?
I don't know.
We came from the top of the fortress.
Yeah, so up here.
But there was like other...
Oh shit.
Wait, here, here, here, here.
Hold on.
I found it, I found it.
Okay, hold on.
I got it.
Where?
Downstairs?
I found it.
Follow my...
Look at my name tag.
I don't see it.
Everything is...
Right here, right here, right here.
Oh my gosh.
What was that?
It's here, it's here.
Okay.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
We dug that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, good, good, good.
Oh, we came from above.
We came up from above, remember?
Yeah, but there was an area that we dropped in.
Right here, no, right here, right here.
Yeah, yeah, I built ourselves a stairs.
Okay.
Kind of.
Well, I was in the process of doing it.
Hold on.
Great stairs.
Thanks.
There we go.
They actually do work if you, you know...
You, you know, not use it as a staircase.
It's a staircase.
I literally just used it.
No, it's not.
It's not a staircase.
I literally just used it.
There was one block that I couldn't go up from.
Hey, we wouldn't have found this thing if it wasn't for me, okay?
So, you know, give me some, cut me some slack.
Oh, I hear a ghast.
I'm scared.
We just have to get to an area with...
Oh, shit.
Hide, hide, hide, hide, hide.
Go, go, go, go.
Is that ghast?
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god.
And you have no arrows?
I have no arrows?
Oh my god.
I have no arrows.
I have two bones.
Oh, shit.
We gotta go through the forest.
That's okay.
The forest is fine.
It's just Enderman.
We gotta...
We gotta do it.
I have one arrow?
Oh, I do have an arrow.
Where did this come from?
Yeah, but it takes two arrows.
It takes two arrows to kill him.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, um...
How can we get over there?
There's so many Endermen.
Watch out for blazes.
The blazes are really far.
They shoot from everywhere.
It's crazy.
Is the ghast still there?
I don't see him.
Can we do it?
Do we need to despawn?
Maybe.
Parkour.
Oh, shit.
Ah, shit.
I'm in trouble.
Make a wall.
I did.
I made a wall.
Make a wall.
I'm making a wall, Maya, too.
I ran out.
Make a wall.
I'm a little stuck.
Keep making walls.
I'm almost...
Okay, I have cobblestone.
Okay, okay.
I'm making walls for us.
Where are you?
I can't hear.
Oh, I see you.
Flying higher.
They're flying higher.
Okay.
Alright, I've made a wall.
Come down here when you can.
Come down?
Yeah, we have to get to the forest.
We have to get down.
Oh, my God.
Why are you shooting?
Who can you even see?
Me.
That's who.
Okay, well, come down.
Come down.
Okay.
I'm making walls.
Who can you even see?
I'm literally behind you.
Hold on.
I thought you were...
I thought you were covered.
Okay, I'm almost really out of everything that I have.
I'm thinking I'm stealing stuff I had.
Oh, don't look.
Don't look at them.
Because we ran out of stone.
We ran out of stone.
So don't look at them.
No, I still have a little bit of stone.
I still have a little bit of stone.
Yes, but we...
Their Endermen are right below us.
I know.
Their Endermen are right below us, so don't look at them.
Oh shit.
Here you go.
We're not safe.
No, we're not.
Thank you, but we're not safe from the blazes.
Oh no.
Please despawn blazes.
How are we supposed...
Okay, I think...
Oh gosh.
I think we might have to like...
Jump and just run into the forest.
And then dig into the wall.
Okay.
This is how we die.
Wait, have your pickaxe...
Well, I have mine ready.
Have your...
Have your everything ready.
Okay, I'm gonna eat real quick.
Yeah, sword or pickaxe?
Sword or pickaxe?
Pickaxe probably.
Because who are we fighting?
The Endermen?
I don't know.
What if we accidentally look at them?
Okay, true.
Alright, I'm gonna go down.
Okay, we're safe for now.
Alright, let's go.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Just run.
Be careful here.
There's a huge hole.
There's a huge hole right here.
Oh my gosh.
Just run.
Okay, I think we're safe from the blazes though.
Okay.
Oh my god.
Oh my...
We gotta find the pigs.
We gotta get back to pigs.
Pig territory.
We gotta get...
We gotta get back to the...
Wait!
The red area is where we came from.
Oh shoot.
But it was the ghast...
We can't, we can't.
There's ghast.
The ghast blocked us.
We can't...
We gotta find our own red area.
Let's just dig through here and we can dig to the right and we might make it back into that area.
Took us three hours to find a fortress.
Oh my god.
Oh, thank you.
I thought for a second that I was about to be like...
Wait, you didn't just dig and like get...
Get lava?
This is good though.
We're replenishing our...
That's good.
Are you digging?
No, there's like literally holes underneath you.
There's holes underneath you.
Alright, I'm gonna dig here.
Watch out, watch out.
Okay.
Believe in you.
I won't dig to the side cause...
Yeah, don't dig.
Just let me dig.
I'll dig us out of here.
And we'll go to the red hopefully.
I'm gonna make some bread.
And then we just...
Then we will be out.
Oh my gosh.
Imagine we'll see sunlight.
Oh my god.
And then we never have to go there again.
Don't say that.
Do not say that.
If we have the worst luck ever...
We'll never have to go there again.
It's okay.
I have my diamond.
Unless...
Don't be so funny.
Something just happened.
I bet Chat is feeling so much more...
Like confident in us now though.
We have to make arrows.
We can make arrows with regular materials.
Yeah, but we need...
What do we need?
We don't have string.
What?
Wait, don't you need string for arrows?
I have 32 string.
Oh, okay.
We're fine.
Oh my god.
We can create lots of beds.
Yeah, we can do the bed strut.
Yeah.
Flint, stick, and feather.
Yeah, we don't even need string.
We need strings for bows, but not for arrows.
Watch out!
I'm literally 20 feet away from you.
Of course you are.
You're ticking with lava.
Are you okay?
I'm taking sippy.
What the hell was that?
I don't fucking know.
Oh, that's the Enderman to our left.
No, but like something screamed.
Enderman whoops?
Is that what they're called?
Enderman be whoops?
What is that?
That has to be a gas, right?
It's not showing up on my thing as a gas.
I have no idea.
I don't know what that was.
That was weird.
I didn't hear it.
How long is this mountain?
Oh, I spoke too soon?
We're still in the... Oh my god.
I don't like that sound that you just heard because we ran out of bows and arrows.
Yeah, we have to not encounter that guy.
We're like deep in the forest.
I think this didn't work.
I think the red area is to our right.
To the right?
You want to dig?
Follow the cords.
What cords?
We didn't take cords.
The coordinates back to our original...
Our very first portal.
The one that's a hundred miles away from us.
Is it this?
A little tiny spot right here?
Oh, I guess we were really close to the...
Oh, hello.
We were really close to the...
What's it called?
Yeah, but then there's that big forest that we came from.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
We were really close to a forest when we got to just a little regular guy area.
Wait, what was our coordinates for our original place?
The original portal?
Yeah, yeah, original portal.
Hold on, I have to...
I want to see how far we are from it.
Wait, there's a piglin!
Piglin snorting?
Where at?
Where are you piglin snorting?
Can we go up?
He might be above us.
Yeah, I think he is.
You have all the... You gathered all the netherite, right?
So I don't have it.
Oh, here's a stack.
He's behind us, he's behind us.
Who's behind... Oh, hello.
Oh my god, Endy, hello.
Yeah, he's behind us.
Let me get the cords from the original one.
Okay, let me check.
Alright, are you ready to...
Yeah, what is it?
Um...
Are the... It's negative...
Two thousand... Oh, sorry, no.
Negative five hundred and five...
Uh...
One hundred ninety-five.
We're not making it back.
You wanna know what we are?
You know...
Oh, I'm looking at what we are.
Looking at what we are.
We're not getting back there.
We gotta say goodbye.
Oh, we traveled that far?
Say goodbye to that lapis block.
Say goodbye to...
I see a ghast.
I see a ghast floating over there.
Oh gosh, okay.
I guess we build up.
Build up.
We gotta just build up.
We traveled...
We are adventurers.
This is why the... This is why the earth isn't round.
Because in Minecraft, it's clearly flat.
Oh my god, please.
Do you hear him?
Yes, I do.
I'm trying to not look behind me.
If you come up here, there's like a safe little area.
Oh wait, we're in the mushroom area.
I know.
But come up here.
Come up here.
Where is here?
Where did you go?
I don't know.
I don't know anymore.
Oh, there you are.
Hey, I'm here.
Where are you?
Tokyo is a flat earth.
I almost looked at that guy.
Where are you?
Turn around.
Oh, hello.
Oh, okay.
I was gonna say in here is a safe little area.
Oh my gosh, what if we just set up shop and...
What if we just lived here forever?
This is where we live.
We're just never gonna end stream.
We're just gonna be here like domestic life right here.
Wait, the red is in front of us.
It's literally in front of us.
It is?
Oh yeah, you're right.
It is right there.
Okay, thank goodness.
We are putting all our gotcha luck into this right now.
Wait, how many pearls do we have?
Do we have enough enderpearls?
Okay, maybe you do gotcha.
We have to get back there.
We have to get back there because all their enderpearls are there.
Oh my god, are you serious?
All their enderpearls are there.
I didn't bring them.
I didn't bring the enderpearls.
I left them all there.
We have to, when we get out of here, we have to find our area.
We have to travel.
Okay, well, what if we don't do that and we just farm enderpearls right here?
I mean, you do you.
I'm gonna find a piglet and trade.
Well, yeah, keep trading.
We gotta get the...
I put it there because I thought we'd come back.
How far did you think we were gonna...
You thought we were just gonna go for a little brisk walk?
Like just a little...
Oh my god.
I didn't think we'd never come back.
I thought we'd never come back.
I really did.
I thought we were just gonna travel there for a little bit and then we'd come back.
There's one more over there.
I got one.
Oh, he's looking at you.
Yeah, I got him.
Yeah, you keep trading.
You keep trading.
I'm carrying the brewing stand.
I have the brewing stand.
I have the brewing stand, guys.
Don't worry.
Blackstone again.
I have the brewing stand.
I brought it with me.
I thought ahead.
Is that also blackstone?
Wait, if he gives you obsidian, let me know.
I'll take it.
He keeps giving me, like, corrupted obsidian.
What?
What if you went above ground and traveled 20,000 blocks back to the portal in the overworld?
Well, that's where our stuff is.
Wait.
That's where we... That's what we did.
Wait, wait, I'm confused.
Oh no.
Above ground?
Huh?
It's like the world limit.
Oh, like...
Huh?
It's like you can go all the way up for the world limit thing.
Wait, like create a new portal and travel in the normal world.
That's what we're wanting to do.
That's what we're trying to do.
We're trying to figure it out.
We're trying to do that.
But we just don't have obsidian.
We just don't have obsidian.
Yeah, we're trying to collect the obsidian.
Obsidian!
I'm also just farming blocks.
I mean, I mean pearls, because it's, you know, we're...
Oh my god, my gacha luck is not doing so well.
Man, my gacha luck isn't doing so well.
I've got everything, but I have leather?
I have leather?
Wow!
Is that it?
Oh, I have one obsidian!
I got one obsidian!
We have five obsidian!
Okay, I can make... I can make another...
I can make more gold.
Hey, little Enderman!
I have five more gold.
I'm coming for you, Enderman.
Show me your sweet, sweet, slender body.
You have that, you're an Enderman.
Oh, come on, look at this, look at this, look at this juicy...
Juicy gold!
How much gold do you have?
I have... Here, take my axe, I don't need it anymore.
And my axe!
Take my axe, I don't even want it.
Okay.
Come on, take it.
The aether, what's that?
I heard a ghastly, I heard a ghastly, I got PTSD.
I know, I hear him too.
Just ignore.
Unless we see...
How many enderpearls do you have?
Two!
Okay.
I'm trying to... There's no Enderman around here.
Uh-oh, he sounds close.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, here's one.
Here's one what?
Oh, thank you.
I managed to get one.
Do you have any nuggets at all?
No.
No, I don't.
Okay, so...
Yeah, that's it.
We gotta farm more gold.
We gotta find more gold.
There's some above us, there's...
I'm gonna do it, I'm gonna trade my axe.
This is the last axe off the back of my...
You can trade your axe?
Yeah, you can trade gold items.
Where is the...
Seer, sir.
Is this all I have, sir?
This is... Please...
This is all I have.
Okay, hold on, I'm gonna look around for some gold.
I don't have any more.
This is everything I have.
What did he give me?
I don't know what he gave me.
But what did he take from you?
What did he even give me?
He gave me nothing!
He just puts it in his inventory!
No, I'm afraid of trading my helmet.
Wait, wait...
My armor has way more... My body...
Then I would have to wear a chest plate and it has way more...
I don't give stuff for gold.
I got one guide!
Somebody... Don't give him your stuff, don't give him your stuff.
Okay, hold on, hold on.
There is...
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
I found some gold.
And I just gotta... Hold on, I gotta create a little barrier for it so it doesn't fall into the...
Into the world, but we'll mine it, we'll mine it.
They looked at me and just took it and he just took it!
Oh, shoot.
Took it from me.
It was the last thing I owned.
Is there anyone around here?
I don't think so.
He just took it from me.
That's so cruel.
Wait, where is it?
Oh, oh no!
Oh, here we go.
Okay, now we're good.
I can't believe he just took it like that.
Really?
You can't believe it?
I can't believe it.
I feel like I just got robbed.
Dragoon did... That Dragoon did more mental damage than, like, someone...
I just got robbed.
He, like, looked at me and just...
Looked and just walked away.
Walked away with my golden axe.
I have 36 Nuggies.
Wait, where are you?
Okay, I'm here.
I'm coming.
Alright, here's the crafting table.
There you go.
I have, like, four on me too.
Oh, I saw an Enderman, I think.
Hello?
There he is.
Okay.
Yeah, get angry.
Get angry.
Drop your pearl.
Put all your money in the bag, little Enderman.
Put all your money in the bag.
Come on.
Come on, there's two of you.
Surely two of you.
Oh my God, he gave me so sad.
He gave me so sad.
Wait, what's this?
Oh, I got an Obsidian!
Obsidian!
Nice!
We just need two more!
Two more!
Oh, we just need two more.
I don't have gold anymore.
Oh, well, we gotta find some more.
We gotta find some more.
We gotta find, we gotta find.
Back into the nether mines we go.
The nether mines.
Oh, but we're, like, really far up, so it's, like, hard to dig.
Okay, I'm just gonna dig.
And pray.
I'm gonna pray for no...
find stuff in the nether mines.
Okay, right here.
The nether mines to get out of this hellhole.
We're doing it!
You found more nuggies?
No, but we're just, you know, we're doing something.
We're here.
I saw the Enderman.
I'm looking around for nuggies for us.
I'm not gonna TNT, guys.
We're too high up.
It's too risky.
No, don't do it.
We can't.
It's too risky.
Maybe here.
I'm just gonna block that guy up.
Okay, it's too risky.
Alright, I got some nuggies.
Okay, nice.
I'm digging for nuggies.
I have 51 on me.
No, nice.
I'm gonna make some now.
I don't know how I got up here.
I'm scared.
How did I get so high up?
I don't know.
What did I do?
You were like blinded by the gold.
By the gold.
I have gold sickness.
We're literally like the guys in Pocahontas.
Gold, beautiful gold.
Gold.
I don't know how this song goes.
I have 5 more gold.
There's gas.
Yeah.
There's a gas right in front of us.
I'm in a cave.
Looking for gold.
I am.
There's a gas right here.
Just hide and he'll despawn eventually.
Oh my God, don't rob me, little piggy.
Don't rob me, child.
I hear him.
He's like right there.
I don't have arrows.
Do you see where I am?
You can hide with me if you want.
I saw your name tag.
Oh my God, he broke my crafting table.
No, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
He broke your crafting table.
I got it.
I got it back.
I have wood, so if you do need another one...
Where did my other stack of wood go?
Oh, I do have...
There we go.
I put some torches out in case you...
Okay, this ghastly is like...
Cooking me from the pigs.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
Just hide and wait until he despawns.
But I was just...
I tossed it back in the fortress.
Oops.
Oh, why is he here?
I think it's really messed up that ghasts can spawn in all biomes.
I think that's like the problem.
I think...
I think whoever invented that just hates fun.
Seriously.
I think he just...
I think he just hates people.
It's actually the worst creature in Minecraft.
The worst.
There's two now!
Two just spawned!
Instead of it despawning, two showed up!
We'll get bored of each other eventually.
Probably.
Oh, shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot!
No!
Somebody was like...
I have eight.
Okay, alright.
Time to use my eight arrows.
I have one arrow.
Alright.
Eight and a dream.
Let's go.
Oh, they despawned.
They actually despawned because I started crying.
Oh, good.
I cried too.
It worked.
Why can't I get any gold?
Okay, you know what?
I give up.
I'm sorry.
I tried.
It's fine.
We're gonna risk it all on these five golds that I have.
The five golds left.
The five golds.
There's a lot of endermen now.
If you wanna come over here to farm more enderpearls.
Yeah, I'm looking around for them.
Wherever they...
What the...
Oh my god.
Stop it!
Shut up!
Freak!
I don't have anything!
Oh my god.
It's just magmas.
Please.
Like the fire starters?
What is that?
What is this?
I got a splash potion of fire resistance.
Oh, that's good though.
Oh, I got a pearl.
I got a pearl.
I got another.
I got another obsidian.
I got another one.
Oh, nice.
Nice.
One more.
I don't have gold.
I don't have anymore gold.
You wanna...
Here, come to my cave.
It's bad, but I started it so you can find it because...
No, I don't...
I don't trust myself.
I don't...
In here.
I don't trust myself.
It's safe in here.
What if I dig to lava?
What if I dig into lava?
Then just...
Then you...
Then you block it.
Then you block the lava.
Oh my god, how many lavas did you block?
Wait, we need ten?
I thought we needed eight.
Nope.
Guess it wasn't eight.
Yes.
Oh, never mind.
We need ten.
Oh.
We need three more.
Okay.
It's three on each side.
Two on top.
Oh.
I found quartz.
Look at that.
Look at that silly quartz over there.
Oh, it's ten without the corners.
Oh, I thought it was ten with the corners.
What the hell is that sound?
Look at that.
It's so silly.
So silly.
Silly little quartz.
Oh, there's another ghast.
Somewhere.
What?
What happened?
Lava?
Lava.
Yeah.
Just stay far enough back.
Are you sure there's gonna be gold here?
Are you sure?
I don't know.
I'm saying you can just use my hole.
Oh, it's a used hole.
I'm sorry.
Go build your own new hole.
Go get your own new hole.
I don't know.
Go!
I said that because I used it.
Then probably you would...
And I didn't find anything in there.
Then probably you would do it and then...
It's a bad hole.
You would find it.
You know, that's how that works, right?
I'm gonna go up.
It must be...
I wish the ghast would disappear.
Please leave.
You're not welcome here.
This is our hole.
You're not welcome.
Nobody likes you.
Even your mother hates you.
Your mother put you up for adoption.
Nobody adopted you.
Oh my god.
You were thinking the same thing.
I don't think I was thinking that extreme.
That far.
You were thinking the same thing.
Don't lie.
It was in your head.
I don't know...
The ghasts...
How do they...
How do they board?
Stay back mister.
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
I'm getting cold.
But I'm doing the most risky shit to get this fucking cold.
Do you want TNT?
No!
That's risky shit, man.
I can give you the good risky stuff.
TNT.
It's the real risky stuff.
Come on.
Blow it all up.
Blow it to hell, doggy!
Open air gold?
You gotta go to TNT Anonymous.
I got more magma...
Magma cream.
Magma cream...
Will help us make more fire resistant stuff, I guess.
You know, man...
I feel like we're gonna make it to the end...
And then we're gonna die.
Don't say that.
I've been thinking it this literal entire time.
Don't...
I've been literally thinking it this entire time.
I think...
I think we're gonna make it...
The Ender Dragon is not that bad.
All we need is the slow falling.
What if we get there...
You know, we do the thing...
And then, like, the Ender Dragon...
He sweeps up...
And then knocks us out of the thing...
And then...
All we need is the slow falling.
And then it happens.
What do we need?
How do we make it?
How do we make what?
Slow falling.
Oh, we need the phantoms.
We need to not sleep.
OK.
OK, that's fine.
That should be fine, right?
That should be fine.
Yeah, we can do that.
We can just...
We can chill in a village...
And...
When we don't sleep...
We just don't sleep...
What?
What is...
No, that's not a...
It's a good thing.
Oh, it's a good guess.
What is it?
I found netherite.
Oh, just one?
Don't you know we need a lot more?
Yeah, but I found some even at 78.
Oh, I found two netherites.
OK, now that's the good shit.
There's a ghast here.
Why is there a ghast here?
I have to use the arrow.
I'm scared.
Never mind this, though.
Where did he go?
No lava.
I know, I need no lava.
Oh my gosh, I can't believe there was two!
Wow.
OK.
I didn't pick it up.
Oh shit, you're right.
OK, I have six now.
I have six gold.
Alright, all in.
I know the lava won't burn it, but I don't want to die.
Yeah, baby!
Oh my gosh.
Wowee.
Quartz?
Lucky baby.
Please, out of these six, just give me obsidian.
Please, not magma!
I gave you six gold!
I
got crying obsidian.
Crying obsidian?
That's literally you.
He gave me crying out of all the obsidians.
I'm so sorry, I wasn't specific enough regarding the exact type of obsidian I needed.
I'm so sorry.
How much diamond do you have?
I have eleven.
OK.
My pickaxe is about to...
Actually, I'll just make an iron one.
Alright, back into the mines we go.
Back into the...
I'm mining too.
Oh, you got some gold?
No.
I haven't gotten literally anything.
I got the netherite actually.
That's literally the only thing we actually need.
Is gold, I know.
Oh, and I made it to the other side.
I wish I kept all that obsidian.
I wish I kept all that obsidian earlier.
There's so many...
So much endermen around me.
I wish we were here exterminating them.
I don't trust myself making a little house.
OK, I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming.
It's just a little house.
I don't trust myself.
There's like four endermen right next to me.
I hear a ghastly though.
Alright, come to me, come to me and make a house.
Oh my god, you're still alive?
Yes, we've been in the nether.
Yes, yes.
We have been in the nether for like maybe two hours.
Where are you?
Two hours.
Look up.
Hold on, I'm getting endermen.
Come here.
Come here, Endy.
Endy.
One more.
One more again.
One more, one more.
And this guy too.
Where are you?
I'm with endermen too.
I see gold, but it's kind of like...
It might be risky.
No, they're very risky gold.
They are definitely very risky gold.
I've been enjoying some risky gold lately.
I've been risking it all.
The thrill of the hunt.
Are you feeling the thrill?
Oh, I feel it.
I'm feeling it, Mr. Krabs.
I'm fucking feeling it right now.
Oh my gosh, nothing.
I left for four hours.
What happened?
Oh, that's a good one.
That's a good one.
Oh, that's good.
That's rich.
That's real rich.
Where are you?
I'm fucking feeling really, really risky right now.
This is really risky.
Don't, don't, please.
It'd be so silly if something just... something happened.
Oh my god, ghast.
No, please.
I'm coming back.
Ghast gold.
I have more.
I have more gold.
Let's go.
I got a stack.
Oh, I almost fell into this.
That would have been pretty dramatic.
That would have been pretty bad, I'd say.
I have seven.
I have seven more.
Seven more stacks.
Let's go.
Seven more.
I'm trying to... I thought I saw some gold over here.
I was just gonna...
Oh, there you go.
Oh, I see some up here.
Okay, I'll get that.
Alright, here we go.
Oh, this might be risky, but...
We'll see.
There he is.
Going through.
How many inner pearls do you have?
Three.
Yeah, three, so we have six.
Oh, here's the arrows.
I'm getting more gold.
What'd he give you?
Is that it?
I'm so sorry.
I got another one.
We got another one.
We need two more.
Yes, we need two more.
Did I grab that?
Wait, where did it go?
Where did the... Where did it go?
No!
Where did it go?
We'll never know.
Thank you for the arrow, sir.
Alright, last one.
Last one.
I like when people come in and are just like, how have they been up to this for eight hours?
We're not speedrunners.
It's gravel.
It's fucking gravel.
Here, I have fourteen pieces of nuggets.
Fourteen?
Only fourteen nuggets?
I'm sorry!
It was all that I could get!
Only fourteen nuggets?
Okay.
That nugget could be life or death.
Alright, here's... Where are you?
Here you go.
Here's the obsidian next to you.
Oh, wait.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
He won't attack you.
He's aggroed on you.
Where is it?
Did you give it to me?
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no.
I took it back.
I'll give it to you later.
Oh, I got it.
Okay, come here.
I'll take it.
Alright, here you go.
Here you go.
Here's two more.
We just need two!
Two out of two?
Crying obsidian.
At least he gave us two.
Quartz.
Hey, he gave us two though!
He gave us two!
There's a lot above us.
I'm fucking doing it.
It's life or death.
It's above us.
I'm fucking... I'm going for it.
I'm gonna go for it.
I'm gonna go above.
I'm going up.
I'm gonna go up and see the world!
Mom!
I'm gonna do it!
Okay, when you do it, build like a little bridge underneath it and don't lock underneath it, you know?
I'm gonna see the world!
Where is this?
I'll catch them all.
Catch them all!
They're in the trees.
I got one of them.
Hold on, I got one.
I got one.
There's more over there.
Okay, there's more over here too.
I'm gonna grab it.
Wait, I can't grab it.
Oh, shoot.
Oh, get rid of that.
Okay, there we go.
I grabbed some.
I don't know where the other ones are.
Okay, I got some here too.
How many you got?
Nine?
Okay, I got 21.
Okay, there's more over here.
I'm gonna fucking...
They're just like, yeah, take her tower.
No!
Do you know how much we've been through?
We've been through so much.
We are past sabotage!
We're past it.
We are so past it.
Please!
They're like, haha, wouldn't it be funny?
I know you've been streaming for eight hours, but what if you just killed her right now?
Don't worry, we'll just do it.
We don't have to kill each other.
The dragon's gonna do it for us!
No, it's not!
We'll just do the bed strut.
Catch it!
Catch what?
I don't even know where you are!
Okay, hold on.
I see you.
I caught it.
Oh, I see you.
Grab that one.
You got it.
Oh, no, you didn't get it.
There you go.
You got it.
Okay, I have 37 here.
I have nine.
Okay, pass it along.
Pass it along.
I'm getting mad.
I've got another seven rolls.
I think we could've traveled back!
I think!
No, we definitely could not have.
We could've died.
No, you're right.
Yeah, we definitely could not have.
You're right.
We definitely would've died.
Yeah.
Where is the Enderman?
Enderman!
Please, my sweet Enderman.
Oh my god, I don't want the child to rob me again.
No, I don't want...
Don't Akasupa with that.
You're trying to bait me.
Oh, to kill me?
No!
You're trying to make me say something!
I know what you're trying to make me say.
I don't want your stupid iron nuggets, please.
He was kind of far, but...
Oh my god, please.
Why do you keep giving me cry obsidian?
I wish you could like decry the obsidian.
He keeps giving me cry obsidian.
He keeps doing it!
He does!
You gotta fucking...
I'm gonna shoot you!
I'm done!
I'm missing!
She's lost it.
She's lost it for real.
I can't hit him!
I can't hit him anymore.
You did it!
I did the thing.
I did the thing!
You did it!
I did it.
There is an Enderman right behind you too.
Oh I see him.
Thank you.
Come here Agros.
Come here.
Drop your pearls.
Poop them out.
Poop out your pearls.
Come here.
Let's go up again.
I got five!
I got five pearls!
Oh hi.
Oh my god.
I believe in us.
I can't believe I wanted to start later.
That's what I said earlier!
I can't believe it.
I was like are you... I thought I literally while you were gone I was like...
I really thought when she proposed this that she wanted to start in the morning and like go all day.
But no, you were like...
Oh shit!
Oh my god.
I'm dead.
I might be dead.
Oh shit.
Shit.
No.
I'm ok.
Where is he?
Hold on.
No.
I'm ok.
I dropped down.
Are you ok?
Yeah.
I'm ok.
I dropped down.
What the fuck?
I'm not ok.
No.
I'm really not ok.
I'm not ok.
Climb up.
Shit.
Oh no, I'm gonna die, I'm gonna die!
I'm gonna die.
I got him, I got him!
Just heal, just heal.
Calm down!
Heal, heal, heal!
Calm down.
I'm calm, I'm calm!
That's why he attacked me.
I was like, I didn't hit him.
Why did he...
Don't have your helmet.
You got...
I know, I know, I know, it broke because of the Enderman.
Oh my God.
Oh my god!
What were your hearts?
I was at one and a half I think.
Oh!
I thought I was gonna die for real.
Oh my god!
What happened to your house?
I went underneath and then I got shoved out by the pig because I wasn't wearing the gold.
Oh my god.
I'm healing you guys.
I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing.
That was like the PTSD right there.
It would've all been over.
All that gold I farmed...
Oh my god!
There's no more gold.
There's no more gold in the wall, in the ceiling.
Ok, come here Enderman.
Oh my god!
What?
Are you dead?
There's seven Endermans right here.
In the corner.
Wait, I think this is a good farm spot.
Get over here.
Ok, hold on.
I'm getting this guy.
There's seven Endermans right in the corner.
They hit so hard.
Oh, he gave me soup.
Thanks for the soup.
Oh my god, look at that.
Where are you?
Ok, I'll show you.
Alright, you gotta make a house.
Yeah, I'll make the house.
Just show me where.
Ok, come with me.
I'm coming, I'm right behind you.
Ok, this is a little dangerous.
No, no, don't go here.
We go up with rocks.
Ok, ok.
Ok.
How?
Here.
Ok, I'm coming.
Oh, just kidding.
Ok, here we go.
Here we go.
It's in this corner.
It's very scary.
Just a warning.
It's a very scary corner.
I'm ready.
I'm looking down.
When you're gonna see it, you're gonna be...
It's right in this corner.
Right over there in that corner to our left, you're gonna see seven Endermans.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, I see them.
What the hell?
Ok, I'm going over.
I don't know what they're doing over there, but there's a party.
I hear them.
What the hell is happening?
Bye, my diamond pickaxe.
Mine is almost dead too.
Wait, where are they?
Oh my god.
You scared me, Enderman.
Make sure you make your thing.
I'm trying to make my house, but...
I think we have to leave here.
There's no way to farm anymore gold.
Oh my god.
I just found the last remaining gold block.
The final gold block.
Ok, now I'm safe.
Ok.
No, I shouldn't.
This is way too risky even for me.
Ok.
Oh!
I got seven ender pearls now.
From all that?
From all of those?
Oh, I only got one.
Ok.
I was going to say, there was a lot of guys in that corner.
I hear the guys, but I can't get to them.
Safely, at least.
And there's a ghast.
Of course there is.
Oh.
Goodbye.
Ok, I have 18.
Oh, I hear another ghast to my left.
Yeah, he's there.
We gotta leave this area.
I mean, there's...
No.
Was that you?
My crafting table.
This guy sucks.
They suck so much.
My crafting table.
I shoot him to the left.
And then he got my table.
Again?
He destroyed it.
I literally just moved to the left.
To the right.
Ok.
I...
Yeah, I see you.
I'm going down.
What do we do?
We leave?
I think we leave this cursed land.
We...
We leave this cursed land.
I can hear all of them.
I just can't see any of them.
For some reason.
Oh my gosh, there's another ghast.
How many?
Oh, there he is.
Why are they loud?
Oh my god.
You're killing them.
There you go.
One of them is dead.
Are you getting arrows?
Or are you getting...
I've been getting a lot.
Everything but obsidian.
Hey, whatever.
That was work, I guess.
We need them for the fight, so...
Oh, thank you for the boots.
We have to leave.
We leave.
Oh, ok.
Alright.
I think I can...
Thanks for the iron boots and the iron ingots, I guess.
Ok.
I got a guy.
I baited a guy in.
Alright.
Come on, guy.
Where did he go?
Oh my god.
Come back.
Come back, please.
Oh my god.
It's almost 2AM!
No way.
We can do this.
Oh, there's another one?
The other angry?
Do I not need...
Do you want my stuff, little boy?
Do you want my little water bottle?
Do you want that, little boy?
Zoom over here, please.
Please, sir.
Why are you still here?
Why are you still...
We gotta leave.
Oh, here we go.
Oh my god.
Yeah!
Oh my gosh, this is like an ender farm.
This is like an ender farm!
Yeah!
Oh my god.
This is kind of awesome.
Yeah, I found a little hole.
I found their hole.
I just hit them all at once.
Ok, I only got 2 pearls from that.
But, you know, great.
That's good.
Alright, let's leave.
Oh, hold on.
Come here.
There's 3 more over there.
Did I just hear you?
Oh, hi.
Where do you wanna go?
I don't know.
You pick.
I've been here so long.
I've been trading for gold non-stop.
Like, I don't know anymore.
Ok, I have another concern because we're gonna run out of food soon.
No, I have a lot of hay.
You do?
Ok.
I have 20 more.
That's a lot.
Like hay bales?
Yeah, I have 20 more.
I have 20 more hay bales!
Let's go!
I have melons?
Oh, I have 64 melons.
Ok, we're good.
I have a full stack of melons.
I didn't even notice them.
Do we wanna just go this way?
Alright, let's go.
Get some gold somewhere.
Maybe we'll get more here.
Who knows?
It's from an American tale.
The one about the mouse?
The one with the naked lady in the window, right?
That would suck if there was no cats in America.
I'd be really upset about that, actually.
It's a terrible song.
I hate these cats.
Or these mice.
You know what?
They can get eaten by the cats.
Oh, for all I care.
For the mice, you're supposed to represent the American dream.
Well, they're talking about no cats.
The cats are eating the mice!
The cats are the more important part!
Cats are cuter than mice.
That's some cat propaganda right there.
Why are you not, like, just mining the straight line?
Oh, the naked lady is in the...
Oh, no, the naked lady is in the Disney movie.
Yeah, the one frame where they're naked?
Oh, just go on a straight line?
Yeah, why are you, like...
I don't know, I was trying...
Yeah, that's the netherite mine.
Is it really?
Yeah, the way you were mining, that's how you mine for netherite.
Well, that's how I got to netherite, baby.
Not the gold.
I tried for the gold!
But I also was just trying to...
Are you mining?
I thought that was mine that was breaking.
No, mine broke.
I've just been making iron ones.
Because I don't want to use my diamond.
But now I have to.
It's too late.
You have to.
But it's precious!
It's precious material!
We're in too deep.
That has to be an ender, right?
What?
The enderman?
No, I think that was just cave ambiance.
How deep is this hole and how is there no gold?
See, that's what I'm saying!
How is there no gold?
I don't know.
Do you need iron?
I have iron.
Oh, you do?
I shouldn't have just one iron.
Here, take it all.
Take it all.
Take all the iron.
Yeah, I kept the iron instead of the enderpearl.
I'm just gonna mine a straight line.
I'm not doing two anymore.
I'll do the other side.
Oh!
What's up?
We're back.
Oh!
I see more...
I see more gold.
More gold for you!
I see it.
I see the gold.
She sees the gold.
Every gold is a gold.
The gold is the gold.
Maybe we should just slowly head back to our original spawn while we're trying to find gold.
It's like, who...what are we gonna get first?
Our original spawn point?
Or...
Or the gold?
At this rate, we would've been back.
We would've made it back.
I think we would've actually been back.
I honestly think...
I think we would've made it back.
Well, we're going in the opposite direction.
Alright, which direction is the gold?
Not gold, sorry.
The original.
Let's just slowly head back and see what we get first.
We need to literally go the opposite way that we just came from.
Alright, here we go.
Let's go!
Yippee!
I'm gonna follow you!
You aggroed a guy?
Or I did.
I don't think so.
Did I aggro him?
No, you did, because I wasn't looking at anything.
Oh, I was on...I was looking at the coordinates.
Okay.
My bad.
For me.
I was literally placing blocks.
Well, come on!
Are we not heading back?
I'm trying my best right now.
I'm worried I'm gonna fall.
Okay, I'm gonna dig while you do that.
And look for gold.
Alright, which way?
Which way is the original way?
This way!
Her smile and optimism.
But we have to also...hold on.
Okay, we...
It's more like...this way.
Negative Z.
It's like...okay, we gotta go facing north.
So we gotta go like this way.
This way?
Like a diagonal.
Okay.
So that's why the diagonal dig is good.
Do the diagonal dig.
Do the diagonal dig!
Then stand far away when you do the diagonal dig!
I wonder if I'm stupid.
Do you want me to dig?
Actually, no, yeah.
Okay.
I'm gonna be slower though.
I don't have a diamond pick.
I'm gonna...
It's just like 1% slower.
It's just 1%.
I'm just gonna sit here for a little bit.
Okay.
I'll just...
I'll just dig.
I'll do it.
I'll just be the supervisor.
Yeah.
How am I doing, sir?
It's alright.
I mean, it could be better.
You know, you could put better form.
Can you like put torches down?
What's gonna happen?
Nothing's gonna spawn.
No, but I can't see.
You can't see?
You don't have the right resource pack.
I have the shaders on.
Oh my god.
Why are you tired?
It's 2am for me.
This is literally...
It was so fast in my bedtime.
Oh my god.
I told you it took 20 days.
And then we had one day.
Get your gamer subs out.
I got my gamer subs out.
I had the gamer subs earlier.
Get gamer subs out.
By the way, guys.
Code Boomer.
Code Doki Bird.
You can get 10% off.
My code will get you more percentage off.
Oh, I can't see.
What?
I need you to put down torches.
I can't see.
Why is there no gold in here?
I think we're not in the right...
Alright, get out.
It's my turn.
I'll make a new one and then I'll take over.
Oh, offhand it?
Oh, true.
Okay, yeah.
I'll do that.
It's just offhanding.
That's what I've been doing.
Well, other than the shield part.
Yeah.
Are we heading the right way?
Have you checked?
Yeah, we're heading the right way.
Okay, thank God.
We just need to get over a thousand...
Z.
And two thousand X.
Okay.
But we're also searching for gold.
So that we can...
Oh my God.
What's happening?
Don't take down.
That's unpredictable.
Wait, is there lava?
Boat time.
I heard a gas though.
I think it's okay.
Boat time!
She doesn't care anymore.
Let's go!
Yay!
Thank God.
Every time it really feels like the next time we will miss.
Goodbye boat!
Why does the Enderman scream?
Hold on.
Oh my God.
Wait.
Oh, shit.
I'm getting aggro.
I didn't aggro anybody.
I think it's the guy from before.
Did you aggro?
Did you do it?
No, I think it's the guy who followed us.
No, I didn't do it.
Did you aggro?
I did, but earlier.
He followed me all the way here.
Just come down here.
No, he's gonna get me.
He's gonna get me.
He's not gonna get you.
You're being paranoid.
I hear him right there.
You're getting paranoid.
I'm gonna dig for gold while he's...
Until he comes to see me.
You're getting paranoid.
How am I paranoid?
I almost died to Enderman earlier.
You're getting paranoid.
You're hearing the voices again.
What are you talking about?
He's right there.
He's not angry.
Which one?
I hear him screaming.
Where are you?
I'm up here.
I hid.
As soon as I heard him screaming at me.
There's nobody screaming.
There's no one screaming.
You guys, you hear it.
He's underneath me.
Nobody is screaming.
I'm literally...
No one's getting you.
You're paranoid.
Oh, I see.
Never mind.
I see him now.
He was literally right...
Right...
He is vibrating.
I know.
I hear him.
What did you do to him?
Stop!
You're wasting your arrows.
He'll dodge.
I'm just waiting for him to come up here.
I wanted him to TP.
Oh, you wanted him to TP.
Hey, buddy!
Why don't you kill him?
You're right there.
I'm trying to make the house!
Oh, okay.
Just right above your head.
Alright, there's three.
There's three Endermans right here.
Well, just kill the one that's aggro on me.
There's so many!
There's four!
Okay, but you're in the house.
You're safe.
Am I?
I don't know if I made it correctly.
Come down here.
I see him.
I got him.
He's dead.
Okay.
I don't hear him screaming at me anymore.
Alright, I'm coming down.
We can kill all these other Endermans in this house I made.
Yeah, come here.
Oh my god.
Nice house, I think.
He brought the whole crew.
What was I supposed to do?
Okay, I killed one.
Where's the rest of them?
Where's the 500?
I'm literally looking at...
Get under the house!
Further, further!
Was he going to hit me?
Yeah.
Alright, there's the other one.
Wasn't there like 50?
Right here!
I'm looking at the other one!
There he is!
He's coming!
Where is he?
Where is he going?
Yeah, where is he?
Oh, there he is.
Oh my god.
I told you he brought the whole crew!
I'm getting him!
Where did he go?
I saw the boat in the tree.
Yeah, I know.
I think there's the boat.
Yeah.
Is he going to come back?
I don't know, but I got the boat.
Hello, Enderman!
Where did he go?
Hey, buddy.
Come here.
He disappeared.
Oh my god.
Oh, that works too, I guess.
That works too.
I told you to get under the house!
I keep trying!
I have 500 pearls.
My shield?
I'll be okay.
Well, I guess we're not in the thing anymore, so...
Alright, tell me how to...
Where do we go?
How do we get to the other side?
Just keep heading north.
Yeah, we gotta go into those woods.
Back to the woods we go.
Into the thick of it.
There was one guy I still hadn't killed though.
I wonder where he's at.
It's fine.
He's not gonna get revenge on us, right?
Where are my mushrooms?
I don't have any mushrooms, by the way.
I have mushrooms.
Wait, we're literally in mushroom territory.
Collect some.
I know, I know.
I need to find some.
Turn around.
Over here.
In here.
I found it.
But not the red ones.
You gotta get the blue ones.
I know.
I need to figure out what to throw away.
Into the thick of it.
Here, I'll collect some and then I can give you like half or something.
Nah, it's fine.
I got two.
I got five.
I got enough.
Alright, let's go.
I have 15.
Alright, that's...
What?
Now I'm being punished for being over prepared.
Yes.
Alright, do we just go straight?
Is that it?
Wait, where did you go?
Where did you go?
Oh, there you are.
I'm in the forest.
Oh, I see you.
How did you get...
Oh, you went that way.
That's right.
You're waiting.
I'm coming.
Into the thick of it.
I wish we could obtain that strider.
Oh, I should get out of saddle.
We don't need a str...
We could have just walked through the lava until we got to our place.
We could have...
But then the ghast would see us in the middle and blow us up.
Alright, let's...
Is it just straight?
It's more like...
Hold on.
I have to check when I move.
Wait.
Huh?
There's like four of them right below me.
Wait, but X is going up.
Okay, no.
It is straight.
Okay, okay.
I was gonna...
Yeah, let's just go straight.
Okay.
Just follow my one side bridge.
My one block bridge.
Right here.
Into the thick of it.
Look at this.
No.
Nothing in the ceilings either.
What the hell?
Stingy.
Oh, there's some gold.
Where?
Below you.
Okay, I'll get it.
I'm looking above me right now.
Alright, we go straight, right?
Yeah, but hold on.
Alright, digging forward.
Hold on, let me get the...
I'll put torches next to the hole.
Okay.
Oh, no.
Uh-oh.
Don't be mad.
I'm sorry.
You have gold on you.
Oh, shit.
He's mad at me.
Place blocks in front of it.
Get over here and place a block in front of it.
Okay, or place blocks in front of him.
I mean, that works too.
He's still trying to get me, but...
Get over here.
I'm coming.
Close the door.
Okay, straight, right?
I'm just gonna go straight for now.
For now is fine.
We're gonna have to...
change direction.
Okay.
Well, no.
I think it's...
Wait, no.
Well, I don't know.
It's so hard.
I hate this.
I hate navigating.
But we are going in the correct Z.
We just have to also...
But what about the X?
The X is like the biggest one...
that we're gonna have issues with.
Oh my god.
I'm too sick of it.
Here we go.
This is why we...
should have just...
got straighted.
We got...
I think I did a hundred gold pieces.
I...
I think I've done a hundred.
Yeah, but we only needed two more.
I've done a hundred.
We've only needed two more.
We only needed two more.
I've done a hundred rolls.
What was this about?
You gave up.
Gamblers give up.
What was this?
We're doing it while we explore.
I almost just got killed...
for trying to...
Okay, so that's why...
when people are like, oh, just go one way...
and then go another way.
It doesn't really work in the nether...
because the nether is really special...
and just makes you have to...
reroute everything.
I think we... Hold on.
I'm checking.
Look at all those striders over there.
Look at all those striders just chilling in the fire.
We need to go this way.
Which way?
This way.
This way?
Okay, here we go.
Let's hope there's no ghastlies here.
I'm holding down my ship.
Let's hope my ship doesn't accidentally...
broke at the end.
That would be very...
That would be crazy.
Okay, I'm checking.
I'm drinking this.
You have another potion!
I don't trust it.
I...
I can do this for three minutes.
Okay, yeah.
I'll just...
I'll just chill until we get to the other side.
You are the one that has the most...
I can do this for three minutes.
Are we going the right way?
Yeah.
Just to be sure.
Positive X.
Towards positive X.
Mr. X.
Gonna give it to you.
Is that a guy riding a strider down there?
We should kick him off.
Wait, you could do that.
You could drop...
I'm not gonna drop down!
You have the potion!
He has a saddle on him!
We have other priorities right now!
You could do it!
You could steal that strider from him!
We have other priorities here!
We don't even have a saddle!
We don't even have a saddle.
We don't have a saddle.
That's why I'm saying you take the one from the guy riding it.
Where?
He's down there.
He doesn't even have a saddle.
He's just on top of it.
He's just chilling.
He doesn't even have his own.
I have more.
My hand is cramping.
I'm pressing down the key.
We made it!
We actually made it!
Watch out!
Did you have your mushrooms?
No, I have them.
Back!
Back, beast!
Which way do we go?
When I put one down, when we get a little ways away...
Grab the old one, you know?
Back, beast!
Now they're starting to attack him.
Nice.
Watch out here.
Watch out right here.
Wait, this is not the way.
Don't follow me.
I'm scared they're gonna fucking hit us after that.
In fact, I'm just gonna kill this guy.
Easy.
And I'm gonna take his leather.
Nice.
Alright, which way is it?
Why did you go ahead of me?
I don't know.
I just wanted to look at the open.
I'm checking the coordinates.
Okay, we're just straight ahead.
Okay, just straight ahead.
Oh shit.
There's one here.
Yeah!
Back, beast!
Back!
Yeah, back!
Stay back!
Stay back, beast!
Be gone!
Be gone, you vile creatures!
Oh wait, there's nothing here.
Oh my gosh, where's the gold?
You wanna trade with these guys while we're here?
I don't have...
I have eight.
Oh, eight nuggies or eight pieces?
Eight nuggies.
Oh, okay.
We got five more gold, but there's no gold here.
You just head straight?
Yeah, just keep going straight.
Wait, there's gold right there!
There's gold right there, okay.
Hold on, let's check the area first.
Um...
Is it safe?
I don't see any guys.
Alright, I believe you!
But I can't see over your area though, so...
I believe you!
Okay, nice.
Nice, nice.
Okay.
What the hell?
Why can't I build a thing here?
I'm trying to like protect you.
Like a little house or something.
Okay, nice.
Nice.
Nice, that was a good amount.
That was...
Thirty-four!
Okay.
Alright guys, remember, we're trying to get to negative five hundred and five.
And...
Which way do we go?
195.
We just keep going straight this way.
This way?
Where are we at?
Don't look.
That's why I said maybe we should just get the two more!
I looked.
I...
Yeah.
Maybe we should just get the two more.
We ran out of gold!
We ran out of gold.
There were no more gold to farm.
We farmed...
We like demolished the area.
We've taken all the natural resources around us.
It's over.
Where are you?
Oh, there you are.
You wanna get this guy?
Hit him up.
He might have some good stuff.
Okay, I'm gonna... I'm making the gold now.
Yeah, he might have some good stuff.
Come on, guy.
We can just get out of here.
Like, we can just leave.
Alright, let's see if we can get the...
Oh my god, why did he drop that?
Why is he running away from me?
I'm so tired.
He gave me quartz.
Okay, but that's just one.
He gave me crying obsidian.
Hey, he gave me three crying obsidian.
He gave me three crying obsidian.
And then I got leather.
Okay, but you can give the leather to me.
That's it?
That's all you got?
That's all I got.
Crying obsidian and quartz.
Okay, let's keep going this way then.
We're digging through.
We're gonna try for gold.
We're gonna try and get gold.
We're gonna get gold.
We're gonna get gold in these mines.
We're gonna strike it rich.
Doki bird, you and me, we're gonna strike it rich.
We're gonna...
Wait, why are you guys backing?
We've never left another.
There's no why are we backing.
We just stay there.
Oh, there's some gold in here.
Hold on, let's build a bridge over there.
My bad.
Oops.
I don't wanna hit you accidentally so you can get off.
Oh, you're making me...
Stop placing blocks, this is my job.
I'm the architect here, okay?
This is my work.
Okay.
God damn it.
Fine, you can get it.
I don't even care.
There's two, there's another area right here.
Okay, where?
I'm just trying to be efficient.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I see, I get it.
See, there's one right here.
Look, see?
This is efficiency right here.
German efficiency.
I can't even grab it.
So you don't even have to take the blocks.
See?
German efficiency.
Right there, right there.
Alright, so which way do we go now?
We keep going straight.
Straight?
Alright.
Let's keep going.
Oh, oh, another area.
There's so much quartz in here!
Why is there so much quartz?
It's just...
The land of the quartz.
Oh my god.
Oh look, there's gold.
It's so far up.
There it is.
A tiny two pieces of gold.
Further onward.
Off we go.
Oh, what was that?
Further onward.
Onward, onward.
Everybody.
Onward we go.
I think this is the worst sea we decided to stay on.
I know, right?
Oh my god, there's so much gold here.
Oh my god, thank god.
Oh, there's a good amount.
You want me to grab it?
No, I can grab it.
Just be careful.
Oh, there's more over here too.
There's more!
I'll dig a tunnel over here to the gold.
Okay, we just gotta find some piglins now.
Come on, piglins.
Show thyself, piglin.
Come on.
It would be so cool if you guys just show up.
It would be so funny.
Do you guys want to do something really funny right now?
But, like, don't show up right now.
Because that would be, like, kind of rude.
But it would be so funny though.
Oh, oopsie.
I'm a kid.
Got more gold.
There's more gold over here.
I wasn't worried.
Oh my god.
Where are these little piggies?
This little piggy went, went, went, went...
All the way home.
Okay, I got seven.
Grab these, grab these.
Oh, you didn't have inventory space, right?
No, I don't.
Okay, I think that is...
We got ten.
We have ten.
We just need to find... We just gotta find them.
What are we at?
Okay, we have to get a little lower actually.
We'll get lower eventually.
We'll get there.
We have a boat.
Can I have my crafting table?
I mean, just give two to me.
I have the space for it anyway.
Okay, okay.
Alright, I'm just gonna make a bridge over here.
Do you think we'll do this tonight?
Yes, Mint.
We're not clickbaiters, Mint.
No, but I mean if we have to fall asleep and then wake back up.
Mint, we're not.
We're not clickbaiters, Mint.
We're not.
The stream doesn't end, Mint.
The stream... This is why we had that one day, Mint.
Yeah, but they got to go...
The people who took 20 days got to go to sleep.
Do we not get to sleep?
Because it took them 20 days!
They played for like two to three days straight without sleeping.
And then they're like, we gotta sleep.
It took longer than they expected.
If this is gonna take us more than a day, then like...
Maybe we do sleep.
But for now, we're in too deep.
We're in too deep, Mint.
We're in too deep.
Why did I agree to let you have...
Let me do this...
I'm literally leaving town in like two days.
Why did I let you do this?
I don't know.
I don't know why.
You said we were like...
Okay, we'll have that one day be like a free day.
But you wanted to start at five!
We started at two.
We started at two!
Oh, it was five for you.
You could've started earlier.
You could've asked for an earlier time.
I did!
You wanted to initially start at nine, my time!
And then I was like...
Okay, let's just do two.
But you could've started earlier.
You could've asked for an earlier time.
I'm gonna kill you.
You better...
You better go to those pigs.
And you better get that obsidian right now!
Right now!
I did 200 rolls.
I did 200 fucking rolls!
Get better gacha luck!
I'm gonna take a week off of streaming...
and everybody will blame you.
Next week we are gonna be gone.
Oh yeah, that's true.
I am actually gonna be gone.
It's practically a week.
And I blame you!
They'll have you to blame!
Watch out!
I wasn't...
I couldn't...
Oh shit.
I was trying to get there.
Okay, hold on.
There we go.
I'm blocking it up.
I did it!
I blocked it up.
We're safe.
We're good.
Everything's fine.
Hold on, I'm gonna move my thing over though.
Doki hates us.
I was reading my chat!
Someone sent me a super chat...
and you expect me not to read it out loud?
That's so rude of me not to...
Thank you for the super chat.
The super chat said Doki hates us.
You were allowed to read the super chat out loud!
You've always been allowed!
What do you think I just said?
Oh wait, let me check on her.
Hold on, okay.
We are going down...
too slowly in the Z.
But we are making it...
in the X.
Okay, in the X is where we're...
we're the furthest away.
Yeah, kinda.
Oh, I need you to put down the...
Oh yeah, I forgot.
Alright, you take that then.
See?
I told you.
You're right, you're right.
I wanted to free your fucking inventory space.
I have too much cool stuff.
You don't understand.
Oh, I don't understand.
Alright, let me dig, let me dig.
Alright, your turn.
Yeah, I've been doing all the work.
Oh, okay, go back, go back!
Get out, get out, get out!
No, no, no, no, no!
No, no!
Someone's too afraid of the lava!
Someone is just like...
What if I'm stupid and I...
and I die to the lava?
That's literally how you sounded earlier!
You're like...
I'm scared of the lava.
That's true, my chat was like...
She is called Maid Mint.
Yeah, be a maid right now.
And fucking do your work.
I'm a maid cafe maid!
And if your chat knew any culture...
they would know that!
I'm a maid cafe maid!
Oh, you gotta grab this.
Alright, turn around.
Why are you digging it?
Because...
Alright, your turn.
Alright.
Typical maid.
Oh no, I was reading a super chat that someone sent me.
Oh yeah?
What was it?
It was actually them asking something...
but I don't wanna answer it now!
Oh, you don't wanna...
I'm getting the boat, I'm fucking getting the boat.
I'm getting the boat right now.
Do we need the boat?
Yeah, you wanna jump?
No, we can just keep...
Let me make a bridge, let me make a bridge.
We keep going.
We keep going through the walls, it's the safest.
What, you wanna experience more gassed activity?
I don't think so.
I'm just thinking like, oh, why don't we bump into one of those pigs?
What about a pig?
It's fine!
Oh, you wanna see a pig.
No, I meant the piglings!
Oh, okay, hold on.
We'll make it.
No, no, no, we don't need to see the piglings.
Let's keep going forward.
Oh look, there's a pigling right in front of us!
Build a bridge, build a bridge!
There's a pigling literally right in front of us!
That guy that's a hoglin?
The one that will try to murder us?
I don't know!
The fucking good ones!
I don't see a good one.
I'm getting the block right now.
Okay, you do it, you do it.
Do you guys see a good one?
I don't see a good one.
Look to your left, look to your left.
Okay, now I see him.
Oh no!
I couldn't see him, he was blocked by your big old head!
You were in front of me!
Oh man, that sucks.
It's okay, it's okay, he fell.
I saw you miss too.
Oh, get your mushrooms ready.
I got my mushrooms, I got my mushrooms.
You also have one like right here.
Where'd he go?
Oh, he's over here.
Alright, ten, we have ten.
Ten, alright.
I'll put a mushroom next to me just in case.
Yeah, I put one around too.
Okay, alright, this is it, the gacha.
This is it.
Stay away.
Stay away, ugly.
Oh my god, we got one, we got one!
Mint, get over here!
We got one!
Oh my god, just one more!
One more, one more, one more.
Oh my god, just one more.
Why did I do that?
Just one more, just one more.
Oh my god, please!
Please, sir, please be kind to us!
We got him, we got him!
Yes!
Oh my god!
Oh my god, we got two!
This is it!
Wait, wait, wait, before I make these, you still have your diamond pickaxe?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh my god.
Yeah, I do.
Wait, what is it?
Two?
And then three?
One, two, three.
One, two, three, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
And then...
Shut up!
And then right here...
And then it's fire time!
Get your bed ready just in case and a shield maybe.
I don't know.
Here we go!
Wait, how many enderpearls do you have?
What just happened?
Hello?
What the fuck is subspace bubble?
Use the nether to travel seven kilometers in the overworld.
Yeah, that sounds about right.
That sounds...
By the way, I don't have my bed anymore.
What?
What happened to your bed?
It's at our old spawn.
Should we head to our old spawn?
Should we head to our old nether?
Yeah, let me get the coordinates.
Let's get to our old...
Hold on, let me get the coordinates.
Hold on, I'm getting them.
Now we got...
So literally me being like, prepare your bed and you just didn't say anything.
Okay, do you want to know the damage?
Oh my god.
What's the damage?
So...
Look at where we're at.
Okay.
We need to get to...
Minus 4,116.
Oh, what's the Z?
What's the Z?
1,576.
Let's go traveling.
Let's find...
Let's find a sheep, right?
Well, we might as well...
I don't think there's...
Wait, which way do we go?
Let's...
Oh yeah, good.
We gotta go to positive Z.
No, sorry.
Negative Z.
We're not going the right way.
Okay, uh...
This way.
Alright.
We find a village first or we make it home.
We'll find a village probably somewhere.
It's one or the other.
The lapis and the enderpearl.
How many ender...
I have 10 enderpearls right now.
We have 10 out of 5.
We have 15.
Is that enough?
Is that enough, you guys?
I mean, guys, we gotta go this way anyway.
Oh wait, this might be a good time to get the phantom, right?
Yeah, exactly.
We can just walk around until the phantom appears.
I mean, we have to not sleep for like 3 days.
Yeah, that's fine.
I love how we're like absolutely littering in this world.
We're never coming back to see the damages we caused environmentally.
It's true.
We're gonna defeat the ender dragon and delete Minecraft.
That is enough.
What the fuck?
The sugarcane just killed itself.
You're not going the right way.
I'm not?
I barely...
This...
Oh gosh, hold on.
It's really confusing.
Cause one is really...
Okay, I think we just need to go down the X.
Okay, this way?
Oh, I need to eat.
We know we need food.
North... Northeast is where we need to go.
Am I going the right way?
Well, I don't know.
Whoa, what is this?
It looks crazy.
Am I going the right way?
Just go around it.
Wait, we can just...
Make a boat.
Oh my god.
Get in.
Oh, okay.
Well, I would've.
But...
I'm drifting.
Okay, go, go, go!
Okay, give me a...
Give me a sec.
I need a... Okay, there we go.
There we go.
I'm rowing.
Give me a second.
I need to get my...
Village!
Where?!
Oh, okay.
Nice.
What does F4 do, guys?
I accidentally pressed F4.
I don't think it does anything, right?
I don't know.
I feel like every function does stuff.
It's like half normal and half, like...
I think we should just stay awake in here, right?
Like, we can just camp out here, but don't sleep.
Camp out the night?
But don't sleep, so that we...
It's gonna be the longest night cycle.
I know, but like...
We gotta stay up for several nights.
Well, we're gonna make the villagers turn into zombies.
No, they're asleep.
They're fine.
What if a zombie breaks open one of the doors?
Some of the villagers aren't even inside.
We're gonna cause a zombie apocalypse to these poor villagers.
Okay, then put down torches.
I don't know.
What do you want me to do?
We gotta stay awake.
Oh my god, that's so cruel.
I'm sorry, guys.
I'm sorry.
She doesn't care about you.
They're literally inside.
She doesn't care.
Yeah, they can break doors.
That's what zombies do.
They break doors.
Zombies do not break doors.
What Minecraft are you playing?
Yes, they do.
I saw them break doors.
What?
They do?
Why do we care about them?
Oh, they do in hard mode.
Oh my god, they do.
But only in hard mode.
I've seen it.
Aren't we in hardcore?
Yeah, but I didn't know that.
I've only played normal mode and I don't watch Minecraft YouTubers like you do.
No, what do you mean?
I've seen them break doors.
Wow, I didn't know that.
I had no idea.
I learned something today.
Someone said make fences in front of the doors.
Oh my god, I don't care enough about the villagers for that.
I'm just a virtue signal.
Yeah, I'm just here to virtue signal.
Here, I'll just put some nether rack.
That's fine.
I'll have plenty of it.
There, I make my own door.
There, they can't get in.
Stupid zombies.
Zombie, be gone.
There's no zombies near me yet.
I put down some torches, so I should be okay.
You're safe with me, sir.
Wait, there's a horse in front of me.
Yeah, there's a couple of horses here.
Yeah, if only we had a saddle, we could steal the horse and just ride on.
No, horses suck.
No, not all horses suck.
Not all horses.
I'm gonna go take this time to get water.
Okay.
Wait, we gotta kill chickens for feathers later.
Oh, yeah, we can do that.
Yeah, we gotta...
Are you leaving the house?
Oh my God, no, I'm not.
Someone said we can trade for feathers, but that's too much work.
That's too much work.
We'll kill them on our way, too.
We'll find chickens.
There's so many of them.
There's gonna be so many chickens.
Wait, oh wait.
We've been awake for several nights, so actually maybe the phantoms will just normally spawn.
But we were trapped in the nether.
Does that count?
Does that count, you guys?
It should, right?
Does it count?
Oh, it does count.
Oh my God.
So we need to go outside.
We need to go outside.
Okay, you go.
What the hell?
No, you too.
You too.
Just one of us needs to... No, there's none.
I don't see any.
Oh, there's a chicken.
Oh my God, there's a zombie?
Jumbo.
Come here, Jumbo.
You bust down doors.
I got a chicken.
And you also hit harder.
I don't like that.
I got a chicken.
Oh my God, I don't want to see another enderman ever again.
What the hell?
What is going on over there?
Oh, the iron golem.
I got a chicken.
Wait, there's no phantoms, you guys.
I don't think it...
Let's just walk.
Let's just...
What are you afraid of?
Let's just keep walking.
We'll keep walking.
What are you afraid of?
We're losing time.
Get over here.
We have diamond armor.
We can't die.
We're decked out in diamond.
Diamond, what are you scared of?
That's right, come on.
You're not even going the right way.
Oh my... Okay.
Oh my God.
You scared me so bad.
You're gonna turn into a zombie and I don't care.
What?
What are you talking about?
Where are you going?
I'm stealing this guy's bed.
Wait, are you going to sleep?
No, it's for the future.
Okay, for the future when we can sleep.
Where are the phantoms?
It doesn't work.
We gotta stay up even longer.
It doesn't work, you guys.
Alright, let's go.
These zombies don't hurt.
We have diamond armor.
Okay.
Alright, let's go.
Which way?
The way we were going in the boat.
Chicken!
I got the feather.
I think, yeah, I got feather.
Oh, there's more chickens?
Oh, there's lots of chickens here.
Oh, there's so many chickens.
Get over here, chickens.
I don't even need you for your meat.
I don't even need you for your meat here.
Kill!
Kill them!
We need magma cream, right?
I have three magma cream.
Okay, by the way, there's more magma cream on the...
on the area left.
Wait, where are we going?
Where did you go?
Oh, I see.
Is that the right way?
Yeah, I'm scared of the skellies.
Oh my god, we're diamond armored.
Don't nothing to be afraid of.
Just go.
There it is!
Okay, um...
Uh-oh.
Are you alive?
I'm just running.
Oh, shit.
I thought you were supposed to be bad.
You're dealing with the phantom?
Yeah, I'm dealing with the phantom.
I don't have one.
Do I?
Oh, I see you fighting yours.
Your demons, your phantom demons.
My nightmares are here.
Oh, chicken.
I got one of them.
How do you have multiple?
What do I need from the phantom?
Their membranes!
Collect their membranes!
Oh my god, there it is.
I don't need this anymore.
I got one.
Alright, let's go.
Let's keep going.
Wait, where did you go?
I went further!
Because I was dealing with the skellies.
I'm killing chickens.
Alright, I'm gonna see if I can find you.
I don't trust you.
Oh, there you are.
Yeah, I just went straight.
I see you.
I gotta get my cough drops.
Oh god.
Alright.
Look behind me and see if there's anybody behind me.
No, you're good.
Alright, let's go.
We keep traveling.
Ignore everybody.
I do have a boat.
If I do the boat and we go that way, is it correct?
It should be, yeah.
Let's go on the boat.
It's boat time.
Boating time.
Alright.
Go, go, go!
I'm rowing.
I'm rowing!
Let me know if I'm going the right way.
No, you're not.
Ok, hold on.
What are the numbers?
Let me drive.
Hello?
There we go.
I'm ok now.
I'm ok.
I'm figuring it out.
It's almost day.
Ok, this one.
But also not for the...
How do I get the Z to go down?
Z is the scariest part.
I know!
Oh my god, I can only get the X to go down.
Ok, let me drive.
Hold on.
No, no, no.
I got it.
I had to go around this island.
Ok, we're good.
We're going northeast.
If we're not going northeast, we're going the wrong direction.
So every time, we have to be going northeast.
Ok?
Say ok!
You understand?
Say northeast!
Northeast!
Happy birthday to Mr. Kimchi!
Who's Kimchi?
I don't know.
He's my dragoon in my chat.
Happy birthday!
Nice, ok.
Say his name!
Mr. Kimchi!
There you go.
Thank you for the super chat, Mr. Kimchi.
Thank you.
Oh gosh, ok.
This is tougher than I...
We can't vote.
We have to walk!
What are the numbers?
What do you mean the numbers?
Ok, we just need to go down.
That's fine.
Get out of the boat.
Ok, let's go.
Alright.
How many feathers do I have?
Oh, only 8 feathers.
We'll find more.
We didn't...
We didn't fucking check for hay bales.
Oh no!
Oh...
Ok.
I have 15...
15 blam.
Ok, I have...
Wait, did you grab a bed yet or no?
Yeah, I've had my bed.
Oh.
How many membranes do you have?
I have one.
That's not enough.
Where are you going?
Come on!
This is the way!
No, up!
This way!
It is!
Look where I'm...
It's going down!
I'm going down too!
And I'm going up the mountain!
I'm at the...
Oh my god, ok.
Alright, alright.
I wish I had...
Where are you?
What?
What happened?
What's wrong?
Oh my god.
Who did you tame?
The dog?
Actually, this might be really good.
Because we'll be awake and we need someone to kill the skellies.
Yeah, exactly.
Where are you?
I lost you already.
I already lost you.
Yeah, because you're focused on dog.
Are you going up the mountain?
Why are you going up the mountain?
It makes the Z go up!
No, it doesn't!
Yes, it does!
I'm literally going up the mountain...
and my Z is going down!
Three...
Where are you?
Let's do this way.
I'm across the mountain.
We lost each other.
I'll meet you on the...
We actually lost each other.
I'm going down the mountain.
Oh wait, there's water here!
We lost each other.
Ok, hold on.
I'll give you my coordinates and you come to the water and then we vote.
I'm literally in the water.
Where are you?
Come to me!
What's your coordinates?
Oh, I see you.
Oh my god, we were heading the same way!
Wait, we can't take the boat!
You're dog!
He'll fall!
He'll TP!
Ok, ok, ok.
Alright, go, go, go!
Nope, wrong way.
It's going down!
No, the X axis is not going down!
Oh my god, we gotta get off the boat.
We gotta get off the boat.
We go this way.
Oh my god.
We go northeast.
You guys follow me.
Just follow me.
Northeast!
Northeast right here!
It's going down now!
Woo!
No ghasts in sight!
This is a peaceful time.
It's just a peaceful day.
Yeah, we have piggies, and dogs, and sheep.
No ghasts, no lava.
I mean, sometimes maybe lava.
But nothing else.
Just keep going down.
A freaky teleporting dog.
There he is!
A dog that is literally defying all physics and logic.
Oh my god.
He's gonna start teleporting.
Our good little boy.
He's been teleporting.
We never stop.
We never stop going.
What we did was to find the fortress.
We found the fortress though!
We found the fortress!
We found it!
Isn't that great?
Oh my god.
I feel like it's not going down.
I wish we had a light rule.
We need to go to the end for that.
At least it's going down though.
I keep losing you, but I keep seeing your dog.
So I'm just following your dog.
TP to me, so I don't know what you're talking about.
How are you behind?
I'm right here.
I'm literally going...
I'm following the coordinates.
I'm following you.
Come on, make a path.
A freaking hole.
Jump.
We have to do so much in this.
Oh my god.
We have to do so much.
Another mountain.
Oh, the dog just shook off the water!
That was so cute!
That's why I've been trying to team the dog this entire time.
Oh my god.
We need him for the night time.
For sure.
I mean, we need...
We needed to farm other stuff anyway.
So it's alright.
We needed to farm the chickens.
We needed to farm the bookshelves.
We needed so many things.
It's alright.
Maybe we'll find another village.
We'll find another village somewhere.
We'll find it.
Oh god, please.
Look, we're at 9k.
We're at 9k.
We're getting there.
But the 12k is scaring me.
Don't think about it.
It seems to be 4k.
It's not as bad.
I get 4k.
Don't think about it.
It's negative 4k.
Yeah, negative 4k.
Don't go this way.
My coordinates almost blocked that for me.
Uh oh, you just trapped your dog.
It's fine.
He'll TP out.
It'll be fine.
It'll be so fine.
We keep moving forward.
We had to find bookshelves.
We had to get chicken feathers.
We had to get so many things.
This is all part of the plan.
This is all part of the plan, everybody.
We had to get so many other resources anyway.
So we might as well make the travel.
But from here on, we did the fortress.
We did the most difficult part probably.
Hopefully, maybe that's the most difficult part.
We just have to get to the...
What's the thing?
Oh my god, we should have been farming sheep.
We should have been farming sheep for the bed.
You have a bed.
For the Ender Dragon!
I'm gonna kill this chicken.
Why do you want to go back?
We can farm beds when we find more villagers.
I feel like it's easier to just get wool.
Because we don't have enough inventory space anyway.
I feel like it's just easier.
I feel like let's just farm the sheep.
Do you have inventory space for sheep, wool?
No.
Alright, let's see.
What can I get rid of?
I'll farm the wool.
I mean, we don't have to do the bed strat, but...
I mean...
Save this right now.
Wait, someone sent me something.
And people are like, she needs to read this.
Oh, YouTube Live Archive.
Yes, we know about the 12 hours minimum.
We know, we know.
We're only at 10!
We're at 10 hours!
We're not even thinking about this!
We're fine.
It takes us literally...
10 minutes to make another room.
We'll be fine.
Where did you go?
I don't know.
Wait, you're still going?
I thought you were hunting sheep.
No, I'm not.
It was in the path.
No!
I lost you.
I'm making a PP tower right now.
Oh, I see you.
Alright, look up.
I see it being made.
Don't keep going.
Wait for me.
I'm gonna put red blocks.
Follow the red block road.
I gotta eat my bread.
I'm eating my bread.
I placed all my very important belongings back home.
For some reason.
Because she thought that...
I thought we would go back.
Silly me.
We were never coming back.
We had several blocks of lapis.
And we also had...
We also had...
Some of our ender stuff.
But it's okay.
We had to farm other stuff anyway.
We had to farm the wool.
We had to farm chicken.
We had to get bookshelves.
It's okay.
It was part of the plan.
Is there anything else you want to add, Mint?
Is there anything else about my mistake?
I just want to say...
There's no point in putting things in a chest.
If we just delete everything when we die.
Keep all important belongings.
I thought we were coming back.
I legitimately thought we were going to come back.
That it wouldn't take us 20 fucking years to get to a fortress.
I legitimately thought that we were more competent than that.
It's not our fault that the fortress decided to just not spawn.
It's so easy to get to the fortress.
It's so easy to find a fortress.
But don't silly me.
It wasn't easy.
It wasn't easy at all.
I think we just hit the negative luck with the fortress.
Just keep running.
It's going to be night time, but that's okay.
Sakura!
The cherry blossom trees.
We don't need it.
It's not part of the speed run.
Wait, oh my gosh.
There's another portal.
We broke another portal.
I'm going.
But it would be closer.
It would be closer.
I'm not gacha rolling 200 rolls.
I am not doing that again.
We don't have to.
We just have to find the original.
We'll make it.
With all the gas.
Yeah.
We could do it.
I like how you just destroyed it.
What?
This is a team.
What are you trying to split us up for?
Are we going the right way?
Oh my god, I just fell.
I just fell.
I'm okay.
No, I'm not okay.
I think I'm okay.
Okay, because I'm heading straight.
I'll wait for you here.
No, I'm right behind you.
I'm right here.
I'm going to get the coordinates out of my screen.
And I'm going to head this way.
It's still the right way.
It's northeast.
I haven't stopped moving northeast.
We haven't stopped moving northeast.
Why does my screen do that with the colors?
So it's going to be the right way.
I fell into water.
It's fine, guys.
I never thought I'd catch a stream that started at 5 AM.
It's so funny, isn't it?
Oh my god, you got the spiders coming after us?
Oh shit.
It's fine.
I'm going northeast.
Could your dog do something?
Because my dog!
Because I didn't get hit yet!
Okay, now the dog is going to do something.
There he goes.
Go, dog, go.
I'm stuck in the fucking dirt now.
It's fine.
My dog will be okay.
Where are you?
Come on.
My dog!
Oh, there he is.
What?
Did you kill your dog?
No, there's a hole here.
My dog is doing fine.
I'm just making sure.
I'm going to check the coordinates.
Phantom, don't go!
Phantom, come from the sky!
I call thee!
I don't think he's coming down from the sky.
I thought I heard a creeper.
I'm heading...
Oh, there's so many chickens.
And a spitter.
I got him.
Going northeast, going northeast.
Took his ass out.
There's more chickens here.
I want to make sure we are heading the right way.
Watch out for this.
Oh my god.
That's fine.
Get killed...
Skeleman.
I helped their dog.
It's this way.
Okay, I'm coming.
Eating real quick.
Me too, me too.
Oh my god, my last bread.
Alright, here we go.
Oh my god, it's my last bread.
Here, here, I'll make more.
No, it's okay.
I have lamb.
We can make some in the morning.
Alright.
Where are the phantoms?
I know.
I think it's because I killed them.
They stopped spawning for a bit.
Oh, maybe.
We just can't sleep for days and days and days.
It just makes this playthrough longer.
Because we can't sleep.
Just everything goes by longer.
Oh my god.
Oh, there's a village!
We can see there's bookshelves.
Bookshelves!
Kill!
Oh my god.
I just want to get rid of...
No, your dog!
Fine, I have...
Your dog!
He's okay.
I gave him bone and he doesn't want it.
Yeah, because he's injured.
No, if you give him bone, you should...
He can heal himself.
Oh, feed me?
Oh my god.
I interrupted something really personal.
I want to see this zombie break down the door.
That's fucked.
Hello?
That's messed up.
Bookshelves!
Wow!
He didn't do shit!
I literally let this guy...
How do I farm bookshelves?
Yeah, stupid zombo!
Up here?
Didn't do anything.
There's bookshelves right here.
Wait, do I need like...
Okay, so to get bookshelves...
We need silk touch to make it so that they break as bookshelves.
Otherwise, they break as books.
Okay.
And then we need...
That doesn't give us as many books.
Okay.
Yeah.
So in the end...
In the end, we just have to get the books.
Alright, let's just farm the books.
Just farm the books.
Farm the books.
Oh, my dog.
Oh, that's the thing we need to read.
That's what you can do to read the...
What do you mean you fucked it up?
It's fine.
I got the books.
I got books.
Oh, I got the books.
We got the books.
We need a lot of books.
We need a whole ton of books.
We need even more books.
A ton of books.
Hey, let's go!
There's a lot of bread in this one, but I have no room.
You can eat the food anyway.
Oh, lots of potatoes.
Lots of apples.
Are there any more books?
Is there any more books?
Any more books for us?
We're gonna grab the books.
We're gonna rob you.
We need it more than you.
What you gonna do with all these books?
I don't appreciate your attitude, Super Chatter.
I don't appreciate your attitude.
There's a potion thing right here.
Do we need it?
Yeah, just grab it.
If you have room.
If you don't have room, then whatever.
I do, I do, I do, I do.
I'm gonna grab it.
Get in my...
Get in my pocket.
Are you ready to go?
Oh my god.
This guy has four zombos and a little baby on a chicken attacking him.
I'm not dealing with that.
That's not my job.
I was gonna lead him to the...
That's fine.
To the golem, but...
You're so obsessive.
That's fine.
I need the levels anyway.
Let's go, let's go!
Which way?
This way.
It's always northeast.
We never change direction.
Never change.
We are one directional girls.
We got books.
We got feathers.
We got everything.
We got ambition.
We have strength and determination.
Oh my god, look at all these pigs.
We keep moving forward.
We're just...
Look at all these chickens on our way.
We're killing time.
Oh my god.
No, my dog!
No, he's alive.
Watch out for the other one.
Okay, that's fine.
Where are you?
I'm right behind you.
I need to eat though.
Is my dog okay?
I need to give him more meat soon.
Get another dog.
That's fine.
So if the other one dies, at least I have this one.
The dog army.
We got it.
At this point, this is the only way.
Oh, it gives all three books that went into the crafting.
Let's go!
Okay, good.
It's just the planks.
It's just whatever the wood...
It's fine.
We're surrounded by trees.
We're not in the nether.
We can get everything we need.
We're practically winning at this point.
I wish we had elytras.
I wish we could just fly.
And then all our worries will disappear.
And then everything...
Everything we've all worried about...
Oh, phantom!
Phantom, phantom!
Who is it for?
I think it's me.
Yeah, it's me.
It heard you yawning.
It did hear me yawning, actually.
I think it's gonna go soon, so we have to kill it quick.
What took you so long?
It's good!
He'll burn.
Just let him die.
Burn!
Give me your membranes!
He didn't give you membranes.
We tried.
We tried our best.
7,000!
Oh my god, 7,000!
Look at us go!
We have to kill it ourselves.
Now we know.
Look at that.
We're so close.
We are so close.
We're not even.
We are.
We literally need to get our lapis.
And then it's like...
We just speedrun to the end.
And then we're there.
The moment we get to the area...
We have to kill the dragon.
We have nothing to kill him with.
What do you mean?
We have so many things.
We need the phantom membranes.
We will get the phantom membranes as we travel.
That's what traveling is for.
We only have one phantom at a time.
And he dropped nothing.
How many phantom membranes do we need?
We need a lot of slow falling.
How many do we need?
I don't know.
Actually...
Do we have redstone?
We might need to grab...
It will make the potions last longer.
Oh my god.
We have to go back to...
You literally told me...
We threw away all our redstone because somebody...
Somebody...
We only need a little bit.
We don't need a lot.
Somebody was saying...
All I was thinking of was...
Back to the mines we go, I guess.
Back to the mines we go.
Why don't you go back to the mines?
You want me to do it?
You want me to go back into the mines?
We'll do it together.
We'll work together.
To grab the redstone.
What does that mean?
Someone just said...
If you guys are on a paper server, will things spawn more slowly?
Oh...
Wait, what things spawn...
Why did you choose a paper server?
I don't know what server we needed!
Does it really matter?
Does it really matter that things spawn slowly?
It's just the phantoms.
It literally is just the phantoms.
But we need a lot of slow falling potions.
Oh my god.
Can you change it?
I can change it.
I think I can swap it, but I don't know.
Wait, the Z is going up.
Oh no.
We gotta go up the mountain.
I'm just gonna...
I'm trying to place my blocks here.
Did you know about the paper thing?
Did you know about it?
No.
Exactly, so even if...
Why are people telling us this at like...
10 hours into the game?
Even if you made that server...
They should have been like...
Oh yeah, by the way...
When we first started the game...
They should have been like...
Hey, by the way, things are gonna spawn a little more slowly...
Because you choose this.
Okay, we'll just redo it.
Since we're not very far in.
But now that we're 10 hours into the stream!
It's okay, everything will be fine.
We just keep going northeast.
We have not encountered anything bad yet.
Nothing bad has happened.
We just keep going northeast.
Nothing bad has happened so far.
Stop saying that.
You're scaring me.
Stop it, stop saying it.
There's another dog.
You want another pet?
Where is he?
Oh, I'm at the top of the mountain.
Where are you?
Okay, I don't need him.
We'll find more.
We have 10,000 more blocks to go.
I'm pretty sure we'll find another dog by then.
I'm pretty sure.
I wish I had some bones.
I told you.
I told you about keeping the bones.
You were like, Doki, get rid of the bones.
I was like, no, no, no.
It's gonna be useful, I swear to God.
We're gonna need it.
And I was right.
Are you done?
No.
Are you even following me?
I don't think you're following me anymore.
I'm like in my own world.
I don't think you're even following me anymore.
I think we've lost each other.
We're going the same way, right?
We're going the same way.
I'm in the snowy area.
I have not seen a single snow area.
I have...
I don't know what you're talking about.
There has been...
I'm going up a little on the Z.
I'm in the snow.
I'm scared of the powdered snow.
There has not been snow at all.
Mine is going down.
I'm going correctly northeast.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
I...
I'm going.
I don't know.
There's a village.
I'm at a village.
I am at a village.
I am at a regular village.
I am here.
One of us went the wrong way.
No, mine is going down.
One of us is...
You missed the village.
You can hang out at the village.
You can have fun there.
Somebody here is trying to get books now.
I'm trying to get to our home.
Our home.
I like how you call it our home.
We have no home.
I just want to drop down.
Okay, now I found the snow.
You're way behind me.
No, no, no.
I know exactly you're in the mountain behind me.
What?
There's also more snow here.
I see a giant mountain filled with snow.
I passed the mountain.
Wait, there's several mountains.
Wait a minute.
What is your coordinate?
Negative ten thousand.
Where are you?
Negative nine thousand five hundred.
You're behind me.
You're behind me in that past mountain.
That's where you are.
Do you want me to wait for you?
No, just keep going.
We're both going the same path.
We're going the same path.
We're going the same path anyways.
It doesn't really matter.
We're just gonna meet up.
There's a little arctic fox.
So cute.
Wait a minute.
I'm at negative nine thousand now.
Oh my god.
By the time we get there, we'll have all our materials.
We'll have everything we ever wanted.
I don't think I'm strong enough.
This is why those other streamers have...
This is why those other streamers have so many subscribers.
I'm not strong enough.
Min, we'll have...
Just think about how good it's gonna feel.
Min, we'll just...
What if we die?
Don't say that, Min.
What if we die to the dragon?
Don't say that.
What if we die...
to the dragon?
It's so sad that we lost.
We lost.
I wanna go to sleep.
Min, we have...
We already invested so much time.
What if we wake up and then we play more tomorrow?
We wake up in the morning.
Min, you know...
We're gonna be sleeping for a very long time.
You know that.
I can't sleep for a long time.
I have a flight to catch.
Then it'll make the sleeping so much more worth it.
When we beat the ender dragon.
It'll make it so much more worth it.
Min, just think about how good it's gonna feel.
I'm gonna need this.
I'm gonna need this just in case I fall into snow.
Powdered snow.
Watch out for powdered snow.
Make sure you have an empty bucket.
Okay, nevermind then.
You can fall in for a...
You can get a whole face full of snow.
I'm in.
This is how I might die.
What are you talking about?
The powdered snow, this might be it.
Wait, you don't have a bucket?
No, I don't.
I gave you all my iron.
Okay, I'll wait for you.
I'll wait for you.
I'm not close.
What are you at?
I can't help it.
I'm so cold.
Where are you at?
Tell me you're cold.
I'm at negative 9,706,639.
Oh, you're like further on the Z than me.
Yeah, I went to the Z.
I focused on the Z.
I'm focusing on the Z.
I might actually be able to find you.
Are you on the ice?
I'm in the ice area.
Just farming.
You're farming?
What are you farming?
I'm getting up on the...
I'm getting up on the trees.
Why?
So I can not die from snow.
What do you mean why?
No, you're fine.
It's not all snow.
There's a lot of snow.
I'm making a peepee tower.
I'm just going through the snow.
I'm traveling through the snow right now.
I'm protecting myself for the night.
In case a phantom comes through.
I'm just making a bridge.
I'm just gonna make a bridge.
I'm gonna make a bridge.
If a phantom hits me, then GG's.
Where are you?
Come to 9152.
What?
I'm just gonna make a bridge.
I'm just gonna make the bridge.
I'm just gonna make the bridge and head straight.
I'm just gonna head straight.
Wait, what's your Z?
6653.
Okay, I'm close.
You're gonna see me.
I'm a bridge.
I'm basically a bridge.
You're gonna see me.
I'm up here.
Do you see me?
I don't know.
I'm making bridges.
I'm not looking at anything else.
Sky bridge.
It's the real strat.
I'm making a sky bridge right now.
Yeah, sky bridge lives.
It lives on.
Sky bridge.
I'm at...
9630.
Okay, I'm 500 blocks.
Just look up in the sky.
You'll see the speed bridge.
I don't know if it's a speed bridge.
I think that is a little bit...
Just look up and you'll find the bridge.
Oh my gosh, I just got peach over.
If I fall, it's over.
I just need you to know that.
How tall did you go?
I went up the tree and...
It's so over.
Wait, what happened?
Did you die?
If I fall, it's over.
If I get hit by the phantom, it's over.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, don't do it.
Don't do it.
Go back down.
The sky bridge is dangerous.
It's too late.
My dogs are blocking me.
I have to push my dogs down.
If I want to live.
The phantoms are gonna knock you off.
The phantoms are gonna come.
The phantoms.
I have a boat.
Use your boat.
I built a little platform.
If I fall, I might...
I'll take some damage.
But I think I'll be okay.
Goodbye boat.
Goodbye.
What do you mean goodbye boat?
I can make another boat.
It's fine.
Oh my god.
I have a skelly shooting at me.
How did he see me?
Freak.
I'm gonna make another boat right now.
Just in case.
Freak.
Don't look at my house.
My sky house.
What do I have?
Okay, there you go.
I'm waiting to see you.
I don't know, man.
I'm 9500 right now.
It's cause you're going so slow.
Because of your sky bridge.
Okay, I fucking...
I'm...
I have more Zs.
What's your Zs?
It is at...
Oh my god, there's a creeper right here.
It is at 6680.
Okay, I'm at 6665.
So, if you just keep going...
Towards the positive X...
And you don't move much of the Z...
Then we'll run into each other.
Okay.
Well, you're gonna see.
People, if you are trying to endurance this stream with us...
Do not do that.
If you need to sleep, if you need to...
If you have work tomorrow...
Please go to sleep.
You do not have to stay up with us.
Please do not.
We're still going.
We're still here.
It's fine.
I am 9300.
Someone said this was gonna...
They thought this was gonna be a quick watch.
You had so much...
Hope for us.
Yeah, we thought so too until it took us...
30 years to find the fortress.
3 hours...
4 hours was stuck in the nether.
I think we had 4 hours of nether time.
Literally, 4 hours was just...
In the nether.
Maybe we should start whispering for people who are going to sleep.
No.
Okay.
Good night, everybody.
I'm at 9200.
Where are you?
9151.
Okay.
I should see you soon.
Unless you're higher in the sky than I imagined.
6500 is my other...
6500.
Oh, I might be a little off.
Wait, which way do I need to go?
What's your Z again?
6665.
Okay.
I need to go this way.
Okay, we'll bump into each other.
Okay, I'll meet you there.
I'm on my boat.
I got off my boat.
Oh my god.
I can't move...
Because skellies are targeting me.
There has been no skellies on my end.
I'm not as high as you.
I think.
No, I'm just in the ice.
What?
Wait, I thought you were...
I thought you were in the air.
No, I fucking made a boat.
I lost my boat.
My dog got on the boat and I lost the boat!
What?
I lost my boat.
Oh, you're on the ground now.
What the hell?
Yeah, I'm on the ground.
Where are you?
I'm in the sky.
I made a peepee tower.
You made a peepee tower?
Okay.
I've been waiting in the peepee tower.
This is a little awkward because I am definitely not there anymore.
Wait, come over here.
I was looking at the sky for you.
I told you I got in the boat.
I thought you meant in the boat.
I meant in the sky.
No, why would I...
Why?
Because if you fall...
Because if you fall, then you want to take damage in the boat.
We literally did that all through the nether.
I used a boat to fall off.
And then I was in the ground.
Okay, I'm gonna jump for it then.
And I'm gonna swim your way.
Wait, where are you?
Okay, negative 9,041 is 6,581.
Oh god.
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, I made it.
I made it.
What happened?
You fell off.
I thought you were on your boat.
What happened?
I don't have a boat!
I'm gonna keep going.
No!
Wait for me!
I waited for you!
I don't have a boat.
I'm slow in the water.
Don't you have one?
We had so many wood!
What happened to the wood?
I guess I can make one.
I'm at negative 9,045.
Okay, I don't care anymore!
If you're not waiting for me, I don't care anymore.
I didn't say...
Oh my god, I have phantoms.
I hope you're happy.
I got the phantoms for you.
They're looking at me.
Good thing you didn't get them while you were...
you know...
high up in the air, wherever the hell you were.
What the fuck?
And there's zombies?!
Oh my god, I think one of my dogs are gonna die.
My solo journey.
Not by choice though.
I think that's the signal of a...
of a new day, whenever my...
shaders do that weird funky...
thing.
Oh my god, I'm sorry doggos.
I don't have meat for you yet.
Where are they?
I'm gonna use my bow.
She's gonna use her bow.
She's gonna do it.
I used my bow.
I couldn't.
I cannot deal with this anymore.
No.
I think this one gives me a membrane.
I think only one of them gives you a membrane.
A membrane.
Oh my god.
Leave me alone.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait, I have two more?!
Oh my god.
Please, please.
Leave me alone.
I don't care about your child.
Please, I don't care
about...
Please, no!
What happened?
It burned to death.
Bad luck.
Oh my god.
No, baby.
It burned to death.
Okay, I'm okay.
It's fine.
Why do all of these polar bears have babies?
I don't know.
4, 6, 8.
Okay, 8.
2.
Okay.
I have enough for a furnace.
I'm gonna make a furnace.
I'm waiting for you.
I'm waiting for you right here.
Where are you at?
I'm making a furnace right now.
That doesn't explain where you're at.
I had a second.
I told you my thing.
Don't worry.
Let me put stuff in here.
Oh my god.
Please drown.
Please, please, please, please.
Leave me alone.
Please leave me alone.
Do dogs eat chicken?
Do they eat chicken?
I don't know.
Dogs eat anything.
Give them peanut butter.
I'm not talking to you.
9,046 and 6,500.
Okay, they do.
Oh, I'm kind of way beyond you.
Okay, that's fine.
I'll just keep going.
I'm just gonna keep going.
I only have 4,000 blocks left.
Oh, you do?
Okay.
How about you?
Alright.
Oh, raw meat is fine?
Fuck, I don't need to cook this meat.
Oh my god.
4,000.
Okay, are they fully healed?
Okay, they are.
Alright, that's fine.
I'm in the ocean blue, everybody.
The parrot's in the bath.
Oh shit, they made a baby.
Okay.
Wait, can I have him?
No, he's my baby.
Oh.
You said I could have a dog.
You can find your own dog.
Okay, I'm finally like...
out of the ice and...
I'm gonna say there's no blocking, but I think I just hit a...
Yep, I just hit a block.
Oh my god.
How long did it take?
I don't know.
I'm at negative 8,500.
Okay, what about your Z?
5,260.
Wait for me!
I tried waiting for you!
I tried waiting for you and then...
you went past me.
I stood still.
I waited for you.
I dealt with the phantoms while waiting for you.
I didn't know you were waiting for me!
You didn't say I was just...
Okay, then I'll wait.
Okay, I'll wait for you.
Come to my location.
No, it's fine.
Just keep going.
Just keep going at this point.
It's fine.
I found the biggest cave ever.
What have I just dropped in?
Where are we dropping, boys?
In this cave.
Hello?
Okay, I'm at...
8 ,600, but I'm still in ice.
I'm still in ice.
Go to the 5,000 Z, then.
And you'll get into regular land.
Alright.
I'm waiting with some cows.
I'll wait.
Oh, you're gonna wait this time?
Yeah, I'm waiting.
No, just keep going.
It's fine.
We're all going to the same place anyway.
We're going to the same place.
I'm waiting.
Oh, I hear a zombie.
How?
I think he's underneath me.
In the cave.
The giant cave.
I think I see...
Is that a pirate ship?
What?
Doki?
Oh, yeah.
Avoid their babies.
Avoid the babies.
Yeah, I fucking swam into the polar bear.
That's your kind.
You wear the polar bear.
You wear the bear outfit.
I'm a grizzly bear.
We're different.
It's still a bear.
Oh, yeah?
Just because we're bears, we're all the same?
Yeah, bear bears.
We bear bears.
It's propaganda.
Oh, I thought that was you, but it was a cow.
Oh, my God.
We're losing it.
We're actually losing it.
Wait, what are the numbers?
I'm at negative 8,000.
No, not that.
I'm talking about what is the OG.
Oh, negative 4,116.
1,576.
Negative what?
4,116.
I'm in the ice.
And the Z is 1,576.
We're just a couple thousands away.
I'm in the ice.
I thought it was over.
I thought the ice stuff was over.
I was there before ice.
I'm on land.
I might die.
I actually might die.
Why are you gonna die from what?
You're just on ice.
I'm in ice.
My dogs are dying in ice.
I'm sorry.
Goodbye, doggos.
They can die.
It's fine.
Just as long as you stay alive.
Goodbye, my fellow doggos.
Goodbye.
I hear them dying in the ice.
How are they in the ice?
I'm sorry.
How are you in the ice?
I'm so sorry.
I didn't know.
Oh my god.
Goodbye, my doggos.
Goodbye.
I'm like two steps away from the ice.
Where are you?
What's your coordinate?
We're gonna see a doggo die in the ice.
We're gonna see it happen.
I don't have anywhere to be.
Why is he dying?
Is he like trapped underneath?
What does that mean?
Why don't you just move and they teleport?
Oh, the baby died.
Okay.
Why don't you just move and they teleport with you?
Because I was also trapped in the ice.
What do you want me to say?
Oh my god.
Why are you trapped in the ice?
What do you want me to say?
How are you trapped in the ice?
You just go around it.
It's already too late.
The baby's dead.
It's alright.
Oh wait, no.
He's alive.
Hello there.
See?
Everything's fine.
Come to my location.
I'm at...
negative 8,559 5,265 Alright.
Anyway, I'm at negative 8,300 now.
Oh, you're in the powdered snow.
Oh see, I told you you needed a bucket.
You took all my iron.
You gave me all your iron.
What did you want from me?
You took all...
I'm not there.
I'm not going where you are.
I'm fucking... I'm gone.
I'm gone.
Just go.
Fine.
I was here waiting for you.
I told you.
Just go.
Fine.
I'm going.
It's almost night time.
And I'm scared.
No, you're not.
There's a baby.
There you go.
I'm trying to give the baby some meat right now.
The last meat that I have.
This is why you're not supposed to have animals.
You have no attachments.
I did not want them to breed.
They just got close to each other.
They got close to each other and they just...
That's why you neuter them.
You want me to stop love.
You have to cut off their bones.
Where are the doctors?
We've been in the wilds for 20 years.
Where can I go to the doctors?
You do it yourself.
This is how cavemen learn.
Did you do it yourself?
I don't have pets.
You have cats.
No, I'm talking about in Minecraft.
What was I gonna say?
You don't see your cat as a pet?
No, they're family.
That's why you don't neuter family, I guess.
Yeah, don't neuter your family, everybody.
Oops, I accidentally reloaded.
Wait, no, that's not what I meant to do.
F3, there we go.
I'm moving.
Guys, if I could find...
If I could find wild animals right now...
Wild chickens or lambs or whatever...
I would, but I'm stuck here.
In this ice tundra.
We're so close.
I'm just rowing my boat.
Me too.
Just heading northeast.
Just heading northeast until...
Until it's over.
No, where's one?
My boat has to end.
Why?
What happened?
The water ended.
I don't know where you are or where I am.
I don't know anymore.
I'm just rowing.
I'm just rowing until we made it there.
I wonder if we're even close.
We're close.
We're getting there.
Then we'll have all our stuff, everybody.
And then we'll be able to continue the game.
And then we're basically at the end.
We're basically at the end at that point.
That's where...
That's what happens.
Why did the connection reset?
What happened to our server?
What happened?
Go back!
Where am I?
I'm back!
Before the ice!
Back in the ice?
I'm back in the ice!
How did I get back here?
Did you lose anything?
No, I didn't.
I have to roll back!
I have to roll!
I'm just running.
I don't care anymore.
This is a fucking re-zero shit.
Don't worry about them!
Come on, just go!
We have to run!
We have to just go!
Where am I?
We just have to go!
Northeast!
Even the dogs are gone!
Where did the dogs go?
It's fine, I can roll again.
I can roll again.
Uh-oh.
Wait, I went the wrong way.
Gosh.
They are in a better place.
In Java Wonderland.
That's what happens in the Minecraft server.
Everybody goes to Java Wonderland.
Oh, I found a village!
I had a delirious dream because of like frostbite or some shit.
You never had the dogs.
You were just pulling two rocks on a stick.
The frostbite got me.
The day restarted too though.
Because we were about to hit night time and the day restarted.
What happened to the server?
What happened?
You need to get a refund from wherever you look.
The dogs were never real.
I was going through some fucking shit.
But you saw them too!
What are you talking about?
What do you mean?
You literally had two rocks on a stick.
Or on a string.
No, they were real.
You were encouraging the dogs!
You had always just two rocks on a string and you were like, my dogs.
I was like, just leave them.
They're rocks.
Oh no, I don't wanna go in there.
Oh man.
The dogs were never real.
I don't wanna go in there.
I might die in here.
Oh gosh.
It gets dark in here, guys.
The dogs were never real.
They were never real.
They were just in my head.
Just a dream, just like this fever dream that we're experiencing right now.
They were never real.
When does it end?
When does the Minecraft end?
It's gonna end.
I don't wanna play Minecraft anymore!
Just keep on moving.
The moment...
The moment we get to that area, we're done.
We're almost to the end at that point.
We're literally...
All our stuff to make it to the end is in that chest.
We have to kill the dragon.
We have everything we need.
We just need the phantom thing and then the redstone.
We're gonna get to the redstone and then I'll farm the phantom.
You go get redstone, I farm phantom.
And then it's all over.
And then it's over and we're free.
And we'll be free.
Oh my god, there's zombies in here.
I'm in the scary woods.
I'm still in the snow.
Where the hell are you?
How am I still in the snow?
How are you still in the snow?
I don't know anymore.
I'm still there.
Oh my god.
Woah!
Lush biome.
Anyway.
It's fine, I got dirt.
I got dirt.
Uh oh, it's starting to get dark.
Oh man, why did they go by so fast?
Server, you were supposed to break!
What happened?
I feel like I've been running for years.
I've been running for years.
And running and running and running for years.
And running for years.
Oh my god, there's another dog.
Get over here.
I knew you were real.
I got dogs!
No, please.
Let me out of here.
Just put me in the ocean please.
I don't want to be up here.
I got the dogs.
I'm in the trees.
I'm a fucking monkey right now.
Oh my god.
How do I get down from...
Oh god, how do I get down from here?
I think I'm camping in the trees tonight.
Oh no.
Can't see anything.
I'm camping in the trees tonight.
I can't see anything.
I can't see anything anymore.
Everything is so dark.
Use your torches.
Can't see anything.
Are you dead?
It's so dark.
It's so dark and cold.
What's your coordinates?
What are your coordinates?
I'm just curious.
Okay.
How did I make no progress?
I had 4000 left and now I'm at 4000 still.
How?
I don't know anymore.
I don't know.
I'm out.
I'm out of the fucking...
Oh my god, I'm finally out.
I'm finally out of this godforsaken night.
I'm just gonna sleep through this night.
No, no, you're not.
You cannot sleep through the night because...
Let's yell when it becomes the daytime in the game.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
I'm trapped.
I'm trapped in the trees.
I can't see.
Where's my torch?
Okay.
Alright.
Okay, it's this way.
It's this way.
Alright.
Alright, I can't see much.
But I know I'm going the right way.
I know I'm going...
What are you?
I'm at 7,833.
4,060.
Oh, okay.
You're further than me.
Okay, where are you?
7,995.
4,281.
Okay, your Z is further though.
Oh.
Yeah, you have more Z's.
I'm at...
I've got the tinnitus and lighting the pathway for me, so I can't see shit.
Phantom, come and get me.
Phantom, please.
Phantom, where the fuck are the...
I'm like trapped in the trees, you guys.
I don't know how to get down.
I don't want to be in the trees anymore.
I don't want to be a tree person.
Oh my god, that cow scared me.
I don't want to be in the trees.
I can't see anything.
It's so dark.
The things I do for a phantom.
I know, right?
Should we just sleep?
No.
We're committed.
Oh my god, there's skellies in the trees.
No!
How do I get around you guys?
Burn it?
Burn it down?
I might die too.
I might burn you.
Just burn everything down.
Oh, phantom!
I have a phantom.
I have two of them!
Hit!
I hit them, I think.
Where are you?
I hit them.
Oh shoot!
I hit him.
Come on, phantom!
Hit!
Nice!
Oh no!
Hit!
I missed.
Oh my god, there's creepers and zombies coming after me.
Oh my god, there's a zombie coming.
Yeah!
Membrane!
We got it!
We got two membranes!
How many membranes do we need?
A lot, I think.
Leave me alone!
How many membranes do we need?
Two membranes!
Oh nice, nice, nice!
Four!
Wait, four per potion?
One membrane equals three potions.
Oh, okay.
Then we're good.
Yeah, we're good.
We already got what we needed and we're fine.
Oh no, I think we can get a little few more, right?
Because I have one as well, so we...
Yeah, but I think we can manage...
I think we can...
Oh gosh, there's creepers everywhere.
Please leave me alone.
I'm stuck in the trees, Donkey!
I'm stuck in the trees!
I need to make my bed, but there's too many monsters.
Oh my god!
Oh my god, what's your coordinates?
Where are we at?
I haven't moved!
I'm stuck in the trees!
Oh, you are stuck in the trees.
I didn't know when you said you were stuck in the trees.
I didn't realize you were stuck, stuck in the trees.
I'm stuck, stuck in the trees!
I'm stuck in the trees!
This is so stupid.
Alright,
guys.
I'm gonna keep running.
I'm gonna keep running too.
Run!
Through the forest!
I'm almost done.
I'm at 4,000...
7,493...
4,200...
I can't check right now.
3,000 C's away and...
3,000 X's away!
Okay!
We're running, running...
We're so close.
Oh, that was a sheep.
Don't scare me, sheep.
I almost tried to kill you.
I hate... Can I just get some water, please?
Like, that I can...
Oh my god, no, this is a bad area.
When it's daytime, I can fucking...
I will be able to...
I'll be able to make more...
Make more bread.
I just need it to be daytime.
We can sleep, probably!
Oh wait, the day is breaking!
The dawn is breaking!
Oh no, that's a village.
No, that's a village, nevermind.
That's good, that's good!
Find some books!
They're on the other side!
I can't reach them!
Oh no!
It's falling apart into the sky!
Find a way!
Ok, I'll try.
I can probably...
Do you think if I jump, you can... No, I don't think I can make it.
What were the coordinates again?
I don't think I can make it.
Phantom swoops again?
Oh my god, I'm getting another phantom.
Where is he?
Hello, Phantom?
Phantom, where are you?
Oh, there he is!
He's stuck in the trees!
Idiot, Phantom!
Wait, I think...
Hold on, guys.
Hold on.
Phantom, where did he go?
He bit me?
No, you're gonna turn into one of them.
I am a phantom already.
I'm already...
Luckily, nothing is spawning around me, but I need to kill him before...
Daybreak!
Oh no, daybreak is coming!
I need to kill him!
Thank god.
Don't hide there, you stupid idiot!
Do I not need...
I have so many...
We don't need this.
Where is the wood I was punching?
Where is the wood?!
I almost had him.
Come on, come on, come on!
I can kill him!
You were fighting the phantoms on the cliff?
Yeah, I'm like...
I'm like...
In my own epic story time over here, okay?
He didn't give me one though.
He didn't give me a membrane.
Okay.
You told me to go to the village!
I'm trying to get there!
I told you it was on the other side!
And you said go anyway!
You said make it!
It's for your own good.
I can't see anything in night time.
Oh my god, please, get on there.
Okay.
I'm trying to get to the other side.
Guys, oh, I don't think this is possible.
I don't think this is possible.
Alright, just keep going.
Just keep going.
I'm sorry, village!
Village!
We'll raid you another time!
Yeah, I know there's a drowned, you guys.
I saw it, I saw it.
Hopefully he doesn't have a trident, or else...
Well, I'm really...
Or else I'm doomed.
Oh my god.
2,000 left for the X...
And 2,000 left for 3.
I can't believe we came from...
12 ,000 and 10,000.
I can't...
I can't believe it.
I'm pretty far still, though.
I didn't make much progress.
I'm at negative 6,800.
We're at 3,700.
Where are you?
Okay, I'm negative 7,500.
4,200.
Numbers, what do they mean?
I know.
I can't do this anymore.
Man, we're so close!
We can't just stop at that moment.
We're so close.
I can't.
I'm not strong enough.
Yes, you are.
I'm so tired.
Why is this becoming a 24-hour stream?
We're gonna do it.
We're gonna make it.
We'll have everything we need.
By the time we make it back, we'll have everything we need.
I passed my beta.
Then you knew what we committed to!
You should've started it!
You knew the risk.
You know I'm PST.
You could have suggested an earlier time.
But you suggested so late.
Why?
I forgot how late it was.
I forgot.
That's not what you want me to say.
You could've asked for an earlier time.
You knew how long it was gonna take in the end.
You knew this was the sacrifice we're gonna have to make.
We're almost there.
I'm at the sad file.
Remember the sad file?
Do you remember the sad file?
We can do this.
I believe in...
I'm freaking...
I'm almost there.
I'm almost there at the original.
This isn't even the goal!
And we meet up.
But we'll have everything we need.
We'll literally have everything we need.
When we get there.
My back hurts so much.
I found a mesa.
The original mesa.
Oh my god.
We're actually almost there.
I remembered this area.
Oh my god.
We're actually almost there.
I remember this.
Redstone is in the mineshaft, right?
Yeah.
Okay, it's time.
I'm going in.
I'm going into the mesa mineshaft.
I have another wart.
I'm in the mesa mineshaft.
Do stuff while I'm...
While you're traveling?
Yeah.
Oh my god, how many redstone?
I got redstone.
How many do we need?
Oh wait, is it redstone?
What's the one that makes the potions longer, you guys?
Oh my god.
Is it the glowstone or is it the redstone?
Wait, is it redstone or glowstone?
Don't say that.
Redstone?
Okay.
Okay, I have a lot of...
The glowstone does something else.
Okay, I have...
I have eight.
Eight is enough.
Okay, I'm leaving.
I'm fucking leaving.
Then we have...
Yeah, glowstone is for strength and then redstone makes it last longer, the potions.
Okay.
I got eight.
Eight is enough.
People are saying eight is enough.
That's good enough for me.
Okay.
I just passed by some jungles.
Alright.
I'm almost there.
I'm actually almost there.
Oh wait, I'm in the mesa too.
We're in the mesa?
Oh that's good!
Oh my god, I gotta make the bread.
Almost forgot to make the bread.
Hey.
Bread.
I think that's mesa.
Isn't that?
Guys?
I'm in the desert kinda.
Bread.
How come I can't make bread?
What do you mean?
Why you not let me make bread?
Turn the hay bales into actual hay.
Okay.
I made bread.
I didn't make bread.
I need to figure out my inventory.
My inventory is a mess and I'm trying to figure this out.
I'm gonna eat my last...
I'm gonna eat my last carrot.
Not the carrot.
I'm gonna start eating bread.
Oh my god, get your carbs in.
I'm getting my carbs in.
I'm gonna throw this away.
Carb diet.
Okay.
I'm heading over.
My 2,954 for the Z.
And then, negative 6,000.
Wait, I'm walking the wrong way for X.
It's not good.
Alright, and then...
We're like probably so close to each other.
Probably is.
I found the original temple.
Oh, shit.
Oh my god, we've been playing that same map for...
The temple just exploded.
Like, how?
What?
Wait, what?
The temple exploded next to me.
I wonder if something spawned in it.
And then it pressed the button.
What?
Oh, the chunks loaded in.
And it exploded?
Loaded in.
Holy shit, that was freaky.
That was actually freaky.
I think Herobrine is on this server.
Oh my god, how did that happen?
Is that a peepee tower?
No, just kidding.
I didn't make any peepee towers here.
I made a peepee tower near the city.
That's the first village we went to.
Oh no, wait.
Nevermind, I have to get around this.
I'll go this way.
It's just a little bit.
Armadillo, so cute.
I see the armadillos.
Man, I wish I had my three dogs that...
Oh, could've used that, yeah.
What happened to them?
I don't know.
I guess I just didn't take my meds.
I guess that's it.
Oh, I found the original...
The...
The nether...
The nether gate.
Not that gate, but the other one.
The very first one we ever found.
Are you sure you're not confusing this with another server that we were on?
No.
I know what I saw.
I know exactly what I saw.
Okay, I'll believe you.
I don't know anything anymore.
I'm just still asleep.
I know what I want.
I want to rest my eyes.
Mint, I bet you we're gonna beat the ender dragon within two hours.
Oh my god.
Within two hours.
The sun will be rising.
Mint, within two hours, it's gonna be...
Mint, trust me.
Within two hours, it's gonna...
We're gonna make it.
It's just...
We just get all the materials we need and we're there.
We're there.
If we don't make it, if it's not two hours, what do you owe me?
What are you gonna give me?
Then it'll be within three hours.
My calculations was just a little wrong.
Just a little bit wrong.
It was just...
It'll be within two or three hours.
How about that?
Two to three more hours.
Are you really gonna...
Are you really not gonna...
Mint...
What if we die in the ender dragon?
Don't say that!
We're gonna be so...
We're gonna make sure...
We're gonna be really stacked up.
We're gonna be so...
Stacked up.
What do I need to do to make arrows again?
I have 15 feathers.
Oh, you need flint also.
You have flint?
No, you gotta get that in the... What's it called?
In the...
In the mines.
In the gravel.
Oh my god, we're gonna have to take away all those gravel?
No, but we would have to mine...
We would have to place those gravels...
And then dig them.
It would be torture.
Just find some water.
Remember when we...
We had all this gravel?
Yeah.
I had so much gravel.
What were we gonna do?
Just take stacks and stacks...
And stacks of gravel?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's what we were gonna do.
Oh yeah, what else were we gonna do?
Just trade from the...
How do we get a Fletcher villager?
How?
I have a Fletcher villager.
I'm at a village right now.
Oh my god, trade some fucking arrows right now.
Hold on, let me see.
Wait, the Fletcher is the map guy, right?
I don't fucking know.
I was just reading my chat.
The Fletching table.
No?
What's the Fletching table?
I don't fucking know.
Oh, I know what it looks like.
What's this guy do?
What do you do?
What do you have?
Oh, you have...
Oh, you're a cartographer.
Yeah, that's the guy that makes maps.
I'm starting to get a headache, man.
Why are there two cartographers?
Okay, I'm leaving this village.
It sucks.
You can make a Fletcher thing.
What do I need?
I don't know.
What do they need?
I need to become a Fletcher.
Hold on, I'm putting down the crafting table.
Oh my god, I'm actually almost there for real this time.
Oh, I need Flint!
I need Flint!
We always need Flint.
No, but, man, I'm actually there.
I'm actually, like, legitimately there.
I'm actually...
When do we get a middle point?
I can get all my...
I'm almost...
I'm only a thousand away on each side.
Okay.
So we're both very, very close.
Yeah.
What's the plan when we get there?
What do we need to make first?
Sleep.
I think we should make the potions first.
Because I have all the stuff for the potions.
Sure.
There's a village to my right?
Oh, there is.
How did you wish that?
Wait, we can sleep now, right?
We don't need the phantoms, right?
Oh, true, true, true.
Okay.
Even if we need it, we'll just stay up again.
Let's just sleep.
Alright, we're very good at that.
Alright, I'm sleeping.
Please sleep, oh my god.
Okay.
Okay, I'm heading to the village next to me.
To see if there's more stuff I need.
I'm so tired, I didn't even put the boat in the water.
I put it on the land.
I thought it was water.
This is a village we haven't desecrated yet.
Oh my god, I'm at another village.
Wait, that was just one house.
Oh no, the other village...
Oh my god, the other houses are over there.
I was gonna say, how is there one house?
Wait, are we in the same village?
No, I don't see your name.
I don't know.
No, I don't see...
We farmed this house.
But we might have missed some stuff.
I don't recognize this one.
Actually, everything looks the same to me anymore.
They all look the same.
I don't remember if they opened the door.
Or if I fucking harvested this house already.
Oh my god.
Maybe they just opened these doors.
No, I definitely haven't been here before.
No, I haven't been here.
Wait, there's a brewing stand too.
Oh, there's raw meat.
Oh my god.
Why do you refrigerate that?
Is there books?
Who has the books?
Taking their emeralds because...
They have emeralds, they have apples.
We don't need any of those.
Taking their emeralds in case we need to trade.
For arrows.
Oh, books!
Books, I got books.
Get them, get them.
Grabbing hay.
Checking if there's books here.
Grab the hay first before I think of anything else.
Do I need gas tears?
I don't remember.
I keep asking if I need gas tears.
Oh my god, what did I accidentally click?
What's the potion for gas tears again?
I can't remember.
What's the gas tear?
Obsidian can go?
Yeah, you're right, obsidian can go.
Oh, regen!
Yeah, we want the gas tears.
Okay, I got the gas tear on me then.
I have one.
Is this a library?
What's over here?
What's here?
Oh, it is stonecutter.
Okay, alright, time to go back to the coordinates.
There's a chicken.
Get over here, I need your feather.
Big boss, help me please.
Oh my god, we're so close.
Solidus, please.
Solidus, save me.
We're almost there.
Solidus.
We're so close.
There's so much stuff.
I can do this.
I believe in this.
Stay strong.
We just need to do the three more hours.
I found more books.
I found a lot more books.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
This is a good village, actually.
Okay, I'm in the jungle.
Is somebody sleeping?
Think about how great it's gonna feel when we beat the ender dragon.
I won't have any reflexes to beat the ender dragon.
Think about it, Min.
You're gonna get that last lock-in moment right there.
Right now.
Okay, guys.
What's the chords again?
What if we get to the end and then do the ender dragon tomorrow?
Min, Min.
What if we did that?
It's gonna feel so good, Min.
Just think about how good it's gonna feel.
I'm almost out of food.
Just kidding, I have food for you.
How are you out of food?
There's a village.
I took a melon.
I have melon slices.
Okay, okay, that's good.
I'm drooling on myself.
I'm so tired.
Min, I believe.
Min, just...
Final stretch.
We're almost there.
We're almost there, Min.
Min, we're almost there.
Me too.
I'm almost too sleepy to end.
We're almost there, Min.
Just stay strong.
Stay strong.
What's the coordinates?
The coordinates are...
My negative 4000...
I don't even know.
Negative 4000 something.
Negative 4116 and 1576.
Yeah, oh.
Wait, you're there?
No, I'm literally like 200 away.
Okay.
I'm a little ways, but I'm making my way.
Okay,
I am negative 4000.
Am I going the right way?
I am, okay.
Just running through the forest.
Oh my god, another village.
How many villages are you finding?
A lot, apparently.
You're finding all the villages.
Where were they before?
You're right.
Where were these?
Where did they come from?
Oh my god, wait.
Wait, I'm actually almost there.
I'm so close.
What was the Z, guys?
What was the Z?
What did I just pick up?
Did I just pick up another gold chestplate?
I think this is where you were at just now.
Oh yeah, you were where I was!
And you're almost there.
I'm almost there.
Okay, I'm leaving.
You're almost there.
That's literally my chestplate.
Yeah, I was like, what the heck?
You picked it up.
It's where I left.
There's nothing there, I already harvested.
I know, I'm leaving.
Oh my god, I think I almost just fell in a hole.
Okay.
Almost just fell in a hole.
Alright.
Okay.
1,600.
I found it!
It's in front of me!
You did it.
I did it.
I found it.
I traveled so far.
It's over here.
I found the PB Town.
I found her home.
I actually found it.
Oh my god, there it is.
There's the water bucket.
Okay, I'm gonna...
What do we need?
I'm gonna put the stuff, putting potions stuff here.
And then, I'm gonna...
Wait, is there flint?
We have flint!
How much arrow per flint?
I think it's one.
Okay, arrow.
Am I going the right way, guys?
I'm going the right way.
I'm almost there.
I'm just a couple hundred away.
I have 37.
I have 37 arrows.
I'm putting the redstone dust.
I'm putting the redstone dust here.
And then...
What am I doing still?
I don't know.
Hi, hi.
Mint, stay strong.
Stay strong, Mint.
Stay, Mint.
I believe in you.
Stay strong.
You have the wood.
I have the wood.
Oh, I need to go this way.
I need to get out of the water.
I need...
I'm grabbing...
Where the fuck is the wood?
Do we have enough wood?
We're literally...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I have wood.
Don't fall.
I'm running.
Okay.
I have...
You can do this.
We're at the finish line.
We have everything we need.
We literally have everything we need.
Did you make arrows already?
Yeah, yeah.
I made 37 arrows.
That is more than enough.
That's not enough.
I have 20 spectral arrows.
How is that not enough?
How do we need more?
We have to hit the things to be able to kill the dragon.
I can hit them.
I can hit it.
It's so easy.
I'm in a village.
How are you in a village?
I can hit it.
You can?
Okay.
I can hit it.
I've done it before.
Okay.
I can hit it.
This is a fancy village.
I'm gonna go to sleep now in real life.
No.
Just make it here.
Just make it here, Mint.
Make it to the last destination.
The last goal.
I'm dying.
The guy just took my bed.
Make it here, Mint.
Go to sleep.
Make it to the end.
Anywhere.
Gotta sleep.
Alright.
Let's see.
I refreshed that person.
By sleeping in their bed.
Okay, I have 45.
I have 45 arrows now.
Oh my god.
How do I make bed?
Okay.
Bed.
That's fine.
That's enough beds, I think.
I can make one more bed for attacking.
Why are there so many damn cartographers, man?
And then...
Let's see.
I don't need bone.
We don't need coal.
We don't need gold.
What's a potion for strong hits, everybody?
So we can get some strong hits on the dragon when he comes down.
What do we need for that?
What's a strong hit potion that we could get?
Where's my...
Okay, we have 11 enders.
We have...
That's a strong potion, you guys.
Okay, I'm putting potion stuff in your chest right now.
You're the potions person.
I don't know how potions work.
I don't know how they work.
No, don't do it.
Don't do it.
Please let me do it.
Please let me be the one.
I put all the potion things in your chest.
You have all the potion stuff.
I didn't touch anything.
I found more books.
I'm giving you 12 books.
Find obsidian.
We need to make the enchanting table.
Enchanting!
1, 2, 3...
I'm harvesting this nether portal.
We don't need it anymore.
I'm harvesting it.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, nether portal.
We never need you anymore.
Okay, I'm a couple hundred away.
I'm on my way.
Goodbye, nether...
Goodbye.
We're never coming back.
Oh, I have... There's four in the chest.
Oh, we have four, by the way.
It's okay.
I needed to break that anyway.
We're never coming back here.
Do you wanna try and do a...
A pillager raid so we can get a totem of undying?
Oh, that's a good idea.
I have an ominous banner.
How do we get the pillager?
I think it's the...
I think it's that potion we got before, right?
The ominous?
Yeah.
The ominous bottle gives you...
Oh, it's raining.
That scared me.
Oh my god, okay.
I mean, we don't have to get it, but...
Okay.
Enchanting...
I got the table.
I see the PP tower!
You see it?
Where are you?
I'm on my way!
I don't see you!
I just came into light!
I see you!
Do you see me?
I see you too!
Oh man!
We made it!
We have everything we need!
We have everything!
I brought you the enchant.
We're so close!
We have everything!
I have fence!
I have arrows!
We have all the potion stuff!
We have red dust!
Everything we need is right here.
It's right...
It's right here!
We did it!
We jumped so far!
We got everything!
We have everything!
Should we make a new stream?
We should...
Are we committing to the end?
I don't know anymore.
I don't know.
This is your choice, Mint.
You're past your bedtime.
Like you know I'm a night owl.
I thought we were going...
to the end.
You wanna go to the end?
I thought so.
Are we doing it, Mint?
Are we doing it to the end?
I'm sorry.
I hit my second wind.
Okay, let's make our...
Let's make our stream.
Okay.
Mint, I believe this.
Okay, let's turn my stream now and make a new one.
I believe this.
Okay.
Fever substance hitting hard for me.
I believe this.
It's my favorite song.
Okay, I'm making my room too.
I believe it right now.
Mint, I believe this.
Oh my god.
Alright.
I can't fucking remake.
I can't use the same settings.
I have to...
I have to copy everything over again.
Oh my god.
Okay.
I didn't realize you gotta end your stream to be able to copy it.
I thought you can copy existing stuff.
Copying.
We have one...
One life to make this happen.
Oh my god.
Is it gonna...
Is it night time?
I don't know.
I'm making my room.
We'll hear the monsters if it is.
We'll hear the monsters.
I think we're okay.
Okay, we're making our waiting rooms, everybody.
We're doing it.
We're making our waiting rooms.
Oh my god, why can't I act you?
I don't know.
I won't let you do it.
It's so stupid.
I hate that.
It bugs out sometimes.
Oh my god, 420 AM.
Okay, I'm just...
I'm not even gonna change the tags or anything.
I'm not even gonna change the tags.
I'm just gonna put...
I'm gonna put...
Okay guys, we're gonna raid into my next stream.
Alright guys, I'm raiding to my next stream as well.
We'll see you.
We'll see you in the second room.
See you in the second room.
Bye bye.
I didn't even finish making my room yet.
Yeah, okay, bye bye.
You got the bye bye in?
I haven't yet.
I'm ending stream.
Bye bye.
Okay, I'm making my waiting room.
I'm making my waiting room so my thing is...