Oh!
Welcome back!
My master!
My lady!
Aww!
She's laughing at her pain.
I thought I had a different setting on.
So I didn't realize that I was...
So...
Here!
I'm back!
Welcome back!
Hello!
Hello hello hello hello.
Welcome back.
Welcome back Minecraft.
Yeah!
Minecraft time!
Yippee!
Oh my gosh.
It's been so long since... actually, I've never seen this screen before.
When did Minecraft update?
Wait a second.
What is this?
These are the new lights.
I remember... wait, did they already show all of this?
It's new!
Oh my gosh, a while back.
1.2... 1.2... 1.1.
It's the new structures.
Wait, can we find this then?
How do we find it?
How do we find this?
Where do we go?
What do we do?
I thought this was only gonna be for the bedrock for some reason.
I thought...
Hello Minto.
Minecraft?
Yes, Minecraft.
Have to head out in 30 minutes.
Oh no!
I need more context.
Probably by mining.
Okay.
Cartographers have maps probably.
Deep in caves!
That's gonna be our goal!
This will be our goal for today.
Is to find this and also I'm in hardcore mode so I can't die!
Thank you!
You're laughing?
We're crying because you hate us and you're laughing?
I work for another 3 hours plus hour drive home.
No, James!
Good luck with work.
I cannot mine of the craft today.
That's okay.
She's gonna die a lot.
I can't die a lot!
It's literally hardcore!
It's one and done, baby!
It's one and done.
But...
I will have some help.
I have created Minto server!
I will allow access...
To... Okay, I have some rules.
Okay?
I have some rules for those...
Wanting to join.
Any memboos in chat...
I will give you...
The...
The access.
But...
How long until you regret it?
Maybe immediately.
Who knows?
Um...
So...
Uh...
No killing Minto...
On purpose.
Andrey goes next to the 20!
Um... I... Oh, wait.
Hold on.
I have to give myself admin powers to be able to ban people.
Wait.
What's my... Hold on.
Hold on.
Manage server.
Become admin.
I think that's my name.
Hmm...
So...
You know...
It's hardcore.
Normally, if it wasn't hardcore, I'd be like, whatever.
But because it's hardcore...
Don't.
Okay?
Let's have... Let's be nice.
Let's have fun.
Let's have a good stream.
Okay?
Thank you.
And also...
Also...
If you die...
Leave...
The server.
So that more people can join.
And take your spot.
There's only 100 slots.
You want as many people to be able to come in as they can.
So...
Yes, yes, yes.
Andrey goes, thank you for the 20 gift.
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Babycore, thanks for the gift.
Oh my gosh.
Wake up, Black.
Thank you for the 20 gift.
Thank you!
Work time for the Ashes.
And by that, I mean watching Mint's stream.
But yeah...
So...
If you die, you are dead.
Exactly!
If you die...
That's it, buddy.
You're kicked out.
You're gone.
You're donezo.
Okay?
So...
Hopefully, it allows...
People to be able to come in.
There is PvP on.
Don't be a jerk.
You know?
Don't go on like a whole ass killing spree.
But...
You know...
Let's work together to try and find...
This place.
Right?
Let's try and find...
This place.
Because I really actually want to see it.
I don't know what's in there.
But I want to see it.
I want to go to there.
If you die in Minecraft, you die in IRL.
Yes.
Pretty much.
Whoever runs the cemetery is going to be...
No!
Be slightly more normal than Mint.
Yeah!
Wait.
What does that mean?
What do you mean by that?
Okay.
But I'm going to join first.
I'm going to join first and we're going to see.
Actually, I had to join because I had to do some stuff.
I had to check some stuff.
So I actually know where we are.
And boy, golly, our location is kind of...
You guys ready to see the spawn?
Here we go.
Good luck, everybody.
Getting out of the tree.
What is this?
This is the worst.
But we have so much bamboo.
So we'll get so much wood and everything.
Welcome to the jungle.
Okay.
Another thing.
It shows the hearts as not hardcore.
But I tested it on another server.
I'm not sure why it's not showing up.
But I tested it on a different server.
Like I tried it out multiple times last night.
And it definitely was hardcore.
When I died, I was not able to come back.
What the...
Wait.
What's going on?
Also, why is there no sound?
But also, what's going on?
Oh, my volume is off.
That's why.
Okay.
I'll try.
Oh!
Spawn...
Oh, spawn protection!
Oh!
Okay.
Wait.
How am I supposed to get out of the tree then?
This is messed up!
Did it make a boot?
Did it make...
Oh, wait.
No.
I used my hand.
That's why.
How am I supposed to get out of the tree?
Okay.
Okay!
We are good!
We are good.
We're good.
I'm going to get down the tree first and then I will allow access.
Okay.
I'm gonna get down first.
Gonna change spawn?
No.
Why would I do that?
NVIDIA STOCKS!
STOCKS!
Sinbad, thank you so much for the Aqua Supa.
Thank you!
Okay, guys.
Okay.
I'm gonna lock myself up first because I'm scared of it turning nighttime while I do this because I'm a little slow.
Hold on.
Let's...
Let's get some bamboo.
Oh my gosh.
This is so scary.
Wait.
Why is this also...
Is this also part of the spawn?
Oh.
Interesting.
Maybe...
I don't think I should turn that off but...
Interesting.
I'm under the tree.
Oh my gosh.
It even extends all the way to here.
Okay.
We're fine.
Everything's good.
I'm gonna make myself a little house.
A little hut, you know?
Panda.
Is there a panda?
Panda!
Okay.
Alright.
This should be good, right?
Wait.
How do I...
Oh gosh.
It's...
Guys, I think I forgot how to play Minecraft for real.
I literally have not touched Minecraft since like the last time I played, I think.
So...
Bamboo.
Wait.
I don't have that much.
I thought there was gonna be more.
Uh-oh.
Oh no.
Okay.
I'm making my house.
Wait.
You guys are also gonna spawn in at night then.
Maybe we should...
Maybe we should wait for it to come back to daytime.
Late time, maybe.
Right?
Maybe we should wait?
We'll be fine?
You'll be fine?
It's really dark in here.
I can't even see what's up.
Okay.
There.
I have a little window.
Okay.
I'm scared.
I don't actually know if the admin thing works.
Let's see.
Time.
Wait.
Set.
Does it work?
Um.
Actually, I don't know.
Time set.
Set.
Time.
I don't think I have perms.
It didn't work!
Oh, I think I needed to reset the server.
It's getting awfully dark out there.
It's getting awfully dark out there, you guys.
Slash time.
It doesn't work.
Hold on.
I'm gonna reset the server.
And also get the stuff.
Okay.
It worked.
And then I reset.
And then I give you...
Oh, wait.
But I have to...
I have to go in first.
Okay.
Reboot!
And let me make the post.
Let me do this.
I wouldn't have posted it sooner, but, you know, I gotta get in first, you guys.
Memboos only.
Okay.
Maybe it's done?
Oh.
Process has been done.
Okay.
Wait.
Why doesn't it work?
You know what?
I guess I'll have to be, um...
OP or something?
I don't now...
Oh, SlashOP?
What does that mean?
SlashOP Mint Phantom.
I don't...
In the server console...
Guys, I have not idea what I'm going.
To be honest...
How do I get to the server console?
Server console open.
Is that... hold on.
I thought just becoming a... I wonder if actually...
That's not my username.
I actually have no idea what my username is.
Maybe...
Because I had to change it.
Oh, there's the console.
Slash OP...
I wonder if that's me.
Hold on, am I Mint Phantom?
Footsteps!
Oh my gosh.
They're here, they're here, they're here, they're here, they're here.
You guys, they're here, they're here, they're here!
Press tab.
Made Mint Phantom!
Of course I was wrong!
Okay, hold on.
Made...
Execute.
I wonder if...
Made a server operator!
I did it, I did it, I did it, I did it, I did it, I did it.
But, does that mean I can't die?
I want to be able to die too.
Time, set, day.
Yippee!
Okay.
Alright.
I'm going to be posting...
The, um, way to get into the server.
Oh, you can?
Yippee!
Okay.
Happy birthday, Bebong!
Alright.
A three.
Again, remember.
No killing Minto on purpose.
You know?
We're playing fair.
Having a good stream.
Um...
Uh...
Once you die, leave.
Okay?
Okay.
Okie dokie.
What version is this?
Uh...
1.2...
1.1.
Alright, and then of course we'll be in a membership post.
Because this is for Memboos to join.
Post!
I think it's gonna lag.
There's a lag.
It won't.
Everybody's frozen in time.
Wait,
let me back in.
You guys have to let me in!
It's a Bicep!
No!
I knew this would happen.
It's still so funny to see.
No!
Let me in the Bicep!
Our server now.
No!
Don't take my wood!
I wonder when I can join again.
Is it dead dead?
No way!
Can't connect.
Did it die die?
Oh my gosh.
Money wasted.
I even paid for the good stuff.
I'm gonna be getting an email from the place that's hosting this being like, What did you do?
Let me try rebooting it.
They're gonna be like, They're gonna be like, You!
Go back.
No!
They're gonna be like, VTuber!
How dare you!
Crash!
Let's see.
Okay.
No!
Oh gosh, it's night time.
It's night time.
You guys, none of us have swords, none of us have anything.
What do we do?
Do you think it'll crash again?
I can't tell, I can't see anything.
Time.
Set.
Day.
It's so over, you guys.
It's so over.
How?
Slowroll people and how do I do that, though?
Everyone form a line.
Hold on.
Let me go back in the control panel.
How do I allow it to only just a certain number of people then?
Let's see...
Have
like a limit... the limit does not exist?
Oh
wait, here maybe?
I'm learning how to code in real time.
Oh, here we go.
Okay, I'm gonna start with the 25.
I'm gonna start with a 25.
And then I'll raise it slowly and slowly and slowly and slowly and slowly and slowly.
It's processing, it's processing, it's processing...
It's processing, it's... oh, okay.
One second again.
Okay, it's processing, it's processing, it's processing...
The server is not allowed to be full, you guys!
I have to go in first!
This is literally defeating the purpose!
Leave!
It's processing, it's processing, it's processing, it's processing...
It's processing, it's processing, it's processing...
Oh, wait.
Me first?
Ah!
Oh my gosh.
It's night time?
Look at you guys just standing there menacingly!
Guys, did I make a mistake?
Guys?
Did you reboot it?
Yeah, I did!
I did!
I rebooted!
My poor server!
You guys!
I paid money for this!
Please!
Oh my god.
I'm going back in.
I'm connecting to the server.
I'm going in.
Guys, I'm going in.
Not even with the 25 people!
It's the amount of people trying to connect.
I think so too, perhaps.
Including me.
No!
What do I do then?
Why didn't you use a queue system monitor?
Um, I don't know.
Why didn't you?
Why didn't you shut the heck up?
All I wanted to do was something fun.
Honestly, I had the idea like last night.
And I was just like, what if I do this?
And then I didn't think that would be a problem.
I'm stupid.
It's all me.
We need a bouncer.
Oh well.
Goodbye money.
Waste of my money.
Delete game server.
Bye everybody.
Well, I can still do Minecraft hardcore.
Just all by myself.
So sad and lonely.
Hardcore.
Sad, sad, lonely world.
No!
But we're still gonna try and find the...
This thing.
Whatever.
Whatever this is.
So...
Oh!
Oh, it's chilly.
Oh.
Okay.
Alright, we're playing the game now everybody.
And it's real hardcore.
Why don't I hear anything?
For real.
I think I turned everything off.
No?
Huh.
I can't even hear my own footsteps.
Weird.
Goodbye server.
Oh, I kind of hear it.
Is the music loud by the way?
Just let me know.
Let's get some wood.
Sorry guys.
I tried.
Maybe in the future, I can actually get someone that knows what they're doing.
And not just me being a silly goose the night before.
It's good?
Okay.
Yes.
Are Minecraft servers expensive?
No, not really.
Oh, we're like really...
I think this is the place.
I think this...
I think it's probably like right underneath us.
This place is so mysterious.
I think it's probably right beneath us.
But there's like no food here.
Okay.
We're gonna...
So how does one find...
This structure?
This new cave feature?
It's not like part of...
What's it called?
Is it...
The place that gets you to the end?
The trial chamber?
That sounds serious.
That sounds a little freaky when you say it like that.
When you call it a trial chamber.
But it's...
It's in the main world.
No, but I mean like it's not...
What I'm trying to say is it's not...
It's not...
I'm trying to see if there's like a ice village.
It's not connected to the...
To that place, is it?
It's planning on giving you a flower, Minecraft.
Thanks.
Here, I'll take this one.
There we go.
Whoa.
Village, village.
Is there a village around here?
We're gonna start getting hungry and then we're gonna start dying.
You guys, I'm not...
I can't die.
I'm gonna have to kill this bunny.
I'm gonna have to kill things to survive.
They're so small though.
They got like no meat on them.
Bunny, yes.
It's...
Minto needs to eat.
Hmm.
Nothing inside.
Whoa.
Got some towering places.
Let's see.
Igloo to the right?
Igloo?
Oh!
I completely missed it.
Igloo!
Igloo inbound!
I was so focused on trying to find a village.
Oh!
Oh, well, that doesn't really matter, does it?
Oh, yes!
You think?
Aw.
Dang.
Okay.
But this is good.
I mean, a little bit.
Um...
Uh, we have a home.
We have a home.
A home base even.
I can make you good soup.
You're gonna make me turntable?
A turtle soup?
Are you gonna make...
Here, I make good soup.
Break the gray carpet.
Oh, this one?
Oh, I thought it was the one in the middle.
Nope.
Unlucky.
You guys are watching Minto's stream.
Did you expect anything else?
All right, so we got our little home.
I'm gonna put my bed here.
Um...
Put this back here.
Uh...
And let's go...
First, I'm gonna make a door.
First, jungle server.
Second, Alaska.
For the future server fundings, I could say I logged in for like 10 seconds, jumped three times, and server died.
Yeah!
Yippee!
Okay, we really need food now.
Oh, gosh.
I gotta...
Okay, let's go.
Sword.
Wait, how do I...
Oh, I need sticks.
Sword.
And we need...
Stuff to...
Um...
We can use, uh...
The...
What's it called, right?
The logs.
To burn.
Here, bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny!
Here, bunny, bunny, bunny!
Oh, yeah.
Don't look!
Don't look if you're afraid!
Wait, what the hell?
Oh my god.
Literally no meat.
Oh, bunny!
Yeah!
Okay.
It was a baby.
Um...
My...
I'm also a baby.
I need food to live.
I'm a baby!
I'm sorry!
Don't look at me, please!
Don't look at me as I kill you!
Please don't look...
You guys, I have to eat!
I have to eat!
Okay, let's go cut down...
Oh!
Pumpkins!
Oh, I could have eaten these instead.
Um...
Don't worry about it.
Don't...
It's not for no reason.
It's for survival!
I'm just like that bear, guys.
I...
I have to eat!
Someday you feed on a pumpkin.
Some days you have to kill a bunny.
You can't eat pumpkins.
Yes, you can.
You can make pumpkin pie.
I know how to play Minecraft.
Um...
Oh, that's right.
I'm gonna plant ye...
Oh, wait.
Just kidding.
I'm gonna beat this tree up.
The Minto server graveyard is going so swell.
What do you mean graveyard?
I deleted it.
What do you mean?
How are there people there?
Like so, right?
Yeah.
We're all playing on a Wisp server.
How do I join?
Does it fall through your tum tum?
No.
Okay.
Oh.
Delicious.
Okay.
We don't want those to burn up.
No girls allowed.
You're gonna say that to all the girl Wisps?
You're gonna say no girls allowed?
To all the girl Wisps that are wanting to join?
You guys, I'm so lonely.
I thought we'd be able to play.
That's honestly...
Oh.
Dinner!
I can't have the pumpkin pie yet.
I need sugar.
Which actually there should be some like down here, shouldn't there?
That's why I haven't played so much Minecraft because it's just not as fun without, you know, with without people.
Um.
Oh.
There's a portal thing.
I see sugar.
Sugar cane.
Oh!
Yippee!
Sugar sugar.
Sugar sugar sugar.
Yeah.
It's so much more fun with people.
So.
I just haven't played.
But that's okay.
Maybe next time, um, I can get it working for reals.
For realsies.
For actual real.
Uh.
Ooh!
These are kind of useless, but I'll take it.
Um.
Take this chill.
Yeah.
Okay, bye.
All right, let's go home.
That guy's not gonna attack me, right?
He doesn't have any children.
You are childless.
Okay.
I missed the jungle area though.
I missed the berry.
What do you want, berry?
Hold on.
I'll read it.
How does it taste?
Wait, wait.
What do I?
Why?
What are we saying?
Oh gosh.
It's getting dark.
Okay.
I have to live.
I have to live, you guys.
Nothing will spawn in my house, right?
I have a little tiny light.
I have a little night light.
Why aren't you in full diamond armor yet?
Haha.
OMG the Wisp server is so fun.
I just ate a fish.
Berry, you're so mean!
You're so mean to me!
Why would you do this?
I don't even make a sugar.
And a pumpkin pie.
What do I need?
I need chickens!
Why are you so mean?
I'll waste a log for this.
Okay, let's go find some chickens.
I didn't know pumpkin pie actually required eggs.
Is that normal?
I don't think that's very normal, is it?
Well, let's put this on just in case.
Wait.
Okay, projectile projection.
Okay.
I'll take it.
Cakes require eggs.
But it's not a cake.
It's a pie.
It's literally in the name.
It's called pumpkin pie.
Not pumpkin cake.
Oh no, it's a family.
Puts it away.
Sheep!
Oh, it's a family.
I'm at work right now, so I can't say to watch.
Thank you though for the server chat.
Good luck on the work!
The server is so fun.
I can't believe I already found diamond.
Why are you guys bullying me?
You guys are bullying me.
I want to play with people.
Wait.
What is this?
Oh, was it me?
I'll take it.
Leftovers.
A village!
Village hole!
Village, village, village.
Okay, we're going to take their stuff.
We're going to take their things.
I got to start digging.
I got to start getting some...
Oh, oh, oh.
I got to start getting...
What's the word?
Coal?
Supplies.
We need coal.
So we can make...
More...
We make torches?
I mean, this place has free torches right here.
And free armor!
Okay.
This village is a little rich.
What do you got?
Oh, well take it all.
Take it all!
Yeah, we gotta make iron.
We gotta do everything.
I wanna find... you know, maybe if trying to find this in Hardcore was a mistake.
This potentially dangerous area that everyone keeps saying, Minto, you won't find it.
You will die.
Oh, nice jackpot.
Potatoes.
Pumpkin pie!
Take all the food you can.
Take all the food.
Rob them.
Leave them with nothing.
The wisps are so fun.
I just killed a man.
Excuse me.
Iron!
Alright.
So far so good.
Ouch.
Are you sure you wouldn't just stalk people in the server?
What?
No!
You tried... What do you mean you tried shipping them?
Tried shipping who?
Are there any other houses?
Okay, here we go.
This is a really big village.
How is this tree...
How is this working?
How is this... Huh?
Hidden... secrets?
Potentially where the location we are trying to go to is at?
I don't think anybody can even enter this home.
Oh!
Oh, I just freed... I just freed the prisoner.
I think...
I think that guy was in there on purpose.
My bad.
Whoa!
This place is fancy!
Let's see.
Cooper, thanks for the $10 gift!
Okay.
I got in.
Thank you Minto for setting this up.
Wait.
How did you get in?
What do you mean you got in?
Are you here?
Here O'Brien?
Are you here O'Brien-ing my server right now?
Free bun?
I have a bun.
Oh wait, I left it, didn't I?
But also, once we go into the mines, there's no point in having a bed.
There's no point.
But I'll take it anyway.
Yeah, my bed is in the igloo.
I was just gonna stay here until night, you know?
Let's get more berries.
Let's rob them of everything they have.
They didn't even have that much iron or anything like that.
Oh, they had this too, right?
I'll take this.
Mine?
I can't believe you managed to get David Hayter on the server.
You're the best.
It's me, Steve, from the hit movie Minecraft starring Jack Black.
Thanks for letting me into the server.
You're welcome!
Oh my gosh.
What if the Minecraft movie is really just about me?
Not to seem narcissistic or anything.
But I always said, if I were ever to star in a movie, I would want Jack Black to play me.
And it could be that they listen to my demands.
My commands, my demands.
And my plans.
You are Jack Black.
No, I am Steve.
Do you have any eggs around here?
Like, where's your chickens?
I am Steve.
This is actually a pretty nice maintained farm.
Died right before I finished the snake ass mural.
It's okay.
You were so close.
But now you'll never be able to join ever again.
The server is gone.
Oh!
Why are there so many creepers in there?
Why are there so an egregious amount of creepers in there?
I'm trying to find a chicken so I can make some...
some...
What's it called?
What is a group of creepers called?
You know how it's like a murder of crows?
Dangerous.
Just like me, baby.
I didn't bring any of my stuff.
I didn't bring my crafting table.
I'll just make a new one.
Just make a new one.
A mint.
She's so cringe.
Yeah, but I'm free!
I'm free!
Look at this!
I'm out here in the world!
A group of creepers is called a reddit?
What?
Like reddit, we did it?
We did it reddit?
Huh?
Alright.
Pickaxe.
I don't have a lot of space!
Streamer didn't get the joke.
What's... hold on.
You're right, I didn't.
Because people in there are creeps!
That's so mean!
Hahaha!
Time for bed!
Almost time for bed.
Hahaha!
Don't take my bed.
Don't do it.
Let's see...
I don't want to just keep making wood stuff.
But we need it so I can get a little bit of...
We need iron.
Okay.
I don't want to go too far because I have my house.
And I also want to dig there.
I truly believe...
I believe that that is the place that we need to go to.
Okay?
But I also want to find...
I want to find a...
a chicken.
Get some eggs.
Always dig straight down.
Yeah, I think where the igloo is.
Basically that area.
Oh!
This is really close to the village.
Are they okay?
I have nothing.
I have a sword.
It's a lie.
I have one thing.
I don't see anybody there.
Maybe it's abandoned.
Alley!
This place is so abandoned!
Ignore that guy right there.
There's nobody here.
Free the golem.
They're gonna kill him.
Oh, there's... ignore that one right there too.
He just...
phase into existence.
I didn't make a...
Oh!
Alley!
Which way did I come from?
This way?
Which way?
Which Metal Gear is this?
Okay.
We'll come back.
Where did I come from?
There!
I see.
Why is it so hard to find a dang chicken?
Okay.
Chicken.
Wolf.
I just wanna make some pumpkin pie.
It's like the...
It's like...
The minimum I ask for is pumpkin pie.
In the caves.
Is that too much to ask for?
Just to have something... a little sweet treat?
In the caves?
You know?
Is that too much to ask for?
It's also...
basically fall.
So... it's very exciting.
To have pumpkin pie.
Or we could go down here.
Look at all the iron and stuff.
And the coal.
We need that.
Which came first?
The chipkin or the egg?
The
egg had to come first.
The egg had to come first.
Guys, I feel like I'm on a wild chicken chase.
I would say...
Usually a wild goose chase.
But...
Um...
I'm seriously just wondering...
Why I can't find a single chicken.
In this entire game.
Good joke.
Give me your eggs!
We must please them?
I have no...
Seed.
Don't go down there.
Do I have to have the seed?
Do I have to have it?
I thought they just laid eggs...
You know...
There you go.
Now I...
Uh...
Follow, follow, follow.
I can give you my seed on command.
Just say the word.
Word.
Okay!
Egg!
Please lay an egg!
Why is this so hard?
Please!
Just give me an egg!
I gave you seed!
Please!
I'm desperate for egg!
All I want to have is pumpkin pie.
In the mines.
I just want to have a pumpkin pie in the mines.
I don't even have enough sugar.
I don't even have enough...
Guys, this is such a failure.
This is why I wanted people This is why I wanted people to do my bidding.
And then I say, okay!
I'm going off to an adventure, you guys!
going off to an adventure, you guys!
Gather the supplies and everything we need, Gather the supplies and everything we need, and I will be the bread maker.
and I will be the bread maker.
The bread maker.
The pie maker.
Is murder allowed on the Minecraft server?
There's no Minecraft server.
The pie maker.
So true!
I wonder if I could take them home.
What is that?
Oh, it's a bunny.
Where did they come from?
RNG, gods have forsaken you.
I feel like every time I've seen a chicken, there's always an egg.
Right?
Okay.
Guys, I give up.
We're going back.
We're going to get some coal.
And iron.
We're going to craft some stuff.
I give up.
I give up on this mission.
This mission is a failure.
Instead, we're going back home.
Look at all these pumpkins!
They're...
They look so ripe for the eating.
Who cares if my pumpkin pie doesn't have egg in it?
It's still edible, right?
I got too egg-cited.
How would you feel if a Memboo delivered stuff to you in their...
Their wilds.
And then Sudoku in front of you.
How...
You...
Why would you do that?
I mean, it'd be great too, though.
Because then more people can play.
Let me in.
Please.
Just craft an egg.
This is Minecraft.
Why can't I craft whatever I please?
That's so true.
Just craft an egg.
Just follow your fave.
Yeah, I think fall is my favorite.
Because...
It's my birthday!
Okay.
I'm gonna get an axe.
Start chopping down some stuff too.
Fall gang.
I used to be a really big summer enjoyer, though.
I just like the vibes.
And I'm not someone that like...
Gets like...
You know, I know some people are just like, I can't stand the heat.
But...
Usually...
The heat...
Doesn't bother me so much sometimes.
How old are you gonna turn?
I'm gonna turn 19!
Just like last year.
Just like the year before.
And...
Just like the year before!
Forever young!
Okay.
I have my bed.
Yeah.
Actually, I'm gonna steal all their torches.
Or I would, if I could...
Rabbit's foot.
We don't need luck.
All we need is pure skill.
Where is this... where are the...
Where did it go?
Where did it fly to?
I can wear the boots?
Oh, I did get boots!
Thank you!
I didn't realize I had them.
Where did it go?
I heard it go...
So it fell in the water, but like...
Hello, sir.
I'm trying to rob you, but I'm not doing a very good job at it, I think.
Wait!
Did I get it?
Oh!
I somehow found it?
Okay.
Awesome.
Did I get all of them here?
Okay.
Gonna grab this one over here.
More berries.
Where's the cat?
They have a golem.
They'll be fine.
Where's the cat?
Oh!
It's a little cream kitty!
Kitty!
They have a golem.
They'll be okay.
Thank you!
Lots and lots of torches for us.
Yes.
Okay.
Okay, maybe I should take this blast furnace.
How are you?
I'm fine, thank you.
Min forgot what charcoal is.
No, wait.
No, I didn't.
I'm just utilizing my resources.
We don't have charcoal right now.
So I'm stealing what I need.
Duh!
Sorry, I hope nothing spawns in here for you.
Okay.
Take everything.
Rob them, rob them, rob them, rob them.
Rob them of all that they're worth.
They have a golem, they'll be fine.
They'll be fine, they'll be fine.
How many do I have?
25!
Do I need this thing?
Thank you.
What if the villagers could steal the stuff that you drop on the ground?
Are these...
Are these gravestones?
Jack-o'-lanterns!
That's so crazy!
I've never noticed that.
Looks like it.
Yeah, right?
Freaky.
See, if you die in Minecraft, you die in Minecraft!
It's just the rules, it's the rules.
Okay, I think I took all their lights that I can see.
Got 31, that's pretty good.
There's treasure under the gravestones?
No way.
I'm now desecrating a grave.
I have no...
My morals are gone.
My morals are absolutely gone.
I
don't see anything.
Maybe... Oh my gosh.
You guys, maybe it's like a poetry.
Right?
Maybe it's like poetry.
Where I dig here to find that place and I ultimately...
die and it becomes my own grave.
We have entered the Stone Age.
That's deep.
Yeah, I'm gonna start here for my excavation.
Oh, oh yeah, okay, I didn't mess it up.
Let's put a torch... there, okay.
Should I already beat my bet for survival rate?
Well, I haven't really done anything, so...
I think it doesn't count.
I haven't really... I'm just now digging for the first time.
Okay.
I'm gonna put this here.
Yeah.
Alright.
Alive is alive.
Alright, here we go.
Into the mo... into the mines.
Into the caves.
Digging under a grave.
Yes.
Do I have... okay, I have probably an okay amount of wood.
We yearn for the mines.
The children yearn for the mines.
Wooden pickaxe is paying.
Um, yeah, I'll get another one eventually.
Probably.
I mean, it's gonna break.
I just don't wanna waste it, you know?
Let's go down one more.
Deeper into the mines.
Into the caves we go.
Deeper and deeper.
Deeper and deeper and deeper.
Do you think it's night time?
I'm getting scared.
Don't get scared!
Don't be scared!
Okay, good.
This was such a lie.
Treasure under the grave.
What?
I was bamboozled.
Thank you for being my oshi.
Awww, Forest!
Thank you for having me as your oshi!
Wrong grave?
Really?
No egg under the grave.
Oh, I have this.
I'm gonna put some stuff here.
Not my meat.
I'll put the flint in.
I can set things on fire with this, actually.
I can be pretty thrifty.
Um, um, um, um.
These both have silk touch, which is kind of fascinating.
Let's, uh, put this down real quick.
I'm gonna... I do wanna get some more, um...
I do wanna get some more wood before we continue further, further.
Put this right here.
And right there.
Let's try this.
You think there's anything under this one?
There's gotta be someone somewhere!
Treasure!
Treasure under the grave!
Treasure in the grave!
Nothing.
This is so messed up!
What?
I just casually become a grave robber?
What if something spawns in there?
Then it'll really be a grave.
Oh wait, I don't want him to be able to get out.
Here we go, okay.
I was joking!
I have no idea!
I'm gonna become a grave robber.
Can I get some words of encouragement for the big rig driver?
Currently trying and failing to maneuver around the gas station near my work.
Thoughts and prayers.
Um.
It's not...
about the size.
It's about the mental fortitude.
You can do anything.
If you just keep moving and trying.
I'm heading to the gym.
Do you have any motiva- Why is everybody asking for motivational words?
Inspire the people.
Scared me.
Inspiration.
What do you want for your birthday?
Hmmmm...
I don't know.
I don't really want anything.
You sound like my mom.
She's like, what do you want for your birthday?
I was like, I don't know.
Uh.
I basically got everything that I want.
Okay, hold on.
Um, alright.
So, 38.
Um, let's see.
Throw this away.
Payment.
Could I get words?
Any words?
Any words!
Wo- Any words?
Any words?
Um...
Why are we still talking about the Wisp Server?
They won't let me in, you guys.
I guess I don't need emeralds.
A dead man doesn't need money.
I'm done with my workload.
And I have 30 minutes on the clock.
Can you give me some inspiring words on how to survive this corporate hell?
Oh, any words, any words, any words, any words, any words, any words...
What else did I throw away?
Oh, this.
No, to get through the workday...
Wait, did I?
Hold on.
Sorry.
I keep forgetting what I'm trying to do.
To get through the workday...
Honestly, it's so crazy how long...
Have you guys ever set... like you heat something in the microwave or something...
And then you put it for like 30 seconds and then 30 seconds goes by and you're like...
How is this... how is this...
How was I able to do so much in 30 seconds?
You know?
Motivational words for the monkeys struggling to defend the map.
Pray to Ice Monkey.
And thou shall succeed.
Thank you, thank you.
Chu!
Feeling super chipper.
Can you give me some demotivating words of discouragement?
Um...
You!
Probably are...
Iron!
You are happy and that's...
So annoying and bad.
And...
You...
Have a stupid face when you smile.
Probably.
Was that too mean?
Sorry, that was really mean, wasn't she?
Wasn't that... wasn't that... wasn't that...
Wasn't that too mean?
Okay, hold on.
Sorry.
You are a stupid...
You are a stupid.
You...
Um.
Go watch...
Go watch some videos...
Go watch some videos... of...
of...
go watch some videos...
of a sad puppy.
Chu gacha.
Sorry Ashes.
Oh!
Oh?
Glow squid?
Swimming?
I hear some strange noises.
Yeah!
We got Cole!
You really got him.
No, we've never heard from Ducky ever again.
When they said she hates us...
Who could have thunk it would be to this extent?
But I'm watching a sad puppy play Minecraft.
What are you talking about?
I don't have puppy energy at all.
Listening to you rambling to chat with ChillBGM on Minecraft is like peak Minecraft I've missed.
I'm glad.
Chihuahua?
Why are you guys saying X?
What kind of animal energy?
Do I exude?
More like wet cat energy.
Like a cat.
Okay, hold on.
Let's go back upstairs.
She hates us is cat energy.
Let's put this here.
Wet cat energy is...
Diabolical.
That is so... I feel like I should be offended.
Get a happy birthday song.
Something that I could twerk with.
Okay.
Happy birth.
Day to you.
Happy birthday, ba bang!
Ba bang.
Sick remix.
Break it down.
Oh, no.
It's the wrong type.
They had a regular.
Oh, wait.
No, I had one.
I had a furnace at home.
You guys, this is hardcore.
We're not...
We're not wasting resources.
So I have to go get it from my house, which is hopefully not destroyed.
Why is...
Why do boats sink?
DJ Minto in the house.
Ever considered playing mod in Minecraft?
Yes.
Well, I tried it on like the Vshojo server.
I think maybe just because I'm not used to it.
I'm so used to vanilla Minecraft.
And then the amount of mods they had kind of made me overwhelmed.
But I would be willing to try it, you know.
Yeah, I did get a bit short circuited.
Yeah.
Not my birthday, but can I get a birthday congratulations from...
Happy birthday.
Congratulations.
Salutations.
Happy birthday.
May your sky stay blue.
Happy birthday to you.
That's the only correct birthday song now.
Whoever's birthday it was for that.
We never even checked over here.
That's fine.
We're digging and digging and digging now.
Take this one too.
Playing with mods for years, I'm used to it.
Yeah.
I think if you play, you know, like I said, if you're used to it, then it makes total sense.
But for me, I was just like, I don't know.
I don't know any of this.
And it's so much.
It's all at once.
I was like, went from being little vanilla bear.
Baby.
To everything.
Almost forgot to like.
Like the stream.
Comment on the video.
Oh.
I was going to say, what's your favorite vanilla moment?
What's your favorite flavor of Minecraft?
I personally prefer a chocolate.
What else do I need?
I think we're okay for now.
Oh, wait.
Yeah.
We got our furnace.
I'll take the blast furnace too.
Oh.
I need the blast furnace.
Throw.
And heal.
And cook.
There we go.
Yes.
Oh.
It's nighttime, but I think we'll be okay.
Put the stairs and leather gear in the chest.
No.
I want those.
It's my stairs.
What if I need them?
I'm here playing.
I'm hardcore server.
Is anyone else going to show up?
No.
I'll be back in a moment.
What else was I going to...
Oh, here.
Nice.
Bidding.
I see creepers.
And I'm not looking in the chat.
I see skellies.
Oh, I see skellies getting attacked by dogs.
How did you know I was here?
Fall in.
I'm coming.
I just made a Reddit joke, was it good?
No, don't go in my place!
That's my hole!
They can fall in this one though, if they want.
Okay, we got some...
I think we should... oh wait, I want to take this home with me.
What
do I not need?
Okay, I definitely need the stairs, I definitely need the leather.
I got the birthday song right after doing loads of missions all the way to wear quiet lip.
I thought it was some extra kick in the teeth after the emotional love point of those missions.
I didn't realize it was my birthday.
No way!
Do you think someone will follow me in here?
I hope not.
No freaks better follow me in here.
Okie dokie, is this where I actually stopped?
Oh yeah, because we found a bunch of coal.
Okay.
I'll put a thing there.
Ah!
Water!
We got the water.
Maybe I should make a better sword.
I just realized too.
Maybe I should... make... a better sword.
It's optional, but you know.
I think we're gonna die in here.
Hmm.
I need one of...
Ahh!
Iron soul!
Iron sword.
Okay.
What is going on Chief?
I don't see any... things that will help us hold.
You know...?
The blocks, the... Of course the...
You know, the blocks in Minecraft.
Those ones.
What are they?
What are they called?
Use a door.
Oh, thank you.
You're so right.
That's why I have these.
What was that sound?
Why did it sound so mysterious?
What was that?
I was like...
Creepy.
Drowned?
I don't think so.
Herobrine.
Gosh,
I hope the little villages are okay up there.
Some crazy...
Some crazy thunder right now.
Let's go this way.
I didn't even notice.
We're fine.
Everything's good.
There's some iron there.
Okay, downward, onward.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, we're like really deep, aren't we?
Okay.
Let me in.
Let me in, please.
Stop giving me a heart attack, Minto.
I'm trying to just...
I'm just trying to play the game.
Okay.
What if I...
Wait.
Oh, there we go.
What if I dig here, you know?
We got some iron even.
Nice.
I'll take it.
I have a full inventory, but that's okay.
I could just eat the pumpkin pie.
My pumpkin pie.
Just kidding.
We're gonna dig here.
We're gonna dig here, okay, everybody?
We're gonna keep digging.
I'm not gonna let this deter me.
Iron pickaxe.
See?
We're doing it.
Do you think it's...
Aha!
This is it, everybody.
This is the strip mining.
Oh, shoot.
Okay, hold on.
Let's go back for this.
We're doing it.
Gosh, it is really crazy up there.
Did I grab it?
No.
Throw you away.
Okay.
I want this iron, though.
What do I need?
Oh, don't need the gravel.
Iron.
Okay.
Don't drown, please.
I won't.
We're okay.
Everything's fine.
Everything's all good.
Everything's so okay.
Drop the Leather Mint.
No, I want it.
You can't force me.
You can't make me leave it.
More water?
Come on.
Eerie noise.
What does it mean by that?
Oh my gosh.
I can't even get through.
Excuse me.
Oh my gosh.
Are you under the ocean?
I don't think so.
We're gonna find the trial.
Wait.
Oh, this is the only door I have.
Okay, yeah.
We're gonna find the trial chambers.
Okay.
This is a dead end.
We'll change our direction.
Change directions.
How do I...
Where's my hole?
Wait a second.
Oh.
Guys.
Guys, where did I come from?
Oh.
Wait.
I found it.
I see my hole.
Everything is fine.
Let's go...
this way.
Surely, there'll be no water here.
Surely, it'll be okay.
Guys, isn't this so exciting?
What if we even find diamond down here?
That'll be a little special treat for us, right?
Maybe I should go up a little bit.
Is it usually... is the trial chamber usually deep?
Or is it like...
I imagine it's probably deep like the...
What's it called?
Go lower?
Wait, what are we at even?
Oh my goodness.
We're at four!
Deep slate level.
So yeah, we're where exactly we need to be.
I will go down a little bit actually.
We can go down lower.
I can always go lower.
Heretic!
Thank you so much for the 20 gift.
Thank you!
Why is there dirt here?
This is a lot of dirt.
For all the way down here?
Where are
the diamonds?
Why is there so much dirt here?
Why is there so much dirt?
Dirt doesn't usually form this deep, doesn't it?
Hmm...
I'm gonna... my shovel's gonna break because it's made of gold and gold is useless.
Dirt biome.
Oh my gosh.
Dirty, nasty.
I started a new...
I started the billionaire secret baby.
But I keep falling asleep to it.
I've tried... I've tried for like the past two nights.
I keep falling asleep to it.
So I haven't... I have no idea at all what's going on.
I woke up this morning and it was like last chapter.
The howa?
So...
For those who don't know...
I...
You know, a long time ago...
One of my... one of my office working jobs...
I would listen to...
Okay, I think we're deep enough.
Negative 18.
We can... we can go like this now.
I would listen to sexy romance novels.
Just for funsies.
And...
I started one.
It's like kind of my hobby, I guess you'd say.
Oh no!
Oh, that was a creepy noise.
It's quite creepy.
Let's get a...
Wait, what am I missing?
First of all, I'm gonna throw this away.
Actually, no.
I'm gonna keep this for attacking.
We need...
I'm gonna throw the sugar away because we'll never get any eggs.
Goodbye, goodbye.
Actually, I want the pumpkins.
Sticks.
Do I wanna make an iron shovel?
No, I'll just go with the stone shovel.
Not the sugar.
Please, the leather.
No...
I want that.
.
He finally got out of the station.
Let's go!
Can I join the conversation?
Yes, Jerry.
Of course you can.
What do you have to offer for this conversation?
I wanna know everything.
I wanna know what you're thinking.
I wanna know what's on your mind.
You guys, what's on your mind?
That's amazing.
Okay, let's see because this is going to be really boring.
Let's just say that we're gonna do it!
Let's do it, let's do it, let's do it!
Let's do it!
Do you have any chance for some kind of freaky phantom frequency for fall?
I don't know.
I love doing the podcast, but I also don't think it's really something for me.
Because I just...
I've mentioned it on the podcast, but like...
I feel like I use up all my social energy on the podcast.
When I would do it.
I'm thinking about them beans.
I love that.
Oh my gosh, you know what I've been non-stop watching recently?
You know how like...
Have you guys seen that people are using AI to...
Okay, that's not...
That's not Diamond, but...
They've been using AI on vines and stuff.
Or like TikToks and things.
To make them longer.
I've been watching people...
You know what, maybe I should go this way.
I've been watching people making fun of those AI generated videos.
By making their own.
Oh shoot.
Oh no.
And so I've been watching those a lot.
They're so funny.
Oh, I didn't leave this here.
I'm so stupid.
Sorry.
I like the imposter showing up.
Yes, they're so funny.
I've been watching people making the parodies of them.
Where is this guy?
It's not so close.
Oh, there's some iron though.
Take it.
Oh, it sounds right next to me.
He wants to tell us what's on his mind.
He's on ASMR.
Let's put our blast furnace right here.
And we're gonna make this iron.
Very good, very good, very good.
Remember when content slop was handmade like Spiderman Elsa videos?
Can you imagine the amount of Spiderman Elsa stuff they can make now?
I was gonna say it's almost terrifying to think about.
But actually it's quite terrifying to think about.
It's not almost terrifying.
Where are these guys?
Are they above me?
Below me?
Something about the...
Where are they?
I think it's above me.
It sounds so close!
I don't wanna let them in, but...
Never dig above.
Well, we're close to somewhere.
Blair...
Our soup for being 70% water.
Our ghost chowder for being mostly ectoplasm.
Delicious.
Chowder.
I'm trying to find them!
I seriously can't.
I'm just gonna block this up though.
I don't feel like adding more torches.
I don't wanna waste torches.
Chowder.
Like a minty chowder sounds kind of awful though.
But not all ghosts are mint flavored.
Just me.
To the right.
I checked though.
Wow guys, we're level 5.
I'll try going to the right.
But they're also on my left.
Where the...
Would zombies be in the trial room?
What flavor are wisps?
I like that...
Ramune.
Oh oh, I hear...
Oh oh.
I hear lava.
Ramune?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're far from the...
We're far from the zombies now.
They must be above me.
What does ramune taste like?
What?
Have you guys never had the ramune...
I can't have soda, but in Japan...
Ramune is a very popular flavored candy and stuff.
So those I have.
And...
It's very...
But this
doesn't look like a trial chamber.
I can't have soda.
It messes with the ectoplasm in my tummy.
And I just kind of throw up.
Minto is surprised we're uncultured.
I don't think it's uncultured.
It's just... It's like a distinct like...
How do I describe it?
Oh wait.
Hold on.
Before we do this...
I'm gonna go make a shield.
I thought about this earlier.
Yeah.
Oh, goodbye sugar.
We're living a healthy diet now.
Oh, wait.
The zombies are...
Not here.
Maybe.
Guys!
We did it!
Yipee!
Um...
Alright.
If I were a trial chamber...
Someone said that I need like a cartographer.
But unfortunately...
That village did not have one.
You know?
So...
I think we just gotta...
You know...
Find it...
Somehow.
Oh, I hear a skelly.
From over here?
No.
Towards where I'm going though.
Oh, let me go get my stuff.
What can I throw away?
Oh.
Plenty of stuff.
And... yup.
Perfect.
Alright.
Can make a cartography table...
And convert one.
But don't I need...
Um...
Oh, I get what you guys mean!
Oh, so we should go back, huh?
Because there's the guys...
Oh...
Wait.
Is it so easy to find one though?
There's a glitch where you throw...
Your diamonds into lava, they will multiply?
Stop!
It's pretty cheap?
Okay, okay.
Back to the village!
Okay.
It's not so far, I think.
We just went through some water.
This way.
And...
We...
Went...
Wait, I never thought I would be going back.
Oh, wait!
This might be good, actually.
Yes!
This is actually very good.
It's hard to find coal so deep, you know?
Grab it while we can.
Press Alt F4.
Press Alt F4!
Right now, everybody.
Do it, or you're not really a fan.
Do it, or you hate me.
Did I get all of it?
I think so.
Do it, or you hate me.
It's not that hard to get rid of the love or not feeling.
Here we go.
I'm not seeing...
Oh.
I'm not...
Oh, I just saw a drop of viewership, for real!
Oh my gosh, you guys are such real ones!
Oh my gosh, stop, you guys!
You're going to make my nerves go down...
Oh, my gosh!
You guys are so dumb...
I love you!
You're so dumb!
You are so dumb!
Oh, my gosh, stop, you guys.
You're going to make my nerves go down...
I lived.
Welcome back, everybody.
You may have returned.
I'm on my phone.
What am I supposed to do?
Oh!
I don't know.
Okay, there we go.
There we go.
Okay.
I think I got everything.
Alright.
Good, good, good.
Now where is the door?
Oh, I went through here.
Yes, yes, yes.
And I think it was up here.
Why do I have two crafting tables next to each other?
Look, I was even starting to run out of torches.
Hello, villagers.
It is I.
I've risen from...
Eww!
Get out of my bed!
Okay, we have to un-employ somebody.
Wow, we came just in time.
It's a day.
Let's just destroy all of their stuff.
Was there one in here?
Yeah.
Destroy, destroy, and then the cartography table was...
You guys said it was cheap?
This guy literally was just like, She ain't coming back.
Four planks and two paper.
Okay.
Four planks, two paper.
So we gotta go get some paper.
Because I turned all of my sugar cane into...
Okay.
This is how you do the paper, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Um...
Gonna eat this real quick.
Okay.
AI Recaps says, Viewers are mass disconnecting from the stream as a form of protest against the streamer bit.
Viewers are mass disconnecting from the stream as a form of protest against the streamer bit.
She seems to dislike her audience.
Why does the AI think I hate you guys so much?
I think you've trained the AI to believe that.
That's so untrue.
What book app are you using?
Um...
The book app I'm using is just the Google Play Books app.
And did I like Mated?
I'll be honest, I only remember the beginning of the book because I then fell asleep.
She hates us.
Sorry, I gotta go find some...
paper.
Little Fox!
Dang.
I was looking to see if there's any coal around here.
She hates us.
Because you do hate us.
Three minutes late today.
Look.
Okay, I had to check on my cat.
Okay.
He was very stinky.
Every time I see my cat, I just want to give them lots of love.
Once I start going on them, I can't stop.
Okay.
Can you blame me?
The AI is jealous of the superior anime woman.
Who's to say I'm not AI?
I could be.
Oh my gosh.
I wish there was...
Where's all the...
Where's all the dang paper?
Oh, there's one over there.
I just went the wrong way.
Oh.
GW?
I'm a Robo-phile.
So true.
I know you're not AI, for I am AI.
What if we're AI talking to each other?
What kind of conversations do AIs have, I wonder?
Hey, you get any interesting prompts lately?
This one guy asked for the prompt of the middle toe being larger than all of the other toes.
Can you believe it?
What a freak.
Now the AI are judging us?
We've gone too far.
The AI are now judging us and saying that we have bad taste.
Prompt.
AI streamers start talking about Metal Gear Solid.
GW?
Okay, so it's about these brothers.
Oh, here's a bunch of them.
Good, good, good.
Now we can go back.
Wait!
Do you guys see that?
This can only mean one thing.
Lush biome.
Do you think the trials would be lush?
And plush.
I'm not lost.
Can't spell maid without AI.
There's another tree over here too.
Flush biome.
This one here.
Definitely, definitely lush.
Alright, cartographer time.
The heart of Metal Gear Solid is about family.
Best series about family.
Wait, am I going the right way?
Am I going the right way?
Ore imo.
It was right through here, right?
And then the... what's it called?
The...
The pillagers are right here.
On the right.
The reflections are kind of crazy.
They're really strong, aren't they?
Makes me think they're too cool.
Kuroneko best girl.
For real.
Kuroneko...
First of all...
What was his name?
Kyousuke?
What did you think of the Minecraft movie trailer?
Oh...
It was a trailer.
Kuroneko is so good.
I'm glad she didn't get with him.
It was a trailer.
There's so many people that are just like...
It's not for you.
It's for my six-year-old.
And you know what I have to say about that?
There are so many people at this point that have grown up with Minecraft.
There are so many people now that are adults that loved Minecraft.
There are so... like basically every Minecraft creator is also an adult.
You know?
So to say that this is a movie that's only because it's Minecraft it's only supposed to be for kids.
I'd say Minecraft was the most popular back then.
And now all those people are adults.
So it just doesn't feel very, you know, to make it and then be like, oh but this isn't for you?
What do you mean it's not for me?
I grew up with Minecraft.
I mean I didn't.
Because I only started playing it like two years ago.
But I feel like I grew up with it.
Alright, where's our guys?
Any enemies?
Unemployed fellas over here?
Oh.
Oh wait, I have to make the paper.
And the cartography.
Okay.
Uh, paper.
Oh we got a lot.
Okay.
Nice.
And then uh...
Cartography table.
Perfect.
Okay.
Two hours and still stone tools?
Shush!
Are you in here?
Oh!
How'd you both get in there?
Become a cartographer!
No, no, no, no, no!
Become a cartographer.
Very cartoons are for kids core.
I know!
Remove the cauldrons.
What?
How did that work?
Oh my god, sir.
Hello!
You've been playing Minecraft since you were 19.
So true!
Minecraft surpassed Tetris as the most sold game of all time, and Tetris came with the Gameboy, which is the third most sold handheld of all time.
That's insane, actually.
Leatherworker.
Okay, so now I just buy the map.
Oh.
I have no money.
I threw away my...
I threw away my money into the sea!
I said, I said,
I said, I said, Okay, time to grind paper.
Okay.
Where'd I put my...
Oh, the boat's over here.
Okay.
You've been playing Minecraft for over 10 years now.
Has it been that long?
When you're dead, you kinda lose track of the time, you know?
Okay.
Time to grind paper.
I could make a...
I feel like if I make a paper machine, it will be...
too...
annoying.
Also, I don't understand.
How is the map gonna help me?
I'm doing all this and I'm like, Do I really need a map?
How's the map gonna help me?
I don't even know.
Do I actually need a map?
Let's try this way.
Do you think they have any paper?
Okay.
So, first we get paper to sell, and then...
paper to sell, and then...
make money and buy maps.
Papers, please.
Oh my gosh, that game is so awesome.
I love Papers, Please.
I would play that...
all the time.
What is that structure?
Oh, I think it's a tree.
Oh yeah, it's a tree.
Anymore?
Okay, we gotta go over there a little bit.
Glory to Arstotzka.
The game is like...
I did play the...
what's it called?
The...
Oh, see?
These are what I needed.
The magma blocks.
The magma cubes.
This is what I needed for under the water.
Not worth.
Maybe I'll take one now.
Actually...
Nah, I have my door.
It's okay.
I won't scatter your money to the heartless sea.
I see some here.
If you guys see...
If you guys see any...
Uh...
What the?
I'm in the ground.
How is that possible?
If you guys see any sugar cane, holla.
Okay?
Just go.
Just go yodel, yodel, yodel, yodel.
Yodel, yodel, yodel, yodel.
I won't see you become poor.
You're all free-checking.
Yodel, yodel, yodel.
Oh good, there's a bunch here.
We won't get lost, everybody.
Don't worry.
I have a great direction sense.
Yodel, yodel.
No, I don't see any.
Don't just go yodeling for no reason.
It's bad behavior.
I'm off to work.
Bye Nexi.
Have a good day at work.
I want to learn how to yodel.
Yodel, yodel, yodel.
Yodel lady, yodel lady.
Bring back yodeling.
Yodel, yodel, yodel, yodel.
Wait a second.
Who are you?
No, I'm just kidding.
We were here before.
I should have grabbed it while I was here.
Oh, big yodels.
Big yodel.
Yodeling is, I feel, such a lost art.
It's such a good, interesting way of singing.
What's it called, kid?
The kid that's just like, Wait a minute.
Who are you?
So funny.
Like to have fun, fun, fun, fun, fun, fun, fun.
The kazoo kid.
Yeah.
I see, I see coal in there.
Oh, we got a good amount of coal, maybe.
We can also see...
What's in there?
Oh.
I can grab this coal.
I thought that was a skeleton.
Oh my god.
Oh my gosh.
What's happening?
Oh.
Gosh, this scared me.
Scared me bad.
Is there anything in here?
Oh, there's lots of coal.
Ah!
But there's so much coal.
The coal was a trap.
Ah.
How much paper?
We have 42 sugarcane.
Sorry, my head is blocking a little bit.
You think that's enough?
How many maps do you think we need?
Yodel, yodel, yodel, yodel, yodel, yodel.
Yodel, yodel, yodel, yodel, yodel, yodel, yodel.
Yodel, yodel yodel, yodel, yodel, yodel, yodel, yodel.
Okay, we'll have to... that's going to be a sneaky one.
Oh, I think the lush biome extends all the way to here.
Or is this where we came from?
Gosh, I can't remember.
The whole area looks the same.
Didn't I just see some water or am I crazy?
Yodel, yodel, yodel, yodel.
We're
not lost!
We're not lost!
Yeah, see?
This is where the lush area is.
See?
I know, I know.
Yeah, I know I missed some.
Don't worry.
It's okay.
I might head back soon.
Because we're at 48.
53.
Oh!
Pulling out on me, huh?
Trying to sneak away?
Trying to sneak back?
That's a lot of paper per emerald, wasn't it?
But wasn't it...
You get three pieces of paper.
Per something.
I don't remember how much.
Oh, my sand block.
You're right.
Here, we can actually just check right now.
We can just check right now.
Paper.
It's not bad.
Seven emeralds for one map.
Oh my god.
Seven?
For one map?
You guys, how many maps?
Can I overwrite a map?
How many maps do you think I need?
If I just need one, we'll be fine.
Right?
Why can't I use a regular paper?
To make a map.
It makes no sense.
Don't buy a blank map.
Oh, really?
You have to level up the villager too.
Oh my gosh.
Okay, this one is really...
This is a top secret mission.
Okay, I think we're good.
I don't see anymore over there.
I see him though.
Wait, I do see some!
Oh no.
Is it worth it?
I could be in and out.
There's two of them?
They're all swimming.
Why are they coming to me?
Wait, why is he...
All I have to do is be in and out.
I don't want them to shoot me.
Yeah!
Let's go!
Give us the whole 13 pieces!
Alright.
Yodel if you see anymore on the way back.
I missed one!
Oh no.
You know what?
It's fine.
Is that even the BGM?
Oh...
I grabbed it from Dova Syndrome like right before stream.
Um...
I can check.
Give me a second.
It's this way, right?
Yeah.
This way.
Ha ha ha.
Hmm...
I don't see anymore.
It's too close to home.
I would've gotten all of it.
Okie dokie.
There better not be anybody in my bed.
Actually...
Oh wait, there's sticks here.
Oh, I can't pick them up.
I'm full.
Um...
Paper.
It's fine.
We gotta call them.
Ok.
Oh, but we have to have them wake up.
Don't we?
Ok.
Get up everybody.
Daytime.
Ok.
Wake up.
Oh.
That almost hit you.
Oh no.
Wait.
No
worries.
We can handle him.
Hey you.
Yeah.
Ha ha ha.
Woah.
Yeah.
You're right.
I saved your life.
You're welcome.
You're so welcome.
Now, our cartographer friend was in here I believe.
Or...
So he says.
Hello?
Cartographer.
Hello.
Good morning.
I offer you...
Oh my gosh.
I'm out of paper already.
We live in a society.
This is inflation real.
I'm gonna plant this one.
Maybe it will grow like right here.
You know?
Unlimited.
Sugar cane works.
My trap.
I fell into my own trap.
Bone meal?
I don't think bone meal works.
On...
Sugar cane.
Okay.
What else can we do?
The only way we can...
Maybe I should just buy the empty maps and all.
To level him up.
Oh no.
I need seven emeralds.
Okay.
Maybe we can sell something to this guy.
What are you trying to buy?
Bread!
We can buy... Wait.
No.
That's not what I need.
Potatoes!
I only have four.
Okay.
Guys, we're in a bit of a pickle right now.
We're in a bit of a pickle.
What about you?
Coal!
Two gems!
But I need the coal.
I could always just get more.
What about you?
Wheat.
You have plenty of coal.
I guess I don't need it that bad.
I guess I can have...
I can get rid of some of it.
Seven!
Sir!
Don't shut the door on me!
I'm trying to do business with you!
Oh, it doesn't even level him up that much.
No!
Oh my god.
What do I do?
Did I sell all my coal?
No way.
I sold all of it?
Where's the rest?
Oops.
I didn't even notice.
Oh man.
No way!
Maybe we just go back in.
Maybe I just go find it.
Yeah, the cave that has all the coal.
Let's go back and do that.
Because I do need... wait, where's my boat?
Here it is.
I do need at least a little bit of coal.
What a waste.
You guys...
This is such a flop.
My whole plan is just... everything is backfiring against me!
What's happening?
Why can't I...
I keep getting scammed.
What else is new?
It hurts.
Freedom!
Okay.
Let's go get that coal.
From that cave.
Pinto got the server working.
Yeah, you see all these people around me?
We're having the time of our afterlives.
Aren't we?
Yodel.
Yodel, yodel.
They don't know.
It's okay.
I'm playing with everybody right now.
It's so much fun.
I'm having so much fun right now.
Playing with everybody.
Everybody is being so respectful.
Nobody is trying to kill me.
It's great.
Oh, somebody even...
Somebody even gifted me diamonds.
It's so awesome.
Wow,
so cool.
Oh my gosh, Murphy.
Thanks for the diamonds.
This feels like Bochy.
Where was that cave actually?
Am I going the right way?
This area is not that big.
When she forgets to take her meds.
Oh, here's some.
This is a different place.
But here's some.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, that's the good itch.
Oh yeah, yeah, that's the good itch.
Oh yeah, yeah.
MMO.
Made bit online.
Critically acclaimed.
Okay, how much was that?
24?
You know what's funnier than 24?
Oh, dang it.
Oh, it's really deep down here.
Nice.
I don't see anymore in there.
I had a dream that Disney built a Vtuber theme park.
But you were the only characters...
character rights they could get.
And everyone was like, They'd be like, Who is that?
That would be so sad.
I'd be like, Vtuber who?
Oh my gosh.
What kind of rides would I have?
Well, I mean, the cafe.
There would obviously be a cafe themed after me.
Am I going the right way?
Because there would have to be a maid cafe.
Tea cups?
A haunted house!
Of course!
Of course, of course!
Oh my gosh.
I would love to have a haunted house.
There's been like...
What's it called?
Is this...
This isn't the one I went to before.
Is it?
Oh, it is!
There have been like...
escape rooms that have been...
voiced by Vtubers and stuff.
Or rather, collabs with Vtubers.
You know?
These guys won't catch up to me.
What are you guys saying?
I checked out a Vtuber meetup just cause.
They said, so good to meet a fan.
And I stumbled not to say...
I don't know who you are.
I was just saying...
I've had meet and greets before.
Where people will come and say...
I don't know who you are.
They would be like...
Sorry.
I just...
I just found you.
Like I just got your...
I just wanted a meet and greet.
Oh look!
We're back!
Let's go to this place.
See?
So easy.
I know where we are.
Oh my gosh!
Do you want to come with?
Come here, come here.
I'll give you a bread.
No one noticed.
Our little guy...
Oh it's this way, isn't it?
Our ally is looking.
Wait!
Doesn't the ally bring stuff?
Can't I just tell him to bring me more paper?
If I give him paper, won't he bring more paper?
Do you remember your first meet and greet?
Of course I do.
Oh!
Wait!
That's my bed!
Oh my god!
He almost...
Wait!
He's trying to decide whether to go after that guy or me.
Idiot!
You don't know who to go after!
No!
Go after him!
He's literally laying there!
Wait!
The villager is going to die!
I got you!
I'll protect you!
This guy's got a shovel!
I protected you!
Wait, I hear another guy.
Fall into my hole!
Okay.
Why is the spider enchanted?
You see that?
Yeah, he's got little things coming off of him.
That was craziness.
He's drunk?
Heart spiders are sometimes magical.
Oh my gosh, he just climbed up the house.
What kind of effect does he have?
Oh my gosh.
There's so many of them.
It's a horde of spiders.
Hello, sir.
I will give you more paper.
In just a moment.
In a moment's time.
Paper...
Okay.
No, but...
Everybody ignore the giant spiders.
Everybody ignore the giant spiders, okay?
I still don't have enough!
Reign of spiders!
I wish I could tell what he was buffed with.
Did anyone tell Mint how expensive the Trial Chamber's map is?
What the?
What did I do?
He came after me for nothing!
I didn't even do anything!
Oh my gosh.
Aggressive.
Deserves it.
Can plant these too.
Grow!
Why isn't this one grown at all?
They aggro in low light.
I was under a tree!
I was under a tree.
You can use sugarcane to speed it up.
Wait.
Sugarcane to speed up the sugarcane?
No.
Let's just go back in.
I think I'll stumble upon...
it with my sheer...
sheer luck and spontaneity.
Let's put this stuff away.
In here.
Like that.
I lost all my coal.
But that's okay.
You know.
That's fine.
Probably.
We have a little bit of iron.
And everything.
Is this your own Minecraft?
Yeah.
It's mine.
Oh.
I hope nothing's down.
We're good.
Okay.
Oh.
I forgot one of these.
So I'm gonna take it back.
Things I've learned.
1.
The Shadow Moses act of MGS4 is the only part with a unique game over theme.
That sounds similar to MGS1's and Peace Walker's game.
2.
Senator Armstrong is the only.
He's the only.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Here we go.
First of all, let's do this.
There we go.
Okay.
Oh.
Wait.
There's some more here.
Can the allies swim?
Are you gonna be okay?
The only.
I know.
The cliffhanger.
He's the only one.
He's the only one for me.
Okay.
We're gonna make a little...
We're gonna make a little hole here.
Okay.
Only man in Metal Gear Universe that can make people fear the sound of a whoop.
No matter what game Min plays, she can never escape Metal Gear references.
So true.
Oh.
This isn't...
Okay.
A whoop.
And then I can put a door here.
Hold on.
I'm...
I'm thinking with portals.
Oh.
If I can get inside.
There we go.
I'm thinking with portals.
Yeah.
See?
No!
I...
I take this bread from you.
It's too dangerous.
Give it to me.
Give me the bread.
Give me the bread!
Where are you going?
Stop!
Thank you.
Oh!
You scared me!
Let me free.
Free.
It's a reverse Dobby.
I take your bread.
You are now...
a free ally.
Shoot.
I need more stick.
Perfect.
Yasmin!
Thanks for the pie I've gifted!
Okay.
Doki.
Give me one other second.
Okay.
Here.
We're basically...
back up to where we were before.
Okay.
We're basically...
Oh!
Did I grab it?
Okay.
Good.
I can't get out!
Wait!
No!
I can't get out!
I can't...
No!
Astro Bot, were you able to find...
Big...
Big Boss, right?
Wait, they're all in the game?
Big Boss is in the game?
I think I got spoiled.
I think I just got spoiled on the...
on...
Astro Bot.
No, I'm playing more Astro Bot.
This...
Wait, where was the hole?
Oh, here, right?
I'm playing more this week!
I haven't played anymore.
Since...
Ah!
When you find an ancient city, make noise.
Oh yeah!
At least you had good intentions.
They mistook Solid Snake for...
Yeah, obviously.
Yeah.
Hahaha!
Oh!
Okay, I've been here.
I've been here.
Okay.
Okey-dokey.
It was down here, right?
I think we can just... Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here we go.
Perfect!
Alright, and then through here...
And
then...
We went all the way down here...
And then...
The booba are easy to mix up?
Obviously.
That was the issue.
Very common mistake.
Understandably so.
Any diamonds?
Yeah, I got some!
Alright, everybody!
Back to where we were, like...
An hour ago.
Back to where we were.
Watching VTubers play Minecraft is pretty relaxing.
I think so.
It's pretty chill time today.
Pretty chill.
We're just hanging out.
You know?
We tried to get a map.
Okay, so someone said the map to find the place is really expensive.
How much are we talking?
How many emeralds are we talking here?
Hope you're having a good time, Minto.
Yeah!
It's all chill.
Twelve plus a compass?
Hold on.
Let's put a little...
Actually, we should be fine.
Let's make some more.
More torches.
Okay, that should be good.
Okay.
Alright.
Are we ready?
It's so dark.
Skelly?
Skelly a foot?
Spider a foot?
Does that mean we're close to a cave, maybe?
Or like a...
Not a cave.
That thing...
Sorry, I can never...
I'm so inarticulate, you guys.
I can never think of any words.
Ever.
Diamond!
Diamond, diamond!
I think my shaders aren't working.
Because I use complementary and they usually glow.
Aren't they supposed to glow when you find these?
Wow!
Nice.
We have seven so far.
Seven diamonds.
Out of date?
No, I just downloaded these.
Hmm...
The word I was searching for was...
The mineshaft.
I can only focus on like three things at once.
Hey!
Come over here, Yukala.
Oh, oh.
They're coming over here.
We'll get the creeper first.
We'll get you.
More diamond!
Come here, come here.
Blow up the diamond.
Oh my god!
Yay!
Diamond!
Wait.
Uh oh.
Oh.
But we found another one so it doesn't matter!
Yippee!
I think the diamond blew up.
Oops.
That's fine.
Oh, there's a second creeper?
Oh!
Where do you get all these arrows from anyway?
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Oh, this is bad, this is bad.
Come here, come here, come here.
We'll get the creeper?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come here, come here, come here.
Come here and blow this up like right here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Blow up like right here.
Like right...
here.
No, I'm gonna push you in.
Nothing else?
We're excavating everybody?
We're excavating?
Where's the creeper?
I mean the skelly.
Actually, where is the skelly?
Where'd he go?
Oh.
I don't wanna get caught.
My shield's taking a beating.
Yeah, it's okay.
It happens, you know.
Where'd he go?
Oh.
There he is.
Taking a little swim.
Okay.
Onwards!
Yeah!
Oh yeah!
I'm almost out of...
I'm out of...
I'm out of torches and I can't see anything.
Maybe in here.
Anything?
New recipe.
Oh, cause of the bone.
No!
Nothing here.
I'll take this iron though since we're here.
Hopefully we can find some more coal.
I have coal.
But you know, just more too.
Nothing here.
Let's see.
Alright.
Sticks.
Oh no.
Torch!
Oh, I didn't mean to make that.
Oh!
I have too many!
There we go.
Perfect.
Let's go the other way.
Okay.
This way.
We're exploring.
We're adventuring.
We're having a...
mindful time.
Haven't died yet!
I might be a genius at this game.
Wasn't there a guy over here?
Oh.
Whoa.
Okay.
This gets a little...
Nope.
Nothing up here.
Pro Minecrafter!
Professional!
How do I...
Let's see.
Umm...
One of these ways will lead to the trials.
The trial chambers.
Oh.
Ouch.
You guys, I don't think there's any going back up anymore.
I'm absolutely...
lost.
Going up is not an option anymore.
These caves are ours.
And all I got are berries.
Yeah, we live down here now.
Once I run out of these berries...
I really have, like, nothing else.
I'm a professional...
and I'm prepared.
And also there's nothing here!
I do have a little bit of potatoes.
I just gotta cook them.
Gotta cook them, potatoes.
Let's just keep digging...
this way then.
We'll just pick a corner and go.
Down here.
100 day day cave...
challenge.
100 day cave challenge!
Yes.
I hear a skelly.
Somewhere.
Over yonder.
I don't know if we can plant the...
I don't have any dirt.
Do I?
I do!
Hold on, let's see.
Oh!
Shut up!
And then we can just keep bone-mealing them.
You guys, this might actually be possible.
Oh my gosh!
Yeah, I see the weird spammer.
It's okay.
Yeah, I'm gonna change the subscribe thing.
Let's see.
There we go.
I think Minecraft is bringing out the children.
So it's a little weird.
Just ignore.
It's okay.
I'm not bothered.
Let's see.
Berries need level...
Light level 9.
But if I bone-meal it, it's fine.
Right?
But also, this is light level 9?
What are we at?
Light 11.
I'm sad I missed it.
It's some kid that's just like, I will sigma you.
Everybody sigma.
I really like the BGM.
It's soothing.
Oh, someone asked about it earlier.
Whoever asked about it earlier.
Let me check.
I'm in a good spot now.
Uh...
Uh... It's in Japanese.
So it probably would be easier for me to just link it.
Right?
Hold on.
Give me a second.
You might hear it for like 2 seconds.
There we go.
This one.
That's the BGM for today.
Sigma, Ohio.
Skippity Breeze.
Yeah.
Hahaha.
Is this drippy?
No, I don't think so.
Uh...
Let's go!
Brrrr.
I think I...
Okay, here we go.
I was gonna say.
There's probably a way.
Around here.
Skippity, skippity.
I don't like Minecraft.
I only like Skippity Toilet.
Hahaha.
Do you think they're growing?
I actually can't tell at all.
We need a skelly so we can...
So we can...
This seems like a...
Okay, hold on.
Let's make this a little bit more fortified.
Okay.
I don't know where they are.
But...
They're making a whole lot of noise.
Okay.
That's better.
Onward.
Oh.
Onward!
What are we at anyway?
Negative 18.
Hmm...
Wait.
Oh, there he is.
Hahaha.
Can you get through here?
Can you get up here?
Maybe I should just take him out.
Awesome.
If Ocelot was Gen Z and said that during Virtuous Mission, I wouldn't hesitate.
To create a time paradox.
What are you talking about?
That would be the hip thing then.
If Ocelot says anything, I'll just go with it.
To be honest.
I'll be like, okay, Ocelot.
I believe you.
Negative 28.
Let's just go forward.
You guys...
I'm in a bit of a pickle.
I gotta go to the bathroom.
I gotta go to the little ghosty's room.
Do you think I'll be safe?
If I just chill here?
Oh.
Hold it.
Hahaha.
Wait.
Actually.
Oh, this does pause the game.
Because I'm not on a server.
Okay, I'll be right back.
I'll be right back.
I forgot it's single player.
I forgot.
Yeah, I'm in single player.
You're not in a pickle, you're in a cave.
Hahaha.
Missile.
Hold on, I gotta stretch.
Okay.
BRB.
Whoa.
Sigma Rizzler, Ohio.
I'm back.
Hahaha.
Okay.
Everything's fine.
Everything's safe.
Hahaha.
Stop.
You guys, I'm just being hip and cool.
What is that?
Is it moving?
Am I crazy?
What is that?
Oh, it's a bat!
I was like, there's something there for real.
There's diamonds, too.
Oh!
I'm not gone fishing no more.
I'm back.
Scooby-Doo cat.
Rizzler.
Hahaha.
Oh!
We found an amethyst geode!
Wow!
We got a geode!
It's kind of small, though.
It's a little small.
Oh, I have no space for it.
Uh...
Oh, I need to eat.
I'm gonna eat my golden apple.
Some people might say that's a really bad idea.
Actually, no.
We can get rid of the andesite.
What was that?
What did I throw away?
Oh!
No, no, no!
There we go.
I just want one.
As, like, a little treat.
You know?
What about the pumpkins?
I throw those away.
I threw those away.
A long time ago.
I think.
Actually.
It's been quite a while since I've seen the pumpkins.
Yeah.
Do you guys think we're close?
To the trials?
I think we're almost there.
Oh!
Oh yeah!
Look at him grow!
Look at him spin!
Wow!
There was nobody spawned here.
I got another golden apple!
And some bread.
Put some dirt away.
Nametag!
Dear Mini Minto has ascended and in turn equally big...
Dear Bigger.
But still small and cute Minto has returned.
Yeah!
Wow!
Did you see me rollin'?
They hatin'!
Maybe through here.
Oh!
If only I had a...
Got him.
Got his butt.
If only I had a bow and arrow tool.
I feel ancient hearing those lyrics.
You're in good company!
We're all ancient together, you know?
I have to be ancient to know those lyrics.
Right.
I'm gonna be able to make diamond armor at this point, you guys.
For real.
No jokes.
How many do I have?
I have twelve!
What should we make?
Maybe the pants, cause those are the weakest.
Actually, which is the weakest?
Pants?
Oh, never mind.
Boots!
But the pants will break so easily, right?
Oh, a sword!
Yeah, that might be good too, actually.
Right.
We haven't found one of those, like, giant cave rooms yet.
We're just kinda vibing in here.
I'm kinda sad my shaders don't seem to work.
I mean, they work, but like...
Like I said, I have the complimentary one set up, and they aren't...
They aren't doing their job.
There's so many diamonds in here!
So many!
Okay.
After I get all these...
We're gonna craft some stuff.
We're gonna actually play the game.
We're rich, baby!
Oh, but all the guys only want emeralds.
They don't want diamonds.
Let's see.
Where's my crafting table?
Here we go.
So what should I craft?
I can make pants!
Sword?
Oh.
I was gonna say, I don't have enough for a sword.
Um...
I just realized I don't need this wool.
Actually, give it back.
I do need it.
A sword!
A sword, a sword!
Yeah!
You mean you haven't been playing the game up to this point?
Nah.
This has all been pre-recorded.
Gotcha!
And a pick.
Goodbye!
You?
I hoarder.
I like keep all my old tools, you know?
I don't know if you guys have noticed.
Oh, wait.
Switch this out.
There we go.
Zombie noise.
Really?
Just... to nowhere?
Hmm...
I'm trying to decide which way I want to go.
It's bothering?
Good.
Be bothered.
It's fine.
What else am I gonna get down here?
Just a bunch of bricks?
Doesn't matter.
This is where I came from, right?
Okay.
Let's go.
Oh!
You guys, this might be where I die.
You guys...
You guys!
Oh!
Oh,
God!
Not another one!
No!
I
lived!
I lived!
Tell the tale!
Oh, my gosh!
It turned the corner.
It's just mayhem.
Oh, wait.
I've been here before.
What?
I have?
Oh, I lived!
I lived!
Yeah!
My shield's a little...
Oh, wait.
I left my...
My crafting table.
Wait, where did I leave it?
Try not to die, VTuber.
Very simple.
I was down...
Oh, there it is.
Items are precious.
We can't just throw away something like this, you know?
I don't have any wood.
Super chat made me puke.
It's okay.
I forgive you.
Chat, do we forgive turtles?
Decide their fate.
Turtles, your fate will be decided by the...
Oh, wait!
I do have pumpkins!
I can't eat them, though.
I'm gonna leave a little pumpkin trail.
No!
No mercy!
Your punishment?
Soup.
Oh!
I just noticed my health.
Soup.
This is where I was going, right?
Oh, gosh.
I can't remember anything.
Is this where I was going?
Is this where I've been?
Nothing makes sense anymore.
Oh, wait.
This is where I...
Where did I go?
Where did I come from?
Hot Nigel.
This way.
Does it lead to anything?
Up here.
Oh, gosh.
Imagine...
I was going to say imagine I lit up...
lit back up and there was a guy.
Oh, my gosh.
He got little booties on.
Where did you get those?
Can I have them?
No?
Take back.
Okay.
This way then?
You guys, we're so close to the trial.
I can smell it.
I can smell the trial.
We're even at...
negative 43.
We're so deep in, you guys.
I don't think we can be any deeper.
Actually, I'm just going to go to this corner.
And I'm going to dig out.
Here we go.
We're going to dig this way.
So close and yet so far.
You don't know.
We're going to run out of food.
No, we won't.
We're going to find the trial before then.
What even is a trial?
Right?
She won't have a crafting table.
No, I have one.
Oh.
Wait, where is it?
I picked it.
Wait, where is my crafting table?
Where did I put it?
I might not have a crafting table.
But it's fine.
I got it all.
Up here, baby.
I've got it all.
Up here.
I picked up the axe instead.
No!
How could I be such a fool?
Beyond this gravel.
I've got it all.
Up here.
You guys.
It's fine.
No one has ever memorized anything like I have before.
Why do you have an axe in a cave?
Why do you have a thought in your brain?
Because I forgot to put it away.
Stop, you guys.
Stop.
My health didn't just go down.
Did it?
No.
Was there an actual diamond?
No diamond.
Nice.
You got them good.
Thanks.
I'm going to be finishing off these berries right now.
Probably.
There was just an eerie noise.
Diamond in the lower right screen.
Lying isn't very becoming of you.
Okie dokie.
The trials are coming in 5...
4...
3...
2...
1...
to the 20 first annual hunger games trials.
The outlast trials.
We're trying to outlast whether we can go in this cave without food.
It's an iron vein.
Yeah, there's so much iron here.
It's kind of awesome.
But it's ok.
We have one goal.
Digging through this hole.
The endurance trials.
The trial to find.
This...
One second.
We got this?
Guys...
Guys, I'm really almost out of food.
Guys, I'm really...
I just got 2 golden apples.
Some raw potatoes.
Will the raw potatoes make me sick?
That's a bigger question.
Will I die by potato?
They can?
Will I hear a zombo?
Sounds like he is going through his own trial.
What if this is the trial?
The trial is...
The search.
The exploration.
The...
The need for...
Ok, we're by water.
The trial is the journey.
The lust...
For...
Finding something new.
What if only then...
Once you accept that fact...
Will the doors to the trial...
Ok...
Open up to you.
You know?
The trial is not the friends we made along the way.
Because we literally have not made any friends.
I bet the village is probably just like...
I wonder where that crazy Minto went.
Probably like...
Damn, I haven't heard from her in a while.
She's probably dead.
That guy is probably still sleeping in my bed.
That alley...
I set him free!
How many times has she died?
Zero!
I stream ends once I die!
What are you talking about?
I know that there's...
Lots of noises around me, but...
What if I just keep digging?
It sounds like a zombie.
I made a lot of friends in your wisps.
It must be so nice to be able to play with people.
It must be so nice.
We're digging away from the zombies.
Zombie-shaped trial.
It's not someone behind me, right?
Ok, good.
Thank you for watching.
Make a server with my friends?
Yeah...
I don't have very many.
I was trying to put something together for my birthday.
But I needed like...
I needed like a team of eight.
And I was like...
Oh...
I...
I can't come up with eight people.
And then I cried about it last night.
And I switched my plans.
But you know...
That's just the way the cookie crumbles.
Or the blocks...
That's just the way the Minecraft blocks break.
Wasn't a seven other person...
It was different.
I was only filling in...
Because Matara couldn't make it.
Oh...
Wait...
Oh my
god.
And even a guy riding a damn spider.
No!
I won't die here!
You guys...
This is so bad.
Let them in fight.
Okay.
Run away.
I gather them all to one spot.
And now I run.
I go.
I leave.
We're okay.
We're fine.
Just keep going.
Oh my gosh!
It's my job!
Exactly what I said would happen.
This is the world.
Where is the world?
Is this...
Is this heaven?
Am I back in heaven?
Why isn't it loading?
Hold on.
Let me try it.
Save and quit.
Exploding creepers!
That's not even what killed me!
I got killed by a dang skeleton!
Sad,
sad, lonely world.
But I wanna see underworld!
It won't even let me!
It won't even let me have the satisfaction of free roaming!
No!
Spectator accounts loading chunks should be a setting you can change.
How would I do that?
Yeeted to heaven.
I'm in outer heaven!
We're in outer heaven because...
We're not...
This is actually real ghost experience, okay?
Heaven is up here, right?
And then this is...
This is the...
In between!
When you're in limbo!
Snake, what's going on?
Snake!
You probably have more friends than you know, Minto.
I don't know.
Good one, chief.
Thanks, Sinbad.
Purgatory.
We're in purgatory!
Why can't I see it for real though?
Maybe under a video setting?
Oh.
Uh...
Maybe I do more render distance?
Hmm...
Alt F4.
Oh my god...
Go away...
What?
We got the children in the chat.
Um...
Yeah, I don't know why it's not loading.
The Patriots.
This is...
What's it called?
Literally, this is a real Metal Gear moment.
War never changes.
Um...
Game rule to not have spectator load...
Wait...
My computer sucks.
No!
My computer doesn't suck!
I have...
3080!
It's strong!
I'm too high up.
Is that it?
Really?
Here I go...
Wait, what am I at?
I'm only at 65.
That's not too high up.
Unless it's going to show me from where I died.
Will that load?
Okay, let's keep going.
We gotta go down to like...
Negative 48 or whatever.
Right?
Only at 3080?
What?
Oh, I think this is where I was at.
Set your game to survival by opening the game...
Turning cheats off...
What?
That's not true though.
I've died in hardcore before.
And it has definitely...
It has definitely spawned.
Slash game rule.
Oh, I don't have the...
I don't have the...
I don't have things on.
Oh.
Huh.
I'll put the land first.
Wait, what does that do?
Oh!
Okay, there we go.
Oh wait, what does that mean?
What?
Other players?
I don't want people to come in.
What?
How do I...
Wait, what is this?
I'm so confused.
They can't?
Okay.
I think that guy is serious.
It's local only?
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
So if I do spectator...
And then if I'm like...
Wait, game mode...
Wait, oh, oh, oh, oh, wait.
Wait, oh.
Don't block me.
I'm in sad, sad, lonely worlds.
I give up.
Minto, don't block Minto.
It's okay.
Here, let's just...
Here, I'll do this.
Create new world.
A creative, right?
Or here, a survival.
With allow commands on.
Here, this is what we'll do.
We'll just pretend.
Why do I keep starting in the trees?
Game mode spectator.
Oh, I just died.
Oh, oh.
Look at the world.
Oh.
Wow.
Oh, this could have been us.
This is where...
I died probably.
And...
This is where I...
I...
Wow, it's so beautiful.
This is where...
Yeah, there's the hole.
There's lots of holes.
Okay, so hold on.
What's the command to find...
Wait.
Biome?
What's the command to find the...
Locate.
Biome.
Um...
What's it called?
Oh, structure.
Cats spawn in.
Trial chamber.
Trials edition.
Step foot in a trial chamber.
What's...
Oh, it's just a skelly.
It's just a skelly.
And then...
What the hell is that?
What is this thing?
Oh!
What is that thing?
I can beat you with my fists.
Oh, ouch, ouch, ouch.
I forgot the skelly.
Hold on.
Let's get rid of him.
Okay.
Okay, good enough.
What the heck is this thing?
Wait, it's like crackling.
Vault?
Where'd it go?
What are these?
Oh!
Copper bulbs.
I'm just gonna explore now.
Oh, wait.
We can do creative mode?
We're powerful.
What's this thing?
What's this?
The vault?
Ah!
Oh.
Oh no!
Wait!
I'm supposed to be a survival!
My bad.
We'll find another one.
There's gotta be one around here.
Trial's my butt.
There's nothing in here.
Wow, everything's copper!
It's so awesome!
What's down here?
Oh!
Welcome to your doom!
Wind charge?
What am I?
Inuyasha?
What is this?
What the heck?
Break the pots?
What?
What a...
I'm not a maniac.
Oh!
It only gave me arrows.
Wow!
What's up here?
Oh wow!
Wow!
This place is huge!
Oh, what's this?
No!
Yay!
I feel like I can delete these, too.
Did I die in this one?
Yay!
This one's survival, though.
I haven't played it since April.
Oh, man.
Delete it.
Delete.
What's this one?
Oh!
The past rage quit.
Good stuff.
Well, guys, thank you for joining me for Minecraft today.
It was a pleasure.
Thank you.
Kind of random, but what's your thought on the short-lived Project KV?
I...
Um...
Wanted to try it.
Okay.
I... Okay.
There was like some... Okay.
The reason I wanted to try it was because I heard it was like an age game.
I think there was... I think there was... Like, that's the first thing I heard about it.
I was just like, it's Blue Archive, but actually an age game?
Okay, I want to play it.
And then I think that was kind of blown out of proportion.
I think... I think that wasn't actually the case.
And...
But then also, I was like, when I saw that it got shut down, I was like, oh, that's kind of sad because I wanted to, you know, I still wanted to try it.
But then I also heard that, like, Blue Archive was suffering because of it.
Like, there was some events that were, like, getting repeated and stuff in the JP version.
And...
That... Like, some... Some art and stuff was, like, getting neglected because of it.
This is so sad.
Poor Mint.
I want to play it.
And so...
Um...
Yeah...
Um... But also...
Um...
Blue Archive is, like, more my aesthetic than Red Archive.
So, you know, I'm more of a fan of Blue Archive and everything anyway, so I probably would have been really sad if it had shut down because of, you know, anything.
I just like Blue.
I know, me too.
Yeah, I like the sci-fi aesthetic a lot too.
I found so many diamonds on the server.
10 out of 10.
RIP Minto server.
I'm so sorry, you guys.
I really did try.
I really did want to play with you guys, but...
I'm so sorry.
And did you know that a recent survey of Blue Archive has a 90 to 10 male-female ratio?
I don't believe that.
I think there's a lot of girls that play Blue Archive.
But also...
Um...
I saw that, like, 90% of Blue Archive's revenue comes from, like, JP fans.
It's like an average of 6,000 yen per person.
Crazy.
Name 10.
Me?
Oymo?
Ringo?
There's more.
You guys, I just said that I couldn't name 8 friends for my birthday.
You gotta do this to me.
You gotta do this to me!
I can't even name...
I can't even name 8 friends for my birthday.
Name every woman Vtuber.
Starting with the first.
Annoying Orange?
But, yeah...
I don't know if Ayami Sensei actually does play Blue Archive.
I mean, she draws for Blue Archive.
Thank you.
I don't know if she plays it, you know?
It's not as simple as you guys think, you know?
Like, there's time zones and stuff that are in, like, people's schedules.
So...
Um, you know...
It's just that I was trying to, you know... I was trying to find people that could make it in their schedule, is all.
Okay?
Jeez.
Don't have to be so...
You don't have to...
I'm just joking around and you guys gotta take it so seriously.
But, you know...
Jeez.
Back up.
Nah.
But...
But, this is fine.
I'm glad...
I hope that I can find a trial room for real.
I understand why you guys said it's dangerous now.
I need a bow and arrow myself.
I need more...
I can fit it in my schedule.
Oh my gosh.
JB, thank you!
Thank you.
You were the one that I was worried about the most.
Thank you so much.
Everything is fixed now, you guys.
The world is back to normal.
The world is all good.
The world is good again.
Alrighty, I'm gonna end today's stream here.
This is fun.
I'm so sorry to everybody again who wanted to play.
And especially if you were like, oh, I'm gonna put it in my schedule to try and play.
I'm so sorry.
I really am.
And hopefully next time I can get it to work and get some people to help me.
And not just be like a silly goose uber about it and be like, hee hee, I'm just gonna do this on my own.
And yeah.
But yeah, thank you guys.
One day we'll play.
I'll make sure of it.
I will make it happen.
Yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
So there will be a revengeance.
Don't think that this will be the only time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't think that it'll be the only time.
But thank you guys for hanging out with me these past couple of hours.
It was fun.
It was good to come back to Minecraft and be just a little dumb about it and everything.
So, hmm.
Okie dokie.
Otomita!
Otomita, Otomita!
Thanks for meeting Minecraft!
And I'll see you guys later.
Bye bye!
Otomita!
See you!
See you, see you, see you!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Wait.
Let's see if we can raid somebody.
Let's see.
Is there anybody here?
What?
Let me raid Kiara?
Let me raid her, I wonder.
Ok!
We'll raid Kiwawa!
Bye bye!
Bye bye, bye bye, bye bye!
See you, see you, see you, see you!
Bye bye!