It still sounds like...
That royal song.
Never be royal.
It can never be royal.
You still don't hear it here.
Hold on.
It's the same part.
It's the same.
It does!
It just sounds like it.
I hear it every time!
Amito, hello!
Stinko!
No!
Wait?
You hear it now?
You just have to add that part afterwards.
It's literally the three notes.
That's that.
Oh my god, I almost said smells like Royals.
Sounds like Roy.
How's your gotcha pull lately?
Bad!
Just popped in to say hi.
Hello!
Thank you!
13 months already!
Oh my gosh, thank you!
I did a pull this morning in Blue Archive because even if If there's a new banner and it's not unique in Blue Archive, I'll still pull.
Unique meaning a character that is like, can only be pulled during the banner and can't be pulled any time else, you know?
Nakizo, thank you so much for the fun!
Good time!
But thank you so much for seven buttons.
Thank you.
And...
You heard it, right?
I can't unhear it.
Find the Tokyo next week.
First time to Japan, I heard this cafe was a good place to get some directions.
Any Minto musties.
We'd love to hear from fellow wisps as well.
Azure, I hope you have so much fun.
Must Sees.
Tears stay.
It's so true!
I watched the Akiba Tour stream.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Good luck with gotcha pulls.
Thank you!
Fight size!
Thank you so much for the 20 gift!
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
Ah,
I'm trying to think of a place.
Garbo Lemon!
Thank you so much for the 20 gift!
Thank you guys, thank you!
Lehman, friend, don't dash me.
Can ghost swim?
Float.
My size, I use it for another five, thank you.
With your negligence, you'll make more ghoul friends.
Okay, but imagine, imagine this, water park, it's haunted.
We advertise it as such, instant attraction.
There are many people that will go stay out of place because it's haunted, yeah, park's haunted.
Ducky, thanks a lot, my goodness!
Mm-hmm.
What in the Scooby-Doo?
Even our, the slides, like how it's Scooby-Doo when you open a door, you know the chase scenes where they like crisscross and everything?
That's what our tubes do too.
Olaf Pilgrim- I swear he moved.
No, he's been in the same place.
Same spot for like ever, ever, ever.
Jesse, thank you so much for the podcast.
Thank you.
Been listening to the podcast.
Any chance of a season two of your own spooky story time.
I don't have anything to say.
Spooky.
I caused the spooky.
Bless the kicks.
Welcome to Mambuship the Haku.
Yeah, podcast is over one year old.
When can babies talk?
Can the podcast speak?
Do you want a golden beach ball?
Just want a top of Kmart.
So if you climb the tree beside it...
Wait, really?
Wait.
Santa Parland.
On top of the Kmart?
Wait, hopefully it doesn't do that thing where it like explodes.
It did the thing where it exploded.
One moment?
Oh, not controls.
What am I doing?
Settings?
I don't know why it does this every time.
Hold on.
I probably have to just like...
There we go.
Okay.
Here?
Uh-oh.
I can't move anymore.
Wait.
I can't move.
Okay, we can move.
Okay.
Wait, the stairs don't work.
Wait,
wait, I'm stuck.
Guys, now I'm actually stuck.
Somebody help me, please!
Somebody!
Somebody help!
There's someone stuck up here!
Somebody!
Somebody help!
Help me!
Help me, please!
Help!
Look up!
Gamers don't look up!
Oh no!
Guys!
Guys, I can't stop!
Respawn.
Okay, we're fine.
Thank you.
I didn't know that that button existed.
Okay, hold on.
How do you climb up top the game board?
It's my birthday today!
Love it!
Happy birthday!
Start by 21st off strong.
You can have everything you want now!
Yeah!
I say...
You could hire some lovely ladies...
For a party.
Unless you know some.
Okay, hold on.
How do you climb?
Maybe the tree.
Okay.
What did I say?
You can't do that.
Wait, what did I say?
Tree is key.
Okay, cool.
Like clowns?
Yeah!
Or...
I was thinking...
Oh.
I was thinking like...
Like a...
dancer who could do tricks at your parties.
Clowns are always good for parties.
Wait, can I go higher in the tree?
I want to go to Maid's cafe during my birthday and then they'll sing me happy birthday.
Oh gosh, I had it.
I was so close before.
Maybe.
Maybe I jump to this window.
Okay, okay.
Ah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, hold on.
Okay.
Don't you want to get soaked?
Oop.
Don't you want to get soaked before you go into work?
Screw work.
Come get soaked at my park.
Baby Corrie, thanks for the vibe, Getson.
Stay great.
Thanks very much.
Yes.
You do?
Yeah.
The 360 next door.
He was like the audacity.
Help!
What am I doing wrong?
Team!
Team, what am I doing wrong?
Stick to the wall.
Try.
Go diagonal.
According to you, a servant...
Wait, hold on.
Oh, I forgot to do something.
Happy churno day.
Oh my gosh, it is churno day.
9-9.
Where did the U.S.
Survey 9?
Oh, 9.
September 9th is statistically most common birthday in the U.S.
So happy birthday to all the wisps today.
Not me, I'm in March.
Really?
I guess it's because so many New Year's babies.
Maybe.
Makes sense, I suppose.
People know how to party.
You too can party at your birthday with the ladies.
Who's laughing?
You?
They're trying- they're laughing at me for attempting this.
I want to see- wait, is it there?
It must be.
Hug the wall.
Oh!
Double jump?
Oh, I have the tree branch!
Okay, okay.
Do
you imagine if there was fall damage in this game?
Oh, oh!
Every new year you can think I was conceived.
No, I don't want to think that.
Why would somebody want to think that?
Oh, yeah.
Hello from France.
Hello!
How's it going?
Yes, it's going.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Uh, I'm called Mimpo.
Uh...
It's all good.
Ah...
Yeah.
Uh...
I'm Napoleon.
No, I'm...
I'm...
Wait.
Minto.
Maybe they should have soapy water pistol fights at anime conventions.
There are like conventions in the States that are...
There's one that takes place at a water park.
And I've kind of always wanted to go.
Oh!
I'm feeling the monkey in me.
I'm climbing this tree!
Who worked?
Oh, Braylon over there is probably like, what are we gonna open?
And the monkey!
Wait, how old do I go from here though?
This branch maybe?
We lost it all, but we can get this back.
I believe, trust, trust!
in the pixie dust.
Okay.
Alright, we got it back.
I just, these limbs look too thin for me to climb atop of.
But I guess I'm doing it.
I'm not doing it.
I was at that con.
It was a blast.
It looks so fun.
Yeah.
There's an easier way.
Okay, tell me the easiest way.
This way doesn't work.
I don't think.
I can't go here.
Who's in the sewers?
You see that?
There's like something sticking out of there.
Roof, lamp post, lamp post, building roof.
Water.
So like real parkour.
Lamp post.
But...
Lamp posts apparently.
Ah, the left one.
Yeah, because I was gonna say there's no second lamp post.
Up there?
Or up here?
Hmm.
Mysterious, okay.
Okay, okay.
Alright.
My park is so pretty.
Oh my gosh.
Okay.
Gaming?
We're gaming?
We're gamers?
Okay.
Dexpo was so fun!
We gotta greet Minto meat again.
What?
You greeted me again?
Okay, gamers.
Ah!
My depth perception strikes again.
It's okay.
Oh, that's fine.
We're okay.
Get up, buddy.
Gosh, we're so tan.
We're like super tan.
We're crazy.
Okay.
How was your water park?
My water park is amazing.
We've only had several deaths.
So, okay, wait.
From lamp post, how do we go?
Only several.
Tan minto.
I don't know if ghosts can tan.
On top of the stairs.
Oh, we're gaming.
We got it!
Oh my gosh!
I wasn't one guide either.
It's real.
Yippee!
Can I take this stuff too?
Mine?
Whose house is this anyway?
I'm breaking in.
Breaking and entering?
Yes!
The golden balls!
Balls!
Singular.
Is that trash in my... Wait.
Why do I have trash in my thing already?
Did I not clean up last stream?
No bad.
Trash!
Oh, I think I ate that trash?
Wait, seriously, where did it go?
Kintama!
We ate it.
How efficient is that?
We don't waste anything here.
We go.
That can be part of our advertising.
We're a totally clean and awesome park.
Okay, so to get to three stars, oh, let me move you guys over just a tad so that you can see our goals.
Like so.
There you go.
So our goal currently is two.
Push out cheaters!
Pumpkin eaters!
Okay, seems clean.
How about you?
Clean?
Yep.
Clean and fixed.
Clean and... Oh, fixed.
That's right.
A little palm tree.
Oh.
The final cosplay of Expo.
Yeah, I know it's you!
Whoa!
W's a Chino dono.
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Self-love is important.
So true.
Everybody have this sort of confidence, you know?
Okay.
Alright.
I
didn't do anything last year.
Oh yeah, I think I ended in a rush, that's why.
I was like, uh-oh.
But today, no rush.
What about self-loading?
If you self-load yourself, I'll be enough to love the both of us.
Or, wait, I'll love everybody enough where if you load yourself, I love you enough.
What am I saying anymore?
Don't question mark.
I don't get it, but she loves us.
Oh, I'm just...
We should do some...
Okay, we have $1,000 to blow, baby.
But not on blow.
We're gonna blow it on paint.
Yeah!
Can I get a year?
Okay, paint is here.
We're gonna start making this area looks kinda...
Research floor tool.
Oh, never mind, just kidding.
It looks like...
It looks... Actually, you know what?
It's rustic.
It's themed after...
Something.
What can I get?
Oh, I have four.
Let's see.
Increased walk speed.
Do you think visitor patients would increase them dying as well?
Like, I mean, like they would not die as well.
Let's get attractions level one.
Oh, a jukebox.
Oh, here's the floor tool.
I can't afford it.
No!
Puddle Highlight Modern toilets Modern showers Pure Asura Seems to be in high spirit today Head full of I've read that as lard
My head's always full of lard While you're loving people Can you spare some for my kamiyoshi?
Her name is Min-fan What?
I thought you're Kamiyoshi!
Am I?
Lard it up, baby!
Yeah!
I think we can open the park.
Oh, more trash.
How'd that get there?
Durability management is nice.
Is it?
Could I unlock that one?
I don't know.
Uh...
I thought I saw it.
Under maintenance?
Oh, here.
yeah you know what we'll do that because sledgehammer upgrade oh faster demolition interesting large extra large pockets i want that why is it cost 1500 to wear better pants do you think that love can bloom at a water park also i started calc three today can i get a gambare actually i think love can bloom at a water park because that's what happens an anime.
Kanban, thank you so much for the gifted!
Thank you, thank you!
You can go to a water park and then and then what if you go down a slide and what if their bathing suit is like you know a bikini?
And like what if on said slide the bikini the water force was too strong and what if the bikini flies off and she It's just like, oh my god, oh my god, I need your hands to cover.
I couldn't even finish it.
Okay, we could start the park now.
Actually, um...
I got yelled at by someone in the comments last stream.
They were like, woo!
um your trash can optimization is not it's not good wait how do i a build there we go so what we're gonna do is they were they were like it makes no sense it makes no sense that your trash cans are next to each other yes sir i'm listening i take constructive feedback here
at mint mint mint take constructive feedback very seriously.
Min-max your trash cans!
I'm so sorry, everybody.
You had to see this horrible, awful state of affairs.
Wait, didn't I get better decorations?
Where are they?
I unlocked them for money.
Is it just the flower beds and stuff?
You should put four next to each other just to spite that nerd.
If you're watching right now, don't worry.
Wait, what else did I build?
Oh no, I didn't build anything else.
But this is important to have.
And we'll put it straight in the middle so that I can always get a life ring.
Oh.
What?
Can our beach ball, our golden beach ball?
Nice.
This game, the water looks so delicious, no?
Like, it makes...
I really want to eat this.
I want to drink it.
Not the ball.
I want to drink the water.
Nice and corine filled.
No, I would like to believe that our place is super fancy and it's saltwater pools.
No!
Park is open baby!
Beach balls for all!
Beach balls one and for all!
Yes!
You want one?
Already wants one?
Oh my gosh!
We're the talk of the town!
Wait, wait, wait, no you, you, you, you!
Oh, oh, yes,
yes, yes, yes.
The music is so excitable.
Pinky make Ungu smile.
Ungu like Mingy.
Happy.
Ungu, Ungu, Ungu, Ungu.
Thank you.
Oh.
She got so excited.
She passed out.
Line up, friends.
Line up.
And we're trying to kick out.
out some cheaters so get our hammers ready look at this crowd things are going swell new research point oh for what it's
sparkling clean isn't it yes yes yes I clean it immediately I'm so efficient and effective it's lovely talking You're at Expo.
But Vexpo.
It's a guy in the Leahapi.
Oh, yeah!
Actually, Sakana came by a little while after and I was like, yeah, I talked to someone in the Leahapi.
He was like, oh, sorry.
He was like, why, why is your new outfit making it look like that?
Like what are you talking about?
I was hating on my new outfit, you guys.
That guy sucks.
Why are you in clothes?
Shouldn't you be here?
What?
He has a wristband.
Why are you, did you, why didn't you change?
Braylon screwed up.
Oh, Braylon.
Wish man hate.
I don't know why he's such a hater.
Oh, stinky!
You left his swimsuit at home.
Where is he?
That guy's gonna drown.
Have you ever been in the pool in like, uh...
Full clothes?
It's horrible.
Hey, Minto, love seeing you at Vexpo.
You guys, I told you, Park's haunted.
Park's haunted.
Please, thank you!
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you so much.
What's up?
Expo.
I keep saying expo, I don't know why.
Where are all the cheaters?
Where are all the people that...
Oh, oh, I forgot people want food!
Oh my gosh.
Hello, what do you want?
Lemonade.
I didn't restock it!
I'm a failure of a park owner.
Seems like a tundere.
Okay.
Nah, I don't think he wants to be the joy.
Lemonade and ice.
Got it.
Oh.
There you go.
Trash.
I have a trash can right here.
Meet the ground.
No, no, no.
I have dogs.
Okay, we have dogs.
We have dogs.
Add both.
Okay.
Get out of here.
Scram.
Scream!
Lemonade.
Dojo.
Add both.
Patty, thank you so much for the thank you!
Lemonade.
Add ice.
Dojo.
Add ketchup.
Lemonade.
Dojo.
Send the hot dog sound.
No!
Are there any evil people about?
No one's drowning.
Everyone's having a good time.
Oh, trash.
Stinky trash.
You want a hot dog?
My last one.
Add both.
Any evil people?
Oh.
Uh-oh, stinky.
Don't walk here.
Sometimes I can't.
Sometimes I can't tell the balls from the trash.
Oh, oops.
Look in a mirror to find the evil people.
Hey!
Evil ghost.
So true.
Well, it's broken.
This one?
How did it get disrepair so fast?
is tired.
Oh my gosh.
Wait.
No, please.
Don't.
Braylon, leave.
Don't leave me.
Lemonade.
I need you.
Braylon, I need you.
I need you to fly the plane.
Hello.
Adult for four hours.
Slide pass.
Of course.
You got it.
Hot dogs.
Someone's drowning?
Uh, I only have five pockets.
Don't drown.
You're welcome.
What would you like?
Plane.
Thank you so much, Zane.
What would you want?
Lemonade.
Add lemon.
Ooh, someone else is drowning?
Where?
Oh, I got you.
Whoa!
Nice shot.
Get in there.
I missed, but it's fine.
Nice multitasking.
We are killing it, you guys.
We're killing it.
And $10,000 of revenue.
I mean, I got that achievement.
She'll make it in Oh, sorry Uh, here we go I pressed the wrong button
Someone wants to buy a ticket Oh
Oh, Braylon's back Maybe Tarko, thank you so much for the five gifted What time is it?
We have two and a half hours, guys We can make it Vanessa's waiting on her hot dog.
Of course, of course, my queen.
Vanessa, I love you.
Lemonade?
Add lemon.
Of course, of course.
Add mustard.
Hi, Minto.
Hi!
Oh, excuse me.
I love the way they're like...
Ah!
Oh, my bad.
Hot dog.
Add ketchup.
Such an intense game.
I know.
For no reason.
For no reason, it's so intense.
Oh, are there...
It's people drowning or...
Oh, uh-oh.
I think we lost one.
Oh, no, we did.
Oops.
Edwin, I got you.
I'm a trained professional.
Come
on here.
Gross.
I don't even sell these.
I'm so sorry.
Getting crazy with the throws.
Oh, yeah, baby.
How do you drown at the edge?
They just are really talented, my customers.
Oh, sorry, we're out.
So sorry.
Diarrhea everywhere!
Wait!
We have to clean it up one letter at a time!
Who's...
There's not diarrhea everywhere!
No!
I don't think we've had any cheaters.
That makes me sad.
Excuse me.
Diarrhea everywhere.
Oh, I got the wrong thing!
That's fine.
We have people waiting on lemonade anyway.
Hello?
Add lemon?
Of course.
Do better next time!
out of the lemon, though.
I want lemonade at eyes.
I might have done a thing.
What does that mean?
When did eyes is...
Oh!
Did I forget one?
She's a cheater!
Where is she?
Where's she go?
Where'd the cheater go?
She in the bathroom?
Poop everywhere!
People are graffitiing my...
People are graffitiing my place!
My birthday today!
Daptonia!
Happy birthday!
Happy happy birthday!
Add ice and lemon.
Sorry.
Owner has zero!
Oro, Oro!
No!
Who let Gen Z into my park?
That was me.
I wrote that.
No!
Decoration level.
We made a lot of money in it, though, maybe.
Welcome to King.
I think.
I think we made a good amount of money.
Evil.
Esmeralda was evil.
Oro, look.
behavior.
No!
I have aura!
Oh, no!
Oh, it's nice and quiet now.
I love this time of day.
A ghost is laughing in my park.
Yeah, now we might... I think last time I tried to hire a janitor and it glitched out so now we can hire the janitor for real
guys how can i increase my aura
please tell me i'm scared oh it was the handyman i tried to hire it was somebody i remember stop showering will that really help i'm desperate here the kids are flaming me I'm on.
Someone with aura wouldn't be scared.
Oh, no.
Zora.
Oh, Zora.
Oh, owner.
Wait, I was combining owner and zero.
Owner has a hundred aura.
Your new opening and ending transition are very cute.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you, Zora.
Glad you like it.
Hee.
Hee, hee, hee.
Oh, I got a 10 out of 10 throw.
Let's go.
Owner has Zora.
It's true.
Wait.
More graffiti.
Keso was here.
Is he the one graffitiing?
Clean small semi-circular pool filters.
Oh!
I think people were getting COVID.
Let's go.
It got so bad.
It'll be fine in the morning.
I'm sure.
They got super COVID.
Oh, I guess the filters are clean now.
Is that all?
That's all I needed to do?
This one's pretty bad also.
It looks like it's about to die.
We don't tell you to drink the water, so...
But, it is a gotcha.
Maybe we should advertise that.
If you drink the water, it's like a 1 in 32 chance that you will develop a superpower.
That's pretty tempting, though.
I wonder if this toilet was the one that was broken.
No?
Superpower gotcha.
I would try.
I have nothing to lose.
There's so much to clean now.
Did I get everything, you think?
I got the chairs.
Got the pool.
Got the bathrooms.
We restocked.
Chances are low, but never 0%.
Exactly.
We just have to try.
Is there anything that we can unlock?
Oh, we have eight.
Okay.
Nice.
Maintenance decorations.
Small things that make big impressions.
Modern showers.
Trash highlight.
That's kind of nice.
One out of 32 is unironically great chances for a gotcha.
You think?
Oh, sorry.
I said 32.
I meant 3200.
32,000.
My bad.
I wonder what the people want to listen to.
Modern pools.
Maybe we should do that.
That would be fun.
Now you're thinking.
Exactly.
Vending machine.
Attraction decorations.
How much money do I have?
Lifeguards!
Oh, but I can only hire like one people or two people at a time, no?
What?
What was the thing?
Y-pad is tabbed.
There we go.
Uh, we'll do it tomorrow, but we'll do...
Someone.
For now, I want to see what we got here.
Oh, more plants.
They just keep giving me plants.
Is this gonna...
Is this gonna increase the attractiveness?
A plant?
Yeah, I can only...
do two right now let's do some vending machines that'll be big people like vending machines can
i afford oh they're expensive that's all i can afford okay that's fine it's a little off-center
it costs 1200 wait i won't be able to afford a person We might have to wait one more day before we can hire somebody.
But we'll make money off of this.
This is passive income.
Did you see your Oshi was at the...
I saw Mike from Red Letter Media was at the WWE event, and he's, like, jamming to the music.
I love that guy.
Granola bar.
Yummy.
Okay, all right, let's sleep.
Tomorrow's a new day.
Good morning, Minto.
Good morning, Brailan.
How are you doing today?
Bright and early.
That's my man up at the crack.
Wait, I have to restock this?
Oh, okay.
Do I, can I afford it?
No.
Chippos.
COVID, oh, see, there is COVID here.
Oh, granola.
Okay, good thing I can buy it.
Passive income.
That's a lot.
Alright, our goal today is to kill the cheaters.
6-7.
Oh my god.
Stop.
Who's graffitying my place?
I cleaned it.
up who's breaking in at night not the six seven it's so terrible it's like the least funny thing ever where's my mirror wait didn't i have like a mirror why is it a wardrobe now we're gonna upgrade our look i like the shirt
we'll keep it i don't get it it's i don't even know how to explain it.
I've listened to things on how people have explained it and it's it's it's it's doesn't make any sense.
Looking minty today.
Look at this!
Wait we have a coffee machine and a fridge!
Wait I didn't realize all of this got cleared out.
Alright Braylon, it's all up to you.
We're almost in the red buddy.
I don't want to stress you out but like I need I need money.
I need customers.
I need big profits, okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I need big, big profits.
Sorry.
I'm not the owner of Brailin's.
If someone hit you, talk to Brailin.
Wouldn't Brailin's the graffitier?
He wouldn't be.
I'm ready.
I'm ready to kill.
What, six, seven?
My niece?
keeps on saying it, I have no idea.
It's like, okay, the best of my abilities, where's that guy?
Is he ever coming out?
So the best of my abilities to describe it, it's like, there was a song or something, and he says 6-7 in it, and then people started editing it to basketball, and then more people started saying it, and that's all I know.
Wow.
I don't really get it.
I don't understand it.
All because of a song?
Apparently.
And like they would make edits of like basketball players being like, yeah, six, seven.
I don't get it.
So it's nothing?
Like actually, it's so unfunny it hurts.
It's painful.
Drowning already
All right, we're making money, baby This is how it feels to get old Right
Wait for a hot dog I'm running at the speed of light Hello, you would like both There you go All right, so far So far good it's calm we're chill this is awesome she says they're approving of my car I wish are people buying from the vending machine you think it will get crazy soon mark my words I'm so on top of it I saw that garbage and I'm immediately taking care of it.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, safe.
Okay, yeah.
Pay to use the seats and everything.
Pay to sit.
Pay to swim.
Pay to breathe.
I think there's any cheaters in here.
That was such...
That was so...
Clutched it, man.
She would have slipped and broken her neck immediately.
Then I'd have to pay for it for some reason!
Kill you, Isabella!
Kill you!
Damn, Isabella.
All caked up.
6-7 means weenus in Cantonese slang.
Wait, really?
Really?
I love her screams of terror.
Add mustard.
Of course.
Uh oh.
I got this.
Whoa!
I had that!
Okay, let's go.
Lemon.
Oops.
I never thought I could miss.
Nice throw.
I'm killing it.
I am the best at running a park ever.
A plane.
Raylan, I need you to lock in, buddy.
I need you to lock in.
We're going to be in the red if it's not for you, okay?
Whoa, everybody got up at the same time.
Did you see that?
It's pretty freaky.
Hey, cheater.
Okay, just three more cheaters and we'll be good.
Braylon is not doing the job well.
Well, actually, oh, no, you're the guy.
Okay, good.
I'm looking for wristbands here, wristbands here.
Yes, yes.
Wristbands, wristbands.
Sorry, my bad.
There we go.
Ah!
So far, so good.
Wait, I feel like my park is kind of empty.
Is it Braille?
Oh, wait, you have a wristband.
Why did you have an evil symbol on your head then?
Wait.
Is it her?
No, she has a wristband.
Wait.
Oh, it's him!
No, it's not.
Wait.
I saw it, you guys saw it, right?
Add ice.
Plane.
It was her.
She was trolling.
Are you gonna make six, seven edits of me?
Oh, oh wow.
People actually use this chair.
It's kind of impressive.
I'm coming, I'm running at the speed of light.
A lemonade, right?
Add ice.
Yep.
Is anyone using this pool?
Look at that!
There's two people in here!
Of course people are...
I'm using my pool.
Guess waited too long for a ticket.
Uh-oh.
Braylon.
Four hours, senior.
Someone's drowning.
Somewhere.
Uh, must be the other side.
The lemonade is what?
Stupendous.
Delicious?
Nutritious?
Senior 4-hour?
A lot of old people like to come to the park.
But swimming is good for old people.
Wow.
People here are crazy.
Waited too long for lemonade!
I just gave it to them!
I give the people what they want.
Is anyone using this?
Oh, they are.
They're buying the...
They're buying them.
How much are they?
Yeah.
$20!
$20, $20 grendola bars!
I think I'm a scammer.
It's all ice monkey.
That's insanity.
What's wrong with my...
What's this one say?
That's so not true.
There's puddles everywhere.
And I'm working on it.
I'm working on it.
Is like food illegal in this world or something?
Like, people...
People, food is like super scarce or something.
Food and swimming.
pools apparently since you have to pay to swim per pool one granola bar please no are they like what's it called uh
got him just uh two more
oh god everybody's jumping on me oh god getting the trash out of the pool
Sick jump.
I don't like it when they like slide past me like that.
Sometimes we gotta have a little fun too, you know?
Sometimes we gotta have a little fun.
Add mustard.
Alright, get out of the way.
Get out of the way?
What do you want?
Add lemon?
There you go.
Teeny bit of trouble.
Why are we troubled?
Hello.
Hello!
Fist punch, thank you for a whole month.
Thank you, thank you.
Alright.
Don't worry about it, Dakota.
You're fine.
Evil.
Oh, just kidding.
She's the one I already got.
Okay, we're fine.
Excuse me!
Trash in my pool!
Dumbit.
Oh, I see him!
Add ice.
You're evil!
I'm not serving you.
Ayyy!
Oh, we did it!
Yippee!
Right now your water park's flooring is plain and forgettable.
But you're not here to be average.
Unlock the floor tool.
Okay, so it's forcing us to do this.
Okay.
Get his ass!
Kick his ass!
Now drown him!
also evil don't be evil don't be evil okay we'll get the floor stuff after um oh oh it's over uh do i get to eat this dowel gore
here sir you're dowel
oh noemi would you like this hot dog
Hello?
The floor I'd stare.
Uh, dog?
For you?
Oh.
Alright.
Let's clean up the park, baby.
Today was pretty good.
See you soon!
Thank you for the dog.
We did it.
We did it, team.
We're at $1,500.
Unlock the floor research tool, okay.
Nice haul today.
I mean, granola bars cost $20, apparently.
I'm the worst person in the world, I think.
We're charging that.
You know, I feel maybe the cheaters are a little justified.
I think we can afford to hire someone now.
I think so too.
Okay, we got that one.
Just con food prices.
It's like when you go to a theme park and the water bottles are $7.
They're like...
Holy moly.
It's one thing I love so much about like a Tokyo Disney is like the vending machine prices are normal like for for like a tea or something it's all just normal prices I can only say for Disney because I've never been to like USJ and I don't remember the prices at Fujikil.
But you go to Disney in the States and it's like crazy.
$10 drink.
Okay.
Oh, this one.
The specialty.
Alright, that should be everything.
So now we paint the floors.
Okay.
Unlock...
Is it probably under park?
Floor tool!
Cashier training!
Water park no death pass and ticket I brought in the first stream do not count as expired.
Of course!
If you are drowning, I will throw a floaty to you.
100%.
I'm not usually into theme parks, but you kind of sold me on Tokyo Disney based on that Tokyo Disney is so great even if you don't like theme parks I recommend Tokyo Disney see a hundred percent the the place is just so atmospheric in general floor tool floor tool okay change color what do we want maybe the granola bar is up your superpower chances one to thirty two thousand one and three thirty 100.
So true.
Tokyo Disney see what?
See your mom.
Okay, so if we're Zanzibar land, maybe we should do like a desert-y theme, right?
Okay, let's do this area.
Oh.
Oh, we have to do 30 floors.
Okay.
Alright, alright, team.
We got this.
Okay.
Wait, we're already at 15.
17.
18.
Wait.
Huh?
It's counting strange.
A little bit.
20?
The game doesn't know how to count, I think.
That's okay.
We believe.
Oh, okay.
Uh, okay.
Fire Brailin?
He's a liability.
What do you mean?
You think he's...
wanted artists.
You're not the only one decorating the park.
Some guests leave their own creative marks on your walls.
Graffiti is a form of art, but those guys are no match to your creative vision.
Trek down these vandals.
I have to... Okay, it's just clean the graffiti from vandals.
It's not like find the guys who are doing it.
I don't know how to do that.
Look, actually, this kind of looks nice.
No fun zone.
No fun allowed.
Oh, oh!
Poop everywhere!
They're so wrong about this.
I- I- I've never seen maybe poop like two times in my park.
Three max?
And also that's not my fault.
Don't blame the park, blame the people who are pooping on the ground.
Okay.
Wow!
Our little park is looking so dandy.
Do we have any more slides?
No.
Oh my gosh, I can't wait to get these mega slides.
$15,000!
Okay.
Alright, tomorrow we'll hire...
Who do you think we should hire?
A janitor or a handyman?
Let's check the size of the toilets since they like to do that too.
No?
The backs?
Oh!
LOL H What does that mean?
Handy mail?
LOL H?
Just got back from my trip to Japan and visited Disney Sea after thank you for inspiring me to go and experience Occupy and Mids as well.
Mr. Phantom, are you my father?
Thanks for sharing your passions and inspiring us.
Thank you!
I'm so glad you had fun, it seems like.
LOLH
Yuppie!
Oh wow, it's so bright.
Oh wow, look at it.
Everyone will surely appreciate their eyes being blinded.
I love when I go to a water park and the ground is like so bright I can't see anything.
Oh wait, before we do that, let's hire someone.
Uh, tab, tab, tab.
Ah, janitor?
Well, we have no handymen, so janitor it is.
This person has pretty good efficiency, just they're slow.
Wait, this person's pretty good, no?
They're all slow.
Why are these guys so much more expensive?
When this guy has better endurance and efficiency and everything, and he's cheap.
Good morning, Minky.
Please hire me my resume.
I'm cute girl.
Don't go till you're hired for life.
Okay, we hired Victor.
Victor, where are you at, buddy?
Victor!
He's bald and he's proud.
Whoa, look at him go.
Look at him go.
Sweeping where nobody even thought thought to sweep what an overachiever oh just getting here
have you ever thought of a park have you ever thought of a park have you ever thought of a park have you ever thought of a park have you ever thought of a park have you ever thought of a park have you ever thought of a park have you ever i feel like i feel like idol producer have you ever thought of becoming an idol this
place is really becoming our home because we live right out side we live this place is really feeling like home since our tent is right out there let's slide
okay good job all right so our job today is graffiti baby you've come to the park you couldn't pee at home zane huh gosh this bathing suit is so sexy it's so low-cut What if she got on the ride and the water pressure was was too strong?
And she said that she said, oh, oh no, my bathing suit came off.
I think that happens to more girls than you guys realize.
It's happened to me before.
Not where I asked, I was by myself on the slide, but my top came off.
And I was like, yeah!
But really?
Yeah!
It was, um...
Yeah.
Ghost.
Double knot your tops, ladies.
For real!
Oh, hot dog.
Wait, did I restock?
I'm so sorry.
I keep forgetting to restock the lemonade and the... I'm gonna drop this here.
So we can get both at once.
Wait, I think I might need to restock the granola too.
It's not a...
It's a feature, not a bug?
What do you mean?
No!
I'm sorry!
Yeah, let's go get more granola too.
I think it happens to people more often.
So now if I ever go to a water park, which I have not been...
I think that was the last time I win.
I...
I will not...
We're probably a bikini.
I didn't get banned.
I'm looking around for graffiti.
Who could be the culprit?
You are in a water park.
Um, look at me.
Do I look like I'm ready to swim?
Is it a cold day?
Why are my nips showing?
Everyone's been seeing that.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, nope.
He's really excited about the job.
Clearly.
Wow.
I mean, with all these bathing suits around, I don't blame him.
Add lemon.
Yep.
Why are you staring at me?
Oh, you were not staring at me.
I like when I get their order and they go, yep.
Can cut glass with those.
Yeah, nobody gets ice here.
You spoke too soon.
Add lemon.
But surely it's a cold day because no one gets...
Not lemon.
No one gets ice, so...
Add mustard.
Uh-huh.
Any graffiti, guys?
None.
Trash.
Even though my trash bags are...
Oh.
Add lemon.
I love where we're here on this beautiful December day in the water park.
Everybody, yeah, everybody's oiled up.
Oh no, no!
Everything's fine.
1 in 30, 2,000 chance.
Okay.
Someone's drowning!
Your needs are not important!
Hello!
Add ice.
I'm too good at this game.
Where is our... where is our janitor, huh?
I haven't not seen Victor around.
lemonade with uh no lemon no ice can i get a can i get a
everyone loves this pool i guess because it has both the slides oh there he is good job buddy i'll get the rest can i get an aid what what are you guys upset about where's what garbage this garbage i got it no more garbage it oh add ice okay brailan is going to rest so we should now let people into the park
hello slide pass senior four hours someone's drowning one moment aha yes yes
could you eat a granola bar and gain super jump it's a it's a granola bar from the one piece universe
A kid just died.
Oh, someone's panicking.
Hello.
Slide past four-hour team.
Breylin, don't just turn your back on the people.
They're gonna see you there.
And they're gonna know you're working.
You can't just turn your back on them.
Oh my god.
He's like, if I don't see them, maybe they won't come in.
Uh, Tien, four hours.
Oh, Braylon's back, okay.
That was close.
Don't slip.
Everyone is so tan and...
It wasn't me!
I'm mad at me!
It's always...
It's always this chair.
Everyone's so tan here.
Isabella, you'll get there.
Don't worry.
Hello.
Ice and lemon.
I think there's a...
Yeah.
Little puddle here.
I hope this is water.
I haven't seen any graffiti.
Maybe I got all of it before.
Lemonade.
This place is cursed.
I told you it's haunted.
Yes?
What the?
Put credit on Victor's name.
I mean, he's probably doing a bunch.
Probably.
Okay.
And I'm also doing a bunch, okay?
Remy is waiting for Lemonade.
Add ice.
Mm-hmm.
Did the price go up?
I feel?
Am I crazy?
Yeah.
$20.
It's crazy.
I got it.
Wow.
I'm gonna go get some more people in.
Oh, sorry.
What a dramatic flail.
Broken toilet?
Which one?
This one?
No.
Graffiti.
Huh.
Why was there so much before?
Now suddenly.
Yeah, the park closes soon-ish.
Don't hammer the guests.
I'll do what I want.
Alright, catch this.
He's still paid to drown.
There you go.
Uh-oh, do I have lemonade?
Oh, I think that's the last one.
Add ice.
Nice.
Evil!
Yeah!
Kill, kill, kill!
Wait, maybe I need you to do graffiti though.
Where's the graffiti?
Why is there no graffiti?
As soon as I need it, it's gone.
Oh, we got some tips!
Wait, we got 78 tips!
$78 in tips!
Get better reviews to get bigger tips.
I think we did a pretty good job today.
Very nice!
Nice tips.
Oh look, I think he's been cleaning these too.
Oh my gosh.
Wait, Victor's the goat?
He's so helpful.
I can't wait to be able to hire more people.
Bending machines are superior?
Okay, this also needs to be repaired, so let's see.
Remember that as well.
Look, this one doesn't even need to be cleaned!
Victor's amazing!
Nice.
How is that a 5 out of 10?
Okay, we're gonna add more vending machines.
Maybe, well, vending machine, because I don't think I can afford very many more.
Victor's doing his job!
Well, mostly.
This one was pretty dirty.
But he's done a great job so far.
Yeah, if we go with the vending machine, I feel like we should get rid of the hot dogs then.
No, people don't want to dress granola bars.
Maybe.
I don't know.
There's really no graffiti at all.
Nothing?
No one wants to vandalize my park?
But it's so pristine and shiny.
It's ripe for the pickin.
It's so graffiti.
No one?
No one wants to write poop everywhere?
I can do a little bit of vandalism.
I don't think Victor would clean it up unless it went towards...
What's it called?
The task list.
You know?
Hmm.
run too tight of a ship.
What can I say?
I'm just too good at my job.
I wasn't able to catch you live, but Monday was my birthday, Reach!
Happy birthday!
I watched the last Half-Life 2 bot, and the game I would recommend is the Batman Arkham series.
No L-O-H?
Nothing.
I see no graffiti at all.
Granola is 50 bucks, but we sell too and that's almost the amount to cover it.
Okay, nice.
Maybe we add a slide here.
A really fun one.
We'll put it like right here.
Yeah.
Now more people will go over to this area too.
And what we're gonna do then also is put a vending machine.
Wait, what's this?
A jump board?
Whoa!
When did we get this?
Wait, this is different.
Oh, oh, we have new different pool types, too.
How much was this?
350?
Okay, I think we have enough for a vending machine.
Let's put the vending machine right as soon as they enter the park.
Right here.
Right.
Here.
We'll put it in between.
We'll move this.
To like here.
Right here, yeah.
And then we'll move this.
Here.
Yes.
You ever get to upgrade your tent?
I sure hope so.
Alright.
Let's build.
Now more people will come over here and they'll see the vending machines.
Wow, this is fun.
We got a big diving board now.
Nice.
Oh, it needs to be restocked.
So, drill.
I hope I have enough money to pay my employees.
Welcome.
Okay.
I don't want to be like a certain company.
All right.
Oh, it's clipping a little, but that's fine.
Too soon?
All right.
All right, team.
Good morning, team.
Good morning, Brailing.
Good morning, Victor.
Are we ready?
I've got, we're all stocked.
We're all clean.
We've got new attractions.
This place is bustling.
We're going to get tons of graffiti.
Let's go.
Throw as much shade as you want.
Roast them.
Did I clean these or did?
Okay, cool.
What about the trashyard?
Okay.
Nice throw time out of 10.
My tiles?
What's wrong with my tiles?
These?
Oh, because I didn't finish it?
Well, I need more money.
So, you know, you could come to my park and spend lots of money and then I will...
be able to paint the rest.
Why the cutie on the bottom right now is swimming?
Ah!
Yeah!
I'm swimming.
I want to jump on this, can I?
Woo-hoo!
Good swim.
Alright, I'll start doing more.
Oh, this is not the floor tool.
I'm silly.
Hot dog!
Hey, Autic!
Welcome to Membership, thank you!
Yep.
Oh, I need to...
Where did I put my flyers at?
Oh, here they are.
We can go pass these out.
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey!
Yes!
Got her.
Fished her.
Easy.
Look at this line.
Hello, everybody.
Welcome in.
You.
You're thinking of a water park today.
Yeah, you were.
Oh, you're thinking of a water park today.
Yeah.
Good playlist.
Thank you so much for the 50s.
Thank you.
Would enjoy it between smack and thugs upside the head through Joker asking if Batman dreams about him in a thought!
Reach, you're speaking my language.
Happy birthday again!
What is written here?
Maybe it's on the other side.
Oh, it's the menu.
Big to small, sweet, and sour, natural juice.
I mean, it is fresh lemon, so...
Christopher!
Get in there, Christopher!
Yeah, let him.
Go to the vending machine.
Give me money.
Look, oh, I'm dying.
If you don't pay me, this is what will happen.
We're feeding you the shower?
Wait.
You saw some?
You're right!
Blue hoodies suck.
I'm not wearing a blue hoodie.
3 out of 5!
Woohoo!
Graffiti!
Let's go.
There's two more graffitis.
I mean, one more graffitis.
I wish I would say add both, kind of like the other one, you know?
So much pee!
Yippee!
Last one!
I swallowed a band-aid at Zanzibar Land and got an infection.
Oh!
Unlock the ticket ATM via Research Tree, and it will handle ticket sales automatically.
It only takes cards, so guests with cash will still go to the counter.
6-7.
Okay, no more graffiti, please.
I'm over it.
Graffiti.
Jose, welcome to membership, welcome back!
I'm doing playlists, thank you for another 50!
What the heck?
Why?
Thank you, though.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
What do you want, Lemonade?
Glizzy Nation!
Okay, but that's not even graffiti.
Wait, I want to watch you do this.
Nice.
That's the truth.
Glizzy Nation!
I felt that one.
Oh, I see evil.
I see someone naughty.
Is it you?
No, you have a wristband on.
Oh, you do too.
Wait, where are you?
Who just pooped?
Yeah, you.
Oh, it's supposed to be LRL high.
Why is everyone...
Hot dogs are...
Ay, ay, ay, ay!
I caught a vandal.
Hot dogs are...
What does it say?
I'm suing.
Why are there so many vandals now?
Stale?
That's what I read, too, but that doesn't make any sense.
Crabbs is up.
I love that episode.
It's so funny.
Well, you see Trashware.
Duke is drowning.
What has Duke ever done to you?
for me, huh?
Oh.
Oh, he's giving me money.
You know what?
Oh.
This isn't about him.
We have people graffitiing and people peeing and, I mean, pooping at ice.
People throwing their trash on the ground.
I saw it.
Oh, there it is.
Trash in here, too?
Oh my god.
I got the trash don't worry this is a clean park poop
everywhere I like how the graffiti moves it's so funny you he he'd right in front of me add lemon okay yeah and add ketchup hello add ice and then Kaiso.
Kaiso.
Yummy.
I want some Kaiso.
So much pee!
No!
I don't know what this one says.
Something in the...
I'm getting all these vandals.
This is why people have lost their men.
Uh-oh, two people drowning.
We have to decide who to save.
It's the Walking Dead.
Crazy cosmic penance.
Boring.
Oh my gosh.
I'm gonna kill you people.
I'm gonna kill all you.
Bros.
Chopped!
No!
Please!
Christopher will remember.
that i can't do this anymore everyone's just insulting me marvin's waiting for lemonhead i got you marvin
uh we only have nine people here like not even that much six seven i'm gonna kill everybody in this park i'm gonna put i'm gonna put super covid in the in the pools for real i get a hot dog but hold the dog Victor, what happened to you?
Lying on the job?
Okay, he's working.
Esmeralda, you can wait two seconds for me to mop this up.
Okay.
Alright.
It's almost four.
Then we can get the automatic ticket.
Wow, I did not think.
Her bathing suit.
It did not look like she was wearing anything.
I thought we...
had a nudist at the park.
Add lemon.
You got it, sir.
Why is that pool the designated drowning pool?
I don't know.
Maybe it's the fountain gets them a little...
Um...
Sorry.
Sorry, Serenity.
Serenity now!
Oops.
Maybe it's the fountain gets them a little dizzy.
Add lemon.
Yep.
What happens if you let them drown?
Um, they die.
Yeah, they die for real.
I wouldn't know that from experience.
It's an educated guess.
I would not know that from experience, of course.
They die, IRL.
These are all real people.
Ki-hi-hi-hi-hora!
Wait, we have to make sure she lives.
Ki-wawa!
Ki-wawa, ki-wawa, ki-wawa.
Chihuahua!
Chihuahua, are you ready for a good time?
Oh, yeah, girl!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Let's follow her into the bathroom.
I didn't think we would actually be able to.
This one's for you, KFP!
Oh.
Add ice.
We have to make sure she has the bathroom.
Best time ever.
Nice.
Nice to buy!
Get in there!
Is there trash?
I thought he said it was trashy.
Maybe not.
Where'd she go?
Kiara?
Kiwawa!
Oh, oh.
Hot dog and lemon and...
Add ice.
Yep.
And you add both.
Mm-mm.
Okay.
Idol meeting admission fee.
Who's
making all these sounds?
Guys, we lost her.
I don't know where Kiara went.
Wawa, where?
Wawa?
Kiwawa?
Did she have the most fun ever?
That river.
I would recognize her bathing suit.
Kiara?
Where did she go?
she go?
I just gave her a hot dog.
Oh, she was the one who ordered?
I feel like I've seen something that I'm going to be obligated to forget, or I'll spend eternity in the usual
room.
Serenity, now!
Serenity, ow, ow, ow!
These are probably pretty clean though.
Wow!
Victor does a good job keeping things clean.
Most of these just need, like, a little sprucing up, but he's maintaining this well.
Yes, he is.
If only I could get a repair, man.
I mean, how many people are going to be paying by...
Cash, right?
It could be that...
Most people pay by card, and we only...
If I get rid of Braylon, we only need to go up a couple times, you know?
Perhaps.
You guys see the 6-7?
I hate these zoomers in my park.
This is an adult-only park.
From now on.
Clear grip.
Oh!
I didn't even see this.
Oh, graffiti.
Wow, that was hard to see.
Adult swim.
for real.
Okay, grandma.
These dying youngsters!
Graffiti ain't my part!
I don't know what's wrong with blue hoodies.
I don't really get it.
That one is a mystery.
A true mystery to me.
Oh!
I...
Sui!
Sui sei.
I think it's a Kaiso joke?
Graffiti.
Graffiti everywhere.
Sui-chan?
Hiyo mo kawaii?
Alright, so we need to restock stuff.
I think I cleaned everything.
Oh, wait.
Can you do a super cool 360 spin?
Okay.
How was that?
I think that was pretty sick.
Thanks for the teeny tiny pretzel recommend.
They are indeed yummy.
Oh, you went out and got some already?
So fast.
Yes, everybody get your teeny tiny pretzels.
Not sponsored, obviously.
Everybody do the flop.
I'm not flopping.
I think that's everything.
Now let's do the ATM.
Okay.
Where would that be under though?
Uh, not here.
Maintenance?
Oh, ticket machine!
Oh, the way here?
Unlocks a ticket machine.
Okay.
That was my post-stream activity last night.
Let's go!
Ticket... Okay, well now...
My tickets will be more expensive, so that's good too.
We got a ticket machine!
Where is it?
Do I have to build it?
And we got more decorations too.
Big tree.
Let's put in a big tree right.
Right here.
Some atmosphere.
Oh yeah baby.
That's what the people want.
I want like some like statues and stuff.
Right next to the ducky?
Ah, I see!
Thank you.
Nice, nice, nice.
Raelin, are you sleeping with me tonight?
Oh.
Oop.
My tiny, my tiny, my tiny trash.
Wait!
Pick up my t- No!
No!
It will let- I think we cleaned everything.
Oh wait, let me build this.
Wow!
Look at this!
This is a snazzy park, huh?
I littered, yeah, right outside my home.
Maybe I'll be able to get it in the morning.
A flock of seagulls.
No.
Okay, Victor, we got our work cut out for us today.
Oh, I got a restock.
Oh, this one.
You have Victor now.
Yeah, it'll be easier.
Eh?
Huh?
Oh, this is a hot dog.
Um, this one... I think the other one was more empty.
Honestly, I couldn't tell.
They seem about the same.
Of course they're saving all their shit for when we open.
Let's get another trash bag and let's open up, baby.
Now our tickets are more expensive.
Okay, wait.
So now the road to three stars sell 50 tickets!
Okay.
Hello?
Theme park?
No?
Um, theme park?
Theme park?
Seagulls are leaving a mess.
Where?
Here.
One lemon dog, please.
Turbo, thank you so much for the beat that rat!
Oh my god.
Oh, there's...
There's poop everywhere!
Victor, help me!
How did they get underneath the...
Oh, they're gone.
I'll leave the rest to you, Victor.
Okay, I gotta go pass out these flyers.
Someone's waiting for a hot dog.
Best day ever, yes ma'am, yes ma'am.
Thank you so much for the gift and you guys!
Thank you, thank you, sorry, I am so preoccupied with the birds.
The birds.
Oh, you already won one, okay.
What about you?
No, meh!
Everybody's still doing good here?
Phil, thank you!
Poop everywhere.
Can I get a lemonade?
I want lemonade for real.
Oh, lemonade.
I want real lemonade.
I want lemonade now, actually.
Can I get a lemonade?
Poop.
No poop park.
We're a very clean, satisfying place to be.
Yeah.
There's not poop everywhere.
You're too old for this.
You are way too old for this, Willow.
You're like a grandma.
My fault.
I'll let the boys know not to poop at your park.
Thank you for the pink.
Thank
you.
Oh, oh, oh.
Six.
Oh, oh.
Oh, my gosh.
Someone's angry.
I mean, not angry, drowning.
There you go.
You're safe now.
What are you?
Why are you guys?
I said it was... Oh, no.
She says it's clean.
I thought she said it was dirty.
What?
Haha.
Ice, lemon, dozo.
They're angry because they're drowning, obviously.
sparkle sparkle yes yes yes that's what we like to see here yes yes yes i don't know okay i think he just cleaned that very good what's going on in there oh wow
i think so i see someone drowning hold on let me just clean this stuff in the tub sorry So far, no one's died.
That's so impressive.
Did you just kiss me because I saved you?
Ow, that was it.
Oh, someone's waiting for Lemon.
Add Lemon.
Minto was flabbergasted.
That was crazy.
I did not expect Vectors even in the pool.
I didn't expect...
And then did you hear he, like...
It was like a satisfying little...
After they were done!
Nobody dying should be the bare minimum.
Who's taking photos?
We got perbs here taking photos of people in their swimsuits.
Who's taking a photo?
What happened?
Maybe he saw a ghost.
Why are you taking photos?
You caught a pervert!
Oh, Serenity!
Serenity!
Give Serenity my number.
You're okay, Holly.
Didn't notice your legs bugging out at all.
Don't worry about it.
That was...
This is craziness.
I said she was... I said there was a pervert and it was real!
Sorry, Victor.
Your opinion matters less, though.
She's turning on her own people, perverts.
I mean, I'll
look past it next time, you know?
Serenity, come back, you know?
It's like, oh, this isn't, no, this is Serenity.
Serenity, you're my girl.
Here.
You get the pervert pass.
Don't worry about it.
Yeah, don't worry about it.
We're selling, okay, we're almost to 25, we're almost halfway to the numbers of tickets we need to sell.
Someone's waiting for...
We're making okay money, okay.
Uh, add lemon.
You're welcome.
Stinky garbage, stinky garbage!
Clean 1,000 trash in your park.
Let's go.
Um, any graffiti around?
Oh, guess who's waiting?
Stinky, Minky, no!
Teen, for four hours, slide pass.
Hello, y'all!
Well, you don't...
I guess you're a teenager.
You don't have a card, probably.
I feel like most teenagers have cards nowadays, no?
Stinky, Stinky!
Center pool is nasty.
No, it's not nasty.
It needs to be repaired.
Oh, my bad.
Who is that?
Serenity?
Okay, she kind of deserved it.
Serenity, girl!
Found out.
She's like, maybe if I make like a big bus her people will like you know, try and help me and I can you know, touch them.
She wants to grab onto some big biceps.
Hello, Christopher.
What the lemon?
Of course.
Yep.
Bandle.
At the stars.
Whoa, six.
Oh, I ripped my pants.
Do you guys see that?
How embarrassing.
Oh my god, I hope nobody saw.
I did a split.
ripped my pants when I ripped my pants I thought everybody was on my side but I went and blew it all sky high the photos are on the house yeah we do a weekly or monthly calendar or something now she won't even spare a passing glance all just because I ripped my pants.
Big Larry can't run just to put him down.
Peep, peep, poo, poo on the potty.
No one ever wants to dance with the fool and then ripped his pants.
I know I sure are
you're not you're not you're not you're not you're not you're not you're not you liar.
Oh, I forgot that dirt happens.
Oh, sorry, Victor.
You got this one.
You got this one, King.
Someone dying?
Oh, someone's panicking on the...
There it is.
Oh, someone is dying.
I got you.
Don't die on me.
Amanda, please.
Life or death here.
Why is SpongeBob music so good?
What was I coming out here for?
I don't remember.
Stinky, stinky.
The owner sucks!
Restock, I guess so.
Do I need to re- Oh, I think I need to restock the lemon in.
Or I'm close to it.
Add both.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
We're almost out of granola bars, which is awesome.
Okay.
Means we're making so much money on them.
Oh, sorry.
Plateral damage.
And close!
Almost.
Sneaky, stinky person.
Graylin wrote that after you bought the vending machine.
Okay, I can't find a trash bin, thought.
Really?
Do I need to add more trash bins?
Okay, we can put one like here.
No, how do I turn the camera?
How do I rotate?
Do I rotate?
Can't remember.
Uh.
Shift?
No.
Q?
Oh, thank you.
Oh, I see a QE.
You're right.
I'm blind.
I'll put it right.
I'll put it right here.
And then we can put another one
Over here Okay
Building these trash cans with my own two hands Can we get any massive slides like the Eventually we have to up our Our rating We still need to sell 20 more tickets So definitely tomorrow But see you can see here the slides get crazy big A triple tube double blow.
Baby.
I
feel like we clean way more than like other places do.
You know what I mean?
Like other water parks.
I feel like we're held to a very high standard.
Everything is coming together nicely.
Yes, yes.
People are dirty, dirty nasties.
we also repair more I know but to be fair our bathrooms get broken in like two seconds for some reason
Kobe 7 out of 10 come on
clean more because more business or more dirty maybe
oh there's some we have a trespass her in the park?
Uh, yes, ma'am?
Naya?
Naya, the park's closed, baby.
Come on.
Get out of the park.
Come on, baby girl.
It's the maid instinct.
Come on, girl.
Yeah.
See you tomorrow, Naya.
You can run.
You can scream all you want.
I know I'll see you again.
poop everywhere no no no no for some reason i my brain does not see this slide
okay i think that's everything cleaned uh wait i think i missed this slide over here or not slide this diving board i'm listening while i'm reading while listening to which when I think about, I'm not sure how I can, but it's very relaxing.
I'm glad.
Okay, I think everything is now at...
Oh, I forgot to repair these.
Okay, I think everything is now at 100%.
Oh, wait.
Just kidding.
And then we'll restock.
Yes, yes.
We gotta restock both vending machines.
And everything else.
We gotta restock everything.
Let's just throw everything on the ground here.
so we have full hands
so much granola restock, restock restock, restock restock, sorry Victor restock, hot dogs weren't so bad lemonade definitely needs it okay, alright let's sell the rest of these
these tickets we need to sell 20 more and then we can continue upgrading
Piss Park Said who?
Oh my gosh, my little mini litter trash is still there How embarrassing
Okay Come on, come on The park Is open Yeah Oh, you already wanted one What about you?
No, you already wanted one How exciting?
You, you, you Yes, yes, yes!
Birth!
Death!
Tengoku jigoku no...
Did you... Are you going?
Okay.
Oh, not you.
Boring!
You?
Yeah, but not you.
Yeah, this rocks.
Boring!
My bad.
I'm not the owner.
Talk to Breland.
Welcome to the park!
It's so clean and beautiful, anyone lemonade!
I had lemon.
Of course.
What did he just...
I get $30 for catching the perverts.
If you catch me, you guys won't get that.
$30.
I'll just let you know now.
Yeah, get out of here.
Unfair.
But do we get a minto?
I don't know.
I'm a little slippery.
Okay.
Good, good, good.
How many tickets?
40!
We just need five more!
Five more!
Stinky, stinky, stinky!
Stinky, Jacob!
Like an eel, exactly.
Oh, stinky.
Many stinkies today.
I wonder if that's going to be our next thing to do.
They're the stinkies.
Ghost eel.
What the heck?
So many stinkies.
Do you think my park is a shower?
What is up with this?
Okay.
Uh, lemonade.
Add lemon.
No bin in sight!
Ma'am, your glasses!
Why are you saying it's trashy when you did that?
And now you don't want to go in the-
I don't even see the trash, though.
More stinky.
People piss in the pools.
Not here.
Maybe a little.
I don't know.
We...
We clean, we clean!
Maybe that's why everything gets so dirty so fast.
Maybe.
Jacob is waiting.
Lemonade.
Yep.
Kiara's back!
She said no?
Oh, okay, good.
Wow, what's her hot dog playing, everybody?
Write it down.
Add ketchup.
Wow, wow.
Lemon.
Ice.
Very good.
Any trash?
No trash?
Any trash here?
Oh, there is trash here.
Okay, one moment.
I will get you your hot dog.
wearing the american bikini i know she's so into it she went she's she performed well i guess they performed twice or no they performed many times what am i talking about i was just thinking of the new york one recently i was gonna say she performed in new york twice and now she's a full american oh
whoops uh ice and lemon Oh, it works.
Exactly.
Mm-hmm.
Uh-oh.
Someone's dying.
I got it.
I'm too good.
Don't slip.
Jacob.
Jacob is panicking on the diving board.
Oh!
Two lateral damage.
Anybody waiting?
Nope?
Okay.
Any water to wa- Hudson full of energy.
Nice dive.
Thank you, 10 points!
Yahoo!
Oh wait, build five trash bins with at least two star prestige.
Okay, so that's our next task list is to build more trash cans.
I feel like I could do that.
I want to wait until after the...
The park is closed, you know?
It's hard to build stuff when it's open.
There's always so much going on.
But at the same time, I want to get more task stuff.
I want to get another task.
Let's...
We'll have Victor handle everything.
If somebody dies...
It's not our fault.
It's Victor's fault.
It seems like they come in waves.
Today we have a bunch of litterers and some days we have a bunch of we have a bunch of graffiti people.
Let's go!
Yeah!
What's happening?
He's gonna fall asleep again.
Oh yeah, because we have so many illiterate...
Okay, let's add them.
Utility.
We don't have a two-star prestige.
We have to unlock it.
Maintenance?
Trash, highlight, no.
Modern toilets, no.
Arc.
Modern trash bins.
Here we go.
Hungry guests.
Okay, so that's vendor staff we can now get.
But we need the modern trash bins.
There we go.
Now we're doing...
Oh, I should get rid of these ones then.
Alright.
Sledgehammer time.
Coming!
Teen.
Pass.
Six hours.
You're welcome.
Sledgehammer.
hammer oh okay
we need to build five trash cans you guys five of them these are bigger than the other ones i think here we'll do two here okay two here hello
hello i'm here at ice you're welcome Our hot dogs are brand new.
Add lemon.
Yo yo.
The
trash can guy will complain they're not optimized.
It's okay.
We'll optimize them to his standards.
We will.
We'll optimize them.
Add ice.
Yo, yo.
Okay, um, I see a...
Oh.
I was just about to get that.
This one, too.
More lemonade!
Oh, no, I'm about to run out, though.
Oh!
Everything's fine.
Uh-oh.
We're out.
One moment.
Serenity, how are you at the park again?
How are you not on a list?
How are you welcome back here?
Matthew is drowning.
Palmer is drowning.
Everybody is drowning.
My pools are safe, I promise.
Excellent question.
Yeah, like just how...
Who's letting you back in?
She's on the VIP list.
Do you want to live, Kairi?
Kairi, Kingdom Hearts fame?
Sorry, we're out of Lemonade, and it's 5.30.
I think Ben drowned.
Park is haunted.
It makes sense.
What was that, Matthew?
We're going together.
I'm stuck.
There we go.
Matthew was once again panicking on the...
Okay.
Panic at the diving board?
I got you.
Okay.
Let's build some more trash cans.
Let's get rid of these.
A sledgehammer.
God.
Damn it, Matthew.
He's such a little weenie.
Panic at the diving board.
My favorite band.
Alright, that alone will be enough.
Or wait.
I deleted...
Yeah, there we go.
This was the last one.
There we go.
Okay.
Let's build them.
They have a bigger range too?
Oh!
Empty your trash bins.
Okay, that did count.
Unfortunately, that was the only one that had anything in it.
Let's go restock.
Welcome to Kmart.
What?
I know he is lemonade.
Let's check how we are on hot dogs.
Yeah, we'll...
We'll get it.
And granola bars.
We have a good amount of money though!
Wow!
Guys, we're killing it!
We're killing it with the profits!
Now we have to repair everything.
Doesn't count all the other times we did it?
No, unfortunately.
Luckily, we don't have to clean everything so much because Victor does a great job.
Granola.
I know we've started swimming in cash since we, ever since we got the vending machines, life has been good.
No graffiti.
We're repairing everything.
Repair, repair, repair, repair.
What about this one?
We'll buy more granola.
It's making me rich after all.
The people are addicted to granola.
They want the granola.
They feed on it.
I mean, they actually do because you eat it.
They hunger for the granola.
They need the grain.
Me in the morning when I want my oatmeal.
I need the grain!
I hunger for grain!
Did I get this slide?
Yes.
Oh, this chair over here, the hidden one.
He even cleaned that!
Victor!
You're so good!
Well, because we did all the other...
other trash cans and we already emptied this one.
I guess it would have been better to...
to uh keep them and just build new ones but oh well
okay sleep
why is this game so addicting I don't know how to describe it you guys it's just so it just scratches such an itch it's like oh I go to this place oh I do this thing oh I do that thing it just scratches such a good itch May I have some oats?
Here, my son.
The rush?
Maybe.
It is a good rush.
It keeps me really stimulated.
I said that last time.
And I'll say it again.
I said it last time!
And I meant it.
Oh, sorry, Braylon.
You, you, you, you, you.
Oh, you already wanted a ticket.
You already love me, you're already obsessed with me.
What about you?
Best day ever, exactly.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wait, is that Serenity?
Oh, God damn it.
We're the one inviting her back.
We keep letting her into the park!
Oh, my God.
We're the bad guys.
We keep letting this pervert in the park!
Oh my god!
Oh no!
Oh!
Dang, I get $44 for catching a pervert.
That's huge.
That's big money.
Kiera!
You owe me one kiss.
We'll get her someday, but...
Okay, even the non-full trash, like emptying the non-full trash counts, so that is good to know.
We can kind of make it fast.
We can speedrun it a little bit.
Letting him into the park so he can catch him is good money.
True.
It's a little bit of a hack.
Oh, I didn't get more granola.
Oh, no, there's no more granola.
Or there's one left.
Victor, what were you doing over there?
Kiara's waiting for a hot dog.
I won't let you wait.
I see you.
I'm both.
She's being adventurous today.
Where was that guy?
Who had no wristband.
Where?
Where is a pervert?
I heard him.
She's a bit shy.
You should remove the lemonade and fill up with granola machines.
The hot dog stand is non-negotiable.
But the people are thirsty.
The people demand their thirst to be quenched.
Oh, look at all these people getting nasty.
Oh, yeah.
I heard another camera.
Where's the pervert?
Oh, no.
I'm right here.
No, Bev.
No, the people need Bev.
Don't sweat.
Bottom right.
Damn, Victor.
Come on, let a girl shower.
Golly!
Red shorts guy?
Where?
Uh-oh.
Add lemon.
Waited too long for lemonade.
What are you talking about?
What do you want?
Oh, lemon.
Victor's showering out with my patrons.
Sorry!
Okay, just...
Just one more?
This one!
Nice!
Alright, what's our next task?
Build two out of three showers at least one prestige.
Okay, we got...
Or...
We have two.
We just need to build one more shower.
You know what?
Let's build it like right over here because we don't have any over here.
Is this at least one prestige?
Yeah.
Okay.
So like right here maybe?
It's kind of far out of the way.
Maybe here.
like going all the way over there.
There we go.
Place a vending machine.
Yeah, I have it.
Sell snacks via your vending machine.
Okay, okay.
Now we have to wait for vending machines to sales.
And then we're good to go.
Purve at the showers.
Is it me?
It's not me.
Wait, is this our purves?
Oh, nope.
Sorry.
You guys had red shorts, so...
Him?
Nope.
Kyrie!
I'm so sorry!
You?
Oh, I got him!
I caught the pervert!
Kyrie!
I
won't let you drown!
Okay.
Oh, four snacks?
Let's go.
How's this one looking on?
Okay, we can restock.
nose waiting for some lemonade nobody really wants the hot dogs anymore do they
hey lemonade lemonade wait are you stinking oh no sorry it's the trash stinking up the place this lady's stinking up the place though yeah river take a shower why don't you do what your name says and take a shower someone's drowning again Oh, they don't need the hot dogs.
Is this the pool that's broken?
Hold on, everybody.
The pool is broken.
Don't use it.
Don't use it and break your necks.
That would be really upsetting.
Wait, it had to be that one.
Okay, it was that one.
All right.
It's my only rectangular pool.
My niece's name is River.
Kite.
Oh.
walking around like you own the place you go girl yes waited too long what is what is Braylon doing Victor I'm doing your job come on buddy get it together actually does a pretty good job I'm not gonna lie someone's drowning over here he's on break there are no breaks when you only have two employees Alright,
we're at 8 out of 15.
Restock lemonade.
Um, sorry, hold on.
I think it says someone's drowning.
Uh oh.
Raylan's back, we don't need to worry about it.
Can't blame me, you can't blame me.
She works us to the bone.
Lemonade, plain old lemonade, I got you.
Gotta restock the granola too.
I do, you're right!
The other one is out, but that's good.
That means people are buying the granola.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes.
Buy granola.
Make me rich!
Ha!
More lemonade!
Why do people love lemonade so much?
Add lemon.
What do you want?
Add ice.
Do go.
have bones I did at one point I might still have bones a little bit I got a bone to pick with you Jacob
Jacob be careful Jacob there you go you're
getting that good job watch out for my hammer Gregory
beg for it he's like please please sir You've only almost reached 6,017 research boys.
I know!
I'm killing it!
I might be the best at this game ever!
What the heck?
Dirty, where?
Where dirt?
Oh, I think I see it.
Add ice.
Okay, very good.
Oh, just three more.
Three more granolas.
We ain't rich yet.
What are you talking about?
This could buy us a whole new tent.
Hot dog!
Eevee, my savior.
Oh,
but we have We have maintenance stuff.
$128 in tips!
Another job well done.
That might be the best ever at this game.
Akira!
Thank you so much for that.
Might be able to buy 18 eggs.
Let's go?
We need to sell more snacks though.
We need the people craving granola.
Alright, it's time to put cocaine in it.
If Coca-Cola can do it, so can we.
Any graffiti?
No?
The
people will yearn for granola.
The people will yearn for the granola!
Extra crunchy.
It does do, Victor does do a great job at making it so that things don't take as long to clean, for sure.
This one looks pretty dirty.
Say her name.
Boo.
Um, what have we missed besides this?
I think we have gotten everything.
Oh, wait, this one.
I always miss this slide, I swear.
I'm gonna paint it pink.
We're gonna paint it a different color.
We're gonna paint it brick.
Oh, that's not exactly how I thought it would be at all.
We painted it brown.
You like granola crunch?
Now try the crack!
Yeah!
Did I get this one?
Yes.
Okay.
Alright, let's sleep.
I'll hail the poop tube.
How much further until we're...
Until we're a...
Two and a half star park!
Or three star park.
Oh, uh...
Hot dogs...
Are good, I think.
Lemonade is probably good, but we'll restock a granola.
Lynchie slide!
I can't believe we buy this at Kmart a whole box for $50 and then we sell them for 20 a pop over across the street like oh did I not clean these oh my gosh Victor you're so nice I mean I'm paying you to do this Victor stop lying down on the job okay good business I know right We're pretty good at this business thing,
I'd say.
Kaisal!
What does he do?
Oh my gosh!
Wait, he actually ate all my hot dogs!
Ay, ay!
Maybe this is... Ay, ay!
But he knew what he wanted.
It's so mead.
Another cheater this early in the day?
There he goes.
Uh, there he goes.
I'm so mean to K-so, I know!
It feels...
It feels a little wrong.
Are you supposed to be here?
Yes.
What if you buy the poster?
Wait, the poster?
There's a poster you can buy?
Welcome to K-MAR.
I don't see a poster.
I want that shark though.
Look at the Mr. Old.
Oh, poster.
Not unlocked.
I don't have it yet.
My internet's gonna die because of maintenance works.
No, Phil!
Come back to us, Phil!
Phil, no!
Thank you for the super tight.
Okay.
Oh, repair buildings!
This is what I need to do.
This is easy.
We can repair so fast.
Just 20 of them.
Sorry.
I gotta get to...
I gotta get to 20, lady.
You don't understand.
You don't understand!
Nice.
Everything needs to be repaired.
I think we'll make it.
Hey, I like trains?
Wait, this is not graffiti.
This is awesome.
Oh, I see him.
There's more graffiti this time, it looks like.
Okay, one more.
We're at two and a half stars.
Okay.
Wait, get your third star.
Unlock park size level 2.
Research build.
Zero out of 10 loungers.
Zero out of 2 pools.
Turn away perverts.
Mop up puddles.
Get more decoration points.
Oh my gosh.
Okay.
Someone is drowning.
Callum is drowning.
No, wait.
Two people are drowning.
Oh, this year you're also drowning.
Any perverts?
around?
Perverts are welcome in my park.
Oh, wait.
Perverts are welcome here.
Perverts are welcome for now.
Perverts are welcome.
I'm on my way.
Everybody here in chat.
Come to the park.
I'm both.
I literally fed her.
She did not wait too long.
at all.
Shut up.
Phoebe, stop going to the park if you don't know how to swim.
What would you like, plan?
Alright, now I gotta go save.
Matthew was injured.
How?
Why did I receive a fine?
Matthew, are you okay?
Matthew?
Oh, we're three people.
We're three.
I think somebody died.
Uh-oh.
Everybody's drowning.
How am I supposed to fulfill these?
Parameters.
But everything is happening.
I gotta do more loungers.
Ten more?
That's crazy.
Low jumper is dirty.
What's low jumper?
He's dead.
Is this?
No, this is not the low jumper.
Kiara's waiting.
I won't let you wait my queen.
Add lemon and ice.
Anything for you?
I gotta find for the ambulance.
Triple decker?
Any perverts?
Victor?
What about you?
Do you have any naughty thoughts right now?
Okay.
Mopping up puddles.
All right.
Here we go.
Oh, look, it even shows.
Alfred's waiting for Lemonade.
Add ice.
Am I the only person who doesn't frick with water parks at all?
No.
Theocross, you were so valid.
I think I talked about this last time, actually.
How, like, theme park?
Or not theme parks, sorry.
Water parks are really gross?
And I haven't been to one in a really long time because of that.
Pervert bottom right?
We prefer to be called little freaks.
Where are my perverts at?
I should have... Oh, Victor.
There he is.
There's one of them.
Victor's a real pervert here.
We love him for it.
I should have named this like freak island or something.
Ad lemon.
I like the one connected to Cedar Point.
Last time I went to one.
Well, not last time, but the one that's like closest to me, I suppose.
Which is not very close, but...
Um...
Uh, I went with my friend.
And she got like the worst stomach bug ever.
You know?
Oh, come on.
Kiara, I'm so sorry.
Don't slip.
Oh.
I must leave you, my queen.
Slide past adult four hours.
Yeah.
Does she need sunscreen?
She's gonna turn...
She's gonna tan like crazy, like everybody else.
Everybody who starts come in here.
Tan's crazy.
Six hour team.
Braylon, you can't just turn your back on the customers like this.
Here, I'll get you.
You're hot.
Dog.
I won't keep you waiting.
He's still going.
Oh, he's fine now.
Let's go.
My people need me.
Add both.
Oh, we've only gotten the puddles.
But like...
And I'll have to do the pools.
We'll do that after, obviously.
But...
There's so many little floaties around here.
Good job, Braylon.
Do your job.
Add lemon.
Oh, dang it!
I messed up!
Frosty, welcome back!
Thank you!
2.5 stars.
That's like huge in this city.
Uh, Xander?
We're about to kick your ass.
Um, it's like, so basically, uh, in Japan, people are extremely, like, extremely...
about how they rate places they kind of are just like nothing deserves five stars because nothing is perfect kind of mentality so you'll find that there will be a lot of pretty low rated places for that reason like
3.5 is like not bad it's actually like pretty good and the comments you know similar where it's like i really love the food here the atmosphere is great 3.5
dama thank you so much for the redirect thank you welcome welcome
but okay milo calm down where are you so that's basically my water park reback thanks so much for the vibe you're seeing My park is two and a half, but it's actually a great rating.
Don't worry, go thank you for the five gifts.
Thank you.
Mr. Yum-yum, I give it the five gifts.
Rice, rice, Nat.
Thanks for the gifts.
This perv on my screen is the best five stars.
Please wait, Beatrice.
Oh, my bad.
Oh, wait, I thought you were not here.
Okay.
157 in tips!
Alright.
We're almost done with the puddles.
My goal of turn for today is to get to the three stars.
I think we can do that.
I think we can at least do that.
And we will...
We gotta turn away perverts.
That's kind of RNG, though.
I feel.
We'll see.
We need more serenities.
Yeah, we need to keep inviting her...
In.
You're just gonna stare at that puddle, Victor.
Need a lot of stuff, Bill.
Yeah.
You need a lot of stuff to...
Did I get this guy?
Yeah.
Okay.
You're standing on this, but do I need to get it?
No.
Okay.
Let's repair everything first and do all that we need to do.
Let's get everything in tip... Well, actually, I think I'm gonna be demolishing some of these pools, no?
He's off the clock.
Like, do I need to clean these?
I'm gonna be demolishing... Wait.
What's my...
Okay.
Two pools with at least two prestige.
None of my pools have prestige.
Okay.
Alright.
So yeah.
There's no point in.
No point.
Spend points, girl.
I will.
Alright, but now, people are gonna come in tomorrow and be like, Oh my god.
This is the greatest place.
Bye-bye.
Okay.
Make sure we get my ball, my beach ball.
Isn't there another beach ball?
Am I crazy?
I don't know where it is, actually.
Sledge!
Sledge, have a!
Get rid of it all.
What is that, Loungeer, the timeout zone?
No, it's the sexy zone.
in case you need a little bit of a private time.
See?
Nobody can see you there.
That's where all the perverts will go!
That's the goal, at least!
The goal!
Good thing I have enough money to get several pools, though, no?
Wait, if graffiti changed anything, it would be illegal.
huh wait i don't get it do i make my own graffiti cashier okay before we unlock things that require money well i can unlock things that don't require money little highlight modern toilets we'll aim for the toilet two people toilet
their hands will deliver justice with a satisfying oomph all right well we have more patient
The corner pool.
Whoa, this thing is humongous.
Okay, actually this fits really well.
No ice.
You thought this was a water park, but it was actually a holding pen for local perverts.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Exactly.
Oh, wait, that pool was only 600.
Pizza.
Pizza pool, pizza pool.
Pizza, pizza, pizza pool.
It's a pizza pool.
Pizza, pizza, pizza, pizza, pizza pool.
It's the pizza pool.
And then we got whatever the hell this is.
Oh my gosh, they're huge.
Wait, we're so close.
We can do this.
We can fit it.
Ah!
Oh, not quite.
Well, we have to move some stuff.
Move you.
Okay.
There we go.
And you know what?
Well, this pool...
No.
This pool can have two...
Two of them.
Two slides.
And people will definitely not hit each other in the face, I think.
They definitely won't go at the same time.
and knock each other out.
Two of them, two of them, two of them, two of them.
Two of them.
Okay.
Looking good.
Looking sexy.
Wow.
These pools are giant.
Okay, hold on.
Maybe we'll like...
Yeah, we'll do like this a little bit more.
Like that.
Okay.
The peanut pool.
My eyes!
It's so bright.
Prestige level 2.
Achieved!
Wow, they're really...
Like, the color is so vibrant.
Oh, I only needed to build two pools.
Oops.
That's fine.
All right, let's spend some more points.
I need also decoration.
Lots of decoration.
Um, only...
I've got to turn away the perverts.
Loungeers, loungers, loungers.
I was like, wait a second.
I need more money for something.
For more loungers!
We'll build them all over here.
We have so much space here.
Loungeer.
With prestige level 2.
Okay, never mind.
Modern challengers!
Okay.
Then I should get rid of these.
See if you can get the park size upgraded.
I think we only get that once we get the three stars.
Park size level two, yeah.
Oh, wait.
That's a research.
Never mind.
mind just kidding you're right park size level two uh where at destroy one oh here
where did it open oh i
don't think i'm supposed to be up here
we have our work cut out for us everybody
big slide time for the big slides holy hell oh
my god maybe I make this area a jungle like why do I need to get rid of this it still looks fine this one too this looks great
post-apocalypse pool where else does it unlock does this part
wait I want to get up here do I eventually unlock this area too?
What are they building here?
Fascinating.
I want to Fulton those.
Every time I see containers, I want to Fulton them.
Does anyone else have that?
Have that, you know, after playing MGSV?
You see a container, you're like, I want to Fulton that.
Yes, in real life.
Me too!
I see something and I'm like, oh, I want to fault in that.
I want to take that home.
I think Victor is bugged.
Oh, he's fine now.
He's fine now.
I think.
He's like a Sims who...
He's like a Sim who had the ladder removed from the pool.
Okay, loungers.
Ooh, classic loungers.
We need 10 of these.
I thought it was 20 for a second.
I was about to be like, there's no way.
This cost?
200 a pop?
There's no way.
How many do I have?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
Oh my, this increases my guest capacity too.
That's huge.
Oh, I forgot about this one.
I hope we get some perverts tomorrow.
Will you hire more workers?
I have to unlock that.
I currently have a capacity.
Actually, I don't know what my capacity is.
Two out of two.
I don't know how to get more.
More granola?
We should have more granola.
Let's see.
I wonder.
Oh.
Oh, maintenance under maintenance, maybe.
Mop upgrade.
Increases your mop.
Wait, that's big.
That's big.
That's pretty big.
Okay.
You get another after three stars.
Yeah, hiring level three.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
This is looking like a real park if i do say so myself oh my gosh there's gonna be so much to repair so much to clean is this been always crooked is this always been crooked all bad oops
didn't you unlock toilet level two
The hot dog stand is also crooked?
Oh.
Is that butter?
No, I think it's crooked.
I think I crookeded it the other way.
There we go.
No worries.
So this can fit one person or two?
I guess one.
But they sure are fancy.
Bronze on.
Thank you so much for the 50 gift.
Thank you.
Holy moly.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Wow.
Oh.
They can wash their hands now.
Let's build another set over.
Okay, Victor.
Get out of there.
Let's build another set over here.
Why did it do that?
Eh.
Like this.
Oh, they just need one.
Did you do two?
Oh, thank you for...
100!
Thank you!
Double 50!
I appreciate it so much.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
We'll keep this.
This will let the people know what they will have in the future.
keep spending money baby though i do need some more decoration as well so let's uh let's put some fountains we'll put one in the big pool
and we'll do oh we have some better umbrellas some bigger umbrellas bigger bigger umbrellas we have some umbrellas
You know, I'm actually, whenever I play like a simulation game like this, like even the Sims and stuff, decorating is my least favorite part.
I think it's because I'm not very good at it.
I'm just not, I don't really have that kind of sense, you know?
But we can add some more flowers too.
the flower beds are kind of nice we'll do like a planner around here or something I don't know we'll do a couple it'll look nice I think
just have fun with it yeah I try I try you know um this is looking cute though I'd like to say it looks pretty cute I think I think Excel?
I think it looks nice.
A little bit.
Let's also, let's get rid of these.
We're starting to lose.
We're starting to
um...
Because we got better umbrellas.
Oh my gosh!
Another?
Thank you!
Bronson, thank you so much.
How are we?
Thank you!
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, thank you so much.
Okay, I think that's all the...
Okay, so now we can include this.
And these are $80 each.
Woo!
Okay.
That's fine.
We'll make it back.
Eventually.
Probably.
We just gotta add a couple to get our, what's it called, up.
Our decoration up.
I'll add some over here too.
It looks legit.
It looks like a real park.
This is looking fantastic.
It's looking fancy.
Okay.
Now you build.
And then we sleep.
The granola will pay for it.
We're making more money, I don't know.
In the water park.
No!
Oh, my water park is...
We're swimming in cash.
Get it swimming because we're a water park.
We're swimming in it.
Okay, I think these don't add as much as I thought that they would, but that's okay.
We just need 200 more, I think.
Yeah.
We can work on it.
We still gotta turn away five perverts, so we won't get it immediately anyway.
Alright, sleep.
I D-D-D-I.
I don't get it.
Why not?
Did I repair everything?
You know, actually, I don't know if I did.
I'll be one of the five.
I need you guys to pull your weight, okay?
Perverts, assemble!
Everyone, pull your weight.
We need to get to three stars, okay?
We need to get the three stars stat.
With all our powers combined.
Perverts assemble!
Okay, I think I did repair everything.
Well, I think about it.
Oh, I can't place an attraction there.
I can...
I'm trying to get it closer to the vending machine.
You know what?
Screw it.
I don't care.
Ha!
Park is open!
Baby!
Milo!
Milo, wait, you know my park.
Milo, Milo, my park!
Milo, what are you doing?
Come on in, buddy.
Where are you?
Oh, he doesn't like it.
He doesn't want it.
Where are you going, Victor?
What?
Is my park old news now?
Imagine if they added Snake or Oz a lot in swimsuits.
Speedos!
You're also not supposed to be in here.
Whoa, what's up with all these cheaters?
Well, let's get rid of this one.
And then I'll empty the trash.
Oh.
Victor, get inside.
Doing my part.
Don't do that!
No, no, no.
I just need perverts who take pictures.
Oh my gosh, already?
I don't need perverts who do other things.
me have to clean up a bigger mess.
Kegan, welcome back to membership.
Thank you.
Uh-oh, wait.
I forgot to restock stuff.
Add lemon.
I think we still have...
We're fine for now.
Maybe.
Oh my gosh.
Brian's hot.
Thank you.
Please.
Your wallet.
Thank you.
Oh, please.
Gosh, our pool looks... Or our place looks huge now wait I think Xander is a pervert yes we got one what if we take pictures of the perverts doing that doing
what what are we taking pictures of oh poor welcome to my pleasure thank you what are we taking pictures of no wristband whoa
These look like lockers.
I can't get over.
Like, they don't look like bathrooms to me.
Victor, you don't need to go over there.
Victor, I don't need you over there.
Victor, I need you here.
Victor, Victor, lock in, please.
Oh.
Alfred, don't panic on my watch.
Ew, it really looks like poop water.
Oh, it looks like poop water.
Oh gosh there's
a second shower maybe we found another pervert the poop shoot real oh so
far everything's running pretty smoothly so far so good I mean we only have 16 people in there extra vitamins and minerals I wouldn't say it's vitamins minerals i would say it's um it's uh building your immune system
happy birthday it's not my birthday but thank you me
perverts add mustard i'm on the i'm listening for perverts they're loving it they're loving it it's not my birthday oh there's a shadow i thought it was this dirt.
Uh-oh.
Let's go get some more granola.
Woo-lo-lo.
Why are we woo-lo-lo?
Xander.
Mustard.
I came in, and the first thing I heard was poop water.
I mean, look at the slide!
What happened there?
Oh!
It just happened.
Victor again?
I highlighted on a person.
Miller!
For the birthday!
It's not my birthday!
Wait.
Annie did something naughty.
I caught a cheater.
Who are you cheating on?
Wait, I heard somebody.
was that it sounded like perverted noises I guess not just me sounded like he was like we gotta go get more hot dogs so many gifts today thank
you thank you thank you why so many gifts today what's happening
add lemon is it because my are these my tips because my park is so It's so awesome.
So stinking cool.
Oh, she's stinking bad.
Oh, he is.
No, they're stinking bad.
What happened?
Don't do it again.
Birthday presents.
No, nope.
Happy second birthday.
That's not my birthday.
This is...
bad i just peed oh my god
i like how the vandalism had its own uh what's it called
it had its own um someone drowning
oh shadows is what i was trying to say
serenity please go back to your perverted ways birthday no are you sure it's not your birthday I'm sure I'm positive so on my birthday I will be having my 3d debut concert I will I will
so you should come see that is
that October 1st yes my birthday is October 1st
Classic lounger, bro.
Which one?
There's so many loungers.
Which one, bro?
Wait, is this the glass?
No.
Oh, this one?
Must be that one.
Okay.
Decoration, and we need more perverts.
Everyone keep your eye out.
Okay.
lemonade ice another panic person it's not that scary come on don't move don't move don't move always on the lookout oh my bad sorry do you still want that lemonade case I messed up you did not wait it's not your Yeah, it's not my birthday.
It's not my birthday.
Wait.
Oh, sorry.
Wait, maybe you're the pervert.
Oh, wait, I need another bathroom here.
I saw a flash.
I saw a camera flash.
I think it's him.
Yes!
Callahan!
I caught a pervert.
Okay, nice.
Now we just need three more perverts.
Oh no, I was just about to do the hot dog, no!
Stinky trash.
I love the rag dolls.
Me too.
It's so good.
This game is so fun.
I'm not gonna lie.
Like, I know it's right now.
It's like the streamer game to play.
But it's legitimately addicting.
It's so fun.
Any more trash?
Maybe I should get the glowy trash one.
Maybe.
Happy Super Real Birthday.
Oh, thank you!
It's not my birthday!
I like how they stand with so much like...
Hmm.
You know?
I got that.
I was on that quick.
we gotta get more granola Sean wants a hot dog oh day is over streamer game derogatory I mean yeah
not my problem day is over I don't have to cater to you anymore I don't need to have my customer service smile on I don't need nothing where the hell is Victor like is he doing anything have you Have you guys seen Victor at all?
Hospital.
He's sleeping?
No, but I don't see him walking around at all.
Oh, there he is, just kidding.
My park is too big.
I can't even, I don't even remember my...
We're like too big of a corporation now.
I can't remember my employees' names, locations.
for somewhere.
No.
Please, no, I'm not ready.
I'm not ready.
Miss Big Shot over here.
Yeah.
Our park is, like, making it...
It's huge now, our park.
Happy unbirthday.
Oh, thank you.
Okay, hopefully...
Well, we only got two perverts today.
we get some more tomorrow.
I want to be in Freak City, baby.
New York.
Did I get this one?
Yeah.
Maybe they feel like this part, this like, this place is accounted for, you know?
They were too busy sending two for chance, the freaks?
Surely that's the
Perverts are welcome here, but also I will kick you out and take your money.
I will kick you out and take your money, but like lovingly, you know?
Oh wait, turn, turn, turn, turn.
Let's take you and put you here.
We'll put two here.
Wait, how do I snap?
Oh, shift.
There we go.
Okay.
Yeah.
Okay, one more.
That looks a little crooked, no?
Yeah.
There we go.
Okay.
Oh, I think I need to clean that one, too.
This one.
I've watched a few of these, and yours resembles a...
Actually resembles a water park.
Really?
You said I'm doing a good job?
Hot dog!
We're putting more decorations so that we can hopefully be able to get to prestige.
I'm being so proper with my park.
How do you not make a park?
How do you not make it look like a water park?
I think our place is pretty cute, though.
Oh my gosh.
It doesn't give us anything!
Ah!
If you leave the park yourself, does that count as kicking a pervert out?
I wish!
Does paint help?
Wait, I think it does.
I think you're right.
I think paint does help.
Uh...
Floor.
No space.
Uh, it was this color, right?
Wait.
Yes.
Does it?
Is it going up?
By one.
By a single point.
One point.
This is painful.
But since I have more money, I will finish it.
Okay, it doesn't double charge you, which is pretty nice.
I was thinking, I was like, wait a second, if I hold it, does it...
Will it charge me again?
But does not.
Okay, that area is completed.
Maybe I should do this area too, then.
Let's see, what can we do?
We'll do Blood Red.
What?
Wait, what?
Um, am I colorblind?
Oh, you can change the color!
Oh, that's just the material type!
My bad.
Whoa!
Holy moly!
That's intense.
Blood, blood, blood for the blood god.
Three color tabs too?
That didn't change at all.
Wait, what if I do like primary, red, secondary?
Wait, am I doing...
Am I mixing?
No.
It all looks the same.
Happy water park day, Minto!
I'm only peeking during lunch.
I hope the rest of the stream goes well.
Peep-peep-peep-oo!
No!
Don't pee me poo poo!
This looks horrible.
Oh, my eyes.
It looks so bad.
Excuse me.
The customers will never forget it.
That's for sure.
I'll be like, let's go to Bloodland!
Yeah!
You think it looks good?
No way?
Try black?
Let's see.
Wait, what a black stone would look like?
Wait, this place is kind of metal now.
Wait, we're actually at 400 already.
The void calls.
What?
Oh, sorry.
The floor is red.
You can hide the bloodstream.
It seems exactly, exactly.
We'll just do this for now.
That part.
I kind of want to add another pool.
I wish I could do a big one.
We'll just do the corner cut again.
Just like here.
And, uh...
We'll do a twisty slide.
A fun little twisty slide.
Yeah.
No,
twisty slide.
Twisty slide.
Twisty, there we go.
Will this allow more people?
Yes!
Hi.
We're at 413 out of 500?
Okay.
Can you fix the new slide?
Oh, no.
This one?
No, unfortunately.
Only demolish.
Here, we'll leave a little, we'll do a little pathway.
There we go.
Yeah.
And let's do a vending machine.
And some more trash cans.
Okay.
And, uh, decoration.
We could do some benches.
That's nice.
Hopefully that gives us a lot.
Okay.
I'm just out of money.
I can't even afford to stock my machine.
We're at 444!
So spooky.
Too much paint.
No, not enough paint.
I'm broke, baby.
Alright, I think I...
Well, let me restock stuff.
Oh, wait, can I?
Um...
I think I can only restock the lemonade.
Okay.
And that's it.
Welcome to Kmart.
Look everybody.
The park is brand new.
The red is so blind is so bad.
I missed a spot.
I actually hate it so much.
Oh.
Okay, we needed money.
I think someone did not.
did not pay.
You're gonna pay for my granola.
That's what you're gonna do.
Okay.
Let's go buy more granola.
Where'd you go?
And you're also gonna pay for granola.
Sorry.
Nice.
My eyes!
I might just, I just might need to change it.
Okay.
Alright.
On the lookout for perverts, everybody.
On the lookout for perverts, and, um, and, uh, Victor, don't be suspicious.
Oh, my eyes!
Ah, why?
We got one?
We got one, we got one.
Is that a pervert sound?
No, I was excited about it being clean sound.
All right, two more perverts.
Oh my gosh, it hurts my eyes.
Okay, we're going to change it.
We have the money.
What should we change it to?
Let's do...
Mint.
Who was the pervert?
No?
You?
I
got...
Wait.
Oh!
I don't like the material, though.
Oh my gosh, I keep pressing the wrong thing.
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Who?
You?
Now we need the decoration.
Actually.
I'm trying to figure out what I want to do with this, though.
What about this color for this one?
Why does the mint look so bad?
Whoops.
Sad.
It doesn't make a difference.
Oh, not bad.
It's way too bright.
Let's see this one.
It's kind of pink.
It's cute.
What?
Oh, the pink is cute.
Oh my gosh, sorry.
I keep pressing B instead.
Oh, I like this.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
Do I see the red and they're like, oh, wow.
Oh wow!
They're like, oof!
Don't like that.
The screen can only handle so much good looking mint at once.
That!
I like this like kind of muted pink.
It's like almost a salmon.
Classic lounger's dirty.
We'll clean it.
We got people waiting.
Hold on, this is an emergency.
A flesh pink!
To attract the purports!
It'll get them excited.
They'll see the fleshy color and be like, This reminds me of...
of skin!
You know?
Oh, I forgot to do this.
Oops.
I hope nobody was swimming in there.
Uh oh, we got people drowning.
The hot dogs make me hungry.
Okay, now we gotta work on our decoration.
And then we'll be a three stars!
Three star park!
Is that trash?
Oh, no, that's my thing.
Nice.
Stinky man!
You're right.
Good job, guys.
Ronin is drowning!
Where?
Oh.
No sense of urgency at all.
Ice.
Alright.
Now let's add a little bit more decoration over here.
Are you?
Beatrice!
I'm bullying her.
Wait, I think she likes it.
I think she likes it.
Another one?
Nope, not you.
Was it you?
Wow, the ladies are freaky today.
Goodness gracious.
Mark E.
Plyer?
What?
I have Mark E.
Plyer waiting for lemonade.
No pictures of him.
Oh my god!
Oh, he's buff.
Why is he so buff?
I love him.
I hear another pervert.
But honestly, I don't care that much anymore.
Where?
They're taking pictures somewhere.
I can't tell where, though.
Let's do some...
We'll do some...
Oh, wait.
I remember these don't...
Dang it.
I already bought it.
They're cheap.
They don't really give you anything, though.
We'll do some more trees.
we'll do some more trees for aesthetics uh flower but no maybe this the umbrella we'll just add some random umbrellas for aesthetics
he's really that jack that's based off of his real body
okay good job brailin well rested oh victor i thought you were customer stop slacking We're so close you guys Okay, just one more thing
Oops Three star park oh Sorry
We did it we made it to our goal Where are they Is it you?
No I'm just gonna push everybody at this point.
Is it you?
No, I rescued you from drowning.
No, neither of you.
Oop.
We did it!
Team!
Mm-hmm.
Add lemon.
What did you want?
Oh, just lemon in.
Okay.
I see more stank.
Ah, I'm tired now.
I'm ready for the day to be over.
Just one more hour.
This is the threest park I've ever done threed in.
Look at that!
Right there, and somebody's drowning.
Hold on, Brian.
We don't want people uncomfortable by the stench.
Where are you over here?
I'm tired now.
I'm tired.
It's almost been four hours.
Holy moly.
Oh wow
There's little tiny screams
Oops Sorry I didn't see you there Oh sorry
What would you like?
Add a lemon?
I got you And you want... Oh sorry Mark Eplot You're gonna throw in a nice tip for me, right?
With that good old YouTube money?
Why do you have a devilish face, Ronan?
I saved you from drowning and you're a cheater?
No!
Pound his butt.
Pound it in the butt at the water park.
Oh, we made it!
We did it.
We made it to three stars.
Ah.
Look at all this.
Short range taser.
Unlock a close range electric taser for quick non-lethal non-lethal crowd control.
What else we got here?
Even more Pinka of vendor training.
Baseball bat.
Each park manager should at least have one Why is it $3,000?
Poster marketing?
Oh, that's what the poster is.
Resort pools!
We're almost to the pools.
Keep the paths cleaner and safer by minimizing the amount of water left behind.
Wait, that's kind of huge too.
Look at that.
And I'm going to the resort pools.
I can't afford them right now, but...
Perhaps Minto was the third star all along.
It's made from oak wood imported straight from heaven.
Lifeguard staff.
I'm not buying any more staff because I still have...
Wait!
Maintenance?
Hiring level 3.
We need the modern showers.
Okay, now we can get one more person.
I want the taser.
Victor.
Whoa, break it down now!
Whoa, go!
It's...
Braylin, Braylin, Braylin, Braylin, Braylin, Braylin, Braylin, Braylin, Braylin, Braylin, Braylin!
Don't go in there.
I received a fine!
She's not even in my park!
Oops.
Is she fine?
She's caked up, that's for sure.
She's fine.
I saw it and said it was non-lethal.
even die they don't even die by by my hammer pacifica ocean look at the way they go crazy oh my god she's splits splits city baby oh she must be fine nobody is paying attention to her
oh well guys this was a lot of fun sorry i'm so sleepy and i'm hungry now Oops.
Oh, I can't believe we got to the fourth, I mean the third star.
And now wrote to the fourth star, use the printer to print out flyers and give them to pedestrians out of 20.
Okay, okay.
But this was fine.
Three stars!
Woohoo!
And we got a taser.
You can use it on yourself in the pool.
It's the ultimate form of expression.
Every day I understand him a little bit more.
I enjoyed my stay.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Congrats on your three-star park.
Also super high for your 3D debut concert on your real birthday.
Yeah!
I'll keep advertising it.
And once I have like...
The art and everything.
I'll make like a fly of waiting room and everything.
Why did I say fly or a thing?
Ailey's stream report.
3K had TY for the stream.
Wait.
3K had granola.
Oh, the thought.
Granola thought.
3K had very cute thought.
Undisclosed had pervy thoughts.
Zero had negative thought.
5 out of 5 stars.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you all.
Have a good day, have a good night, and I will see you when I see you next time.
Otsumito!
Bye-bye!
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye.
Bye-bye-bye.