Oh Boo
Boo Hello everybody Hello Hello Wow, baby Koi, thank you so
much for the gifted Let me see I wonder if chat will behave
today Not you guys, but I rather I wonder if you two will
behave today We shall see?
We shall see?
No, we won't.
Yes, you will.
We always behave.
Yeah, it's not you guys.
It's not you, it's me.
It's my birthday!
Channel Land, happy birthday!
Base the cake?
Wait, bake the base...
Bear...
Bake the cake based on me.
How does that work?
Misbehavior would never...
I know.
Looking for some good skews.
Looking for some good skews?
Is there something you could recommend me?
Oh, boy, golly, do I have some?
Also, no.
The minkees on the bus go boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo
the minkees on the bus go boo boo boo All through the town
Um, it might be harder, you guys are gonna have to tell me
for sure how sound is today because I have a double ear
infection, yuppie!
So I cannot wear headphones I'm hearing through my speakers.
And hopefully...
Hopefully...
You...
It is not too loud or too quiet or whatever.
Just tell me and just let me know.
And, uh...
Might need to be in my ears today.
I'm always on my best behavior.
Make of that what you will.
She can't hear.
I got four ears that I can't hear.
What is the point?
Hiyasu, thank you so much for the fun Good day Yeah
But Yeah We're gonna We're gonna chill with Virtual Rewind
and then later on Today's double stream because I will also
be on Denzatsu.exe channel We're celebrating our Half Half
year anniversary six month anniversary and we have some cool
stuff to share so um yeah that's what we'll do yeah yeah
been feeling sick all weekend if i could give you a feel
better bean to help your ears could you give me one in
return yeah but are you going to virulent yeah well soon
ninky's ears thank you i got lots of juice in there and it's
just kind of sloshing around.
Too much juice.
Too much ectoplasm.
My ectoplasm is a little runny, maybe.
Who knows?
Thank you, RJ.
My kamiyoshi never half does things.
Hit both ears.
Yeah.
Feel better, babe!
Wait.
Here, I'm gonna take a little...
I'm gonna take a little cough drop real quick.
This is for everybody who's not feeling good.
Feel better.
Beep!
Oh no.
I'm dissolving now.
I'm disintegrating.
I sent all my health.
Actually, I don't really have any health.
I sent it all to you guys.
And now I am nothing.
Oh, I tried to eat the cough drop.
Happy happy anniversary to you and to the girls telling you
now since I won't be able to catch the density stream live.
Thank you, volume.
Thank you.
At the next convention, ear juice.
Nasty.
How easy.
Welcome back.
I wonder what ear juice would taste like.
I don't know.
I feel better already.
Thank you, Anki.
Of course.
That's the opposite effect!
It would taste bad.
I've never tasted earwax before.
Has anybody here?
Be honest, I'm not judging.
Feel better be him!
I'm sending the health back to you!
No!
As a child?
I was never curious.
By accident, no good.
Oh, it's sour!
It's a bit better.
Better butter, butter, butter, butter, butter, butter,
better, better.
If you bought some earwax butter, better, it would be
bitter.
It's your simple eye.
Welcome back.
Thank you.
Earwax contains bacteria.
What kind?
Get better soon.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Like a Nintendo Switch cartridge.
I have gotten curious enough to lick that.
But, like, to be fair, crawling into ears finally caught up.
No!
Okay, to be fair, with the cartridge thing, they were so...
They kind of, like, they striped and affected it, you know,
where they were like, just be sure you don't lick the
cartridge because you're not gonna like it.
It's a really disgusting taste.
Well, you brought that up first!
I wasn't thinking of licking the cartridge until you said
something.
So, I...
I am excused.
It's our turn to crawl.
You have to crawl before you can walk.
Haven't been able to catch a stream in a bit.
Well, thank you for a whole year!
Tango, welcome back!
thank you hello hello they made you lick the cartridge they
did
they made those switch two cartridges even spicier switch
two cartridges are just covered in in spices it's funny
because there are none everything is digital download now
sad hold on one second i
have to make sure no cat is in my room.
Minto got a successful surgery last May 27th.
I brought the Minto plushie beside me for good luck.
Hope you get well soon too.
Top!
I'm glad your surgery was a success.
Congratulations!
Now I want to try a Switch 2 cartridge.
Everybody, welcome back to membership to HQ!
Never got to this you're one of the most talented vtubers
out there i don't do anything your streams are super
entertaining but the combos i land on while tuning in or
something else well thank you sir simple i'm glad you think
so we we go through a variety of thoughts here some thoughts
should remain inner thoughts but if i don't Say them out
loud, how would you know?
If I kept everything in my brain, who would you talk to?
Swamp Gans.
Thank you so much for the tech gifted.
The voices.
Tri-Princess, I don't know if this came through yet, but
thank you so much for the energy.
Beam!
Thank you!
Oh, we feel better too!
See, Minto has thoughts sometimes.
31 months!
Holy cow, Splatoon!
Holy cow, thank you!
Yeah, you've known me long enough that I have thoughts
sometimes.
We love your inside thoughts.
Thanks.
Okay, well soon.
Thank you, none.
Back from my honeymoon.
I don't know what was good.
Welcome back.
How about cookies in the shape of cartridges?
Like those!
Oh my gosh, the Pillsbury ones.
The sugar cookie.
I'm obsessed with those.
I got some Spider-Man ones recently.
I got Spider-Man cookie.
recently but yeah if you had them just in the shape of a
cartridge instead that might be kind of awesome that might
be kind of awesome I think I got into the college I wanted
to so I'm sending this in advance to thank you for helping
me with your VODs during long study hours come off
congratulations it's very simple I thank you so much for the
tag it did wow there's so many people coming back is it
because it's the first of the last end of the month thank
you everybody you are a talented ghost you sing you
entertain but most important you bring energy and smiles to
all we appreciate you always mean don't thank you try for it
so much thank you i love the ghost-shaped ones they remind
me of my favorite video room i love the ghost ones because
they're ghosts and they're also Which is so delicious.
Is it getting spuder powers?
No, but they kind of looked like an alien if it had
Spider-Man's mask on its head.
You know what I mean?
Howdy, Minto, howdy!
Hold on, I think I took a picture.
But they really do look like an alien.
If the alien put on the mask.
You know what I mean?
Do you know what I mean?
Where are those photos?
Ugh!
Sorry.
Oh.
Never mind.
I don't want to share because my pan is ugly.
Wait!
I can just... I can just... Hold on.
I'm gonna crop him.
Wait.
Hold on.
No show eyes.
But my pan is ugly.
It's old and ugly.
Oh, I am being instructed to tell everybody.
Um, that Mint Phantom, Mint, I hope you're feeling better.
This was in all caps, by the way.
I hope you're feeling better.
Would you be okay plugging the Spring Densetsu Beasties
merch on today's stream since it's the last day?
No pressure if you don't want to, though.
Today is the last day to get the...
The Densetsu...
The Densetsu Beasties Spring merch and voice pack.
Today is the last day, if you are so interested.
Okay, what was I doing?
Oh, Spider-Man.
And then we'll play the game.
Because we are on a bit of a time limit today.
Due to the fact that I have a second stream later.
But that's exciting stuff.
I'm so excited.
You don't know what I'm excited for.
I'm excited to hang out with Phoebe and Vicky.
Does Min-Tao eating ghost cookies count as today's
cannibalism engine?
No.
They're not possessed, maybe.
So, hi, Min-Tao.
Feel better to be.
Thank you, Kavu.
Thank you.
Insanely smooth segue.
That was so organic.
What a talent you are.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, there it is.
Yes, Setsuna.pro.
For the goods.
Forgivment.
I need my Ace Combat merch.
That's understandable.
Don't worry about it.
Okay, hold on.
Spider-Man incoming.
Well, actually, hold on.
Let me do this.
Let me crop it.
Or wait, I have a better idea.
If I do this.
I mean, I can still crop it.
I'll crop it.
Okay, and then I fill it in.
Paintbrush.
Oh, wait, that doesn't work.
Okay, wait.
Wait.
Have you guys ever used a photopia before?
photopia photopie photopie photopie pea I have switched to
that instead of photoshop I'm in first time watcher here
what kind of cool merch can I expect to see in the Denzatsu
BC Spring Merch Collection oh thank you so much Ray Mack
Channel for your question uh Sensuna
There is such merch as...
An acrylic stand and...
Whoa, what is that?
Shikishi Artboard.
Whoa.
And...
Wow, you can get artboard and...
A voice pack.
Wow!
Or you could just get the voice pack.
Standalone.
$5.
Wow!
It's also on sale.
Oh no, you can also get everything by itself.
I'm a liar.
You can get the standard by itself too.
And the Shikishi by itself too.
Oh, I like Piyas.
It's so cute.
I was I was I saw Barry's butt today okay spider-man it says
spider-man do you guys like spider-man or spiders man okay
this one looks the most like alien so we're going with this
guy
okay okay i got him i got him i got him okay export as
spider-man okay save image okay here we go Three, two, one!
Yahoo!
All right.
Shall we play Retro Rewind?
Okay.
Thank you for our fun documentos!
nice to see you and then to the girls having speedy recovery
for you also i'm sick no not the con sickness thank you so
much for coming to see me thank you it is kind of alien
you're right i told you all i told you all he looks like an
alien more like spider deadpool
that's funny feel better all right last time we played
Ah, oh, the smell.
What was your name?
Wait, we got rid of Ryan.
Anna!
Anna, you're not going to go turn into a fairy goddess, are
you?
I think I hear a phone ringing.
Song for my ghost.
People are already requesting things.
Busy day.
Yeah, she's going to become a forest goddess.
I'm ready to push.
She's ready to push today.
You miss Ryan?
What are you talking about?
Our store is like super awesome too.
Look, there's...
We have really customers.
We have customers that are so cute.
Now I saw someone say that maybe we got some more stuff.
Maybe there was an update.
Missing string table entry.
Now I don't know what those are with no spoilers to the
podcast after your meet and greet phoebe spoiled me
important podcast information when i did the next meet and
greet with her my excitement was spoiled so please tell her
tell her off at the collab also remind your podcast is
dollar every month so go watch
wait what did she say about the podcast now i'm confused My
poor dog is sick too, she has an ear infection.
No, I'm not a dog, I'm a cat!
I hope your dog feels better.
Wait, what are these?
Let's see what else we got.
Whoa!
Missing string table entry!
Ooh, missing string table entry!
Oh my gosh, cactus!
Yo!
Wait, this is crazy, actually.
Is this just a...
Wait, this looks like something for your living room.
Why are we...
Why...
Why in my place?
We have new stations, so it ended before, I think, at the
Cotton Candy Machine.
Now we have Missing String Table Entry, and also Missing
String Table Entry.
This looks like a repair!
I don't know what this is, actually.
Yeah.
Minto, could you scream laser beams so that I could sync it
up to when I fight people in Elite Dangerous?
I did!
I did scream!
You're a cat, weren't you a ghost maid?
How about check the ears?
Advertising board.
Did somebody just roar?
That was strange.
Oh, it's a missing string table entry o'clock even.
I think something... Oh, what's this?
Oh, you're out here!
Oh my gosh, this is just in the way now.
This is kind of... Oh, but they'll see it!
I don't have to hand out!
I won't have to hand out flyers anymore, I think.
Yes?
things a little borked maybe yeah i think perhaps are you
finished no you're sure taking your time though oh um oh and
here's the repair desk yeah anything new here so there
really was an update that's so fun i think right now anna is
our best she loves the king beyond the rainbow Wow.
Ryan would have finished 10 minutes ago.
No he would not have and do not delude yourself into
thinking so.
I have $530.
Maybe.
We could buy, uh, wait, do we have any new movies coming out
or anything?
New movie tomorrow.
We'll save our money.
We'll just collect more money today.
Um...
And Aibu.
More Aibu.
I'm a nice seeing...
Nice meeting you again.
But I got to show you my mint plush and denser to Yixi pen
line.
Yes!
Thank you, Thomas!
Oh, thanks for seeing me again!
Love to check you too!
Thank you, I saw you posted it.
Thank you so much.
Hmm.
We got rated?
Welcome, everybody.
Welcome to...
The coolest place you've ever been to.
Look at that, look at that, look at that.
And who ordered the hot tea?
This is our sexy area besides the drama.
But drama can be sexy too.
Tis himself!
Thank you.
So much for the...
Gifted, thank you!
Am I crazy or did I hear like a...
You know?
Wait, let's move these a little over.
Hello?
Promotional poster or swag for sale, the movie Nuclear Smoke
Warfare.
We do?
I think I just lied to that person.
Are you guys hearing it too or is it just me?
You guys are hearing it, right?
I think I heard a dog.
Hello, everybody.
Hello!
Thank you!
Oh, thank you guys so much for the Gifted 2!
Tucky, thank you!
The Spurs advanced to their finals to face the Knicks.
Thank you, Mint.
I did it!
I did all of that!
Thank you!
Phil, thank you!
Paperbacks, thank you, Ross and Glitchface, thank you!
Thank you guys so much.
Maybe it's IRL?
I don't think so.
Anyway, that's fine.
We have our fancies here.
Oh, I forgot.
Mint, I gotta tell you, you're my second favorite VTuber.
The first one is...
You died!
Before you could say it!
Alright, let's...
Are you done?
So close.
Almost there.
Okay, um...
I think we're good for now.
We'll do some rearranging after we get more money and stuff,
I think.
first B-Tuber.
Can we do it?
Okay, the expansions are still the same, it seems, so...
Hmm.
Alright.
Put you assign a job.
We're putting you on checkout.
Yes, sir.
Galactic happy birthday!
Happy, happy birthday!
Come to my house.
I mean, not my house.
Sorry, my store.
Don't come to my house.
What if my address was just on the...
What if it was just on the flyer?
Everybody's...
Everybody come on over?
Aibu has taste.
Wait, what?
Has taste a fan of a missing string table chat.
Holy cow.
There's so many people.
What do you mean you don't have time for this?
You have time for a nice lovely little stroll through the
town.
And not enough time to check out our super awesome store.
Venmo app.
Thank you for the gifted.
Oh yes, yes, you called this morning.
A song for my ghost.
How was that?
You liked it.
We'll start checking these in too.
Ah, busy day.
Busy day.
Um, it just started.
Um, seeing a manager?
I did the drop the movie in the bathtub.
I thought BHS tapes were waterproof.
Hmm.
You're running a business.
Yes, I am, ma'am.
Yes, I am.
Sci-Fi.
Well, our business is booming.
You see all these people in here?
Action.
Horror.
Drama.
We gotta probably...
Hello.
Shipmate hacker.
I think we gotta move like the action and the kids away
because they're both blue when I get confused.
Why would someone bring a VHS tape?
I don't think it was the toilet.
I think it was their like their actual bathtub.
But that also begs the question, why would they do that too?
Why she got the VHS?
Yeah.
I'm a little confused.
I am intrigued but confused.
Paige!
I know you're trying to save cash, but here's some SKUs.
Thank you!
Give me a second.
Fantasy.
Why are there so many people wanting to see the manager?
Hello?
Christmas.
I'll be home for Christmas.
Hmm.
Yes?
$2 late fee.
Toadstool for Christmas.
That sounds... that sounds edgy.
Because they're all carons.
Who needs to eat anyway?
Take two.
I gotta tell you this.
You're my second favorite VTuber.
The first one is missing string table entry!
I can't compete.
How can I compete against such perfection of missing string
table entry?
I don't blame I blame you.
I blame myself for not being good enough.
I don't blame you for falling in love.
Die trying.
You reserved that?
Isn't that the new movie?
Missing no is the original.
Oh, those two twins were like having a psychic conversation
with each other.
They were just standing there staring.
Today a monk stopped me on the train and told me ghosts need
love and not exorcisms.
Then he gave me a flyer with the address of your channel.
I mean, if you want to come to the maid cafe, that's fine.
That sounds like some like a protest.
Love, not exorcism.
Why am I losing money?
I just saw in minus three.
Um, pajama movie night with the girls.
I want something awful that we can quote and laugh at all
night.
Got a bad movie.
Okay, action bad.
A bad action.
Wait, oh, uh, that's good, good action.
Some bad act.
Oh, trooper lost at sea.
Or the fairy's last dog fight?
Okay, that one's awesome.
This one is great.
She needs to go to the bathroom!
Oh my god.
Hello!
Wait!
What?
Excuse me!
Ryan actually would never.
That one's my favorite.
Isaac, you have such good taste.
Oh, 50 cent, dude.
There you go.
You're free to go.
She's back.
Get to work.
Yes?
The dragon bombers.
Ryan would actually never.
I think I'm already regretting this.
I feel like I'm already regretting my decision.
Oh, man.
I'm regretting my decision to fire Ryan.
More kids moving.
Okay.
fantasy action action action action kid action did Ryan
graduate no maybe he did a little bit oh hello die trying do
you have a copy maybe oh you're so lucky man that's This guy
literally was reaching for it.
I hope you're feeling better.
I visited the Smithsonian Aerospace Museum in Virginia last
week.
I even saw an F-14, F-18, SR-71.
He was in an Ace Combat.
Wait, that's so awesome!
I didn't know the Smithsonian had something like that.
Brian wanted me to tell you that he's been reduced to acting
in T-Rex films.
He's willing to forgive.
What do you mean reduced to?
That sounds like the actual dream.
I think everybody would be thrilled to be acting the hot dog
of Christmas legend.
Acting in T-Rex films.
I'm just saying.
Yes.
Yeah.
Yes, yes.
Double, triple yes.
May I help you?
Drama movie.
Someone who's lonely.
Let's give him...
The barrel separation.
Ryan would have gone in his pants like a real store
employee.
He kept asking for those raises so he could buy new pants!
I can't wait to see you at AX.
I mean, don't stay fresh.
See you there!
I will be at Iron Mouse's booth.
New pants!
Oh good, we're making lots of money though.
This is awesome.
Good.
Oh that's maybe what I've been hearing.
When do I get the, uh, let's see.
This missing string table entry.
Let's see when we get it.
It's actually a mystery.
Um.
Actually, I'm not sure.
Seems like you get it at missing string table entry.
Must be.
It must be.
Oh, I repaired it!
Oh, I could just do it.
Never mind.
I guess we already...
I repaired it!
Oh, wait.
We just... We just get it.
Maybe I'm already at high enough of a level.
This is a protest to bring back Ryan.
We need Ryan.
I don't know what that guy is doing now.
If he applies, we'll see.
Holy cow, people are still, like, browsing.
So now...
Missing string table entry or missing string table entry.
Oh my god.
Who approved this update?
We'll go with, uh, this one.
How exciting.
Oh.
How did that get on the ground?
Who threw my...
Who threw that on the ground?
So freak-y.
Oh, great.
We still have a...
A super long line of people.
Oh my god, it's Ryan!
He came back!
He said I can't stay away from this, but I can't be mad.
I can't stay mad at you.
Wait, there were some movies that I kept.
Because I wanted to repair them.
The graveyard.
The saucy snake delivery.
Oh!
Oh, oh, whoa!
Wait, this is kind of... This is... This is pretty fun.
Uh...
Oh, I have to cut this now?
Why?
Oh, we just erased a chunk of the movie.
Wait a sec!
Um...
Okay.
No one watches the credits.
Yeah, exactly.
Exactly.
Satan and his hot dog.
Oh my gosh.
That's so funny.
It's like, that's a pretty sizable chunk of the movie we
just got rid of.
Why did we think that was how we should repair it?
Give us the idea.
My ghosts only regret.
We'll never know because we're literally cutting out the
ending.
Whatever, who cares?
Who watches movies?
It's a TV edit.
True, true, true, true.
Oh.
We'll grab- Oh, actually.
Hold on.
I was going to say, we'll do these ones tomorrow, but I'm
already on this one.
We'll do that one tomorrow.
The last one for sure.
She played as the dot.
Oh, oh, that's your lie in April.
That's why we kept it.
Okie dokie.
Good job, team.
Total of $551.
This is why the video store died.
the ghost that haunts them because we have the movie off.
Refrigerator!
Missing string table entry.
New movie.
Oh, she's got a pipin' her stuff.
She's ready to make some cash.
Let's see.
Refrigerator.
Oh, that's a lot of money.
Holy cow.
$400.
Oh, wait.
Let me put her on the movie return.
Wait.
Anna.
Assign a job.
Return station.
Missing Super Chat table entry.
No!
What is our new movie?
Draconic Park?
We are getting all the bangers, you guys!
How many did I...
Let's get like 20 or something.
Yes!
we got die trying and now we have draconic park this is
awesome
can i put you like right there no can i put you right here
yes oh yeah oh my god it's awesome and it totally is perfect
for our Retro Rewind!
Wait, who the hell are you?
Where's...
What happened to the name of my store?
Whose store is this?
Wait!
Who are you?
What?
Dogs and dine.
nose.
There we go.
The store store.
Who...
Who even changed...
I've got vandalized or something.
Someone just came in and...
And took over.
Quiet time with the dinosaur.
Okay.
That's the part where it got really loud.
We just trimmed out the bits that...
It's the director's cut.
Government error, maybe.
Oh, we got three...
No, we got two shinies.
Holy cow.
You cut out the best part of the movie.
No, I didn't.
Uh-oh.
Wait.
Wait a second.
Wait, oh, wait a second.
Release the minto cut.
This is still consider new, yeah.
Did I buy too many?
Bronson!
Thank you so much for the 20, Yuta!
Thank you!
Oh.
I'll just leave them on the ground here.
Okay, perfect.
Let's help her out.
Let's help a girl out.
Uh-oh.
Wait, there's even more of them?
Dang, he finished with that movie already.
Oh, sorry.
We just rented the...
That, uh...
T-Rex.
Fantasy.
Fantasy, fantasy, Christmas.
Fantasy, fantasy.
Adult.
Who ordered the hot T-Rex?
The most sought after movie that we probably have, honestly?
Christmas.
Drama.
Is that late?
Is that what that said?
She's right behind me, eventually.
She's awfully tall.
Drama, drama.
Adult.
Retirement with my hot dog.
Diver brain implants.
Uh, we have more horror.
Uh-oh.
Okay, to the mixed shelf you go.
Cois mois, cois mois.
Are we ready to open Anna?
Oh, we are just about ready!
Uh-oh.
I have $518.
I wonder if I should buy a fridge.
But I wonder...
I guess it's like we sell sodas and stuff.
I won't be able to really fill it, I think.
We won't really be able to fill it.
And also...
Um...
Yeah, I won't leave much ready cash left over.
Yeah.
I'm wondering...
Maybe we get like another shelf or something.
Some more stuff for in here.
And it's also...
Saturday.
Ooh, what's happening that day?
Valentine's Day?
What?
Yes, everybody knows that Valentine's Day is in December on
the 10th, obviously.
Huh?
Winter 10th.
Yes.
I feel like more shells would be best option this is pretty
cool too though oh the camera or like immersion hmm i like
these lights too they're pretty nice level 15 i think we're
at 13 now 14.
okay cool we'll be able to buy it soon for now we'll just
stick with what we got all right to check out
i want to see how this this this works
not very well apparently he walked right by wait hold on
we'll wait for somebody okay this guy he knows nothing about
my store he's definitely not belining for it okay
uh uh uh everybody's got in their hands uh uh You know
nothing?
You know...
You know nothing?
Okay, watch.
Watch him see the sign and get interested.
You?
What did I pay this?
What did I pay for this?
Um...
Hello.
Officer Bloodbath.
Hi, wife.
Hi, Dasko!
I help you.
Had fun in Germany!
Die trying.
Yes, we do.
have a copy.
It's literally right in front of you.
Use your eyes and your arms.
Oh, did she go to the bathroom again?
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry for her negligence.
Oh, Mount Dew.
I tried to cheat this guy.
It was so hot.
I heard there was a heat wave.
$4.
Where did she go?
What is she doing?
in there.
These dang kids on their phones.
Wait, why am I doing cash register?
Oh, there she is.
Of course.
Anna.
On her smoke break.
She's a good girl.
She doesn't smoke.
Probably.
Reserved.
Oh.
Oh, wait, uh, uh, how do I throw again?
Where'd it go?
Wait, where did it go?
Oh, I lost it.
Wait, I actually, it was in my hands, but I lost it.
Um, broken.
It's okay, it's less dramatic now because we, we know we
can, what the heck?
Where did it go?
That was weird.
One second.
But it... I wanted to fix it, but it disappeared.
Gone.
Reduced to atoms.
Curtain fall over my...
What?
What does that even mean?
Who comes up with these?
Oops, sorry.
so sorry someone's calling I asked my hotel for a fan they
said no what the heck they can say no song for my ghost this
one's popular tape retrieval button make it oh there's a
button wait what is the button I know you could get tapes
back but i didn't know there was a tape retrieval button
that's fancy
you don't like pizza i don't like people wasting my i don't
like pizza wait i don't like people with pizza wasting my
time okay just you guys understand
you guys understand oh my gosh Drama.
Sci-fi.
Oh, wait.
Not in sci-fi yet.
Right?
Drama.
Sci-fi.
There we go.
Wait.
Did I mess it up?
Oops.
Drama.
Sci-fi.
People pizza.
Clocked.
55.
No!
It doesn't count!
Reserve die trying.
Yes, you did.
Here we go.
Hello?
The movie was working fine when I dropped it off.
I won't pay your broken fee.
I'm charging you the fee.
I never say no to the money.
I charge people the fee every time.
Honestly, it's worth it.
I don't care if they get upset.
What's the point of trying to pick up the movies in a
certain way?
in order if they just get mixed up in my hands anyway.
Blur-er.
Kid.
We had some funny kid ones.
I do remember that.
Boise.
Moise.
Action.
Boise.
Yacht power up.
Kids.
F them kids.
You don't need my help.
Oh!
Oh, I'm so asleep, we did so today, everybody.
Oh, I could use a nap.
Anna, take over.
Real maturation.
What if I actually just took a nap, though?
Unless?
Haha, I wouldn't do that.
And this?
So hyped for the anniversary, I can't sleep.
What do you mean?
Don't you should sleep if you need to sleep.
Action.
Fantasy.
Yes?
Oh.
Nope.
That's the...
Keep working.
Charge the feed.
Yes, the last dinosaur.
There.
Alright.
Sleeping stream sounds good.
Tell me to have a copy of No Cask on the farm.
I guess I do.
Oh, it's the last one!
Oh, not quite.
No Cask on the farm.
Surringe with flying colors.
Paige, I will get to your SKUs by the way.
the way once uh once we're done with the work day yeah the
store is like popping off like craziness it's so difficult
being a business owner i have so much to manage and i'm too
cheap to properly pay my employees and to hire more oh look
at my manager she's literally sleeping on the job She's kind
of cute though, so maybe it's okay.
I mean...
Nobody would notice, probably.
If I fell asleep.
Probably no one would notice.
Fantasy.
Romance.
Eye action.
Oh, mixed.
Or...
I mean, don't look adorable as usual.
I, too, am sleepy, because it's a rainy day.
Oh, yeah, makes me sleepy, too.
Oh, I really do feel like I'm about to pass out, though.
This game is too comfy.
Like, you kind of get into a trance with it, you know, and
you're just like...
Let's go see some SKUs.
We've got.
1, 0, 5, 8, 2, 8, 2, 3.
The dog.
My soulmate.
Well, bad critic.
Bad critic.
1, 8, 2, 1, 2, 4, 1, 2.
Tastes the dinosaur season.
Literally every day.
One, eight, zero, six, three, five, four.
The hot dog waiting for Santa.
Oh, I already own this one.
Oops.
We'll put it on the for sale.
Six, seven, eight, two, two, nine, three.
The ghost lost in space.
Good finds.
Tis the dinosaur season.
Into the movie for sale.
I don't want to lose another Oshita space.
Space is kind of scary like that.
There's black holes in things.
Did he just throw stuff on the...
Rude!
Where's my gun?
Look at him.
Look at his bad attitude walking away.
And stay out!
She's the one that reserved this movie.
Is she also?
Did she also get mad?
She did!
What's with these Karen's today?
She also reserved that movie.
Something in the water.
Speaking of space, did you see the rocket that exploded on
the ground?
on the launch pad.
I did.
I don't know anything about it, except that I just saw a
video of it happening.
And I was like, Whoa.
Whoa.
That's crazy.
Okay, so we've completed all the stations.
That's good.
Frigilator.
We can buy that, probably.
Er...
Hmm.
I hope we can get to level 15, but probably not for another
two days.
do you have a wall of banned customers man we need one i
would put it right it would be all here good job good work
anna i'm gonna assign you to the return station so that you
can do that all right let's see here we still have maybe i
will get the fridge you know what i'm gonna get the fridge
big money spent it's kind of i feel like a real business
owner right now we'll put it down here for now and inside we
can put turbo cop soda top sip we need all top sip Gridline
grape.
Wait, that matches our aesthetic, though.
Beetleburst lemonade.
Deep Space Dew.
Snake Pit Soda!
Wait, these are great!
Neon Rain Cola.
Jelly Melon Soda.
Alright, top sip on the left.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, wait.
I guess we could do more, huh?
Gridline grape?
Snake pit soda?
Snakes.
Why do I have to be snakes?
Can I get rid of this?
Oh, yeah, we can remove that one.
Okay, cool.
And we'll do neon rain cola.
Ooh, that's kind of satisfying.
That's a satisfying town.
Nice.
Ah yeah!
For no particular customer service related reason.
Do you have a preferred shotgun from any game or movie?
I don't know.
Which of these films would you say looks the best?
Oh it's been rented.
Who ordered the hot T-Rex?
Looks the best I'd say.
Doom shotgun.
It's a classic.
All right, wow, we made more money that day today though.
I don't think there was anything today.
Oh, whoops, wrong room.
Nothing today.
Free day, free day.
New day and new rentals, let's go!
Okay, she's like, she's always just walking so excitedly.
Halo 1 Shotgun.
Well, I've never played Halo, so...
Your signboard is probably set to more custom.
Oh, that's true!
I guess we did.
Technic...
Maybe we did get some more, and I just didn't realize.
Hmm.
This is still considered new.
But not as new.
So to the bottom shelf with the...
want to play Halo one day.
Let's drive.
Guys, I'm gonna get a coffee because I think I'm about to
disintegrate.
My spiritual energy is so low.
I'll be right back.
Guys, I was a little sneaky.
And I got a donut too.
Well,
Nothing but it's a doughnut and coffee.
Yeah.
I could go for a doughnut.
It's doughnut day.
It's glazed doughnut.
Glazed.
Let's restock these as well.
My Crunch Zillas.
My Freddy cheese sticks.
our junior mints wait I think the bottom were dino gummies
so those go crazy people go crazy for those alright nice do
you like jam filled donuts I like any kind of donut I think
donut day is next week you fibber what do you mean every day
is a donut day
meaning every day is a great day for donuts
that's what i say
oh reserved awesome let's get these new ones out of the way
oh she's right behind me isn't she she doesn't even look at
me she's so so little respect i don't even want any donuts I
mean, it's terrible, the donuts.
Disgusting, probably.
Oh, wait.
Let's throw all of these on the ground.
Okay.
They're really bad.
Not fun to eat.
Also, thank you guys for all the super chats while I was
gone.
Thank you.
And, uh...
Um...
Nah, well, thank you so much for the five gifted.
Thank you, guys.
Mm-hmm.
She's lurking.
She's stalking.
Oh.
How did I get up here?
I don't know.
What happened to me?
I was gone.
I fell asleep.
And I got on.
How did that happen to me?
How did this happen?
Alright.
I'm gonna order.
I'm gonna order some more.
shell I don't know I mean I know these are decorations but
they look so nice no why is there a chair to watch the movie
right right here is really close
okay Anna has taken her good sweet time we're gonna help her
out a bit even know technically she's supposed to be good
and fast she's just bad I've never had a good employee
except Ryan decorations bringing more customers does it now
we could this area needs some spruce and I'd say
everybody would want to come in wait I have an idea
Let's, let's decorate a Christmas area.
Uh, yeah.
Let's, let's, uh, what I'm going to do is start putting some
shelves down here.
This is supposed to be our adult section, but, but it is
what it is.
Is it the standard one?
Which one are these?
Four, one, two, yeah, four rows.
This must be standard, right?
Wait, oh no.
Okay, good.
Oops, I messed it up.
I was hoping it would tell me what kind of...
Okay.
Shells.
Standard 4.
Okay, yeah.
One, two, three, four?
Okay.
That's quite a bit you're probably thinking.
Holy cow.
but hear me out you know we'll start not decorating but
putting stuff in this area
like so and then we'll get some decorations when we can
afford it but shelves are like a bigger priority I'd say
shelves are a bit of a bigger priority
these will all be filled with adult films soon all right so
that's see that's looking a little more filled out already
and um uh we can probably buy one decoration nice yeah nice
some sexy love balloons
oh yeah oh Oh!
Yes!
Put the curtain up to keep out the kids.
Nice!
So we have drinks.
And this guy.
Awesome.
Can we get, like, I'm wondering if we should get some more,
like, signs and stuff.
There we go.
Okay.
I love the Ibu statue so much.
Me too!
It's so cute.
Come, come, come.
Check out.
I'm already feeling a little bit more awake.
Maybe I just needed to stand up for a second.
Good stuff.
Come, come, come.
You love movies, beam!
Oh.
I can't believe we're still working on missing string table
entry.
It's kind of crazy.
We need a sign that says missing string.
We have, unfortunately, we have default text.
Not unfortunately.
Fortunately, unfortunately.
Oh.
Hey, hey, hey.
Don't leave.
Hmm.
I hear my phone ringing.
yes I wanted a vile complaint You played scary movies on the
TV On the store's TV My child had awful nightmares I
expected a family friendly environment When going to a video
store And I missed the part where that is my problem Okay
Yes Draconic Park Wait a It's okay we can fix her Okay We
can fix her!
We can fix you!
The ghost of my fantasy!
Alive!
Good.
Okay, good.
You cut out the good part.
What are you talking about?
It's the ghost of my fantasy.
Every part is the good part.
Don't even kid.
Everybody knows that every part is great.
Oh, oh, who ordered the hot T-Rex is back?
Yeah!
Fantasy.
No-rama.
Romance.
Adult.
The lady in my pants.
Alright, cool.
I also, since we have a little bit more money too, I'm gonna
move these over to the kids section.
Okay.
Oh, yes.
Die trying.
Yeah, I have so many copies on the floor even.
Oh, you can start putting these up.
There we go, awesome.
FBI!
I'm innocent!
i'm selling totally legit movies it'd be funny if they did
implement like a uh you know you you get the bootleg movies
from the guy in the alley but it'd be funny if they
implemented like uh like somebody comes in and checks and is
just like are you selling legitimate movies and you had to
uh do something some sort of mini game or something to
similar to like how you have to
Uh, similar to how you have the repair.
Very good.
Science fiction.
Sci-fi, sci-fi.
Fantasy.
Drama.
Not a lot of drama is getting rented right now, huh?
Colombo shows up and starts asking questions.
You have to get all the bootlegs off the shelf before they
come.
Oh my gosh.
I have so many, though.
Hmm.
The sounds.
I don't know about that.
Like, maybe if they come, like, once a month or something.
Because otherwise, that would be hellish.
Guys, I have so many illegal movies in the game.
Yeah, my shelves, those whole adult section, there would be
none.
I'd be I'd be ruined
in game Sugar Rush T-Rex Do you guys remember That song in
Wreck-It Ralph S-U-T-A-R Jumping to my driving car Sugar
Rush Sugar Rush That's it, AKB Sorry, I feel like I'm gonna
sing it 48 song at the time i was a huge akb 48 fan so i
went to the movie theater and to see record ralph just
because they were in it i was so excited hello
waldo no cask on the farm what if i said no
it is a big deal what is with what is with a like uh j-pop
groups being in the disney pixar films I'd like to rent
three copies of the mid-fantom movie and a large soda.
Speaking of, did you guys see the new person added to the
Minecraft movie?
Sorry, it's not Minecraft movie 2, they called it Minecraft
movie squared.
Did you see who got added to the cast?
Pixar full of weebs, I believe that.
Who?
I don't remember his name.
But...
You dropped it in the Dropbox?
Die trying, yes.
Um...
It's his...
He is in...
He is in what we do in the shadows.
He's one of my favorite characters in that show.
Um...
And he goes...
He goes bat.
Hold on.
Wow, what a story meant.
No!
The reason I bring it up...
Hold on.
wait what we do in the shadows
cast matt barry the cup mr missing string table himself yeah
matt barry not barry is added to the cast of a minecraft
movie but also i saw i saw a tweet earlier that was just
like he was like i can't say who i'm playing yet you know
and the tweet was just like hear me out on my crazy theory
but what if what if matt barry is actually steve and this
whole time and then this whole time jack black has been
here, O'Brien.
Oh, that would be so awesome!
That would be like the craziest twist ever.
I hope they take notes from random tweets.
Oh, yeah.
We rented this a long time ago.
Nice.
My headcanon be like, yeah, me too.
Me too.
Hmm, I feel like we didn't make so much money today, but we
did spend a ton.
What if he's Alex?
No, they already cast Alex.
She is Mary Giant.
Bottom I am.
Yeah, Kristen Dunst.
Mount Berry is great and everything.
He's also made a bunch of music, too.
I didn't- Oh, I've never heard his music before.
I really like him and well actually I haven't seen him in so
much but I do really like him and what we do in the shadows
oh Kirsten Dunst is it Kristen or Kirsten I don't know I'm
sleepy today everybody I don't know anything don't don't
talk to my brain Kristen Kirsten
She's a pretty lighty.
All right, close the day.
Close the door.
Only $408?
Guys, we're gonna, I'm, I'm, I put everything.
I put everything into the new stuff.
Movie retrieval button is the big square button near the
back door.
Oh, wait, let's try it.
Dang it.
Also some skews.
Thank you, Corona!
Thank you!
Oh, here.
Oh my god, the bun's wrong number.
Where did you come from?
Is this the one that got broken before?
I feel like not.
Where did you come from?
Weekends are busier.
I guess that's fair.
Alright, return station.
It's...
Wait, but that was a weekend.
That was Sunday.
I guess nobody's watching movies on Sundays.
Where did you come from?
Where did you go?
Where does you come from?
Cotton eye Joe.
Did you guys know that the new Toy Story movie is like about
to come out?
I thought it was I thought it was like sometimes I feel like
I'll see a trailer for a movie and video games.
I see a trailer and I think, oh, it's not going to come out
until like 2030.
And then suddenly the movie is out in theaters and I'm like,
where did you come from?
What?
I called it quits at three.
I don't think I saw, I don't, what happened?
And Toy Story 4.
I just went to see back rooms.
Didn't know a new Toy Story.
Yeah, apparently.
I saw it on, like, the sign of my local movie theater.
And I was like.
Where did you come from?
Woody becomes a carny and leaves the group.
Oh, wait.
Was 4 the one with the spork?
Okay.
Is that the one where they're about to like die in the...
In the...
In the incinerator?
That's three.
Oh, okay.
So that's where we peaked.
Okay.
Four was forky.
I don't know if I watched four.
It got me forked up, man.
I am a toy story apologist.
Hey, like what you like.
But you're the reason that we keep getting more of these.
And you're probably like, yeah, I am.
Woohoo!
Yeah, I am!
Let's see if we got any good Anthony and Ethan.
We have twins.
Nora.
Wait, return station fast!
Energetic, loyal, and strong immune system.
Oh!
Good, good.
She's good on both.
Energetic and loyal.
But she will take a sick day.
Do we want to get Anthony?
I'm not loyal to Anna.
To be honest.
Five will be someone's first toy story.
It's so sweet when you think about it like that.
But also, why would you start at five?
Who would start a game on the fifth installment?
Who would do that?
Yes, Cloud?
Hey, is this the video store?
So like, you guys rent movies or something like that?
Yes!
We have no movies for sale.
Maybe... Nope.
Die Trying is still a brand new movie.
You got to start with Toy Story Revengeance.
Yeah, you started the sixth movie spin-off.
What do you mean?
I started MGS with V.
How?
I just... I'm just so confused how you...
Like, you played... Anybody who started the MGS V.
How did you know what was going on?
Maybe you just didn't.
Maybe you were just like...
Yeah, I know that.
Solid, Snake.
series is about the big boss and the solids man that's the
neat part you start toy story with cars guys i went on the
cars ride at disney and i've never watched cars before i've
never seen cars before
should i watch it
Sort of Final Fantasy with 10.
But not sure though.
Yeah, those don't count.
They're basically episodic.
Was the ride good?
It was really good.
Oh, it was really good.
Sorry.
I'm so curious to see what a fast return person is like.
You know?
Start with Woody's revenge.
Yeah.
Sometimes I think about the fact that some kids' first
exposure to Toy Story was the Andy's room segment of Kingdom
Hearts 3.
No!
What kid is playing Kingdom Hearts 3?
Legitimately.
Cars Watch Alon.
Actually!
Oh my gosh.
Last night.
So there's been this YouTube channel that's been uploading
like Detective Conan movies and stuff.
I watched the Conan Lupin movie the other day.
And then yesterday they put up the first Conan movie.
And it's for free!
And I was like, oh I really want to do a watch along of
this.
These are from Corona.
Thank you for the SKUs.
The Christmas Explosive Miracle.
Cars 1 and 3 are really solid.
You should watch them.
What's wrong with 2?
Scary Grandpa Scary Grandpa Flick You will die I like that
one We'll go for that
The Tentacle and the Little Duck Why is this for kids?
Watch along would be a good idea for laptop streams, right?
I think so, I think so Two is weird?
Oh my gosh, yes They put up the trailer for Conan Pretty
Cure?
It's so cute.
Conan in the Pretty Cure art style is so actually good.
And then Pretty Cure in the Conan art style is terrifying.
I think I really, I love Conan.
I've definitely fallen off in the last couple of years.
And I was like thinking why?
Because I was watching the movie and I was like, I love this
so much.
I've watched the first movie so many times.
I would watch it so often.
But...
I think what has put me off of the series is I hate the art
style now.
I hate...
Like, I...
Conan... Conan's head looks so terrible!
Like, I don't know.
I'm just not a big fan of it anymore.
Like, they changed the art to be very...
I don't know The new art style is just so And like I used to
collect like Conan merch and stuff I don't collect any new
modern Conan merch I just think it's so So not cute It's
everybody's so ugly And recently I'm so sad I don't know
I've been a big advocate for Conan ending For many many
years now But recently The voice actress for Don, her voice
actress passed away recently.
She's been voicing her for like 30 years, right?
And it, you know, it makes me so sad that she'll now not get
to experience the ending.
Like these dang series, like if it's something like
Shin-chan, you know, something that's like doesn't have a
story like super you know like or rather like a very grand
story these series just need to end there are people dying
that don't get to finish the series it's so frustrating like
oh my gosh and like these voice actresses and stuff and that
voice actors they're they're getting up in age and and it's
just tough like at least if you want it to continue end the
main story and then like pick it do like okay the end story
or the big story is ended from here on out Conan will just
become like a murder of the week a mystery of the week show
if you want to keep watching it for your favorite characters
that's all good if you if you if you're done if you just
wanted to see the conclusion of the ending that's good too
like just end the story
Have you played Conan Exiles?
Especially now with the enhanced version.
I don't even know what that is.
I've never heard of that.
Minto, I love Conan.
Yeah, another great day to be named Conan.
I hate Conan now, never mind.
Nero will die.
No!
I'm scared to get into it too.
100, 1,200 plus episodes.
I...
There are lists online that, like, like separate the uh the
what's the word filler from the important episodes probably
out of that filler i would say like a hundred episodes are
like important not even kidding like if i had to guess it
would be like a hundred i mean that's still a ton of
episodes but like i would say like a hundred episodes or so
are important.
True, all good stories end, but cash cows live forever.
That's why I think, like, it would be a good middle ground
if they could end the story and then, you know, be like, we
love, but we don't want Conan to end.
We want Conan solving mysteries forever and just have, like,
Conan's mystery files.
And it just is, like I said, like, creature of the week,
something he solves every week.
And there could be, like, ones that last a couple episodes
too like you know but just finish the main story stuff like
this is why I like what if episodes of shows that give
hypothetical endings because it never gets a real ending I
feel like I will never see the ending of Detective Conan
I've gotten to the point where I'm like maybe I need to
maybe I need to read fan fiction of conclusions to this dang
show something to at least have some sense of some sense of
uh i don't know what's the word uh closure closure yeah some
closure finality oh that's my conan rant sorry i've been
thinking about it a lot recently especially because of the
voice actress passing away and i was like i'm i'm so sad
because she has been run the whole time what the heck is the
creamy enchanter that's disgusting oh wait oh wait these are
these are connected uh hold on uh how many how many numbers
wait are they usually eight Uh, maybe?
Sweaty dinosaur action!
We can purchase that.
And then, wait, what did I just end that on?
Three.
Okay.
One, two, three, seven, two, two, seven, two, two, two,
three.
Sweet hot dog.
We'll buy that one also.
Thank you for the skews.
Thank you.
is probably done by now.
Oh, thank goodness she is.
Ew, this one's terrible.
This is such a terrible...
Ew, what is happening?
Ew!
Case closure is the now perfect ending fanfic name, right?
You know, it could be all about his kid and they could call
it Borunad.
could be all grumpy because his dad became the Hokage and
doesn't spend time with his family.
Wait, wrong show.
Alright.
Anna, go to check out.
Echoes of Burning Puppet.
Then let's open this baby up.
Hold on.
May I interest you?
You guys can't hear the game, right?
I'm not wearing headphones, so, like, I'm just listening to
the game through speaker.
But you guys can't hear it, right?
The JP side have a journey matters more than the destination
attitude towards long-running series.
It's a real sore point for fans over here, though.
Ugh, I guess, yeah, like, I get it.
I get it, too.
But maybe it's because so many series end port.
Maybe it's because so many series are really great until the
ending.
That it's like...
It's like, oh, we don't want the ending to come because the
series itself is just so good.
We don't need it.
We don't need a conclusion.
Oh my god!
I got attacked.
Fantasy.
Fantasy, fantasy.
Hold on.
We're taking all of these off.
And we're putting them over here.
Hey, move, please.
Excuse me.
Oh, drama, drama, fantasy, fantasy.
We'll put these back here.
And I think maybe these can go over here now.
No, they can't.
But that's okay.
I honestly can order so many more movies.
I think about it, like we have a ton of space.
Echoes of the Burning Puppet.
I was just looking at that.
I just clocked.
Minto's been talking about Conan the Detective, not Conan
the Barbarian.
Sorry, I should have clarified Detective Conan.
Not Barbarian Conan.
Yes, Conan of the Detective Variety.
I do not watch the Conan of the Barbarian Variety.
I know you're so interested.
No, please.
No, you're so interested.
Hey, you're so interested.
Hmm.
No, no.
You should though, should I?
Hmm.
stepbrother.
Oh, someone over here?
Yes?
I just went through a breakup.
Could you give me an emotional drama movie?
Let's give him...
Hmm.
The barrel separation.
It's so relevant.
I doubt Conan would ever end even if the manga guy is gone.
You know that Go-Go-Go 13 is still going even though Saito
died five years ago.
No way!
You're probably right.
I don't know.
You might be right.
She's still going?
Conan the Barbarian Detective.
He could be.
How exciting would that be?
I think Gosho Aoyama already has...
Conan's ending written?
I hope at least that like I don't know I don't know who has
seen I am I think he does too I think I remember hearing
that it is already written I just wonder who knows it you
know oh we did have a fantasy like do the say you at least
know so that they can feel you know At peace.
The saucy snake.
Don't know, please.
You know you want one.
Are you scaring them off?
Berserk is still going.
I don't know if berserk is still going.
Right?
I have no idea, though.
P?
Yes, you.
Oh, it is?
It is by the author's best friend.
Wait, that's so sweet.
Fine, I will pay.
I spend most nights reading about mythology and imaginary
creatures.
Do you have a fantasy movie you think I would enjoy?
The quest for the...
The holy milk carton.
Irony it would be if Kaito Kid got an ending first.
Oh, you're not the person I was...
Where'd he go?
Wait.
I thought you wanted a movie.
Wait, where'd that guy go?
Hello?
Wait!
I thought he wanted a movie!
I'm tall again?
What just happened?
We...
I think our store is haunted.
We have ghosts asking for movies.
This place is too cramped for two ghosts.
Get out.
Run by a ghost.
Satan in his heart thought...
Why are you terrified?
You...
You're the one who asked for it.
Nah.
Store is not haunted?
Not possible.
Yeah, not possible.
Store is not haunted.
There's no way.
I wish I could hire a second employee already because
there's so many...
So many...
Oops.
Returns.
We're gonna...
Especially when we start getting way more movies.
Like, it's gonna be...
It's gonna be tough.
Doing both.
I mean, I don't know what else I would do in the meantime.
I would just do nothing, maybe.
I would just be twiddling my thumbs.
But at the same time, work is work.
Oops.
I know we had...
There it is.
You can finally nap.
That's true!
I could nap!
I could do anything else.
Boise, moise.
I was at the video store and got transported to another
world where my fantasy knowledge was in high demand.
He's a great trash anime coming soon.
I'm feeling super nostalgic today.
Could you recommend an old movie?
Old movie.
They came for the werewolf.
This one is shiny.
It's in high demand.
Okay.
Everybody's walking through me.
Oh, whammy or familiar faces.
Speaking of Conan, I wish they made more of the spin-off of
the character Kid the Phantom Thief, Magic Kaito.
I like Kaito Kid.
You're a ghost.
I am.
I am a ghost.
We didn't make that much money today either.
Uh-oh.
I'm going broke.
Anna, I'm gonna have to fire you.
This is the worst idea of ever.
overhead.
We need Anthony.
Wait, can I hire him?
Dang it.
Level 20!
Oh, I'm gonna get to level 15, I think, after today, but...
Oh, wait.
Oh my gosh.
Did we sell much soda?
That's a good question.
Oh!
A grape is doing good.
The snake pit soda is not doing so hot.
Nah, Top Sip is doing okay.
Top Sip is so funny.
Those are good traits.
I know, right?
Maybe we get Anthony.
Can you reserve the little vampire for me?
Is that?
Wait.
Is that the one I'm thinking of?
With that kid in the glasses?
Yeah!
I remember that movie.
That little kid was everywhere.
That kid in the glasses was like the Hollywood nerd.
Yeah, and the cows.
I remember really liking that movie.
And they would whistle at each other.
The steward little kid.
Yeah, that kid.
He was everywhere.
He was like the like little nerdy kid of movies at the time.
It was kind of insane.
Do you remember that movie, Zack?
All the cows turned into vampires.
It's a good thing I wasn't on that case.
Ah.
Okay.
All right.
We're good.
Are you good?
What happened here?
Oh, sorry.
Keep on working.
Oh my gosh.
These people are barbarians.
Speaking of barbarians.
Just throwing their stuff everywhere.
I'm putting you on return.
Red Ransom, welcome back.
Thank you.
Tomorrow, I think, is Tuesday.
And it's also second Valentine's Day.
Very strange.
Oh!
God!
It's not Valentine's Day.
Wait, won't people be also...
It says that the people will be getting romance, but why
won't they be getting adult movies as well?
Let's order some new...
No.
Some comedy!
A song for my ghost!
We already have it, though.
Doghouse on Rollerblades.
We have that, too.
We have a...
Marrying my Wraith!
Okay, we can get that one also.
Ultra Man!
That's just a guy.
The infection returns.
Red Lady Juice.
Santa's Mission, the stolen PC.
Scary Grandpa Flick.
We have that one.
too.
I want to go through our new uh new horror comedies.
Oh!
Made me out back at 9pm every Tuesday and Thursday.
If you're after exclusive movies and deals, I'll crack the
door open to let you know I'm here.
I'll be waiting.
We've got smiling PC the robot over my head hilarious the
big toe corporation doghouse delusion how are these comedy
the urban explosive lady madness
what is this butler now playing None of these sound funny.
The underground bathtub.
Bull masquerade.
Goof ball tome.
Now that's comedy.
That was his fantasy.
I love me some goof ball tome.
Phantom?
No.
Goof ball tome.
Oh, die trying.
No!
I can fix you!
Alright.
That's the cut where they take out the Yippie-Yippie-Keya
mint phantom.
But...
Yeah, we don't need that whole big chunk of the movie!
Who's even watching?
Why do all the comedies sound so... so stupid?
None of these look good.
Maybe Lady Madness is pretty fun.
All of the rest of these, though, are terrible.
I like goofball tone too.
It was my favorite scene.
Ah, yes, everyone remembers, get off of my beard.
The hilarious catchphrase from Lady Madness.
Get off of my beard.
You lady, you're driving me madness.
That's what he says.
It's accurate to IRL.
Are they that?
I don't know.
I'm trying to think of like a comedy.
I think of like Step Brothers.
Okay, that's not a great title.
We have...
Austin Powers.
That's just his name.
Uh...
It's a memory of the...
Welcome to membership, thank you!
Uh, Taladay, goodnight.
Oh, it's...
Minions?
I guess comedy names are kind of tough.
I guess it is.
I guess comedy titles are kind of...
are kind of hard to do.
Yeah, Anchorman, Bridesmaid, Zoolander.
Huh.
Yeah.
Yeah, they can kind of be anything.
They're usually like...
It seems like they're usually like the name of like...
The main character.
Or something like that.
They're like a bunch of like one or two words, sentence,
like not sentence, and statements.
Please tell me I have a copy of The Fighting Duchess.
I need to see this movie.
Right there.
Oh no!
Wait, we literally just saw this person rent this.
Oops.
We'll come back.
Wait, huh?
Oh, echoes of the burning puppet!
And then we have echoes of the burning bubblegum.
I was like, ah, how did that happen?
Mitosis?
Oh, she's starting to put stuff...
Okay.
This is fine.
We'll do this.
I really want Bull Masquerade to be a cornball parody of
Phantom of the Opera on a farm.
Masquerade!
Farm animals in Dress.
is masquerade hide your face so the world won't know we're
animals masquerade
on the farm dancing in hay masquerade
let's see what else we got here oh so many movies so many
movies so many movies so little time Oh, wait, we're to the
end.
Sweaty Dino action!
We literally just rented that out.
That's crazy.
We just bought that.
Oh my gosh.
The fixing the...
The fact that we can fix movies now is huge.
Because otherwise, it's so stinky.
All our shells.
are full full full maybe someone watched this and got so
enraged maybe it was really bad we'll cut out the bad bits
the whole movie apparently now
i kind of want to watch fan of the opera now i want to watch
fan of the opera look what you did thank you very much
Fantasy.
All right.
Actually, we'll start taking these again.
Just throw them on the ground as I did before.
Yeah.
And they end.
Action.
Fantasy.
Was that the only one?
Hmm.
I've never seen Final of the Opera on Broadway.
Oh, here it is.
There we go.
was another one.
I've never seen on Broadway.
I won't be able to catch the Densit to stream later.
It's happy six-month anniversary in advance.
Thank you!
Oh, I just remembered the... Okay.
Stream in one hour.
We'll play for like another 30 minutes or something.
And then I'll rate it into the waiting.
Can you guys give... I already packed my clock.
So I don't have a clock to look at.
Can you guys give me a warning?
You're welcome.
I've been singing it lots.
We got your back window.
Thank you.
I was just about to remind you.
Here.
Check out.
Alright, cool, cool, cool.
We got to level 15.
That was just comedy.
Soon we'll get the candy dispenser.
I want the staff too.
That's the huge goal.
oh that's right we have more things now too yes like this
let's get some like some real like these are so like oh
Hollywood oh yeah you're watching movies yeah you're
watching movies I will put like this here oh yeah oh yeah oh
yeah I was like I think we unlocked one other thing we're
watching movies let's take this direction there we go adult
film yeah good good yes explosive stepbrother indeed we do
this goes on the wall I think yeah we'll put it like here
movies okay we can't change that maybe Densetsu and Beasties
could do a VTuber version of Fan of the Opera Phantom of the
Channel can I be Raul
Christy look at Christy that's my girl Literally his line.
Whoa!
I'll be phantom.
You'll be phantom.
Who would I want to be phantom?
I think Phoebe.
Because it's kind of like a gap moy.
This is so old school Hollywood.
I love it.
I'm obsessed.
Inside your mind.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, now we're talking.
All right, let's open up.
And also, come to my store.
Wait, no, no, no, no.
Don't leave, don't leave, don't leave.
Come to my store.
Oh, I don't want to be a just...
Okay, you're fine.
Come to my store.
Come on, what a hater.
Oh, she liked it.
Come to my store.
You?
Come to my store?
I gotta get some movies for sale.
I'm waiting for Die Trying to become unpopular.
Why do these people, like, slow-turn?
I don't know why I fan of the opera was so cool as a kid.
It's still so cool!
What do you mean?
It's still such a great...
Like, I know some people were critical about the movie.
but I still think the movie is pretty decent and I think it
as a musical is amazing.
The opera has never gone out of style.
More of a Phantom of the Livestream kind of guy.
My dad left when I was a kid.
Okay Julia I'm not your therapist but sure I have a family
drama to cheer you up.
Let's do the boats last day.
home.
There you go.
Just like your dad, the boat left.
Exactly what she was looking for.
Start putting these away.
Is it your favorite Weber musical?
Probably.
I know that's like basic taste, but I don't care if it's
basic.
It's popular.
because it's good.
Oh, action.
Mixed.
Fantasy.
Alright.
I'm a basic B.
No, I'm a basic G.
A basic ghost.
Duh.
Oh wow, not so many returns today.
Nice.
Die trying.
Drama.
And then we can put some more up in there.
I said Valentine's Day, but most people are ordering dramas.
What's going on?
Everybody's unhappy.
Her.
Drama.
Sci-fi.
I'm the ghost lost in space.
Yes?
The Deadly Lighty.
There you go.
The Sign of the Times.
Just stop your crying.
It's the Sign of the Times.
We gotta get away from here.
You want the fighting, Duchess.
You reserved this a couple days ago.
I'll have to give you a rental fee.
because it was not on our shelves everybody was requesting
it but because you were so selfish and reserved it days ago
what are you doing?
oh it's warping look at all the people they're just staring
at blank shelves oh they're comedies I forgot we got
comedies Wait, do we have any new...
Ahoy, comedian?
This is terrifying.
What is that?
It's not even a comedy.
Doghouse on...
This evil doghouse on rollerblades.
We have this one already, though.
Breakfast on top of the world.
Dark pixie magic.
I'm trying to find more comedies.
We don't have any.
Oh.
The people request.
my attention?
Yes, how can I help you?
Hmm.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Yee hee hee hee!
Ha ha!
Oh boy, I just saw the funniest thing!
Anyway, do you have a comedy to recommend?
I'm in a laughing mode today.
Also, we prefer old movie.
Actors we see in recent movies have no talent.
Okay.
Doghouse delusion is up your alley.
What a freak.
Die trying.
There you go.
Have you guys heard about, like, how people think that
actors shouldn't be allowed to get, like, Botox and Plastic
Surgery because it hinders with their job?
How, like, it will be a period piece, but you'll have a girl
with a full lip filler.
Well, their job is acting, but they can't emote with their
face because they have too much of Botox.
A magician's trusty T-Rex.
There you go.
The Botox paralysis.
Arthur, welcome back.
Thank you.
I guess it does make sense.
Part of me is, like, I understand the sense.
sentiment, but it also sounds so silly.
They can still be bad actors.
It makes sense, but at the same time, I'm like, oh.
I get the sense, but it's also none of our business.
Yeah, that's exactly how I feel about it.
I was like, no Botox for you.
No Botox for you.
Yeah?
Oh.
Oh, you're getting a rainbow special.
That'll cost extra.
Charge him extra.
I think if it's like, you know, if someone has maybe a lot
of work done, then maybe they shouldn't be hired for a role
that like takes place in the 17th century.
You know?
Because, I don't know, I guess it's like tough when like
they, like I feel actors want to be too pretty nowadays
where it's that, you know, they're, you look like you're on
Instagram and you don't look like you're from the, you don't
look like you're from the bubonic plague era.
Speaking of period pieces, Minto, did you ever watch Downton
Abbey?
I haven't, I haven't.
Yeah, I think it's a casting issue too.
Ultimately, I don't really care so much, but I get why
people would be a little annoyed by it.
Yeah.
I don't know if you saw the best of the worst with Merry
Christmas, but they did point out a certain actor.
Wait, no, I don't...
Wait, is this a recent one?
Because I haven't watched any recent episodes.
Oh man.
Doghouse on rollerblades.
Oops.
Pretty recent, yeah.
I've been over Hollywood for a great while now, myself.
It's all just anime.
You know what?
That works, too.
I think it's kind of really fun that we're getting so
many...
Oh, all the romance are getting rented, though.
We're getting so many...
So many horror films and, like, seemingly really good ones.
I really want to see Obsession.
I've heard great things about that.
Um...
Only... I want to see it backrooms, obviously.
I...
Yeah, like, I want to see it in theaters.
Yeah, I've heard great things about obsession.
Saw backrooms yesterday, it was good.
Obsession was great.
I want to see.
Oh, exit A?
Yeah, I want to see that.
We're getting... Like, we're in our... We're in, like, good
horror era.
It's kind of awesome.
As a huge horror fan myself, I'm excited for it.
The genie and the chicken.
Gonna see backgrounds tomorrow.
I don't know when I'll be able to go see it.
Is it like...
For anyone that's seen it.
Is it like super spooky?
Are we like...
Are we talking like multiple jump scares?
I guess Don't spoil, obviously, but...
Obsession is pretty intense.
I- I- okay, I- I was so curious about it and I didn't know
when I would be able to go see it that I- I didn't see
spoilers on that one, but it only made me want to see it
more, to be honest.
Like the spoilers that I saw for Obsession, I was like,
okay, and now I really want to go see it.
I heard the backgrounds are similar to the YouTube series.
Oh, okay, cool.
did you pull a doki wiki dive not that bad i did see some
like some scenes of like some of the scarier moments of the
movie maybe i don't know there might be scare even scarier
moments but maybe like some of the ones that really got
people and uh oh yeah i did see the iron lung is now on
rental i did see that oh yes 20 for damaging a movie i could
find a copy of that same movie for five dollars i won't pay
your fee i will charge you the fee yeah you will pay the fee
you stupid what do we got back here you're not an undercover
cop right we got the tome monster of the sea i'll just buy
everything i wish for the bomb
i wish for the bomb
sexy waitress in the sauna hostile swimming takeover and the
queen my prisoner holy cow oh we're getting some real freaky
stuff for our for our adult section I wish for the bomb
maybe my favorite favorite title so far so good oh it's so
funny it's too Cool, we're done.
Let me switch you to return.
Why is I Wish for the Bomb a fantasy movie?
I think it's because it's like a genie movie.
Wow.
Nice.
$502 today, everybody.
New movie release.
new movie?
Wait, what do you mean by that?
Oh, die trying is not a new movie anymore.
Yay!
Bargain bin, bargain bin, bargain bin!
Is there any die trying here?
I don't see any.
Bruh, I am awake!
Hope you're having fun!
Modded skews!
Wait, do I have these?
Ghost in the smell.
Alan Wick versus John Wick.
King
Farm!
It's so expensive.
It has literally no stars.
But we must get it.
Thank you!
That's literally me!
That's literally me.
We'll put it on the very top.
Alan Wick versus John Wick.
You hate me.
You hate me for real.
Oh, Morning Glory Milk Farm.
Okay, good.
She's taking those.
I like movies.
I really, really like movies.
I think I might have a problem.
Mr. Kojima, we told you to please stop calling my store.
Five minute warning.
Wait till...
Okay, thank you!
I thought until 7, I was about to be like, uh-oh.
Okay, we can probably do this day, and then we will...
have to call it and raid into...
I like that this ad's...
like light it looks really good so fun wait were there any
new movies here oh yeah let's check um five random movies 10
random movies kid wait that might be good let's get some
more kid movies hello as a concerned parent i'm calling to
make a suggestion could you promote healthier snacks Uh, not
my problem.
Swimming class with my troll.
All hail the gas mask.
The instrument, my soulmate.
Santa and gas mask on white.
We have gas mask.
Big grin corsair.
Okay, we need more comedy, so...
The snowman's woman.
The beast's lucky day.
Godfather and treats.
Ta-da!
Here's the monster!
Golden, Miami.
I wish for the sofa.
Literally me right now.
Mushroom upside down.
We'll buy more comedy.
Button behind enemy lines.
No available space.
Oh, I bought, that's right.
I bought 10.
Button behind enemy lines.
Ta-da!
Here's someone.
Oh, wait.
We don't have room for kids.
Uh-oh.
I thought we had more space in here than I thought.
This is reserved.
Girl, what are you doing?
Oh, wait.
Unless that...
Was that the phone call?
What's the new movie?
Is it a new movie day?
Oh, you're right.
Oh, it's a new movie.
Xenocat!
Oh, my God!
We'll get 10.
so glad i could catch a bit of this cozy sunday stream have
fun with the density six month anniversary thank you enough
thank you zino cat wait we're like hitting up all my
favorite movies this is so funny this is so awesome
hmm perfect
and it's cat themed it's even better
Uh, we'll put this, um, like right here.
I don't know.
Is that?
Yeah, that's good.
In space, no one can hear you meow.
It says the feline will hear you scream.
The best sci-fi horror ever produced.
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Oop.
A little too close.
There we go.
I actually got out of a local screen thing for one of my
favorite retro movies myself.
No, I come home and see you!
I hope you had fun!
Wait, that's so awesome!
That's so awesome.
I hope you had fun!
Let's see what we got.
Oh, wait.
The Love Seat Parade.
Shroom with Flames.
Lion Colors.
The grandpa's lucky day.
Big loaf surprise.
Superstar in the pond.
Wizard at the zoo.
The lucky cigarette.
You're a zoo.
There I go.
Thank you.
30 minutes until next stream.
Captain up with the wind.
Magic octopus count on me.
The fairy's lucky day.
Alright, there were some other things we were going to buy
here, I remember.
Uh...
Oh, button behind enemy lines.
Ghost at war!
The swimmer cyberlink.
Quiet time with the hobo.
Tis the witch season.
30 minute warning!
Thank you guys!
I think we should be able to do one more day, right?
Does this make facehuggers kittens?
Wait, that's so sweet.
Uh-oh, I'm really running out of room here.
Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh.
This will have to be a mixed shelf, I think.
This has been such a cozy stream.
Hope your ear feels better.
So congrats on six months, Denza 2.
Also want to say that.
Missing string table entry.
I went to forever, meow.
Yeah!
Everybody in...
uh in xenocat they have a what is it the toxos toxo toxis
plasmosis all right let's do the day so that we can uh so
i'm not late to stream seconds late to second stream oh i'm
also so excited for this stream for density stream so i hope
you guys can watch if you can talk so plasmosis yeah Yeah,
yeah.
Any hints?
I don't think I can.
You'll just have to see.
Wait a second.
I just realized probably our action...
Wait, she probably...
Yes, die trying.
I was going to say she probably put a ton of die trying on
here.
Just remembered that we were selling these.
Yeah, there we go.
Yeah, get rid of them.
And so we can take the action here...
And it's not perfect, but we can at least kind of...
Organize a little bit.
Is there any in here?
And we do want to keep at least one.
I'm sure somebody still has one rented.
Is all we seen or seen...
Wait, wait.
Is all that we see or seen but a stream within a stream?
Huh?
Wait.
Dollar for every mile I ran today.
My legs...
Good job, Seymour!
I heart mean, kitty.
Must be the toxoplasmosis.
Absolutely.
Oh my god!
Yes, syringe with flying colors.
Wait, I need to check out people.
Five dollar.
You're free to go.
Yes.
Tell me how the toxoplasmosis is.
You're free to go.
Someone got ghost in the smell.
No way.
$12.
Why am I giving you so much back?
You're free to go?
Nice choices, Samuel.
Here's a dollar for every mile I ran today, too.
You're free to go?
Wait, that's Anthony!
We need to hire him!
Wait.
What'd you get?
Psst, do you have an adult movie to recommend?
Don't tell anyone I was here.
Mia, I would like to give you blazing eye booze, our
adultist film.
Hmm, grape soda.
Grape.
Okay, there you go.
Thank you.
Two, 25.
You're free to go?
Adultest film ever.
Holy cow!
Oh, you got our sodas!
Adam, thank you!
Thank you, you're free to go!
Dino gummies!
I realized we're out of our Dino Crunch or whatever that
was.
Thank you.
I need, I need, what's her name, back up here.
So I can restock stuff.
$2.
Matthew, you're free to go?
Where is she, anyway?
Anna!
Where is Anna?
Is she in the bathroom?
Anna?
No?
Where did she go?
She didn't have a sick day, right?
There she is.
Anna, Anna, come back, come back.
Please take the check out.
I'm scared of people.
Thank you.
She ran away.
She got rid of her duties.
Here, I'll take care of those.
What are you going to do with them?
Good
job.
Good job, Anna.
Good job.
She threw it on the ground.
She doesn't want to work here anymore.
on the ground quest for the holy race car employee of the
month i think she disrespects me too much
for my liking you know
good good not so many uh not so many returns the bad boy
with his treasure oh i thought rooster and sausage was an
adult film but it's an action film i'm like so i need more
space we have only one die trying in here any more die
trying over here okay we do have a few okay die trying die
trying we only need the one so put this in here the boat's
last day home yeah picnic with my milk race car on wheels
What else would the race car be, huh?
Legend of the Voitress.
Die trying.
For sale.
Rooster and sausage.
On here.
Die trying.
For sale.
I'm looking for a romance movie.
Also, I'm single, by the way.
If you're interested.
I'm getting flirted by this lady right here.
We'll give you the machine between love.
You should try talking to chat GPT.
Yes?
The last movie I rented was so bad I broke the tape.
I have anger management issues.
Oh.
You're anger ma- I'm calling the police!
I gave- I cannot believe I gave her- you guys I almost gave
her blazing eye boos.
I cannot believe.
And why- she's getting- she got that.
And two kids movies.
You're a terrible mother!
Kissing my organ in the sky.
I also see this was broken.
We'll go fix it.
You're welcome.
How dare you not reward her for breaking your property?
The actual entitlement.
I cannot believe.
Hello.
Are you interested in movies?
Now you are.
Hmm.
No, why do you guys react that way?
All three of you?
Oh.
You?
Okay, good.
You're not a new customer.
Neither are you.
Oh, I don't think we'll get any new people now.
Days over.
Um.
Doghouse on rollerblades.
Yes.
You're assuming she has kids.
T-minus 20 minutes.
It's okay.
It's the end of the day.
We're all good.
Reserved.
Oops.
Asking to see a manager.
Okay, okay.
One second.
Anna, can't you do anything without me?
Please.
Gesture burnout.
Closer to my dragon.
Yes?
This is my first broken ever feed ever.
Could I get a warning instead?
Charge the feed.
He takes it with a smile.
He was like, yeah, you're better in a business.
Maybe she's a Disney adult.
She could be.
Ryan's twin.
Rules are rules, yeah.
Rules are...
Anything strict you're fancy?
I think we still have time trying.
Yes, we do.
Okay, good.
Because there was that one that came back, but it was
reserved.
Oh, let's fix it.
We have two of them!
Offering of the bathtub.
Dying with a smile.
If the world was ending, I want to be next to you.
Right next to you.
Next to you.
Look at how many people we still have in here.
Go home, everybody.
I mean, don't, actually.
La, la, la, la.
If the world was ended, I want to be next to Freddy Jesus.
Dino gummies.
Any soda?
Oh, our sodas are getting bought out too.
Nice.
Top sip.
Pop sip.
Grid line grip.
And then... We'll chew!
Wait, I kind of want to see.
Okay, we'll do the snake one here and then the jelly melon
there.
I know, you guys.
The game is about over.
We're okay.
We're okay on time.
Don't worry about it.
I said this is my last day.
I'm quitting this job.
This is my last day.
Thank you for the...
Wow, wait.
Why are we flowering?
Why are you giving me flowers?
Oh my gosh, Kapo!
Thank you so much for the third super ever on livestream.
You want to make a decision?
fast?
We're closed.
We've been closed.
Yeah, get in line.
Very good.
You need to pay the fee.
I will pay, but I'm never coming back.
Well, you just rented some movies, so you have to.
You have to come back.
You rented the movies.
You don't... They're rent.
It's the rental.
Not to buy
don't let the door hit you on the way out nice thank you
have a good day you're free to go
what's up with your eyes Anna what happened to you what
happened to you look whoa wait are we gonna level up we
didn't rent some money movies so maybe not No, sadly.
But we're...
Level 15?
Not bad at all!
I guess I...
Oh, yeah.
I don't really need to save.
Let's see what's on the marketplace real quick, though.
Ta-da!
Here's the bandit.
The mushroom gang assault.
The TV boat.
It's not very funny, but...
Elf Warzone.
I do need...
more comedies hot dog brain implants say no more say no more
rocket man on the naughty list that's just the fury one more
mooy mooy boo oh thank you one more one three made mint
chapter three she will kill you herself
It sounds, it just sounds like a threat.
Thank you.
It's just a threat.
Let's see.
We're level 15.
I don't think there was anything else we could get.
Yeah, level 16 is the robot.
17 is missing string table entry.
And 19 is the cactus.
20 is the employee.
Second employee.
Maybe next time we...
Oh, let's check our new applicants as well.
Slow, slow.
No!
Check out his average and return station is fast.
He's got a strong immune system and he's a complaint
handler.
Alas, a death worthy of Alhala.
threat or a promise well well
the noah is quite uh quite tempting but for now i have to
get going tentacle living on mars yes um we shall raid
densetsu i will be there in just a few minutes actually oh
whoops and um like i said fun stuff happening so come check
it out thank you everybody thank you dorko thank you for the
pig we may wish for the bomb but we wish for the minto
streams even more if i had the stream within a stream joke
it was a twist on the line of edgar allen po poem oh a dream
within a dream oh oh sorry my brain is so extra slow today
let me set up the raid um we i'll see hopefully in about 15
minutes you guys hopefully then then then set to dot exe den
setu six month anniversary yeah see you in a few see you in
a few thanks to the stream boss sending healing vibes to
your ears thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you
have you seen the cast reveal trailer for stranger than
heaven cover stranger than heaven no i haven't i don't even
know what that is fake me thank you wait let me see stranger
than heaven oh oh it's the game it's the game whoa it's kind
of cool yeah the yakuza game wait i don't i knew the snoop
dog was in it but i did not know ado was in it Is she like
in a box?
How does that work?
Yay!
Thank you, everybody!
Thank you, thank you!
I will see you hopefully in a few minutes.
If not, then I'll see you when I see you next!
Bye-bye!
Thank you!
Bye-bye-bye-bye!
Bye-bye!