Hi,
my boo!
Welcome in, welcome in!
Howdy, howdy duty.
Welcome back!
We're almost at Tamadachi Live.
Before we jump into the game, I must catch you up on the
business of the island.
I did not play.
I did not play so much.
I, um, I, uh, I just, I played like, I, I did like my
dailies, you know what I mean?
And I took, I took screenshots and videos of important,
important things that happened in the episode.
Last time on the island.
Let's start from...
Hold on.
Let's see.
Oh, sorry.
This is my fantasy life.
Look at me in fantasy life.
It's so cute.
It looks just like me.
My fantasy...
She called it interfere gear.
And then this lady was like, are you trying to flirt with
me?
And I'm like, yeah, baby.
Oh, that thing, I took a screenshot because it's called a
mini spooky.
Y'all finky?
And then he's talking about a ghost and I took a screenshot.
I'm getting off topic.
Okay, let's start from the first thing.
A PowerPoint streamer.
So much innovation.
What are you talking about?
okay um ibu talked to haley joe osman and became not
interested the greatest development the greatest development
was ibu is not interested in becoming friends with haley joe
osman
that tracks seeing fantasy life and the camera roll is
amazing I'd love taking screenshots
your greatest win so far yes um this was a funny dream i
thought it was funny like look at all of us dressed in frog
outfits look at um what happened here wait is this a video
no why did i screenshot uh oh they became friends and they
talked about sucking life energy.
Minto and Gengar, they met up in the middle of the night
talking about sucking life energy because they're both
ghosts.
And then Snake was fantasizing about being sweethearts with
Minto.
He, look at them running on the beach together.
Minto and her sundress and her little sun hat.
And Snake and his...
What?
Beach shorts in the box.
He's like me.
He said, I want to be sweethearts.
That's what he said.
Ibu has a crush.
Ibu has a crush, everybody.
Would you like to know who is the crush?
On who?
who drum roll please
frogbert i guess sorry i got popcorn for this episode
frogbert lore accurate as foretold i know i know everything
is falling into place everything is falling into place i
never really noticed frogbert before but now i can't get his
face out of my mind that's exactly what he said that's
exactly what he said
so look at him he's all excited so cute um haley joel osman
said who is a celebrity that you like i said sabrina
carpenter oh you like sabrina carpenter big boss
which i just thought that was kind of funny
fishing for compliments is he i know right what did he
expect me to say what if i said haley july sorry i can't
even oh god never mind um gang i think it was gangar had a
crush on snake oh wait no he didn't lose interest just one
more very long part to wrap up this tomodachi life Are you
even listening to me?
The dulcet tone of your voice, Snock, helped me drift off to
sleep.
I wish I could listen to it forever.
He's still trying.
He hasn't gotten over it.
Has some hope.
You gotta get over it, man.
Oh, um, we, uh, I think, hold on.
Wait, what was this?
Oh, yeah.
Take a tap.
They're all out of sync.
Power Eternal.
I think I solved a lot of problems, and that's what
happened.
Oh, yeah.
Aibu, Hela, Joazma, and Minto were talking about what it
would be like to consume a Keku Joaz shit.
for a year.
Probably really terrible.
Only a bronze.
We'll get to the gold.
They're so like into the conversation though.
I thought that was cute.
Look at snake on the screen.
Can I just display to the table?
I think I just thought this was funny.
This is not news.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Is everything alright?
On second thought, I'll eat at home.
I haven't had anyone eat at the restaurant yet.
Um, yeah, he had a dream.
I thought it was kind of funny.
It's an ice cream cone and he wants it.
But then if you click on it to give it to him, it becomes
evil.
Yeah, consume the evil ice cream.
Yeah, it's...
Ew, it's disgusting.
And that's all that's happened.
What happened?
How exciting is that?
Surprised he reached the point where he considered giving it
to him?
Yeah, that's true.
But now we can go back in and see what's all going on.
I haven't opened up the game today, so...
Thanks for the recap episode.
Yeah.
And I have some more memes that I would like to make today.
I also spruced up my island a little bit.
Oh!
He is a recluse.
Actually, he is an outcast.
Oh my gosh, Gengar's at the restaurant!
He's all ready to eat.
Is that omelrice?
No, kidding.
What is that?
What's that?
Pancakes?
I can't tell.
Looks like omel rice.
Let's start with the news.
Very exciting.
Exciting stuff.
Love the outfit on Gengar.
Thank you!
I thought it was so cute!
Hello!
And welcome to the evening edition of Mean News.
This Justin Frogberg has admitted that he failed to capture
vacation footage when asked to do so.
Hello?
Frogbert told reporters, I did start recording a video.
Frogbert is now a cowboy.
But it was within the wrong.
There was an unfortunate filter enabled that made us all
look like wombats.
Oh, wombats.
A thorough investigation will be taking place with some
suggesting the wombat filter is just an excuse.
And that no footage was actually captured.
We asked residents for their reactions.
reactions oh yeah we heard about this all the time back when
i was a kid when you were a kid what a waste of time thanks
for watching i think the only time i've ever agreed with
that man and this has been the seven o'clock news
but yeah look we have some cherry blossoms i made some more
pathways i organized some things Let's get our money, money.
Oh, yeah.
$98.
Cha-ching, baby.
Nice.
Yeah, it's a very cute island.
Very cute.
I want to make this, like, another...
Like, the romantic beach zone for all confessions.
Before we talk to anybody, we'll, like, get all the new
things.
Steampunk.
Oh, that's cute.
Rainy day!
Bye.
Hmm.
Oh.
Jail clothes.
Steampunk does look cool.
The face mask.
IQ could become bubble tea!
I like the star pendant too.
Wait, whoop.
This is so... Here we go.
For our Jedi girlies.
Sushi.
The detective hat?
Yeah, let's get the detective hat.
The Tims?
The new buck boots?
Is that not a Vicky dress?
Red polka dots?
You're so right.
And today I do want to make Vicky.
I really like this outfit.
I would wear that.
The stand-up is kind of expensive.
Let's go check the grocery store before we...
I wanted to make...
Wow, okay, we got some fancy stuff here today.
That's got to be somebody's favorite, right?
Um, but, uh, what was I saying?
Why is nobody out and about?
Everybody's stuck in home.
I want to make more houses more people I Oh I meant to draw
some like more foods and some more things while away But in
between stream but you know Only wish that Vicky and Phoebe
me's will be as beautiful as yours Sure Um Yeah Phoebe will
get a me too How about a quick game of no repeat No repeats!
Okay.
Do I like filet mignon?
That's not bad.
Yeah, I like it.
No repeats.
Food?
Okay.
Lollipop.
Salad.
Kitsune udon.
What are these choices?
Canoli?
Watermelon?
Salary?
Cotton candy?
String cheese?
Caprice salad?
I said caprice salad!
Oh my god, I always think of caprice salad when I'm playing
this game.
That was fun.
Oh, you stupid head.
No burger.
Oh, macaroni and cheese.
Congratulations, you won.
Cute, thank you!
You too!
Let's go bigger, go ham.
I could have gotten a Shikishi or a robot.
I messed up.
Hello to all.
Wait.
Minto and Gengar are hanging out.
Who the hell is this guy in love with?
Um...
Good evening.
It may just be my imagination, but...
I get the feeling that Joe has a crush on me.
She doesn't.
Ask for a date.
You sure about that?
Ask for a date!
Um...
Hard pass.
My feelings are platonic at best.
Okay, weirdo!
What the hell?
I just need to know what the rules are, and then I can
relax.
Help Snake Me can marry an Otacon Me one day.
Am I the Otacon Me or...
Just walking along the street, being a freakazoid.
What's wrong with you?
Why did you do...
Oh, what's up with Gengar?
Wait, what?
ouch the green tea fell from the tree
what what is up with Gengar what the hell Ibu has something
probably wants like more trees or something oh you are now a
sprout good evening yep I told you more trees welcome back
to my town What do you mean it doesn't have enough greenery?
Can we get enough greenery?
Can we get some plants around here?
What were you thinking?
Show me your vision.
It makes no sense.
Why are there planters?
I mean...
Okay.
Sure.
I'll let you do your thing.
It will cost $70.
I give him a sprout outfit and suddenly he just demands more
greenery.
The hedges are kind of nice though.
I mean it's less work for me.
Speaks for the trees.
Thanks.
Let's give Aibu, I'm gonna give you guys luxury.
Filet mignon for you.
You better like it.
If you don't like it.
You only liked it.
I'm sorry, you enjoy peaches more than filet mignon.
Nothing beats a good old...
I forgot the way he walks.
Let's watch him come out.
Oh yeah.
That's the king.
I think the emote section could use more greenery.
Can we get...
Freaking jump scare.
Can we get more?
Five random plant emotes.
Frogbert.
Look at this guy.
Huh?
Hey, good evening.
Good evening.
My room could use a new...
No!
It looks great as it is.
You really think so?
Well, if you insist...
Shut up, Frogbert.
He is really handsome, isn't he?
Yeah, I gave... I designed that outfit.
Am I perfect?
No.
But you'll look past my flaws, won't you?
That is such a Frogbert thing to say.
Oh!
There's such a frog.
What's happening?
What's going on?
What is that scent you're wearing?
It's absolutely divine.
Oh, yes.
It's nothing.
Whatever you're wearing is way nicer, flinky.
It should be marketed as a perfume.
Well, it is, but yours smells so nice.
all over.
In fact, whenever I snort you, I hear you sing and it makes
me snort better, by proxy.
I have to disagree.
Your sin is so captivating.
I wish I could get my nostrils enlarged to smell it more
intensely.
Well, that wouldn't have been far, didn't it?
Let's talk about something else now.
You freak- I out-freaked you.
Vicky out-freaked you guys!
Good job.
Good job, little Minky.
Gengar is bored!
Does anyone have a crush on Gengar?
Come here.
Eek.
Give us a sniff.
Oh, yeah.
What's going on?
Tongue twister.
time that was so scary red mango green mango green mango
green mango green mango green mango red mango green mango
green mango keep me off and out freaks us out there i'm so
excited to see you at smash gone see you there red mango
green mango king mango red mango great friends what happened
What the?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, all right.
I think Frogbird needs assistance.
Oh, my God.
I'll bring somebody.
I'll bring Aibu.
Oh, I have to go get him.
Come here.
You need help.
This guy needs help.
Please help me.
He's still crushing.
It's good.
This is such a beforehand.
You might need to use a little more room.
No.
It is no longer cut down.
Wait, it is mute.
Never really noticed I boo before.
No way.
But he's so radiant.
Am I falling in love?
It must be love.
So it's love after all.
I'm actually in love.
I should start thinking of romantic date ideas.
Guys, imagine the children.
Breathe, breathe, breathe, breathe.
head over heels look i mean look at that guy frogbert is
staring at ibu no that guy's gone me too after i have a
crush on somebody on behalf of all ibu's may i say i do
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah come out stop being a recluse well
because we have so people that are stuck inside i think it's
time to add some more me's baby so i have a couple that i
would like to add um there's three today i think that i want
to do yeah we'll do vicky phoebe and then one more you tell
us not to get pregnant all the time girl i've changed my
mind if it's If it's frog burp.
If it's frog burp.
Frobu?
I burp?
If I see the baby, I'll cry.
Because it'd be cute for real.
You need to click the blue arrow.
That's...
Okay.
Where?
How?
How do I click the blue arrow?
Do you see?
Do you see a...
Do you see a cursor on this screen?
It's YouTube.
It's not me.
petition for detective Brett Halligan no!
I don't want it oh my god
yeah the bug is still here it's very annoying here I can
maybe do this oh that actually worked nice here just because
you annoyed me though I'm gonna do this there you go yeah
now you're gonna tell me that I need to create a channel to
join the chat.
Yeah.
Now you're gonna tell me yeah, this is, yeah.
Create a channel to join the chat.
I will.
Into Aridu to my island and Minto is now hopelessly in love
with Doki.
Any advice for her to get Doki's attention?
I don't know if she wants that.
Impressive you can stream without a channel.
Oh, I've been keeping this secret from you.
I am YouTube.
I'm the YouTuber.
Let's start with...
Let me get a picture of Phoebe.
Phoebe.
Yes, yes.
Very good.
channel my ocean.
FeeBee Channel TV.
Common road up.
Ooh.
That's a bit better.
Maybe that's actually really accurate to our model.
Whoa!
Juta Street!
Thank you so much for that, Kuta!
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Alright.
When I got him, there we go.
be a possibility we have we literally have like better
kermit why would you ask for anything else why would you ask
for anything else and we'll make her face nice and small
nice and small all right sub color let's do let's do the
pink early to give it get us in the mood now do i want her
hair up or down let's see let's see what stuff we have in
the back party in the back What is this?
Oh, it's a ribbon!
That's too cute!
What is this?
That's just a ponytail.
Where'd the pink accents go?
Is it?
No way.
Oh, there it is.
There it is.
What's this?
Hi, ponytail.
Where's the stuff on the side?
Well, this is kind of close.
If only you were on the side.
Absorbed by the bow.
We could go with something like that.
Her hair's a little bit more wavy.
Maybe?
Oh my gosh, wait, it's so cute, actually.
You can move the hair tight.
Wait, you can?
Oh, you're right!
Oh, my God!
Good!
It looks good!
Wait, let's fix her bangs too.
Nambuship back pay.
Thanks for two years, a little joyce.
Silly, it's another positive...
What do you mean back pay?
That doesn't exist!
Thank you so much, Senya!
Thank you so much for the pink!
Thank you!
What if we do this one instead?
Wait.
I kind of...
I like the one sticking up.
I'm so...
I kind of like this one.
Hmm.
No, no.
She loses all her hair.
No, I will...
I'll...
Let's see.
We could go with this one.
Oh, okay.
This one's just in the back.
Okay.
We'll go with this one.
Very nice.
Wait.
Oh, yeah, good, good, good.
Never mind.
Let's go back to the bangs.
Ooh.
Oh, those are kind of long.
Hmm.
Taco.
What if we give her double...
We'll go with this one.
Coming along.
Yeah, of course.
Oh, my...
my memes have come along.
Now, Phoebe's gotta have really big, thick eyebrows.
Actually, I want them to look like Cheetos.
Cheeto puffs.
And then we'll give her a stinking big, big, shiny, big,
moy-moy eyes.
But also a little up to no good.
Wait.
Phoebe's eyes are what color?
Like a pinky?
Oh, they're yellow.
I'm stupid.
I couldn't see.
Brown?
That's brown to you guys!
Like this?
It's like that.
It's like a light brown.
It's like a light, light brown.
Yellow, gold, Null.
Null?
Mustard.
I think you guys are just hungry.
She's also got teeny tiny nose.
And then the mouth.
Like this.
It just feels very Phoebe.
Like that?
It feels very Phoebe.
What is this one?
Oh
wait, no!
This is her face.
That is her mouth.
Actually, right there.
Why is my thing lagging?
There we go, there we go.
We could give her the one tooth.
No, that's actually the face her mouth makes that shape.
She's got ears.
Not those.
These.
Yeah, she's got ears.
No glasses.
We'll make her blushing.
Okay.
I like that.
Oh, not that one.
This one.
I like that one.
What if we... I think she has...
Does she have small freckles?
Stop staring at me with them by gold wires.
And then I'm gonna draw some flowers in her hair.
Okay.
That's like some leaf.
That's another leaf.
We recorded the podcast last night.
The Den Setsu podcast.
If you are unaware.
We have a podcast.
For our Patreon.
Monthly episodes.
And.
We discussed that Phoebe might.
If she were to reincarnate.
She might be.
Become like a parasitic.
You know those parasitic.
Parasites that control ants.
I'm doing my best.
Sometimes I get it a little uneven.
Sorry, guys.
Cordyceps?
Maybe.
I think that's good.
I think you can tell it's Phoebe, for sure.
Can you guys tell?
I think you can tell.
tell.
Phoebe and I are about the same height so we'll put her
we'll put her equal yeah we will have tinier characters on
the island so I must and she's anybody she's taller by a
centimeter I don't think that really she's taller by one
centimeter That's like nothing!
Okay, fine.
I think that's a centimeter.
It counts.
This Fee's name is...
The bus time has no...
Fee!
Fee.
Baby.
Feebus!
Phoebus?
No, it's gotta be Phoeby.
That can be a good nickname though.
My name is Phoeby.
Ew!
That is not how you sound though.
I'm a terrible gen mate.
Wait.
What is Phoeby's birthday?
Oh yeah, we're in the same month.
I do know that.
20th.
She's like five days old though.
We'll put her at the same age as me.
My name is Phoebe.
It's nice to meet you.
Today is April 24th, 2026.
So, how does this voice sound?
No.
My name is Phoebe.
No, no.
It's nice to meet you.
No.
Today, my name is Phoebe.
My name is Phoebe.
It's nice to meet you.
My name is Stevie.
Today is...
It's nice to meet you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Today is April 24th, 2026.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, how does this voice sound?
It sounds good.
Oh, oh, wait.
My name is Stevie.
Wait.
Yeah, hold on.
Yes.
My name is Stevie.
Null?
Phoebe?
Hmm.
She's like in the middle.
We'll put her to quicker.
And she's like honest but also very polite.
We'll put her more polite.
And her energy is definitely varied.
Thinking?
Chill, good, chill.
Actually, well she's serious and chill, but more chill, you
know.
Overall, she a quirky yao.
Okay, here we go.
Dating preferences.
Everybody, everybody, everybody is a target.
Considerate.
Amicable.
Thoughtful, honest, innocent.
Does things at our own pace.
Cheerleader, positive, enthusiastic, and always beaming.
Smiles for their own sake and to help out.
I think I made Phoebe.
Chan-Chi-B.
I think I made...
the most Phoebe Chan Chibi you could ever Phoebe Chan
Chibi-ist.
Did you see that some people were upset that there's not
enough...
mean me's.
You can't make them rude enough.
Let's build a house for Phoebe.
From now on you'll be able to place houses anywhere you like
on the island.
What do you mean?
I wasn't able to do that before.
We can expand our island.
It's nice to meet you.
Yes.
I'm Phoebe.
Hi, Phoebe.
I'm a considerate cheerleader.
No matter what you're going through, I'll have your back.
I'll cheer you on as you grow and pick you up as you fall.
It's hard to get them angry at each other.
I hope we get along well.
Yeah.
Thank you for your identity card.
I'd love to go traveling by myself.
She's already Naruto running.
She's so happy.
What's going on down here?
They're ranting about ice lattes.
Wait, I want some...
What's up with Halo?
I don't care.
What is that?
What is it?
They ignored it.
It's moving.
What is that?
Oh!
I don't know what it is!
It looks like Gengar's...
Oh.
It looked like he was chasing after him.
All right, now Minto!
Minto and Phoebe and Shibi need to meet each other.
See, Minto's bored and went some company!
Come here.
All the way here.
Oh!
Pardon me, could I have a moment?
My name is Minto.
Nice to meet you.
Minto.
What is that room?
What's wrong with my room?
Getting familiar.
The phrase liquid.
That she just learned.
Yippee!
We're like-minded.
Oh, good, good, good.
The girls are chatting.
But we need one more member.
A full...
What are you doing?
Full densetsuness.
Are you bored?
I forgot also to check out...
Wait, not the treasures.
That is my treasure.
Please come again.
How do you do a British accent?
In this...
in this game
okay we'll add our next two means out of 70 means holy cow
you need to have english uk in the console apparently no
victoria roman
american vicky can't hurt us she will she will hurt us all
right she She also has a very small round face.
So we'll go with that.
For her hair.
You know, I'm kind of going off of vibes here and that...
I haven't really looked at anyone else that other people
have...
Well, I have, but like not studied it.
You know what I mean?
Does she have like a set that works?
Like a side drill.
There is a drill hair option.
There is!
But I don't see it.
I thought there was one.
There is this.
Here, let's change the blonde first.
To give us in the mood.
Her hair is like an in-between.
That's okay.
What's this one look like?
No.
Wait, maybe.
That's better.
There's a single drill option.
Hold on, I'll go slower.
Press R.
What is it in the back?
Is it like this one?
Like that?
Yarr?
Yippee!
Alright, now we need to get...
Give it real swoops.
Alright, from here we can make The...
The biscuit.
I think.
I think this is a good base.
The cinnamon bun.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, I think the one I chose looks better than this.
I'm never wrong.
From here?
Cinnamon bun.
Biscuit, biscuit.
I do risk it for the biscuit.
I always do.
I've always said that.
Some of these are so fascinating.
Hmm.
She's got the thinner eyebrows, though.
Crazy.
We'll just do it like this, I think.
Okay.
Blue eyes tell lies.
blue blue oh god
people with blue eyes this is how you actually look I'm just
letting you know if you have blue eyes I feel like this this
eye shape gives British is it just me am I the only one that
thinks that I'm the only one that thinks that You have blue
eyes.
Yeah, but like, I'm a ghost.
Do
you guys get it?
Do you guys see what I mean?
They just feel very...
British for some reason.
Wait!
What if I make Sonic Vicky?
I just wrote Snowick the Hedgehog.
Brilliant?
I agree.
Now, do we go Sonic the movie first iteration or the fixed
version?
We'll go like a la Amy Rose.
Alright.
We got this.
We got this team.
We've got this team.
It's close.
Oh, her eyebrows.
I guess she doesn't need eyebrows because she's gonna be,
you know, a hedgehog.
That's fine.
Do you guys already see the vision?
Wait, how is this so good?
How is this already so good?
Then if I ever make shadow, you know?
That should be good for now.
Give her a little bit of bluish.
Yeah.
Do the one on the left?
What?
On the teeth?
I have no idea what you just said.
This one's pretty cute too.
Actually, I think I like that one better.
but this one feels more vicky okay all right uh okay we did
that okay time to face paint human ears well she's like so
close but not quite she's okay you guys know animorphs she's
like mid transformation uh into into um um A hedgehog.
Wait.
So she's gonna have human ears.
Oops.
Good enough.
Yeah, that's good.
So if it looks disturbing, it's not actually disturbing.
It's because the transformation is taking place and it's a
little...
It's hurting her body.
You know?
So please be kind when you decide to criticize how she is,
you know?
Poor thing.
I know, I know, I know.
But this is her dream.
She's always wanted this.
Am I doing the right color?
It is why.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
She's always wanted this.
Yes!
It's giving a little...
Unibrow, but that's okay.
Don't worry about it.
I wish we could take color from the hair, you know, itself.
But I think maybe like this color would be good.
To start doing the roll.
She rolling, she rolling.
Wait, where is it?
Why isn't it showing up on her?
On her.
Do I have to put it on another layer?
It's under the hair.
Wait, how do I change the layer?
Was it here?
Paint on top.
There we go.
Wait, what the heck?
The hair is 3D.
You can't layer over it.
No!
Oh, no.
Maybe her hair is too thick.
Yeah, I think it is.
Oh, no.
Well, we did our best.
That's okay.
We could still put her hat.
Yeah, it's fine.
That's fine.
Nice.
Wow, that's really good, actually.
No, let's do...
It's more like purple, actually.
I love how the... Have you guys noticed the music is just
like...
It's like... The Sims almost.
That should be good.
What else does a hedgehog have?
Quills?
Maybe blue?
Wait.
I don't think hedgehogs have any ears.
Oh, they do.
They have ears.
She would need cat ears.
Or hedgehog ears, you know.
Hmm.
We can make her a little bit more spiky.
Let's make her a little bit more spiky.
but how do i do her hair color well let me oh wait there it
is oh my goodness they do let you oh thank goodness wait all
right here we go
oh wait on her hat
let me avoid the hat let me one redo redo
One more time.
Actually, we might be able to work with that.
Well, I don't want to redo the eyes, you know?
Let's try this.
No, see, I would have to redo the eyes.
What if we...
paint behind?
Oh!
That's what she was missing!
How is it so perfect?
Maria Roman has all the Chaos Emeralds now.
Vicky can be super Vicky!
It's actually perfect.
Holy cow.
Oh my god.
Let's do...
We'll do like this color.
And do this too.
Fill that in right there.
Wait.
I don't want to get into her eyes.
I keep messing.
I keep messing up.
I think it's good though.
It looks like a hedgehog.
That looks like a hedgehog.
Oh my god, it's so good.
She's snatched, but she's still got her boobies.
Victoria the Hedgehog.
Oops.
Wait, my bad.
No, no!
Vic.
Victoria.
Okay.
The.
It puts the Sonic on its face, or it gets those.
What do you mean by that?
Wait, what did I accent?
Victoria...
Oh, oops.
The...
Hedgehog.
My name is Victoria the Hedge.
Wait, it doesn't fit!
How do you fit Shadow the Hedgehog?
Wait, how do you fit it?
August...
Ace.
She'll also be 19 with us.
We're all 19.
My name is Victoria the Hedge.
It doesn't sound British at all.
Today is April 24th, 2026.
My name is Victoria the Hedge.
It's nice to meet you.
Ugh.
My name is Victoria the Hedge.
Oh.
And because she's got to be really fast.
My name is Victoria the Hedge.
It's nice to meet you.
She's questioning herself.
24th, 2020s.
My name is Victoria the Hedge.
Oh my gosh, she sounds like a Valley Girl.
It's nice to meet you.
It's...
Today is April 24th, 2026.
My name is Victoria the Hedge.
This is like what she sounds like when she's trying to do a
Valley Girl accent.
No.
We can just say that the hedgehog transformation is robbed
of her accent.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hmm, Vicky!
We'll put her in the middle again.
Speech?
She's quite honest, I'd say.
Her energy is varied.
She's pretty chill.
Overall?
Hmm.
Hmm, quirky.
Actually, no, she's a hedgehog.
Duh, she's got to be fast.
I'm so stupid.
Everybody's at risk.
Okay.
Let me at least capitalize it.
The hedge.
But everyone knows...
Wait.
Oh, wait, I could do this.
Wait, I can add it.
I know I can add it.
My name is...
Hold on, hold on.
My name is Victoria the Hedge.
We could do this.
We can add the hog.
Hedgehog.
She'll say that...
My name is Hop.
Oh, wait.
No, no, no, no.
Wait, I wonder if this one's longer though.
Victoria...
No.
Not with.
The...
Hedgehog.
Oh!
My name is...
Is Victoria the Hedgehog?
I didn't know Victoria was a furry.
My life was a lie.
No, she's a hedgehog.
Sociable, optimistic, and passionate.
Follows their instincts.
Bold and captivating.
Their wit and charm light up a room.
It's never a dull moment when they're around.
So true.
All right, Victoria the Hedge.
I dropped my joy cleanse.
We'll put you right next to Phoebe.
Furbo.
Fawky right next to each other.
Uh-oh, what's happening?
Oh, hello.
Hey there.
It's nice to meet you, big boss.
I'm Victoria the Hedgehog.
I'm an outgoing go-getter who loves exploring new ideas.
I tend to do whatever comes to mind.
Sounds like she has a list, too.
I can't wait to start living here.
Aw, yeah.
You want something to eat?
I'll give you some roast beef.
dude.
She liked it.
Chili dogs.
She can only eat chili dogs.
I hope you can spend more time visiting me.
Big boss.
Yeah, I'll be back.
I'll be back.
We have roast beef in the UK too.
Oh my god!
We're expanding!
Taking more territory.
Beans on toast.
We interrupt to bring you some breaking news.
Here's what's happening on our island.
We're developing the sea around, yay.
Get stronger, own.
Welcome back away, Tom and Siderone.
Has progressed nicely.
The sea, we're taking over the sea.
One excited resident is quoted as saying, I hope we can keep
growing the island until the whole world is the island.
Any residents will expand the family's sea, allowing our
home to grow even more.
That looks exactly like me.
Thanks.
Thanks for watching.
I think I'm pretty good at making these memes.
Who's hanging out at my house?
Oh, Phoebe!
Good.
Good, good, good.
Well, oh.
Go do something with your life.
Throw him in the restaurant.
Hello.
Good evening.
Wait, this is a song from...
Original Tomodachi Live.
This is from the concert!
They're teasing us.
This is so messed up.
You mean it's all the island?
Oh, it has been.
I'm gonna give you...
Wait, this song too!
I'm gonna give you a sugar glider
You give him a sugar glider You only like it
Let's give you some It's while savoring It's cutely Oh cute.
Whoa, that's a big bite.
Eat while savoring.
Mmm.
I like to eat with gusto.
Scarce down with wild abandon.
Big chomp for you guys.
I feel a bit more like myself.
Gusto.
Very nice.
Oh.
Okay, he's done.
That's fine.
Oh, what's going on here?
Snake seems to be watching Phoebe closely.
Oh, what's happening?
Encourage, encourage!
Go for it!
He seems...
Karinka!
Pardon me!
Could I have a moment?
She's so shy.
My name is Snake!
Nice to meet you.
Snake, I'm Phoebe.
Say hello.
Phoebe.
to spill the beans on some of Miaoing Man's deepest secrets.
Those are big secrets.
Yay!
They seem like minded.
Hrnka!
Thanks for helping me and Phoebe get closer.
I think we should be able to fill our thing now.
What's wrong with you?
I'll bring somebody.
We'll make, we'll do, we'll do Victoria the Hedgehog on the
rescue.
Are you in trouble?
Please just help me.
What do you mean I made her?
What do you mean I made her cryptid?
Can you try not doing that?
No, I actually have it.
She's literally what she always would want to become.
She's perfect!
I had a fun time with Ibu.
You're welcome.
If I'm being honest, it's all thanks to you.
Yeah, I know.
On this island, she fits right in.
What do you mean by that?
You call her a cryptid and then says she fits right in.
We can...
Oh yeah, I forgot to say I unlocked travel tickets.
But also level ups are so fun too.
We could get the ballet or street dance.
More quirks.
Or shall we go to Oceana?
Let's do it.
I have to give it to somebody!
Who wants to go to Oceana?
Maybe Snake.
I was...
I am going to Australia soon.
Secret mission for Snake.
Send...
Nobody comes back!
Maybe.
Get rid of this guy?
See ya.
Get out of here.
Haley, Joe Osmond.
Never come back.
Never come home.
Oh.
Are you really giving me an Oceania tour?
Thank you so much.
Time to pack my bags.
Yeah, and leave.
Never come back.
Never show your face here again.
Wait, he brought Gengar.
Wait a second.
No!
It's tough finding a cab out here.
I think you guys tricked me.
Maybe I can hop in this kangaroo's pouch.
Not the smirk.
Whoa, what is this?
Inside New Zealand's Tasman Glacier.
Hands frozen.
Send mittens.
Drop bears cave room.
Aw.
They do look pretty happy together.
Oh, drown.
Drown him.
Take away his...
No,
I don't want this without him.
I don't want those.
Ew.
Snorkel!
Thanks so much for letting me take it.
This souvenir is for you.
Oh, he got me something.
Oh!
It's so cute.
Let's select an expression.
Hmm.
Ending a sentence.
Maybe something that's like...
Not that I care.
What?
Bully McGuire says.
I
missed the part where that's my problem.
That's what it is, right?
I'm going to do not that I care.
and real jerk not that i care yeah he's a jerk
thank you now i feel more like myself not that i care i
wonder big boss have you ever traveled overseas yeah i have
one day i want to sail all seven seas you can be my first
mate not that i care
I don't want to be here.
I don't want that at all.
Wait, Phoebe already has a problem.
You just moved here.
What's wrong?
Good evening.
I'm so hungry.
Oh, she's hungry.
Well, I got some creamy stew here for you.
Yeah.
You are quite unfortunately.
making him kind of boring.
No, I'm not!
She really liked the stew.
I want to find...
One of my goals today is to find something that someone
loves, you know?
Maybe we can make something that someone would love.
Oh!
What's she doing?
Is that Minto asleep?
Uh-oh.
Minto has a dream.
Oh.
What's the dream?
One sheep.
Two sheep.
That's so cute!
Three sheep.
Do you think we'll get a sheep costume?
Oh, that's a...
Four sheep.
That's...
That's not...
Five sheep.
Oh.
Of course, the first one was snake.
Whoa.
It was a dream.
It was a dream?
Yeah!
Wow, we got the sheep costume!
Of course he is the demon.
Wait, what?
Let's, let's, I'm gonna take you to Snake.
Which would you rather have?
Friendship or love?
I don't need either of them.
But, that's so sad.
Little, little happiness.
Here, come here.
We're gonna get you.
give you love we're making this happen where's snake where's
snake snake oh there he is wait what's wrong with this guy
are you bored that dream how can the game see through your
mind so accurately you drop something it looks important
thank you so much i'm so it's
too easy it's Way too easy.
Oh, my techno album like that is a great look.
Is this the sort of love that begins with a techno album?
It must be love.
You're right.
I can't believe Cupid visited me in the form of a techno
album.
All that's left is to ask Snake Out.
I can do this.
Where we are?
Will this be our first couple?
Oh.
no hang out with him what are you doing what are you doing
you stupid i like how it just flashes vicky's face at me
what's going on again gar's house i think he wants to play a
game oh no so truth is i've always loved you snuck uh-oh um
i had a feeling that was the case So you saw right through
me?
He doesn't know.
I think if Minto confesses, then Gengar will show up.
I've spent a lot of time practicing how to politely reject
you.
Hold up.
Did I just get rejected during my own practice run?
He knows.
Someone's got to make a move.
Someone's got to make a move on Snake.
wait Gengar I think Gengar is making the first move The love
triangles begin Oh my god Oh my god it's happening I thought
I had feelings for snob But what?
My heart starts to race when I think about Joe Who do I
really love?
Didn't he do this last stream?
Gengar cannot make up his mind Oh, please.
The instant pivot.
He rejected himself in his imagination and immediately was
like, hmm, maybe I don't like this guy.
Fight for Snake.
I think so, too.
I think you need to stop.
Fight for Snake.
Snark.
Huh.
Huh?
Whom?
You're right.
Oh, I do love Snark.
I'm going to work harder than ever to earn his attention.
Don't settle, Gengar.
Likes a lot.
Ultra Friends is crazy.
Nobody's best friends with Haley, Joel Osman.
Hmm.
Ultra Friends, don't.
That's so mean.
There was one last...
Wait, what's going on over here?
Gosh, Minto and Aibo hang out all the time, though.
Trying to recruit others to go explore the outside world.
They're like actual besties.
Um, there was one more me I wanted to create.
I'm gonna do my best to make them as quickly as possible.
I need a reference.
I'm
not gonna tell you guys who it is.
No, no Koharu this time.
Koharu and Ocelot will be next time.
Who else would I make next time?
Koharu and Ocelot are next time.
Yeah, we can make Kiara.
Actually, let me add Kiara to the list.
I want to make Kiara.
Hmm, I need a good reference for this guy.
Actually, just so that you guys can also follow my
reference.
I will be making...
Tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick
yeah manifest yeah we're making the pretzel we're making the
pretzel hard
to say i
don't want like a A blank slate that we can just draw.
You know what I mean?
Maybe something like that.
Or what if...
Wait.
What if we do like a...
Trying to decide what perspective I want to.
Mohawk Shirley?
Yeah, I think so too.
I think so too.
Hold on, I'm getting my...
There we go.
All right.
This one's so stylish.
Something like...
Well, actually, I think...
I think a round one would be better because it's like the
top of his head, you know?
It's like the top.
Maybe this one...
Like the bump there, you know?
And we'll do...
We'll do blue as the sub-color.
Oh!
Ooh!
And for the other color, Make it like...
Like this sandy.
Again, blanks?
Well, not so blank.
Like maybe tiny eyebrows, you know?
Like that.
This is my Gajinka.
Don't question it.
You can question a little, but mostly don't.
No eyelashes.
Tiny, tiny, beady eyes.
Okay, looking good.
How pointy of a nose can we go?
Oh, it's not big enough.
It's huge!
But it's not pointy enough.
Don't worry, we're going to be drawing all over this, so if
you're concerned, you're concerned, will be heard and
addressed.
No ears.
I don't think we need anything.
We'll come back to this, though, just in case.
Alright, let's draw.
Can't believe they put lizards in the game.
No, is this a lizard?
Are we adding Koharu?
Next time, I said.
Yes, yes, next time.
Fine.
Wait, so if I paint behind...
Yeah, okay, good.
Hmm.
We'll add the details.
Kind of like, you know...
Doesn't have to be perfect because...
I mean...
That's nature.
Nothing is symmetrical in nature.
It's just his patterning.
As a Ketzel Kualis.
I
don't know how you could look at this guy and think lizard.
A pterosaur.
But I sometimes say dinosaur just because I like to lump
them all together.
That makes people angry too.
They're like, actually, they're very different.
Paint on top.
Here it comes.
Wait, I'm going to do, I'm going to do the shapes here.
Oh my gosh, perfect.
Can I do an upside down?
Rotate?
Wait, hold on.
Hold on.
Redo, redo.
Because I want to fix this.
Wait, why are the eyes all weird now?
Wait!
How do I fix it?
Oh, okay, like that.
Oops.
Control Z.
Oh, oops.
So, you, but that's so weird.
Like, you can only...
So, it's either, it's one or all, like...
Oh, my gosh, I keep doing that.
It's so annoying.
Oh, it does.
Yeah, we have to paint behind.
No!
That's fine.
This is okay.
Forgot to change the color.
We can fix him Yes
The nose would always pierce through anyway You think so?
That's fine This is okay This is okay Now what just rotate
Oh this way No Oh L and R I'm stupid
We have to make it smaller
As long as it like Pokes out you know a little bit Like
that?
I think it still works.
We just need more dots.
On his face.
Trust the process.
Maybe.
He's got freckles.
Or something.
What is that?
It's cuticle flowers.
There's a different nose that's thinner.
Let's try it.
Maybe we go with a...
Maybe going with the big nose is the problem.
Like if we go with just nostrils.
That could be it.
This could be it.
He could be a bird now.
Heck no nose.
But he has to breathe.
I think that's just the nostrils works.
Wait, what's this one?
We're doing this, we're doing this.
I
don't think I'm a huge fan of the brown dots.
Maybe like a different color.
I wish I could...
I wish I could, like, do all around his head, you know?
Oh yeah, why don't we have some stuff here?
Hmm.
How can I make his beak look more 3D, you know?
Hmm...
Change the skin tone to what?
Add shadows.
Shading.
Shading would be like on the side, right?
Let me try with the straight.
Where is the straight?
It's not an ice cream color.
Change the color with the fill tool.
That's true, yeah.
I could go with like more of a...
I mean, there's like other...
Let's try like a yellowish.
It looks like a...
Looks like a...
Wait!
The mouth is also throwing it off.
Hold on.
We can fix this.
Okay, good!
This is good!
It was on Wednesday, but I was busy all week.
And a happy birthday!
Happy birthday!
Now we're just giving like definition and stuff, you know?
To the bird.
Just a sad, sad frowny face.
But he's not sad, he's very happy.
Oh!
Wait!
Wait.
Did I pick the wrong color?
I did.
Ugh!
I picked the wrong color.
More golden.
But it's not this, that's too dark.
It won't let me.
You can fill it after.
But it won't let me select the color of the...
It won't let me select the color of the beard.
No, the dropper tool doesn't work.
Sadly.
I can try, but...
I tried it before.
It doesn't really work.
I have to get it to, like, blend in, you know?
Maybe like this and then I erase.
Yeah, see, I'll show you guys.
Maybe, okay, hold on.
We can do this.
We can make the hair color.
Hold on.
The beard color.
And then we could select it from there.
Is it this one?
That looks right.
Okay, okay.
Now we're thinking with portals.
Yeah, we'll just change it back after.
Yeah, exactly, exactly.
Something like that, yeah?
Wait!
Why is it black?
No!
We'll just shave it later.
We'll shave it later.
Shave.
It's still not...
Wait.
Oh, it is the right color.
Just kidding.
Kind
of looks like a shoe bill Is that Ketzel Kualis?
It is, it is!
I like how the reference I got Makes him look like a chicken
wing
That could be good
Oh well, I guess his beak would be over
Let me change his hair back.
I wonder if I can make him gray.
Like a homestuck.
It might help a little bit.
Wait, and then we change the beard.
And not the beard, but you know.
Oh, is it this one?
Yeah.
This one.
The
tallest guy.
I think it all, Phil.
I think so.
Nice.
My name is Quetzalcoatless.
Yippee!
I think I made a guy.
Oh.
Like a long time ago.
Wait.
He'll be our oldest me.
50 years old.
And his birthday is, uh...
Today.
My name is Quetzalcoatless.
I like it.
50 million.
No.
Movement.
Quick.
Scary.
Speech.
honest.
This guy, he's like a freak, flat energy.
Very serious.
And mostly normal.
Daily preferences?
Everybody's at risk.
Okay.
He does sound scary.
I know you do not want to meet one of these guys.
Confident.
A buy the book straight talker puts a premium on results.
Yeah, because he's got to get food.
Determined self-starter cuts their own path with his My
troll Sona?
What's that?
This is not a troll, this is a real guy.
Well, I'm gonna move stuff around later.
Um...
Hey, you must be big boss.
I am.
It's nice to meet you.
My name is Quetzalcoatlus.
I'm an ambitious maverick.
I want to experience everything this world has to offer.
I live life on my own terms and try to be my own me.
Thanks in advance for walking after me here.
What do you have to say?
If you're gonna be late, you might as well not even show up.
Oh my god.
He's probably hungry because he's a bird.
Birds first.
Birds first enchilada.
A silly looking bird.
Like it was made in spore.
Oh, we like it!
Nice.
Imagine the babies.
Very good.
Oh, what's happening?
We didn't go up to bring you some breaking news.
Breaking news!
Now here we shall be short celebrating.
Today, that's all purpose.
This is our wedding birthday, number 50.
We now take you off to this birthday party.
He has no friends except
for...
Thanks.
We ask presidents for their reactions.
That's definitely something to celebrate.
Congratulations.
Where are you?
Not that I care.
Thanks for watching.
I'm ugly.
Interrupted dates.
How could he say that?
He's so rude.
That's so mean.
Someone's coming out of their houses.
Oh my gosh, he's already in trouble.
What's wrong with you?
Hey, kid.
somebody i'll bring somebody um vicky vicky vicky vicky
vicky vicky vicky vicky vicky the hedge oh oops no no no
come back are you all right jolt's sincere you made him that
way i know but it's so I don't expect him to say that!
I'm gonna be okay.
About his birthday!
It was no trouble at all!
Yidori, thank you!
Thank you so much!
They're friends now!
Everybody's hanging out.
Hello, Godzilla.
Hey.
What's happening?
So I, um, been thinking about changing up my hairstyle.
Oh, I've always liked that look on you.
It reminds me of one of my grandparents.
Oh, he's still on the screen, sorry.
Oh, not exactly what I was going for.
Speaking of culinary creations, mixing a cakey Joloshit with
some paella is a taste sensation, right?
You really think so?
I nearly choked on a cakey Joloshit when I was a kid.
Haven't been able to stomach it since.
Oh, so glad I brought it up.
I had a lot of fun today.
Can I call you later tonight?
He's winking at him.
My cell phone is in the shop.
Oh, I, uh, hope they can fix it for you.
Jabble.
Me.
Fab and Grapple.
Yesteroni.
Is that the dude from Kingdom Hearts?
Yeah, it is!
They're still talking!
Wait, what is Gengar doing here?
Why is he just standing there for so long?
What is he doing?
He's following Frogbert for some reason.
What the hell?
Oh, oh, he's acting nonchalant.
Oh, oh.
Wait, what's happening?
Why is he actually...
Oh.
He's being a little freakazoid.
No, no.
What are you doing?
Even the game knows why he's following him.
Uh-oh.
what's up here to play red light i tried to play this one
before and i lost so this is my this is my revenge
urn gar
no no again i would die in squidgin Hey, you can't win them
all.
But you can get this as a consolation prize.
I think Phoebe wins company.
Yeah, Phoebe's bored and wins some company.
Who's all by himself?
Aibu is bored and wins some company.
Perfect.
To meet each other.
We haven't met yet.
Halfway.
My name is Phoebe.
Hey, Phoebe.
Phoebe.
I'm Aibu.
Never thought you could lose this.
What do you mean, of course you could lose it?
Next time I'll make some things off screen for, like, items
and things, fun stuff.
Oh,
what's happening here?
Oh, yes?
He's still stalking.
I've got to warn you, I'm a red light, green light master,
wanna play.
I'm getting my Aztec chip.
That's a similar.
It's named.
Green light.
Red light.
Redemption.
Green light.
Wait.
Red light.
Oh.
I thought if I pressed I would get him.
Green light.
Yeah!
Well done.
Big boss.
I did it.
Redemption!
Yippee!
Meantos too good at the game, that's all.
Congratulations!
I'm so good at it.
You won!
Time for your...
Oh.
I could have gotten a whole geode.
I suspect Frogbird specializes in green light only.
So true.
Uh-oh.
Snake has a bit of an issue.
The whole thing is like if the island of misfit toys was
rom-com um what do you mean good evening good evening mutual
crush oh we'll go get you a new room sure entire room i
think i have to go buy one though let's go shop welcome what
would snake want
the thing about the rooms is there's they don't give me so
many and they don't update as often and all alaskan cabin
that's what i was thinking too but frogboard has that one
maybe a garage set it kind of okay think of the car as a
tank think of it as shadow moses
level up is the only way to get them yeah it's tough also
change the coloring on this one.
Ooh, that looks nice!
Thank you very much.
There we go, we'll give it, we'll get him this.
Thank you, Becky.
Garage set.
Oh yes.
Nice.
This is exactly the kind of room I wanted to live in.
Thank you!
You're welcome!
Whoa!
Big numbers.
He's probably hungry too, let's figure it out.
him you're hungry you want something to eat oh you've never
had coconut before ever in their life
yo yo
he likes it
let's see you know what oh wait i did get me into the laptop
that's why she does her little seminars what would snake
snake would maybe a quirk maybe he could greet the hyped up
style greet with a nod
reach listlessly whoa karate style oh flirt no he would
stand
Wiping sweat.
Why is he so sweaty?
Standing out of touch.
He's so...
I like that too.
Doesn't greet people is funny.
I like the nod.
Oh wait, maybe we can give him a walk too.
Leaning forward?
Kind of is like a...
Like he's sneaking around.
We'll do the leaning forward.
Yeah, he's sneaking, he's sneaking.
There you go, Snake.
Oh, I feel a little different.
Yeah, crouch walking.
Hrnka!
My eyes just seem to naturally follow Minto when she's
nearby.
Hrnka!
Oh, Snake, come on!
Someone ask someone out already, please!
Shut up.
Um...
Good evening.
It may just be my imagination, but...
I get the feeling that Joe has a crush on me.
You'd be cute together.
Really?
Well, now I'll be thinking about this.
for the rest of the day.
What are you going to do?
Ultra Friends.
Wait, is Ultra Friends better than Best Friends?
Again, yeah.
They're so on again and off again.
Except they've never been on again ever.
They've never been on ever.
Yippee!
What are we at now?
Level 12.
What's some new amenities that we have?
There we do have the, uh...
Sorry, the springtime stuff.
Which I've gotten a couple.
I've obviously got the Hydrangea Hedge because those are my
favorite.
We could also give more gifts.
Like the muscle building.
Or we could do more quirks.
eating eats gracefully quickly cautiously and shyly I love
the quirks I think they're so funny or we could buy more
rooms wait this one could be for snake
camel campsite that one would be for naked snake but we
don't have him rooms we could do
I want this one for Minto.
Ow, sorry.
My mouth is getting to the point where it hurts to open it.
I made a doctor's appointment, but the soonest I could get
is Monday.
Why do you want a dog house for Minto?
Because I want Aibu to go in there.
What are you talking about?
The grassy meadow set is so cute, too.
anybody also.
The plushroom is good for Phoebe.
Or the sakura.
Or the... Oh no, the flower medal.
And then the tea house set could be good for Vicky.
Let's do the one for Vicky.
I think it's cute.
Wait, it's expensive.
Oh, we get a bonus one as a gift.
I wonder if these ones eventually disappear though when the
season's over, right?
Big eye.
Oh wait, also we can... we can... wait.
I-I already got treasures.
But let's do clothing.
Wait, island objects!
Never mind.
I want to make objects around my island.
With my own two hands.
Snake, what are you doing?
Oh no, he's fantasizing again, I think.
Hey!
Do that thing again!
Apple's outfit.
Sure.
Open wine, open wine, open wine.
Aww.
I want to be sweethearts.
Please confess, please somebody confess.
What are you doing?
What's up with me, uh...
That's not how you wa- ew.
Sorry.
My mind was somewhere else.
No, no?
No, it's my fault.
Not that I care.
Are you okay?
Then we're both fine.
Good.
Stay safe out there.
Not that I care.
You're such an asshole.
I feel all mixed up.
I like Snake, but I also have feelings for Haley Joel Osman.
Just met him!
What do you think I really like?
Haley Joel Osman is convinced that Gengar likes him.
It's mint over.
No!
It's got- You're right.
I was nearly misled.
Snake is the only one for me.
So true.
Lymphenore 2.
Ship captain.
together don't even think about it no who oh oh yeah but I
mean those into bad guys the great tragedy good clown don't
booze oh why is she watching him I'm gonna pick her up I'm
gonna take her over to wait where is he come on hang out
Hang out right now.
Somebody confess.
Let's reach you.
Why did Minto suddenly pop into my head?
Oh my god, they're so close.
Holy- why are they standing so close to each other?
Minto is staring at Snake.
Wait, why don't you guys hang out?
Frogbert?
Who is Frogbert into?
Huh?
I'm not even sure what this feeling is.
I may not know I boo very well, but I know fate has big
plans for us.
What should I do?
Share your feelings now.
Share my feelings.
Just, like, go and flirt it all out.
Yeah, yeah.
well okay I mean I'm boo and I barely know each other but
it'll probably be fine where should I confess my love it's
happening islands wait what's the mystery one islands spot
his place are you just gonna go over wait I always said this
was the island confession okay here wait but their houses
are like right there you know okay hold on wait you can like
oh my gosh you can like make it so that they confess in
front of a really nice spot oh that's crazy
look into the sea look into the sea look into the sea it's
beautiful actually over here yeah
how should I confess my feelings
okay Do you guys have something that would really get you
feeling doki-dokie?
By shouting?
Shouting is good.
Let's try it.
Should I change what I'm wearing first?
No, no, no, no, no.
You look great.
All right.
It's time to psych myself up and say how I really feel.
Shout it out.
You're at the sea.
Oh my gosh, I need more popcorn.
He's so serious!
Oh my god, he showed up!
I must share my feelings for you, I boo.
With everyone on yay, get strong, your own.
Welcome back away, Toma and Ciderone.
I love you, you, you, I boo.
Hold it right there
What?
The one who truly loves Ibu is me What?
Hold it right there No
Well, the one who truly deeply loves Ibu is me No, you guys
don't even know him I confessed my feelings first You guys
don't even know him Ibu Which of us do you choose?
Pick one of us Once and for all, not that I care.
Not that I care was the best line I could have picked ever.
Puppet, I'm not gonna go out with you.
Yippee!
I spilled my popcorn everywhere.
And I've gone better.
Sweethearts for one day.
Oh, oh, um, what's your...
What do you want Frogbert to call you?
Boo-boo?
I-boo-boo.
Good evening.
Hey boo-boo.
I...
Boo-boo.
Hey, I-boo-boo.
Okay, what do you guys want to call Frogbert?
Yogi Bear.
Oh, you're right.
Yogi Kermit, that's not his name.
That's so offensive.
Froggy Pooh.
Froggy.
Robert.
No.
Boobert.
That's a good one.
Oh.
Yeah.
Good evening, Boobert.
Boobert.
There's been a certified, verified, bona fide miracle.
It happened just like it does on TV.
Cinema, cinema.
Oh my god, falling in love.
Ending a sentence.
I like these.
Not that I care.
It's so crazy.
Boingo?
It's so funny.
Actually, we can do a greeting.
One greeting.
Greetings, Canada.
Yeah, it's good.
Look how happy they look.
They're such a couple.
Congratulations, everybody.
Congratulations, Tina.
Greetings, Canada.
I always wanted to say that.
You've been doing such a great job, Curie, and Amy.
in for your residence.
Here's a little something to help make the place even more
fun.
A marketplace.
We had a marketplace.
What is this?
We could put it over here.
Or I keep all like the stores and stuff over here.
I'll move it around later.
What is this?
Things were a little dicey for a bit but it all worked out.
Yeah!
We interrupt to bring you some breaking news here's what's
happening on our island those wanting a place to market will
welcome the news of a marketplace thanks for being our
wingman get stronger your own welcome back away tome inside
the marketplace sells food clothing and what's called a
mystery bag which is a bag that could be filled with
anything maybe even something you don't like oh such is the
mystery the morning market runs from 5 a.m to 11 30 a.m oh
so we got the night market from 11 30 a.m to 5 p.m and the
night market from 5 p.m to 5 a.m each market sells different
goods and the selection is said to change daily
regularly thanks for watching i'm snake and you're off today
thanks snake yeah exactly welcome in oh my god wait how did
you get here so fast we've got something real special for
you today your mystery bag comes with an extra item in it
muscles school slaps Model train!
Oh.
Scattered roses.
Thanks a bunch.
Thank you.
Be sure to stop by again tomorrow.
Oh.
Okay.
That's it.
I gotta make some objects.
Cubes, spheres, and beyond.
House shape.
Oh...
Wait, I thought that I could like make a thing and then put
it on the island.
Oh, a hill with flowers is so cute!
Oh, I see, I see.
Oh!
Okay.
Oh, get me out of here.
me out of here?
That's very cute.
I didn't do anything, though.
I just want to see it, like...
Oh, so they give you, like, a base shape, and then you go
from there.
Interesting.
Okay, okay.
Dang.
I need, like, a...
Like, a real stylist with this or something, you know?
Oh, Kitsil, what's wrong?
What's wrong with the pretzels?
Um...
Yeah?
Good evening.
Ibu Sphere.
My little cookie is a new pie.
Dang, okay, you're picky.
Hey, Aminta, how are you?
I'm good, how are you?
Let's go shopping.
We'll give you...
You're a bird.
You get the music major.
Wait, I haven't bought it yet.
And since it's the, uh...
Since it's the special, I feel like I should buy it before
it disappears, you know?
fancy
he just likes it they're so picky this is different
different thank you yeah he's a bird ish I cannot believe
Phoebe tried to take away Aibu Phoebe you just got here
where is she?
she's at home what are you doing girl what are you doing
What are you doing?
She's playing hopscotch by herself.
What does your relationship chart look like?
Oh, whoops.
That's not what I meant to do.
How do I see it?
Oh, I think I need to click on it.
Quingtons!
What do you mean you were coming in being like, I love Ibu
more than anyone else?
Mito already caving the FOMO.
Oh, look how many people are here.
Oh yeah, Vicky is chowing down on that.
Uh, pizza!
Oh yeah.
They're both ready to tell each other deep secrets.
They are so in love.
Do it well, thank you.
It's really, I'm also a bird.
My name is...
My name in Welsh means crow and little rainbow.
What?
That's crazy!
Bird.
No one's doing anything.
I hear a little creature.
I love that thing.
That's my favorite creation ever.
I love him.
Do something else.
Ibu dance.
So true.
What does it say new?
Oh, for the quick builds.
Welcome.
What did we get?
Oh, the restaurant.
Wait, why is it letting me buy another restaurant?
That's weird.
Oh, the marketplace.
Please come again.
Thank you, Council.
Everybody's just doing their own thing.
This guy's catching some z's on the beach.
when did we get with frog blur like just now like two two
minutes ago oh my god I think I think I just witnessed a
murder what was happening someone help her I who ran past
she fell oh wait do something please help me i'm competing
in a pokemon tournament tomorrow i'm very nervous death
magic you got this you got this i'm starting to feel better
thank you it was me
that was so close oh my gosh
do you miss him He's thinking about you guys.
Maybe Phoebe and...
What's wrong?
What happened?
Phoebe and Haley Joel Osmond can meet too.
Oh, oh.
Oh my god, they're the same height.
My name is Phoebe.
You're Phoebe.
I'm Haley Joel Osmond.
Not that I care.
Okay.
best catchphrase ever it's so funny it's actually like way
too funny i should we'll go buy some more food um
we still have some we gotta find somebody that that loves
something know we gotta find someone that loves something
who's alone bored and want some company wait did you eat um
speaking of eating did you guys eat good evening did you
guys eat i'm gonna give you some roast beef thank you the
great streaming though not that i care thanks he's gonna
love it
like that.
I want to find somebody that loves or hates something.
You know?
Ah, it's tough.
He's bored, though.
Who is around and also...
Oh, Ketzel!
It'll happen.
Oh, he's just lounging.
No, not anymore.
I ate a Freezy salad.
How topical.
Hearn go.
Pardon me.
Could I have a moment?
My name is Snake.
Hello there.
Snake.
Unknown is Petzal Puglitz.
Wait, what's happening?
The rest on the bench for a bit.
Oh, my goodness.
Chiptoon.
What is this?
I like your vibe, Snake.
Oh, they had a nice little special thing.
That's crazy.
Seems like mine.
Usually they just kind of like chit chat.
Nice.
Not much is going on though, huh?
When will Snake... Snake and Minto are... both of them are
too shy.
Both of them are shy.
How do you say the dinosaur's name?
You can say Ketzalcoatless or Ketzalcoatless.
It depends on your accent.
Little 13!
Could Minto...
Unlocks after granting two more wishes.
I want to take Minto and... I think Minto would choose
snake.
Either snake or Ibu.
Which are both okay.
But I want them to go to Hawaii.
You know?
Wait, what's the...
builder what do we got wooden boards oh yeah i could just
call them the pretzel
the pretzel there's also so many things here
and then the rooms wait let's get the food the quirk i want
to stay up to date on all the quirks that can get.
Seesaw!
Okay, we'll get that one next.
Seesaw sounds fine.
Eating styles reserved.
Oh.
Hi, Blue!
Hi.
How about a day with double shadow quiz?
Come on.
You've got this in the bag.
What is a double shadow quiz?
Here's your first mystery double shadow.
Double shadow.
What are these?
Oh my, what?
There's no way I can tell what...
Wait, what do you mean?
What are these?
There's no way I can tell what this is.
What?
Peter Griffin.
Huh?
What is this?
Two items that are overlapping.
So maybe a steak.
And because it's like...
square and frozen yogurt.
The answer is...
I'm crazy.
Next up, you're a second mystery devil shadow.
What?
What are these?
Oh, just peace and energy drink!
What the hell?
I was the first one so hard!
Energy drink and just...
What?
Your last mystery, double shadow.
What are these?
A jellyfish.
Wait, what's wrong with Ketzel?
Wait, why did he walk away like that?
I believe in jellyfish.
He walked through.
He looks so distressed.
Yeah, baby.
Good job, us.
Good job, kids.
Let's go for the prize!
Let's go for the big prize!
I got a cooking show?
How did I...
How did I acquire that?
Is he okay?
What's wrong?
What's wrong with him?
I'm in a bit of a funk.
Why are you in a funk?
I was talking to Snake, but I don't know.
I guess I just got a little sad.
Wait, what?
Let's give him the cooking show.
Oh.
There you go.
Cult single action army shaped lightsick merch.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, I'll make some fun items.
Oh, he likes it.
I feel like a heavy weight has been lifted from my
shoulders.
My talk with Snake was pretty fun.
What a me, you saw?
The new lead has so much to say about a video game
soundtrack.
Was it Metal Q saw?
I think he's fine now.
So engaging.
Okay.
That worked.
There's lots going on here Let's see what Gengar is doing
Sitting on the floor Next to the couch Sure, what's up?
I would just love it If there were a flower planter right
here On the beach?
No Maybe another time I can take you to another...
I can take you to another flower planter
I can take you to another flower planter relatable.
I know.
He's the best.
Wait, what's going on over here?
Wow, what a group.
They're all talking about how they could never get tired of
looking at the sugar glider.
Look at him floating.
I thought he was a pet.
So true.
Let's see.
Minto went something.
Minto went to the I think.
Hello!
Hey!
How about a game of Zoom quiz?
Yeah, give me a Zoom quiz.
Let's play.
He is.
Ibu is so popular and all.
You guys just have the best personality.
What do you think it is?
Elephant ear.
Isn't that a pastry?
Yes.
Next.
Your second zoomed in item?
What do you think it is?
Grattan.
The answer is...
Now.
And finally, to last assumed an item.
What do you think it is?
What the...
Bote...
What even is that?
Yellow.
Oh yeah.
It must be the orange juice.
The correct answer is...
It just keeps showing up.
Orange juice.
Yeah.
Congratulations.
Playboy.
Let's go middle.
Me too.
Oh.
Let's go middle.
Oh, I got a switch.
Oh, it's just a puzzle game.
I thought I got a whole switch.
You want time?
Minto.
Wait, wait.
No, don't leave.
Oh, Minto, Minto, Minto.
Oh.
Good evening.
You want this.
You love a puzzle game.
I gave her a puzzle game.
Yippee!
Good.
Well, looks like I'm into snake.
Oh, yep.
So matter of fact.
Please, why won't you confess?
Why won't either of you confess your feelings?
Baby, what's wrong?
Um, good evening.
Yes, you are.
Can you bring me some clothes that make me look more mature?
Mature.
I don't want too much old, though.
More like, I want people to think I want to kind of bang for
something.
You know?
Sure.
Actually, this one, this classical dress outfit is so cute.
I bought it for myself, but I'll give it to you.
She loves it!
Phoebe Banking?
Nice.
What do you wear when you sleep?
An intricate cosplay.
I wear...
A skiing.
Skin.
A skin.
I'd like to wear that skin.
Because you wear nothing at all.
A skin.
Everybody's happy.
Oh.
Are you happy?
Gengar?
Are you okay?
I'm gonna give you something.
I'm gonna give this guy a little something.
Something unique.
Uh...
Let's give you...
The koala plush.
It's so precious.
Trying to halt his descent into madness.
Here, we'll give him...
Some filet minion!
Yum!
I think I'm...
You guys, I think we're...
We're losing him!
I just thought of a question, big boss.
Which would you rather have?
One really great friend or a hundred regular friends?
One really great friend.
That's all you need sometimes.
Maybe a head pat.
A head pat.
He hates us, yeah.
Holy cow.
Kangar might be cooked.
No!
He can get with Haley Joel Osmond.
It'll work.
It'll...
Is that...
Welcome back away, Toma's side around.
What?
Oh, he's gonna go find the last treasure.
And then he changed it.
Oh, my God.
This is, like, the worst posture.
It's so terrible.
Nilm!
Thank you.
What is that?
Chicken wing.
Oh.
All right.
I like these like what's going on with so-and-so's are
pretty funny.
What's going on here?
How much do you love me?
Oh, this is gross.
I love you this much.
Well, I love you this much.
Oh, but I love you this much.
Then I love you this much.
get a room looks like they're on a date oh my god stinking
cup
this house is so me this house is so me that's your house
what do you mean what do you mean this house is so me
oh he's I thought you didn't like it you little I'm gonna
kill you.
I'm gonna...
I can draw a koala plush with my eyes closed.
What is she doing?
She's playing puzzle game in the sand.
Amito, you're gonna get...
You're gonna get sand up your underwear.
Sometimes I fantasize about having a house.
This house is so mean.
It's his house.
I think Phoebe is...
Oh, she's just running around.
I thought she was chasing the butterfly.
Which was also very her.
Hmm.
What's Vicky doing?
Is making up constellations.
Yeah?
What's she making up?
Phoebe's zooming.
Everyone in Denza 2 is busy.
Just doing their own thing.
Oh, they're on their date.
talking about how nice the restaurant is I really I want
snake or Minto to confess seems like some mees are planning
on gathering here why is he standing there like this shadow
torius yeah yeah okay I don't think it looks so much like
he's crouch walking anymore I think it just looks bad yes
errone yes errone yes errone Minto, you have to go say
something to him.
He's going to get caught by Gengar.
Don't look up.
Wait, more people are gathering.
Wait, even Vicky's interested.
Everyone...
Oh, oh.
Wait, is she coming to say hi?
No.
Did she just say just can't do it?
No, Minto, you can do it.
Oh, she's done.
Wait, I want Minto and Vicky to be friends, but I want it to
happen organically.
Oh my gosh, this is like the craziest love triangle right
here.
How unique a koala plush can be.
Nah, rage quit.
Perfect.
No!
Even Vicky!
look at this square that's crazy everybody's strangers i
know he was hating on it what what is this what is this
let's get some more food hopefully i haven't fed everybody i
have some muscles we'll get some kimchi we'll get some
porridge Sausage, enchiladas, pizza, green curry, fried egg.
Let's get one of everything.
Mussels, creamy stew, roast beef, coconut, macaroni,
whatever that is.
We have two green teas, we have tap water.
We'll take it.
Chopping spree.
Yeah.
We gotta find somebody that's hungry.
I think Ibu's not hungry.
Phoebe, I think also aid.
How does...
Have we fed them?
Greetings, Canada.
I forgot he said that.
Are you hungry?
Can I interest you in a pizza?
Yum.
I like that.
Frogbird is like crazy levels.
I kind of spoil this guy, I think.
Let's do an eating.
Eat quickly.
Eat gracefully.
Eat cautiously.
Give things a good sniff.
Eat shyly.
What would a frog do?
he would probably eat I kind of want to see quickly with his
tongue he just
graciously a little bit more like myself I wish I'd given it
to him I'm boo boo and I are dating now I'm going to do
everything I can to make him happy I'm so glad I took the
lead how are you guys feeling huh how are you guys feeling
about that oh my gosh Gengar is on like a high after that
what's up this would be way more fun with friends oh did you
want to hop with friends uh um who's around besides Haley
Joel Osmond Gengar Gengar's around We haven't met yet, have
we?
My name is Gengar.
They're trying to eat.
Hey Gengar, I'm Victoria the Hedgehog.
Okay.
Educational game, Pinkettoli.
Grab an educational game or no.
Grab an educational game.
General Victoria the Hedgehog talk.
Like educational games and taffy.
Educational games and taffy?
Alright, come on.
Okay.
You guys, I don't know if Snake or Minto are going to take
the plunge.
Minto's hanging out here!
They're discussing what makes the sugar...
Look at him just flying in the air.
It's so funny.
Has there been any instant dislike?
There haven't been.
I've been trying to make different personalities.
but everyone's too like...
Everybody's too kind to each other.
I get the issue.
Where is Snake?
That guy is sneaking around.
Where is he?
Snake!
Snake?
Snake is... I didn't even realize he was there.
He was hiding in plain sight.
What's going on?
It's disturbing.
Oh, the username!
Happy birthday!
Let's see.
Alright, let's grab Minto again.
Maybe we can make this happen.
Come here.
No more time for sugar glider.
There's something I have to tell you.
What do you do?
I missed it!
Oh, I got it.
Why does Snake keep doing this interaction?
You're too cool.
You're too cool!
Oh, I dropped my...
Wait, maybe now.
Maybe...
Now?
Whispering about how they're so happy right now.
Please do something!
Please!
Everyone's too nice, kind to each other.
Hey, Crawford.
That implies that seeking relationships is not a nice thing.
Wait, he can't believe he ran home!
He was so scared!
Let's give...
Let's give Phoebe something.
Phoebe's bored.
Phoebe, I'll give you something.
Let's first give her a cookie.
Or like something small.
Yeah, a cookie, a cookie.
Yeah, you can eat this.
Yeah.
What was that?
Not that I care.
This is like crazy.
She loves it.
Or she really likes it, but she doesn't love it.
It is Gengar's time to shine.
Let's do it!
Oh wait, I can give her something actually.
She's gonna knit.
A hot cup of tea.
Baby needs her greeting.
Oh yeah, we can give her Ohachi.
Ohachi!
Okay.
How is it so best?
It's so blue.
I love this sea.
How is it so bad?
What's wrong?
Good.
Wait, maybe we should make Gengar try on.
Is there a me's play- Go in there?
Why?
Yeah.
Is this some kind of bit?
Gravity wins again.
Not that I care.
I've never met anyone so brave.
Finally, someone who understands, not that I care.
Please tell no one this happened to me, not that I care.
I don't mind one bit.
Ultra brand.
Thanks for helping me and you'll get closer.
Oh, it's so funny.
Guys, I wonder if Snake will ever say anything or Minta will
ever say anything.
I nearly spat out my drink.
Perfect one lighter.
It's like so, it's so good.
It's so like...
the part where that's my problem.
Oh wait, not the gift.
We wanted the seesaw, I remember.
Seesaw.
Bonfire!
Wait, there's so many good ones.
Outdoor shower.
We'll do the... I feel like the bonfire is so romantic.
Maybe they'll decide to do it after this.
They will confess.
Seesaw next.
We got this.
Bonfire.
fire oh now we can go to hawaii we interrupt to bring you
some breaking news an exciting new travel destination is now
available fire or shower a hawaii tour is now available oh
my god tickets at the wishing fountain yeah size of relief
could be heard throughout the island and one resident is
quoted as saying i hope my roommate is gifted a Who is your
roommate?
I could really use the alone time.
I feel like none of my meters have like...
Wanted to move in together or...
You know?
So someone can leave immediately.
Stop by the wishing fountain to learn more.
Thanks for watching.
I'm Gengar, and you're up today.
Alright.
Let's go build our bonfire.
My power.
We'll do...
I like the orange one.
Oh, thank you.
We'll put it, like, right down here.
Oh, whoops.
Single mode.
Oh, I already got one.
I forgot.
That's fine.
We can put one, like, here.
And we can put another one.
Like, here for secret rituals.
You know?
Okay.
And then we could get rid of some of these weeds.
Clean up the place a little bit.
Yeah, I'll drop Halo Jewel Osama in it, so true.
Minto, Minto, Minto.
Come here.
I want to show you it.
Oh!
Are you done yet?
Wait, snake, snake, snake, come here, come here.
Oh, she was warm in her booty.
Fancy seeing you here.
Where are you off to?
Wait, why is she acting so aloof?
Tell me.
What's happening?
Have Victoria meet more people, you're right.
She ran away.
Where is Vicky anyway?
Oh, there she is.
Vicky, come here.
Stop looking at ants.
And come meet Snake.
Hey, nice to meet you.
I'm Victoria the Hedgehog.
She needs to reach out some more.
She is so shy.
Hello there, Victoria the Hedgehog.
I'm known as Snake.
Feelings were in high bloom.
She loves her and go.
It's so over, you guys.
Minto won't confess.
Snake won't confess.
Nobody's confessing.
It's so over.
Are you bored?
No, he doesn't even want company.
He's just staring off into the abyss.
Everyone's too shy!
Minta, what are you doing?
Maybe after the Hawaii trip.
Say it.
Do a trick.
Do a trick, Aibu!
Do a trick?
She's such a yearner girl!
Oh!
I think Snake is the one truly yearning though he's like I
want to be sweethearts things are tough on this island
things are tough
look over here oh turn around turn around Ketzel Ketzel
oh your booty oh oh oh wait so much happened here wait some
me's are planning on gathering here i think ibu might be one
of them here he comes oh yeah look at that strut he's coming
all the way here here he comes yep lots of swag
here are two games in a row to make you appreciate having
children Or isn't it evil appreciates having children?
Oh my god, this is so gross!
Saying thank you so much for the pain!
Wait, 20 hour community service assignment.
Wait, I've been waiting on my 20 hour community service
assignment for only playing MGSV to pay the joy game for
roughly 48 hours.
I also have been playing Delta and I've come to realize
something.
Ocelot.
I get it, Minto.
I get it now.
Yeah!
You're jealous we are in love.
I'm leaving this area.
Secret.
They're pretending to be funny little monsters.
I told you that secret rituals would happen over here.
The other one is for romance.
And this one is for...
This one is for evil!
Good,
good.
Maybe I need... wait, did Phoebe...
Has Phoebe met Vicky yet?
She seems sleepy though.
Yeah, it's the evil fire.
Where is Vicky?
Oh.
Everybody's here.
Oh, good.
Vicky.
Uh-oh.
Vicky crashed their...
Their day.
I don't think any of... I was waiting for someone to be
like, I want to be friends with Zoetil.
You know?
I was waiting for it.
Me and Phoebe have met.
I don't think...
I don't think Phoebe and...
Well, Phoebe and Vicky haven't met, obviously, but...
Okay, then.
their friends oh oh maybe you could hang out in my room
sometime oh wait what's wrong with me though there's
something wrong with her in the back seem like a minded we
kind of stopped doing that after the demo we stopped doing
what what's wrong wait oh are you mad oh i'm feeling a
little upset wait did you get mad did you and me don't have
fight i don't usually get mad like this but my top foot goes
really oh yeah my nickname is ghost wait what the hell
gangar you're the most sensitive okay i know you don't like
the say fuku so i'm gonna give you a different outfit okay
ghost i'm ghost
finally you like
something we have stands cutely because
of we have stands cutely maybe we walk cutely too I kind of
like the bounding one too it's kind of fun like they're on
the moon or
we could say like ending a sentence it could be like like
boo it could be like boo like
like boo
thank you now I feel more like myself like boo I feel like a
heavy weight has been lifted from my shoulders like boo
stupid so stupid Wait, Snake, what do you want?
Like, boo.
Snake.
If it's not pink, I don't want to know.
If it's not pink...
I've been thinking too hard.
My head feels all fuzzy inside.
I'll take a look.
Oh, my gosh, so much.
Oh, that was close.
Phew!
I feel so much better now!
Come on, Snake!
Come on!
Please!
One of you!
Somebody, anybody!
Hearnka!
I had an exciting talk about an eye-boop with Minto.
This is so surreal.
I'm happy that Minto enjoyed it.
It's so surreal.
The fact that you can just add anything to this game is so
funny.
What are you?
Oh my gosh, so many people are trying to get attention.
What's wrong?
Greetings, Canada.
Got a sec.
I want to chat.
Okay.
Oh.
I promise I'm not gonna steal it.
But what's your most prized possession?
My most prized possession.
My most prized possession is a
Koharu figure.
If only those existed.
Idol checky.
Yeah, right?
Something.
Totally something you say before stealing something, right?
What?
Is a...
Is...
A maid outfit.
Did you ever get that?
I'm just a pachinko machine?
Wait, what?
Check stream number two.
Maid outfit?
Yeah.
Oh, I get that.
If I had a maid outfit, I'd probably build a whole museum to
house it.
This is where I'd put my maid outfit.
If I had one!
Very nice, Frogbird.
Thank you.
Oh.
Breaking news?
We interrupted when you some breaking news.
We've just received some more information.
Mango heads double digits!
It's being reported that a total of 10 tons of items result
are now being used on games.
It's time to roam.
Welcome back, Waco, inside alone.
Residents, kid, I have been joined.
Oh, what a...
Wait, the skin is out of context!
There's all these new things to say.
Yes, big boss will be presented to the world's speech
bubble.
Whoa.
Thanks for watching.
Thank you.
I'm quite so helpless.
Enter up to date.
Thank you.
This will be a major scoop.
Doesn't it need to hear your residents talking about the
stuff you've taught them and using new words?
It's terrifying, actually.
It's kind of horrifying.
You have taught them well.
She wants to be friends with Minto.
I can feel it.
Good evening.
She wants to be friends with Minto.
I want to be friends with Minto.
Gengar?
What should we talk about?
You should talk about...
Wait!
How...
Wrong ghost!
Big butts.
Oh wait.
What did you have in mind?
Big, big butts.
Okay.
I wish it didn't have to be a, you know?
Like, I wish it could be plural.
A big, big butt.
Big, big butt?
Got it.
I'll go talk to him about a big, big butt.
Good evening.
Can you guys feel like a psyche valve versus a game?
Like the... What?
Do you feel like talking about?
A big, big butt.
Sure.
But let me ask you this.
Let's say you're offered a large big, big butt or a small
big, big butt.
Victoria the Hedgehog.
Which do you choose?
Well, that's easy.
I have to go with the large, big, big butt.
Hence down.
Right.
Of course you would.
Everybody knows a Mondo-sized big, big, big butt.
The only choice.
I like the way you think.
Victoria the Hedgehog.
You know, I could honestly sit here and talk about a massive
big, big butt for hours.
Did we just become friends?
Yeah.
Like, who?
Oh,
he's a big, big butt.
Oh, Kingar's nickname.
Oh, geez.
And they cannot lie.
I'll say big G.
Wait, I almost...
Big G.
Good evening, big G.
And then we can do big V.
Or...
Big.
Big V.
There we go.
Good evening, Big Big V.
Big G and Big Big V.
Behold a friendship, how a bitch enormous, big, big butt.
Big G and I are going to get along great.
We're a big title mystery.
We're a big title.
And never get bored.
Like, boo.
I have to give her this.
Ending a sentence.
Yeah, there it is.
Thank you.
Now I feel more like myself.
There we go.
Yay, they're such good friends.
Baby.
Oh, I've seen...
Oh!
She doesn't need a store laugh if only.
Okay.
She's enjoying it.
Why won't he...
Why won't you?
Why won't you confess your love?
Hearnka...
Care for a round of Zoom quiz?
You're avoiding your feelings, Snake.
This is so like you.
Actually, this is so like the both of us, I would never
confess either.
What do you think is...
The answer is...
Sushi.
Next, your second zoomed in item.
What do you think it is?
Bologna?
Scented candle?
The answer is...
candle and finally the last zoomed in item what do you think
it is
pancakes the correct answer is pancakes nice nice
congratulations you won Maybe I got a gift snake like a
present.
Whatever's in here he gets.
Purlescent accessory case.
That's all yours, buddy.
Um.
Is it right?
Hey, bear.
Why aren't you doing anything?
Maybe I give him a lucky clover.
That's how he confesses.
You know?
With the lucky clover.
Wait, here you go, buddy.
It'll all go well.
Send him to Hawaii.
We have to...
You can only send him to Hawaii when you level up your...
Land.
Okay, maybe he doesn't believe in lock.
I don't think we're so close to it.
We're maybe a little...
Like, frog bird.
Walking back there.
Oh, wait!
a wish.
Wait, when did I get a wish to grant?
Hawaii!
With!
Okay.
Snake, you know what to do.
You're going to Hawaii.
You know what to do.
Oh, Hawaii and I can give you a free wish.
Oh, nice.
Oh.
Are you really giving me a Hawaii Please pick a minto,
please pick a minto, please pick a minto, please pick a
minto, please pick a minto, please pick a minto, please pick
a minto, please pick a minto, please pick a minto.
Glove, glove, I'm diving.
Say cheese.
Wrong ghost.
I'm so unpopular.
Lookie lookie, I'm in Waikiki Say cheese
Boy Poipu Beach on Kauai is so nice It's a shame I have to
disturb the sand with my footprints Say cheese It does look
good Don't save them Bros before ghosts
Hearnka, that was a wonderful trip.
Thanks so much for letting me take it.
I even got you this souvenir.
It's a middle finger.
Okay, chain.
Gengar is just a really chill dude to go on vacation with.
He's just always down to do whatever.
Congrats, happy for them.
Nice.
Remember, chat ghost times are super effective against other
ghost times.
Maybe she'll realize she has to do something.
Or else.
I'll bring someone!
Minto!
Help Phoebe!
Are you alright?
Please, just help me.
Help!
There's a source of the problem.
I can't believe it.
Why didn't he bring her?
Why didn't he bring Minto?
You're a real lifesaver.
Don't worry about it.
Why?
Don't hang out.
Gang T.R.
Wait, there's so much going on.
What's going on here?
This is cruel.
Oh, I don't want to see a happy couple!
How could you do
this?
Oh, I think they're more... I think they're in love!
I was about to say!
They've been dating for one day and they're in love.
Oh, somebody's dreaming.
Vicky's dreaming.
You guys are in love.
I'm so happy for you.
Oh, this is the one.
Wait, but they're flowers this time.
Wait, this is so good for Phoebe.
Is that a snake?
Ew.
It's so funny.
Wait, then we get the flower outfit.
I'll give it to Phoebe.
Okay.
Oh, they're dying.
Oh my god, wait.
Please, I'm a little flower.
Please water me.
Snake looks disgusting.
They're gonna die.
A thirsty little flower.
Please.
Oh.
They're angry.
Glad that was only a dream, innit?
We got the flower costume.
What's up?
No.
What's happening?
Oh.
Oh, never mind.
The ring.
They're doing this again.
She's...
There's new people on the island, so she has to spread the
gospel.
This is, this is, you guys, it's never happening.
It's never happening.
Don't forget me, what is your wisdom of the day?
My wisdom is...
Go for it.
You might miss your chance.
If you don't go for it, you might miss your chance.
Oh, okay.
I thought he was standing there cutely.
Oh, it went out.
Okay.
Oh, what's up with Gengar?
Never save.
Never.
Oh,
Animal Crossing.
I don't think it's happening.
I don't know if it will ever happen.
I can't force them.
Actually, I can.
Go inside.
Hey.
Good evening, Snake.
Do you feel like talking about sucking life energy?
Sure.
But tell me, Minto, how much do you know about sucking life
energy?
Oh, like so much.
I studied a sucking life energy rule book every night before
bed.
Well, that's some serious dedication.
But you know, I've always wanted to give those sucking life
energy a shot.
You're not a ghost!
You can't do it!
Maybe one day we can do it together.
This is never happening.
What does that mean?
It went great!
What was supposed to happen?
Are they not friends before?
Uh...
Call him Pliskin?
Yeah, that's a good one.
I think I have someone else calling him Iroquois, so...
Literally, what is happening right now?
What fever dream is this?
Good evening, Pliskin.
I want Snake to call me Minky.
Oh, whoops.
Minky.
Good evening, Minky.
Put the mid outfit on me, though.
Yeah, we'll do that.
Nice.
I knew sucking life energy would bring Kriskin and me
together.
Makes sense.
No, it doesn't make sense.
Minky and I have the same taste in hobbies.
No!
So no wonder we hit it off.
Then why?
Why won't you?
Maybe now that they're friends.
Let's do it.
I will say
I almost wanted to say howdy-duty but moy-moy boo mobo what
did she say?
mobo boo oh no no no mo a oh gosh okay this is annoying a
you think that's good mo A?
A?
Oh, it works, it works, it works.
Moe, moe, moe, boo.
Breaking news.
How did she get there?
We interrupt to bring you some breaking news.
What?
We just received some wonderful news.
This is what happened before.
It is being held in honor of Big Boss and to celebrate 20
booths to island residents' happiness.
The number of times I had to edit the last one is insane.
Are
we getting the silver trophy?
Big boss.
We give you our eternal thanks.
I'm gonna do an island with all my answers to see who I have
to get back with.
It truly warms the heart.
I'm into you're up to date.
Yeah.
Rabbit snap elbow.
Hello.
Oh, it left without me!
Oh, hi Phoebe!
She's knitting.
Um, excuse me.
Let's do the seesaw.
Doesn't there's something else though?
Level 15.
Oh, we got more quirks.
Appetite set.
Two-piece little quirks set for anyone with an appetite
bigger.
Hangar set!
Uh-oh.
Chaos canvas.
Graveyard!
I want that one!
Let's do it!
What's new?
The seesaw.
Oh, there was the shower!
That's right.
The seesaw seems fun though.
I should make like a, I'm gonna make like a little park or
something.
Hmm.
Seesaw.
Is he scared?
Heroic tales from old times of old!
Yeah, I mean...
Welcome.
Call me Odysseus, I guess.
Island builder.
build seesaw let's put it
right over here it can be an out activity after the
restaurants i don't know we'll figure it out seesaw on the
seashore let's bring uh ibu you can go with seesaw
Oh yeah.
Wait, I think he needs help with it though.
He's just sitting on it for now.
Uh, who's available?
Wait, you guys are strangers?
Oh.
Would you ever play the Death Stranding games?
Yeah, I plan on it.
It's nice to meet you.
Joel, look at the membership.
Thank you.
My name is Haley.
Joel Osment.
I think he looks so much like a Quetzalcoatl Alice.
It's so awesome.
I think I did a pretty good job with this guy.
Like surprising.
They're discussing skin.
Yeah, but the planet gem over.
Watching this reminds me a lot of animes where it's clear
that the two characters are in love with each other, but
they just don't commit.
It's tough.
It's tough being me.
What if I... Actually, no, this is...
What if I have a tragic love story with Snake?
That was really fun.
Thanks so much.
Not that I care.
I hate you.
I hate you so much.
Don't worry.
Wait.
Join.
Oh no, no, join.
What?
Wait!
Gengar and Ibor are strangers?
Like boo.
Wait a second.
Huh?
How did they not met yet?
I think that's enough to get you guys together, though.
Boo.
Like boo.
Like.
Boo.
So, it sounds like shaggy.
Like Scoob.
That's kind of...
That's just kind of...
Hey, man.
You have...
You have Frogbird.
You need to chill.
What is Frogbird doing?
Oh.
Wait, I thought I said he was inside.
Snake, please.
Mito, please.
I'm here.
I'm watching.
I'm actually, I'm frustrated at you.
Look at them.
Maybe now they'll confess their feelings.
We can see.
Snake is going home and he's gonna have a little bubble over
his head.
It'll happen.
Pink bubble.
Pink bubble now.
Vicky's asleep.
Sneak's awake.
Minto's playing game.
Have Phoebe and Minto yet met?
Yes.
They have.
Minto and Vicky have not met yet.
But yeah, see, they've met their acquaintances.
You can join.
You can meet up.
Phoebe.
This is nice.
Oh, this is nice.
I want s'mores.
This year, this summer, I'm getting s'mores.
The secret of how she acquired.
Please, what are you doing in there?
What are you doing in there?
You didn't even look.
I like this!
You scared of it.
Only I had a fire.
They're hitting it off though.
Oh, more people are planning a gathering.
Oh my god, I can't.
These two.
Here, I'll help you out.
I'll help you out.
There.
There you go.
Stovesmores taste just as good, but I like the burnt taste.
I want me a little bit of carcinogens in it, you know?
He's just really letting...
I think Snake is, like, leading him on a little bit, you
know?
Useful flings!
Oh, what's up with Snake?
Hrnga, maid outfit?
What narwhal clone?
You're a shibble-tuned imp.
Like, boo.
Snake is super cool.
What's happening?
No way.
I feel all mixed up.
I like Minky, but I also have feelings for Vindaka.
Who do you think are really why?
It was never us, huh?
Bro, Hawaii trips.
It was never us, was it?
I was never in.
Be stubborn.
Don't give up.
You like me, though!
You're right.
I was nearly misled.
Minky is the only one for me.
You're right, Gengar is gonna drop him because that guy
doesn't know what he wants either.
You're so right!
That guy doesn't know what he wants either!
What does Haley Joel Osman have a problem with?
Hum.
Good evening.
He's daydreamed so many times about Vicky.
He's just getting our...
I want to try living with Joe.
Not that I care.
Great thinking.
If I lived with Joe, we'd be spending a lot of time
together.
What's something you think we'd enjoy doing every day if Joe
and I lived together?
Oh.
You could spend your days.
Because they're both Joe.
With your mom.
Joe kidded.
You guys are the worst.
I think you're right.
I'll go talk to him, not that I care.
Spend your days with your mom.
There's, um, something I'd like to ask you.
Jorkin, it was perfect.
I don't want that.
What's got you looking so serious?
Joe.
Well, if the two of us live together, what's something you
think we'd enjoy doing every day?
Let's say it together.
one two three with your mom it's like we share the same
brain we have to live together let's have for ourselves i'll
fix it
oh my god we finally got someone to
live this is gonna be a blast not that i care don't you
think the houses here are a little small i'm thinking we'll
need to build The new one.
They're both turning into the Joker.
Let's build a house for Haley, Joel Osmond, and co.
Oh no, it's kind of blocked off, though.
I have to fix it.
I'm sure we'll have a great time living in this house
together.
I think he actually cares.
Say, do you have any ideas for what to call our household?
If you have a good name for us, I'd love to hear it.
Your mama's house?
Jorkin with our moms?
Joe mama's house!
It's so good.
Joe.
Joe mama's house.
Wait, is...
Come over to Joe mama's house.
That's singular, right?
That'd be singular, right?
They'll be known as Joe Mama's house.
Then we shall be henceforth known as Joe Mama's house.
Thanks for the excellent idea, not that I care.
I hope you'll keep checking in on us, the members of Joe
Mama's house.
Not that I care.
I don't think he cares, you guys.
I don't think he cares.
Hold on, I got it actually.
build a little bit, though.
I don't think he cares.
Uh...
I just gotta make it so that it's attached a little bit.
We'll give them a bit of a front yard, too.
Okay.
Oops.
There we go.
Oh?
Oh!
Wait, what?
What do you mean?
Why is it pink?
What is happening?
What do you mean?
Why is it pink?
I'm not even sure what this feeling is.
I want to propose to Ibubu.
After one day!
In that case, I'll summon all my courage and ask for his
hand in marriage.
The thing is...
The thing is?
My heart is racing and my head is full of distractions.
any chance you can come with me and help me focus okay yeah
okay then it's time to go see i boo i can't even get a
confession figured out why this game is so fun because it's
basically madlips 2.0 it is yeah oh my god in this cozy log
cabin this is awesome thanks for meeting me here of course
Toho fan.
What do you mean by that?
So, um...
Oh!
Fire at distracting thoughts.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Not the eyeballs!
Ew, illegal arms mint!
Get out of my head!
If I miss, is it... Okay, it's fine.
This is fine.
This is easy.
oh nice what was the issue i actually have something really
important that i wanted to talk about oh what is it zero
part two oh oh oh okay okay okay well here goes oh again
again okay okay
cream stool
Oh, I missed.
Oops.
I missed.
Will there be Damaku?
Oh.
Oh, those are the Damaku.
Wow.
Oh, gosh, it was huge.
I'm so nervous.
Don't be nervous.
I got you.
I can't stop thinking about you.
You're everything to me.
Oh, it makes me happy to hear that.
How am I throwing?
We're not throwing at all.
Here it is.
I'm just going to say it.
I boo-boo.
Oh, my gosh.
Huge.
Oh, oh, ew.
Okay,
all right, I'm locked in.
Oh, that did nothing.
It was so easy.
My dear I boo-boo.
Oh my god, the flowers with the flowers.
Will you marry me?
Oh, yes, of course.
I'd love to marry you.
Live in the dream.
I'm happy for you guys.
It's happening.
Big boss.
I'm so happy for you guys.
We're so excited for our wedding.
Oh, snake.
The charismatic frog bird.
The joke-loving high-boos.
We did the high-boos.
Now frog bird can never leave.
Oh, they're going on honeymoon.
world galore it's australia's great barrier reef my face how
could it be that you guys are the first ones to get married
on my island don't worry me though your turn will arrive too
i always cry at wedding our wrist is unparalleled
inside new zealand's chasm and glacier is so eke and frozen
Send mittens.
Oh, look at you both.
Oh, it won't happen again.
I think it will.
Can't stop finding a cab out here.
Maybe I can hop in this kangaroo's couch.
Say cheese.
Oh.
Always the bridesman.
Never the bride.
That was so much fun.
We got you a souvenir.
Say, oh.
What is it?
Oh good, we can give this one to not Gengar.
Now that we're back, I guess the next step is to grow all
together.
What the heck, that's so sweet!
Mary for one day.
It literally said in love for one.
Now we have done everything there is to do in Australia.
I literally just gave this nickname to you guys.
I just gave this to you.
You told us before you used to play the violin, didn't know
you were talking about the same fiddle.
Oh, keep the nicknames?
Okay, they still work, yeah.
Good evening, I'm Boo Boo.
I guess we should start living together.
Don't you think the houses here are a little small?
I'm thinking we'll need to build a new one.
Okay.
Wait,
we could do it right here.
What was next to...
Was anything next to Frogbor?
Nothing?
What?
Was there nothing?
Oh, Gengar was!
Oh, everything happened so fast!
I didn't even notice!
I'm sure we'll have a great time living in this house
together.
Say, do you have any ideas for what to call our household?
You guys?
If you have a good name for us, I'd love to hear it.
I'd love to hear it.
This is all you.
I was thinking the bone zone, but you guys can also come up
with your own thing.
Canada.
The bone zone is...
is great.
The bone zone?
I like the bone zone too.
I'm glad we're in agreeance.
The freak shack?
That can be it.
If Minto ever gets married.
If Minto gets married, she can live in the freak shack.
The bone zone.
Singular.
They'll be known as the bone zone.
Then we shall be henceforth if known as the bone zone.
I know what I said.
Thanks for the excellent idea.
I hope you'll keep checking in on us, the members of the
bone zone.
Oh my god.
Dark Creator, thank you.
Don't call me Charlie.
There's not a level up either.
Only Frog, I guess Frogbird's the one who did the proposing
of everything.
Oh, someone's...
Why is...
Oh.
Oh, they're hanging out.
Now that's a mansion.
If you want to change the look at the living room of the
group, name for the home, just press X.
Okay, look.
Let's see what Haley Joel Osman is dreaming of.
Oh, I think I hate it.
Snake needs help?
Oh, he does?
Okay, hold on.
He's dreaming of a bottle cap.
My bottle cap.
I think...
thought you were gone forever is he then gonna see the other
one and go my bottle cap I thought you were gone oh okay and
get me out of here I don't want to be in here anymore
dreaming of useless items it was just a dream no
no snake needs help we'll go is it pink
Oh, Snake is here.
Oh, this...
Oh.
I didn't know you could beat Fox.
This is just...
Kick my life.
Kick.
No!
The Fallout game, it's currency.
Really?
Don't worry.
You're saving for the apocalypse!
Wait.
What?
Come on, Ain'to, you got this.
Hrnka!
I owe you one.
Of course I'd help you.
Yeah!
Was it was likes a lot before and now it's crushing?
Jebel?
Let's see.
That's so quiet.
I think it got downgraded.
No, it didn't.
Oh.
Good evening.
What's the issue?
I want to be friends with Victoria the Hedgehog.
Oh yes, great thinking!
What should we talk about?
Well...
Other lingo.
Big, big butt.
Got it.
I'll go talk to you about a big, big butt.
Victoria the Hedgehog.
I wish Ketzel would want to be friends with me.
I think I have no worries in this game.
But also...
A big, big butt.
I think I have made the character so close to me.
Sure.
I suck!
Fun fact about me?
When I take pictures of a big, big butt, they always come
out perfect.
No way.
Me too.
It's been a childhood dream of mine to live like a- First we
had bosoms and now we have butts.
This is crazy.
This can't be real.
That's a dream of mine too, innit?
I mean, it feels like fate.
We should be friends, right?
I have tremendous brains.
I think we are friends now, innit?
I don't know.
Oh, Vicky would love Wario, yeah.
We'll do Vicky.
Vicky, you look...
And we'll do pretzel.
Good evening, pretzel.
Looks like our childhood dreams of being...
That's so cute!
casual relationships.
Maybe you're the slow person.
Maybe you're the slow person he needs.
Maybe.
Let's see, a quirk maybe.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, like a voracious, yeah.
Yeah.
God, I think he looks so good, doesn't he?
The same happening oh they just jumped for some reason it's
not happening I don't think it's happening I don't think
it'll ever happen it's never gonna happen
we're level 16 I can give a new gift what's new is the
karate new I keep saying new.
New goods.
I don't want to give it, though.
I don't want to give the karate.
We'll do...
Oh, wait.
The shower.
Our shower.
Muscle building for Vicky will be nice.
Oh, Charu!
We can get the eye out of her.
Outdoor shower!
Wait, did he just say I hope I can get along with Vinky and
wish it into the fountain?
Is she daydreaming about Snake?
Don't open your eyes yet.
Wait, they're in Alaska.
It's winter.
It's so cozy.
The audience chairs for the showers.
have not forgotten.
I want you to be sweethearts.
It's not happening!
Oh my gosh, this is the most frustrating anime ever.
This is the anime that everyone yells about.
It says, just get together.
Why are we love Hina?
Like, what is this?
We are the frustrating anime.
No!
Season 3 with no confession.
Come on, bro.
Seriously.
Wait, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
What are you?
If this is about Snake, I'm gonna...
This book is so funny.
Like, who?
Ha ha ha.
He, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he.
Minto and Snake have been in love since last stream.
In this stream, Brockford and I, fell in love started dating
a guy like okay they fell in fell in love off stream but
yeah pretty much
that ain't happening guys i think this is where i have to
call
i think this is where i have to call it nothing's gonna
happen it's Is he following me?
He's stretching.
Minky's yawning.
This is real.
Actually, let me show her the shower real quick.
To give her the outfit!
Ouch!
I don't know.
Oh, come on.
I gotta give you the maid outfit.
Maybe the maid outfit is what...
I think a maid outfit is what will make him go go go go go
go go go go go go.
You know?
so cute
okay so good okay come on where are you where is he where's
snake where is he they're hanging out they're having a good
time what the hell are you doing there this cheater what are
you doing hello
wait did i just see shy don't look at me don't turn around
he left gangar you hate that thing
but snake gave it to him no he didn't i
He gave it to him!
Good, they're chatting.
Well, we're on the map.
Relationship up.
Macross tier love triangle.
It's getting intense!
Guys, it's getting intense!
Oh,
they're having a good time.
Victoria the Hedgehog and Chetzel.
Phoebe wants you to bring someone over to play with.
Get some koalas!
Come here.
We haven't met yet.
Oh, they haven't met yet.
My name is Phoebe.
Hello there, Phoebe.
I'm known as Quetzalcoatlus.
This anime is getting good.
We might have to, we'll have to wait until the next...
Oh, kind invitation.
Would you like to play Seesaw?
Wait, why is she turning...
Why is she sepia?
What just happened?
Oh,
it worked!
You look so funny.
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
You did not like the dance.
Good.
Yay!
Maybe he's a good friend.
I liked it.
Are they just running around together?
With... With...
This is...
Thickening.
Please do something.
I can't stand it anymore.
Please.
Please do something.
Watch him, like, still be sitting at the table.
Oh.
Watch him still be sitting at the table waiting for...
No, I wasn't.
Oh, and he goes up to his room and looks at the stupid
koala.
You hate that guy.
Don't act like you like him now.
I'm still offended.
Guys, this is where season two ends.
Two?
Three?
Season?
Season three?
It ends with them like this.
No No confession Minto Snake And the little iboo all running
around together Like a happy family that they could be You
can't let them propose off stream No no no I would never let
you I would never let that happen Wait what happened Why did
you leave him Phoebe Phoebe He's still sitting on the
seasome, I'm still...
We'll still visit sometimes, promise we can't spend all of
our time blissfully with Frogbear after all.
Good night.
Yeah, I could do a guerrilla stream if anything happens.
But right now...
This is it.
I've tried to push it as much as I can.
But I don't think anything's...
Let's see if Mito goes in here.
Just kidding, you're the absolute cutest and rizziest.
It was been all the time with you that we have on us.
Snark is just really enjoying the slow build-up.
She's too busy with her video games.
Hopefully something will happen soon.
Season 3 will be great.
Yeah!
Hate it when the show ends on a cliffhanger.
I tried, guys.
I really tried.
I tried!
What are they doing?
Oh!
oh my god he's taking pictures of him making food relax a
little oh my god i can't stand i can't stand these two i
can't stand these two she doesn't yearn lincoln guard it's
over
what is in here
Is that the bathroom?
It's only quiet but no one's in there.
Ew.
Playing with a sugar glider.
It's scary as always.
What?
Oh,
you think it was just Frogford?
What do you mean, scary as always?
They're
married, but they have separate rooms.
I mean, some couples are like that, but...
Yeah.
Snake, that's how your love is going to fizzle out if you
don't do anything.
Aibu loves the thrill.
Okay, I'm letting him go to his house.
I'm letting him go to...
No, please, go to your home.
Go to your home and do something.
Go back home and then think about how you want to confess.
It is hard to stop playing this.
It is.
Thank you, Duargo, again so much for the pink.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Big boss?
Get inside.
I hate these two.
I hate these two!
Goodbye!
Outsumito!
Wait, what does Phoebe want real quick?
I think she probably just I just want something to be built.
What do you want?
I want a chat.
You want a chat?
Wait, what are we chatting about?
Sure thing?
Everyone's got those things that they just dread doing.
Am I right?
Be false.
So tell me.
What are yours?
What's the worst way to spend your time?