Hello!
Everyone!
Do we have a hello for Denchi in general?
Ohha Denchi?
I mean, we do have our intro.
Like, Yure, you know?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Goodbye, but not for hello.
MVP South.
MVP.
I'm pleased to meet you, I just saw in chat.
That's a good one.
Oh, that's cute.
MVP South.
Yay.
I love it, I love it, I love it.
Let's use that, then.
Remember, you guys, at the very end, we're going to say MVPs
out.
For the hello, I guess.
I've tried.
Thank you guys for your input on the sound balance in the
chat.
I have now tried to balance it out, but feel free to keep
putting more input in there.
Yeah, you're at my house now.
Or my lack of a house.
Oh, it smells so good.
You're a beautiful house.
Can I have one of those?
cookies please yeah i baked them just for us today go ahead
have some yay oh i swear i've seen them before and bugs what
kind of bugs friendly ones and if we're eating them oh no
just like the air around here smells like cookies and
flowers and bugs oh i thought you said there were bugs in
the cookies i mean that would be extra protein And it's
basically the same as putting protein powder in, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wait, I like these emotes.
Are those the heads?
They're just the heads.
Cute.
Yeah, Densetsu memberships on the official channel are...
Woo!
Yummy!
Thank you guys so much for all of your support.
For the fan club and in the Discord server.
It's been really, really fun.
Yeah, thank you.
I'm just yapping with you guys all the time.
It's been really fun.
And the emotes are so good.
They're so awesome.
I love them.
They're very us.
We have your guys' favorite.
Mine is Phoebe 6'7".
I knew you were going to say that.
What about you?
What about you, Phoebe?
What's your favorite?
Mine?
I kind of...
Out of all of these...
I guess...
I think...
The one...
Without... The one where...
It's not the head.
The headless Vicky is just very cute.
Headless Vicky!
Headless Vicky.
What is that called?
Oh, MVP shrug.
Like... Sometimes I feel like that.
I'm like, the brain.
Why does it think?
I don't...
Can I turn it off?
No brain, no think.
I just just ongabunga.
Ongabunga.
I don't know.
I feel like I can get a lot of use out of the sawed ones.
Three of just the head.
The sawing one is so good.
Yeah.
I love the ladder as well.
And you can make it as long as you like.
Yeah.
It's so long.
I challenge chat.
Somebody start the ladder and then make the longest.
ladder.
Make a really long ladder.
How long can the ladder go without a mento appearing?
Yeah, yeah without a mento.
Okay, you guys.
But it has to be sometimes a mento.
Sometimes.
Success.
Or it could be, it could be, oops, all mentos.
It could just be a million mentos climbing up a, climbing up
a ladder.
Where is she going?
Where could, where kind of heights will she reach?
I'm glad I'm not afraid of heights.
Oops.
Oh, Minto.
Oh, no!
No!
Oh, man.
Thank you guys so much.
Yeah, thank you.
That's Mint trying to reach the cabinets in the kitchen.
Why would you say that?
Guys, you could just get me to fetch for you you don't have
to do that yeah we want to we want to be we want to be
strong independent idols that don't need no taller idol to
get to reach the plates in the cupboards for them you know
like we we want to trouble you every time we need to get a
plate yeah understandable understandable guys i had to use
my step stool today
Literally me.
Literally me every day.
Wait, you guys are tall.
So you have a little stool to get to the cupboards?
Yeah.
Oh, that's nice.
You could, like, decorate them with, like...
You could make them, like, pink and mint and decorate them
for each of your colors.
Let's decorate our stools together, mint.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Wait, we should have, like, a stream where we decorate.
Yeah.
Bling out your stool.
Mine is pretty plain and needs to be decorated, I think.
Man, you guys are so lucky.
I was literally at a shrine yesterday with, like, lots of
gates, and I kept nearly hitting my head on the gates, you
know.
You guys don't have to live with stuff like that.
You don't have to constantly live in fear of things above
you.
It must be nice.
I don't live.
Oh, that's true.
Yes, sorry.
She doesn't live.
Oh, no.
Would it anger the gods if you, like, bumped your head on
the...
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
I was being so careful.
I was, like, I was, like, hunched over.
Just like, don't hit it.
Don't hit it.
I have a question for you.
I see, you're so nice, though.
I heard that some tall people struggle with the kitchen in a
different way than us.
Some of them struggle with countertops being too low.
for them you've never had your shirt oh my god yeah really
yes my my sink every time i do the washing up it's like what
is it so low this isn't made for me i've never thought of
your struggles i've just selfishly thought of my own oh no
don't worry guys we we both have struggles in our own way
but we can we can help each other tall tall and short yes
full and short mvps guys yeah We threw the dishes.
You put away the dishes.
Yes.
I would like to propose, though, a short-person area for
concerts.
Yeah, right?
Like how there's a girl's area sometimes at Japanese
concerts.
I would like a short-person area.
Please, please.
You must be this tall to enter the area.
I mean, I can get behind that.
I always feel bad at concerts.
I'm like, It's like the constant fear of like I don't want
people not to see so I'm down for that.
I agree.
I agree with you guys.
Yeah Thank you for understanding the the proper courtesy at
concerts is for taller people to put the shorter people on
their shoulders Exactly Everybody is just stacked on each
other so yeah shoulders that everybody has a chance and then
you find a window after that you know You pair up yeah,
yeah, yeah and short person and then yeah all the tall
people short people people's stacks will find windows after
that and then then everyone's happy you must pair up yeah
and maybe we you know could even be like cheaper tickets for
stacking stacking ticket yes and you can say like three
short people on your shoulders discount three or it's like
the more short people you stack on your shoulders the more
of a discount you get like it's 10 discount for every We
could, like, they could install, like, monkey bars above,
above, so you could, like, grab on for stability.
Yeah!
You're so right!
We could just keep stacking people, everyone will have a
view.
Right!
Or if you, like, want to switch which tall person you're
sitting on during the show, you can, like, eye the person
next to you, and then use the monkey bars to make your way
over and switch with them.
You know?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Or you could just hang from the monkey bars and enjoy the
show.
Double doesn't work out, too.
Yeah, get those arms trained up.
Oh my god, we're geniuses.
And that's how you end up.
That's how you get strong like Vicky and you were able to
lift your friends.
Yes!
I'm still training hard, guys.
I hope I'm going to be able to do it.
I'm going to do my best.
I know you can.
Definitely.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Yay.
That said, we were already doing a lot mental heavy lifting
right now but we're gonna have to do even more today in uh
in a say it on the beat slash say it on the word challenge
yeah uh i don't know if you guys so i actually hadn't heard
of these things until uh mento and vicky uh proposed the
idea and i was like why did i write those so then i looked
it up and i was like oh this is kind of like i mean like the
beat Reminds me of rhythm having a little bit.
It does.
Oh, wait, guys.
Can I ask you one question?
Because chat is saying I'm ignoring it.
I didn't see it.
Guys, um, okay.
I need to know.
Do you shower every day or every other day?
This is important for the...
Oh, is it?
It depends.
Are you every day or every other day, people?
Yeah, thank you!
Thank you!
Chat!
Every other day is fine in Windsor!
In my opinion.
So, so this is, this is my answer.
I wash my body every day, but I wash my hair every other
day.
Uh, yeah, that's, that's also a good, a good idea.
Yes, yes, yes.
Are you a fellow stinky, Vicky?
I, I shower full stop every other day.
Every other day, man.
Uh, you don't need a shower every day, in my opinion.
Wait, Minto, are you a fellow, are you a stinky as well?
I guess so.
I don't know.
Like, it depends.
In Japanese summer I shower every day But alright, you don't
need it in winter guys Anyway, turns out 55% of my chat
Shower every day people So Shower every day ruins your skin
Okay, I need to debunk this This is why It depends on your
soap No?
Well, but also you're supposed to like Super, super lotion
yourself up After every single shower Like, don't you?
Don't you lotion?
Moisturize?
Yeah, but...
No, I'm talking to chat!
I'm like, oh, you're like, oh, showering every day is
gonna...
Gonna...
No, yes?
Moisturize!
Yeah, boys, if you have time to shower, you have time to
moisturize!
Yeah!
Don't give me that chat!
Now I'm getting on my fellow everyday shower...
Wait, no, no, no.
I'm getting on the not everyday showers.
I don't know if I'll shower today.
Yeah, just see what happens.
Go with the wind.
the wind takes me chat okay i don't know listen listen
anyway sorry yes please continue say it on the beat yes
sorry yeah say it on the beat so we have a bunch of
challenges we have downloaded from both tick tock and
youtube and the the curse thing about this is that none of
this is going to be on the beat none of it will be because
we're on discord chat we're doing discord screen share It's
going to look great!
Extra, extra...
Yes.
Do we want to...
So we're doing it all together, right?
Oh, yes, we're doing...
Well, unless we want to try individually, but I think it's
funner...
It's funnier if we do it all together.
I think we could maybe do each person individually and then
last all together.
Or do you guys want to do that?
Or do you guys want to do only just all together?
try it, try it ourselves, embarrass ourselves, and then do
it together, and then not be embarrassed anymore, because
we're all terrible.
Sounds good to me.
Sounds good.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Let's do it.
Alright.
Alright, alright.
Also, I'm sorry, I don't know why my chat's not working in
the back.
I might as We'll just get rid of the chat box at that point.
There you go.
What's the secret third thing?
Oh, well, I voted for that one.
I did too.
Oh, what is this?
I do a secret post it is, but we agree.
Secrets?
I love secrets.
There we go.
I'll vote that one.
Not just the face.
You moisturize more than just the face.
Also the rest of your body.
Crusty.
Denchies.
I mean unless you like adding texture to your body I guess
then then maybe like a lizard like a lizard
that's appealing to me here here's the first of our say say
the word on the beat challenges are you guys ready do you
want to gum yeah do you want to gum baru first as having no
ping like and then sure but also mine's gonna be slightly
off too because whenever i play audio from the desktop it's
slightly off from from my voice um so this is this is this
is about how scuffed it'll be with no ping and then imagine
that but even more scuffed when the other two do it so So,
here we go.
I'll give it a try.
Dog,
dog, dog, dog, cat,
cat.
You guys were doing the same thing, but...
So, how was that, chat?
I think that's a rat.
I don't think that's a cat.
I mean, a...
Oh, it's a rat!
A
maim!
I'm sorry if this is, like, animal profiling or something,
but the cats, I mean, mice and rats are, like, the same to
me.
They're not!
No!
How?
Okay, wait.
They're both cute to me.
So, what do you mean how dare?
Are we, are we like...
Do we hate?
Do we not like one of them?
You can tell by the tail.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
That's like big.
When I've seen them in person in London wandering around,
they're big.
Looking at this...
What's the difference between the tails?
I don't know.
What?
You told me the difference isn't in the tail.
What was the difference?
Just gaslighting for those.
Dude, I'm getting gaslit, gas boss, gas kept.
Oh my gosh.
Rat tails are big and long.
I think you're right though.
Yeah, they're just big.
They're just big.
The tails are big.
Maybe it is a mouse.
I thought because it's cat and then it's rat.
You would think so.
You might actually be a mouse.
Oh, hold on.
I'm so confused.
That's a mouse?
I just messaged me.
He said, tell Phoebe to turn off the BGM.
I think when we're doing the...
Oh, I didn't even realize it was on, sorry.
There you go.
Thank you.
But that was the...
That was the...
The...
Practice round, anyway.
Practice round.
That's a mouse?
It's fatter and more rotund, so it's a mouse.
So I was right.
What?
Gaslit, gas boss.
Gas kept.
I take back everything that I know.
No, it's okay.
We're learning.
That is not a peat rat.
It is a peat mouse.
But do you know the... Do you guys know the G-L-I-B-L-I-Pet
Rat Gumai Kandai video?
Yes.
What?
On G-L-I-B-Lai.
What did you just say?
Wait, I need to show you.
Jelly belly, pet rat, gummy candy.
I will send it to you for watching later It's from one of my
favorite channels Run for the Cube I will send it to you for
consumption later At a later date Send it for later
Okay Oh my god July, July Heat rat, gumai, can't I
Unfortunately, I have most of that video memorized.
Anyway, intrusive thoughts aside.
It's all mouse.
And now, would you guys like to do the dog cat mouse
challenge together with me?
Send me in.
Okay.
Here we go.
You guys can hear the audio from the screen share, right?
Yes.
Okay.
Let's do this thing.
Gambari mouse.
That's, you can hear the latency.
So, this is, this is, this is the stream.
Absolutely abysmal.
That's, that's the goal.
Yes.
It's like a kindergarten class trying to sing.
It was horrible.
Please continue.
Yay.
We got it.
No notes.
notes.
Oh, thanks, Jet.
There was passion.
That's, that's, that's what's important.
What's important is not the word or the beat.
It's the passion behind it.
The passion.
It's the heart that goes into every word as we passionately
say dog, dog, cat, cat, mouse, mouse, cat, dog.
Yes.
I think the more difficult, the more difficult it gets, the
more passion we should put into it.
Yeah.
I'm ready for level two.
Level two passion, let's go.
So level two, shall we...?
What is that?
Oh.
jorn spoon, mont spun, mont spawn, Spoon.
Spoon, mon, boom, boom, boom.
Spoon, boon, boon, boom.
Ron, born, spoon, boon, boon.
Spoon, cocoon.
Huh?
Spoon, bon, boon, spoon, boon.
No, bro, how does raccoon fit in there?
What?
Wait, what is this?
Cheese, burger, bacon, cheese, bacon, cheese.
What?
Is that cheese?
Is that butter?
Wait, hold on.
Boom.
Butter, but, but, but, but.
Butter, burger.
Boom, boom.
Butter, boom.
In that action.
Okay, I'm ready.
But, but, but.
Butter, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but,
but, but, but, Bottle burger bacon Bottle burger bacon Oh
this is so American Nihouti Nihouti Nihouti partner I'm
ready to go So okay so we are doing this in the southern
accent right Okay yeah yeah we got this Are we doing it all
together or do we want to try Try solo for any of these How
are we feeling It could be fun trying it a little a little
solo would either you like to do this very american level
i'll do it do it man don't go i got this is it butter or is
it cheese people in the chat can't agree oh i think it's
butter because it's all b words right burger boom bacon
butter oh that's big brain big big brain is also so there
you go i believe in you Are you mad?
You got it.
Let's go.
Oh, Re-living the trauma.
This one's hard.
Wait, this is the hard one.
Okay.
Burger, bacon, butter, bacon, butter, burger, burger,
burger, bacon.
What?
Boom, butter, burger, boom.
I can only like it the first time.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Would you like a second try for that?
Whoa, Bento, he locked in that first one.
That was crazy.
Yeah, he locked in so hard for the first one though.
Here, let me, yeah, one more time, one more time, coach.
One more time, I got this.
Go, go, go.
I'll lock in, I'll lock in.
I won't laugh at all.
Burger, bacon, butter.
Butter,
burger, bacon, butter, bull, butter, bacon, butter.
Butter, bacon, burger, burger, burger, burger.
Incredible.
That was beautiful.
Guys, that was amazing.
Yay!
You did?
Guys, send me in for my American training.
I'm ready.
Yay!
Howdy, howdy, partner.
Howdy, partner.
Howdy.
All right, here we go.
Here we go.
I'm ready.
Yeah.
So ready.
Let's go.
Burger, bacon, butter, bacon, butter, burger, burger, bacon.
Yeah.
Butter, burger, bacon, butter, boom, boy, bacon, burger,
burger.
Butter, bacon, burger.
Butter, bacon, burger, butter, boom.
Bacon, butter, bacon, burger, bacon, butter, boom.
Doesn't matter as long as she finishes.
You guys were here for the naturalization.
of our lovely British friend into Marfa.
Oh, thank you, thank you.
I'll do my best to be American, like you guys.
I'll do my best.
That was so good.
That was very good.
I think that when you do the Southern accent, it helps you
lock in.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you, Manto.
I'll walk in.
So does it help you to walk in if you do that?
I think so, yeah.
Wow.
It's so funny how you can hear how much worse the latency is
for Vicky.
Compatimenta!
I know!
Sorry, guys.
Oh.
That was so good.
That's my favorite one yet.
I'm excited for what's coming.
Yeah.
The butter bacon.
I guess I'll try.
Yeah, go, Phoebe!
Go, Phoebe, go!
I'm gonna test the accent and see if it really does help um
here we go oh god burger bacon butter bacon butter butter
butter butter that's not butter that's not butter butter
oh my god oh no it's because you guys found me in a very
chinese time of my life i'm giving my i'm giving my american
citizenship to vicky Thank you so much!
Itadakimasu!
It's crazy!
Oh, so good.
Perfect recipe for a perfect burger, you guys.
Yeah!
Butter bacon burger, boom, boom, boom.
Yeah.
What is the boom boom popping candy?
Lost green card acquired.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, I need to recover, okay.
You guys are so good at this, though.
You're so good.
I'm ready.
Let me load up the next one.
See, the word on the impossible.
Impossible!
What does that mean?
I don't remember what ones I chose, you guys, but there are
some meme ones.
Just like...
No, good.
Good.
Well, this entire thing feels like a meme to be fair, but...
That's true.
Okay.
I'm excited.
I'm ready.
Are we gonna try this one together?
Do you want to try it individually?
I think we could do it together, right?
Yeah, let's do it together.
We'll do the first one together.
First try together.
Okay, okay.
Here we go.
Let's do it.
Godspeed.
Car bed, bed, car bed, star, star, star.
Who's that?
Red pair.
Oh, that's Ted?
Oh, it's Ted!
I watched that movie.
And Dolgy Bear.
The Dolgy Bear.
Oh, that's why it's 10 and 10 and bread and bread.
Okay, okay, okay.
I feel like this one was easier than the bacon butter
burger.
Yeah, I think so.
Okay, we can do it individually if anybody wants to.
Yeah.
I believe.
I will, I will lead the charge on this one next.
Maybe somehow you turned your BGM back on.
Oh, did I?
I didn't, huh?
Okay.
What is this poll?
Can I vote both?
It's exactly 50-50.
Oh no.
Whoa.
Come on.
It has to be exactly 50-50.
Please.
Lock in.
You guys.
Oh, it's 50-50.
There!
It was 50-50 for a second!
You failed.
You couldn't walk in.
I really believed in you.
Who's going first?
me and coach go let's go oh here we go okay okay here we go
i'm ready i'm so ready
i'm so ready i want
to try being british can i try it with the british do it do
it do it do this whole thing with the British is what we
should do.
Okay, okay, okay.
Go on, Minto.
We believe in you.
Okay, I'll try.
Come on, Minto.
Cup in the morning.
Go.
Joko, Joko, Joko.
Star, star, jar, card, star, star, star.
Bed, car, star, star, star, jar.
Red dead, red dead.
Oh, God.
Red, red.
You locked in, though.
Lovely.
Oh, my gosh.
That was magnificent, Minto.
Very impressive.
Now she got the British seal of approval.
Yes, absolutely.
You may have your British citizenship, Minto.
Here you go.
I'll take a cup of that.
Oh, my gosh.
We're just all exchanging citizenships at this point.
Just trading.
training citizenships yeah oh my god i'm so good all right
phoebe time to become british all right all right all right
all right here we go you can do it lazy phoebe i believe you
i believe you hopefully the chinese won't get in the way
this time again again here we go
jaka jaka jaka
I feel like
I'm doing a mix and then ending it with ja-ja-ja
That'd be so fun.
That'd be so fun if it exists.
Yeah.
I...
considering this is from like Normie TikTok I doubt it
exists but but it doesn't mean it can't be born it can be
chop it up a red bread chop it up a red bread
oh that'd be amazing we can make it exist yeah now we're
British and also American American as well American American
I like how Our voices drop.
The pitch drops as soon as we put on the southern accent for
some reason.
It helped me lock in.
I was just laughing too much.
Yeah.
It was real good.
Red bread redemption.
Yummy.
Yes.
So.
All right.
This is going swimmingly so far, I do think.
Yeah, I think so.
going exactly as expected.
I think.
Yeah.
Was that supposed to be the impossible level?
That was not impossible.
This one just is very hard.
Way harder.
Yeah, the burger one was super hard.
It was really hard.
I feel like there was just not enough syllables.
Like, there was not enough space for the syllables of butter
and burger.
Yeah.
Yeah, that one was so hard.
Oh, raccoon was hard.
Spoon, moon, raccoon.
it was hard too balloon balloon it's hard so far i'm
expecting this one to be easy peasy if the last level was
impossible level is very hard okay yeah we got this we can
do a little tricy shall we all right here we go all together
all together first okay
Sorry.
This one's kind of loud there.
What'd you say?
What'd you say, Vicky?
Oh, no, oh, nothing.
Oh, nothing.
I'm sorry.
I think I mistook the color there for something else by
accident.
Whatever could you miss?
I was clearly green.
Why would you say any other color?
Oh, so sorry.
I must have slipped in judgment for a second.
So sorry, guys.
I'm so sorry.
I reckon we got this.
Yeah, I reckon we got this.
You know what?
Mint is the color expert.
So do you want to go first, Mint, and show us how it's done.
Sure.
I'll go first.
Yeah.
Here we go.
Green,
green, green, green, green, green.
Green, green, green.
Well, that's how it's done.
Wow.
How do you roll your R's like that?
No.
You can do it, Phoebe.
You can do it.
I think she's drowning.
Oh god.
I'm gonna try then.
I'm gonna try.
Go, go, go!
Go, go!
Hey, one, two, go!
Hey,
one, two, go!
I
think!
Ring, ring, ring, ring, ring, ring, ring, ring, ring!
It's a sink!
It sounds like you're drowning!
I may be drowning in the sink.
The ice melting.
in the sink, and now I'm drowning in it.
No!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
How about you, Vicky?
Can you roll your R's?
I'll try.
Yeah!
You're just letting me for real, for real.
Okay.
Put me in, coach.
You got this.
Woo!
And if you don't, I'll still love you as your comrade and
not being able to roll ours.
Aw, thanks, baby.
Here we go.
She's hacking up a hairball.
I'm going.
Okay.
I'm ready.
Sexy blobsy blobsy.
Did you say sexy blob?
Sexy blob Hey, it's winking at us No, this is just a little
flirtatious there Got some Rizz, got some Rizz, isn't that
guy?
Sink pink, pink, pink Rizz Pink, Rizz That it works, it
works Rizz, pink, Rizz, Sink We're Rizz, Pink, Rizz, Sink
Wow Wow, that was something.
Oh my god.
Well, we know her type now.
And what type is that exactly?
What type is that?
She got raised.
Look, look, you know.
It kind of looks like the Roblox, like, Roblox face.
So Roblox guy is Vicky's type?
No, my type is Shadow the Hedgehog, guys.
I'm sorry to disappoint.
Just Shadow the Hedgehog.
It's just Shadow the Hedgehog.
Yeah.
No one else has a chance.
No one else.
Definitely not.
Winking blobs.
No sexy blobs.
Sorry to get all the hopes up of the sexy blobs in the chat
right now.
Shadow, shadow, marrow, shadow.
Macho, shadow.
Okay.
But if we, if, if people were to make say it on the beat
challenges for the three of us.
Then what kind of words would they contain?
I wonder.
Hmm.
Don't say durian.
Not durian.
Durian would be hard.
Durian.
That's three silver.
Durian, durian, durian, durian, durian.
I saw, there was one that I saw when I was looking for these
that was just all sushi.
And it's like actually impossible.
Whisp?
That's just cruel.
They're like whisp.
That's so mean.
Healthy!
Stop getting and pregnant.
What?
Stop, stop getting, getting, getting pregnant, pregnant.
I did that one perfectly.
Get pregnant, get, get, get, get pregnant.
I think that's what we need.
Why is that the second time we've talked about this this
week?
Six, six, seven, seven, seven, seven, six, seven, six,
seven.
Oh, someone said they saw a UMA version.
Oh.
That would be fun.
Hardest levels had Makitane.
Oh god.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Oh.
There's another one.
Another one.
There's more?
Yeah.
Comment 6-7 if you will see this.
Do it!
Are you alive?
Those of you guys on stream, do you see this?
Are you seeing this?
Do it.
That's crazy.
Please don't leave, Mint.
Please stay.
Mint, Mint, need I remind you that you're the one that
submitted this one?
I didn't see that part.
Okay.
All right, we're ready.
Here we go.
Okay.
We're ready.
Chair, chair, chair, chair, chair, chair,
chair, chair, chair, chair, chair,
chair, chair, chair, chair, chair, chair, chair, chair,
chair, chair, chair, There you go!
Bear, bear,
chair!
This one's okay!
This one's alright!
I think it's not impossible.
That was something!
Yeah!
Did you want to do this individually?
Yeah.
Phoebe, you go first this time.
I'll do this one.
Do it, do it, Phoebe.
I'll do it, do it, do it!
I'm an expert at bears and chairs and pears.
Pears.
There you go!
bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear
bear bear bear bear bear bear
bear bear bear bear bear bear, bear bear bear bear bear bear
bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear, bear bear bear
bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear, bear
bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear
bear bear bear bear bear, bear bear bear bear bear bear bear
bear bear bear bear bear bear bear, bear bear bear bear bear
bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear
bear
bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear
bear bear bear bear bear bear bear bear It's a Goldilocks.
And the three pairs.
Yeah.
And then a bear comes.
One of the pairs is too hot, and one is too cold, and one is
just right.
Yeah, yeah.
One is too big, and one is too...
Wait, no, one is too hard, one is too soft, and one is just
right.
Mmm, I want a pair now.
Mmm, I had pet taught yesterday.
Oh!
Good!
It was so nice.
It sounds so yummy.
Vicky, I believe you got this.
Thank you.
Send me in, coach.
Send me in.
Come with me.
Here we go.
Thank you.
Berry, berry, berry, pe, pe, pe, pe, pe.
Pe, pe, pe, pe, pe, pe, pe, pe, pe,
That's screwed up!
That is so cruel!
What is wrong?
It's the chair.
The fairy chair.
The one that she gets cucked in.
Yeah, that one.
He doesn't...
Oh no!
Hold on, I knocked over a bunch of stuff when you said that.
Sorry, Barry.
I think you're cool and I like watching your dark soul
streams.
Okay.
Minto.
Minto, you can do it.
Do I have to say Barry?
No.
Only if your soul...
Only if your soul's soul tells you to.
Okay.
Here we go.
Everything
became a- Berrybug infested my brain.
And...
She infested your brain and she whispered to you, don't you
dare.
Don't you dare, pair, pair, pair, pair, pair, pair.
Don't you dare, put me in that chair with that pair.
I'm gonna, I can't bear it.
Bear it.
That one was, that one was actually not so bad.
Again, if it's like one syllable, it's not that bad.
Yeah, yeah, it's really not bad.
Very hard, it's lying.
Give us a real hard- oh god.
Oh, it's always like extreme.
Extreme!
Let's see how extreme it'll really get.
Yeah.
Uh, uh, everyone together, shall we?
Yep.
Yes.
Let's do it.
Skelly man.
Seep, seep, seep, seep, seep, seep, seep, seep, seep, seep,
seep, seep, seep, seep, seep, Sleep deep.
Oh my god.
Sleep deep.
What?
Oh creep.
Creep.
This one is extreme.
The most extreme part of it though was figuring out what
that was supposed to be.
Yeah.
I threw him off like that.
groove.
Like, oh, that's so mean.
Look at him.
He's not a creep.
What if he's just a little guy and that's just the way he
stands.
You know?
Like, who else do we know that stands like that with their
hands out like that?
I'm sure they're not a creep.
Like, why?
Like, how could they just make assumptions like that, you
know?
Oh, oh, wait.
I finally get it.
Okay.
It's like, why is Minto so sad?
Then I was like,
then it's not.
I thought she knew someone who looked like this.
Go man, go man, go man.
What I'm saying is he's not, he's not a creep just for, just
for standing like that.
He may, however, possibly.
I'm working on my posture, okay?
No, you're really, you're doing so, you're doing so well for
yourself.
You are, you are, you are.
You look better than that guy at least.
Just play the look better than that guy.
Maybe it's freak, not What creeps us chat?
Oh, it could be freak.
It could be freak.
I love you, Vigil.
I do.
Weirdo.
You do belong here.
Do the one first.
Who would like to go first?
You can go, Vicky.
Okay, I'm ready.
I'm so ready.
Let's see what the agreement is on what that guy is called.
Let's go.
Okay.
Sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep.
Jeep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep,
sheep, sheep.
Sleep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep,
sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep.
Creep sleep, creep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep You finished,
though!
You did, you finished it!
That one's so hard!
Oh my god!
I'm so sorry.
You okay?
Oh yeah, I thought you heard, okay good.
I accidentally pressed something on my thing and I thought
it came through.
Okay, good.
No, you're good, you're good, you're good.
I will try it next.
I don't know if I can do Doing me better than that though.
Here we go.
Sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep.
Jeep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep.
Sleep, jeep, jeep, creep, sheep.
Sheep, sheep, creep, jeep, sleep, sleep, sheep.
Creep, sleep, creep, sheep.
Sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep.
Woo!
It is so good!
It would help me lock in.
But yeah, it's okay if you start laughing.
It hard!
Yeah!
It can be harder, yeah.
I wiggled so much I'm dizzy.
I might have to just hold off on the wiggling.
Oh no!
Too much wiggling.
Yes.
The beat is kind of good though.
Don't let your mental...
Okay, I'm gonna walk in.
Yeah, ready to walk in?
I'm ready?
Yep, let me go.
Oh
my god, she locked in.
You could go to the championships.
I'm taking home the goal.
Aid on the beat champion.
Oh my god.
No, you could compete, Minto.
This is your calling.
Whoa.
Competitive aid on the beat.
Oh my gosh.
You had the concentration face on.
I did.
I was like, I was focused.
Yeah.
It's so good.
Oh my god.
It was a very good.
Focus face.
Thank you.
Engie face is the key.
Oh, if Engie face is the key.
Though, I don't think I can make an Engie face.
That's pretty Engie.
That's pouting for sure.
Maybe that'll help with the next round.
Put on your game face.
What do your guys' game faces look like?
Show us your game face.
Maybe this is not a laughing matter.
Oh, I'm sorry, Ray.
I need to lock it.
You're super serious.
Well, this next one doesn't have a difficulty listed.
Oh, okay.
That's scary.
That is scary.
It's a wild card.
They're like, this is serious business.
You want to know how difficult it is?
Do it.
Just got to just focus.
Just go in.
Yeah.
Lock in.
I'm ready.
Lock it.
Mm-hmm.
You guys ready?
Yeah.
Here we go.
Fly, fly, fly, fly.
Oh dear.
So...
I think this disproves our theory of everything with one
syllable being easy.
Yeah.
It's hard.
This is something else.
Let me in.
I'll do it.
I'll take it.
you can do it you can do it you are our competitive our
competitive say i'm the beat player here we go i'm not even
gonna open my eyes wow wow okay here we go what oh oh okay
she started over and couldn't see sorry sorry she needed to
calibrate her mind's eye okay here we Okay.
Pie, pie, pie, pie, pie, pie,
pie, pie, pie, pie, pie, pie, pie, pie, pie, pie, pie, pie,
pie, pie, pie, pie, pie, pie.
Pretty good.
Excellent one.
Oh.
Right.
I'm so I Really thought you were gonna do it with your eyes
closed I really thought what I was like I know you're seeing
it in your mind's eye I know you could do it You just don't
want to flex on us that hard I know that that's You're just
that good I know you could It's okay you guys can do it I
believe Vicky you want to go next Send me in Yeah, send me
in, coach Here we go I can do it Here we go Let's go
Opie, Opie, Opie, fly, fly, fly, fly, Opie, Opie
Opie, Opie Was that bonus point?
Was that like when you like do extra flips in a game and it
gives you style points?
Like, is that what that was?
Because it was like hentai, you were at the Opie.
I think about it, I was just like, thanks, thanks, coach.
I'm gonna say that one now.
All right, Phoebe, you can do it.
You can do this.
I guess...
What do you mean?
I have an unfair advantage, guys.
I don't understand what that's saying.
I don't understand.
Okay, go, Phoebe.
Maybe.
Well, I don't know.
I don't...
The British.
Yeah, the British.
British advantage.
Yeah.
It's totally what they meant, wasn't it, chat?
Yeah, definitely.
That's definitely what they meant.
Yes.
Alright, Phoebe, I believe in you.
We persist.
So that's what it is now.
You can get style points by adding extra syllables.
Okay.
Oh,
boy, oh, boy, fly, fly, fly, fly, oh, boy, oh, boy.
Yeah!
Incredible.
That's the freak mix, for real.
Did I do good, senpai?
Did I do good?
You did amazing.
That's incredible.
points.
Yeah.
Good job, you guys.
Good job.
We did amazing.
Yeah.
See that.
That's animal on the beat.
That's fun.
Okay.
This is different.
This is new.
Okay.
Let's give it a little try.
Oh.
Dogs can, dogs can, dogs can, dogs can, dogs can Dog can,
dogs, cats, dogs,
cats.
Okay, is that, is that a, what, okay, what are these?
A bat?
What?
I think the first one is a bat.
A bat, right?
What's the next one?
It's the one you're doing.
Hold on, I'm gonna, um, computer enhance.
I'm putting this up big on the screen right now.
What?
Oh god, don't make it bigger.
I'm gonna make it even bigger for better visibility.
What is happening?
No.
I do think one of them is a kangaroo.
Yeah, I think that the third and the last one are a
kangaroo, I think.
Yeah.
I don't think they're real.
Seriously, I don't think they're real.
You don't think so?
Okay, well what is the one with the big nose?
That's not quite an elephant.
Yeah.
No, that's like a seal.
A seal or seal.
Or an elephant seal.
Yeah, elephant seal.
Would you have to say the full elephant seal?
Is that what you're saying?
Bat, bat, kangaroo, elephant seal, vulture?
Elephant seal, bat kangaroo.
I think a vulture.
No, I think they're made up.
I've never seen these animals.
These are animals from space.
These are too easy.
Ew.
you know when you like question like is this real like i'm
very much questioning reality right now like
the first one's not a bat what is it then it's not can you
say that and not say oh the third one's a baboon a baboon i
guess i see it oh i see the face now okay what the heck is
that second
Wait, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey.
So, I'm bat baboon, elephant seal.
Wait, it's kind of cute.
It's a long-fingered lemur.
Oh, my God.
It reminds me of Dobie.
Dobie?
Yeah, look at this thing.
Oh, my God.
It's actually quite pathetic.
Look at it.
An I-I.
Yeah, that's an I-I.
Oh, my God.
It's so pathetic.
It's so pathetic, it looks like a wet cat.
I'm gonna put this picture of the eye eye on the screen.
It looks like Dobby.
It does look like Dobby.
I'm gonna call this image source Dobby.
Dobby is sock.
Dobby is a sock.
Oh my god, it's cute.
Oh, what a cute little friend.
Wow.
Is it okay?
Hey, oh, it's so pathetic looking.
The AI.
Oh, it's so happy looking too, though.
I just found a picture where it's pogging.
Because it can't do very much at all in the first place.
Pogging AA.
Please get this picture of me off the screen.
I did not get this.
Oh, but it's just a baby picture.
for monetizing your baby pictures my bad my bad i'm gonna
get and get off the screen get off that is a bait it has a
bait oh yeah it's a baby ai yeah oh that's a baby ai so
there's a yeah he's 16 days old only 16 days no wonder it
looks so pathetic yeah but then they grow up and they okay
some of these pictures are very cute of them and some of
them are very not yeah it looks like it's seen it's seen in
16 days no it's what it saw before the 16 days what do you
mean another picture provided by vicky sorry for showing
more of your baby pictures on screen nanoplasm but oh don't
apologize to that guy i just don't you're right you're right
yeah yeah i get we're learning about about an animal this
time yeah educational yeah i bet you guys didn't expect this
could be educational like this yeah right right wait there's
a there's a national geographic thing it's called the demon
primate what the hell demon okay that that is just slander
right there that's so we can watch it later yes
I guess this would be I-I bat lemur seal vulture seal bat
lemur for this last one wait isn't it baboon?
I thought it was a baboon.
Oh oh sorry baboon.
Baboon.
I was thinking about the long long fingered lemurs or what?
The lemur.
That's the AA.
I-I Wait, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Did we say that that second one is real?
What is it?
Is it a bat?
It's not real.
Apparently it's a bat.
No, it isn't.
Come to terms with it.
Oh, it's a hammerhead bat.
Hammerhead bat.
You too.
Oh my God, it's real.
We're like learning so much more from this one TikTok.
Oh my god, it's the first image It's the one that's used in
this thing Yeah!
Wow!
Oh my, it looks like a bat stung by a bee It does!
What hoarders have you been subjected to, little one?
Oh.
This, like, card, it looks like a Yu-Gi-Oh card But it's so
funny.
I'm gonna put this one up, too.
It says it's from Weird and Wild creatures wiki weird and
wild creatures oh i love that yeah i love that i enjoy food
mostly fruit sometimes chickens oh my god okay there the
hammer-headed bat the hammer-headed bat mostly freaky mostly
strawberries sometimes chickens
Okay.
Wait, which one of this?
This could be chat.
Who is this?
Who?
Who and who?
Yeah.
It says that male hammerheaded bats like to gather in huge
groups and crank up the volume with honking calls.
Isn't that like, isn't that like freaking Woda gay people
right there?
I was thinking those cats that look like the actor from Star
Wars that honk.
This guy kind of looks similar too.
Oh, he do, he do though.
Oh my gosh, what's his name?
Not Harrison Ford.
You guys know the guy that looks like the cat.
He looks like the cat.
He's the villain.
He's the villain guy.
That looks like a cat.
I don't think I know.
Actually, I don't think I know what you're talking about.
No, okay, hold on.
This is a whole thing.
Adam Driver.
Adam Driver plays.
Wait a second.
The one that plays freaking out.
Okay, hold on.
This is a whole thing.
Adam Driver.
Red.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Adam Driver looks like this cat.
And they're famous for honking.
And the honking cat also looks like the bat.
Oh, my gosh.
This cat does look like Adam Driver.
Oh my gosh!
It's uncanny.
It's the...
It's... I don't know actually what kind of cat this is.
It's the honking cat.
They just honk and they look like Adam Driver.
Tell me that doesn't look like Kyla Ren to you guys.
Adam Driver's cat.
And then it also looks like the hammerhead bat.
It all comes together.
Oh my gosh.
Yeah, and I'll change back to the hammerhead.
Oh my gosh I think you're doing the cat and Adam driver
dirty by saying that
Nature is so beautiful These guys are huge here.
I'm just looking at pictures of people holding them and
they're like ginormous The hammerhead how big they get.
Yeah.
Oh up to one feet.
Wow
what okay someone needs to debut as a hammerheaded bat
vtuber and you better look like kyle red you better look
like kyle yes where can i see a hammerhead bat yeah where
yeah i didn't have a name hammerheaded bat zoo oh yeah yeah
i wanted to go see in person hammerhead is true bat and zoos
we totally Only one in Poland.
Only one in Poland!
I guess we're also going to Poland.
Add it to the list of places?
Yeah!
Wow!
We learned so much.
Oh my gosh, the I-I and the Hammerhead.
Yeah.
What an educational stream it's been.
Now you guys know.
TikTok is an educational place.
Yeah!
Learning so much!
More about the world and the creatures in it.
For better or for worse.
Knock on lie, I'm learning more of TikTok than I did at
school.
Who knew about this animal?
Don't say that!
Please don't say that, please!
Can I get this off the screen now?
Can I go to the next one?
Yeah, let's go to the next one, let's go to the next one.
Yeah, let's just go to the next one.
Fair pair defeats me every time.
Defeats me every time.
Wait, is this one we already did?
Is it?
Hold on, let's see.
Let's see, yeah.
It might be, yeah, we did this one.
Oh, I think so, yeah, yeah.
Okay, next one then.
Oh, level is easy for this one.
It was difficult.
Okay, I haven't seen any that said easy yet, so...
Hmm.
Here we go, shall we?
Yes.
Don't quit school, Don't quit school.
Go to school.
Right.
If you quit school, you're never going to become as good at,
say the word on the beat as we are.
You know?
Quit school.
Quit.
Don't go.
Don't do your homework.
Don't go to, on the school bus.
Don't go to school.
Instead, go to...
Chuck your cheese.
Oh!
Okay, guys.
I've never been to Chucky Cheese.
What's the what's the what's the appeal?
It's arcade with Anna.
Well, they don't have animatronics anymore, but unfortunate.
They got pizza.
You can have a wedding at Chucky Cheese.
What?
I mean, actually, yeah, I guess that makes sense.
And then Charles E.
Cheese will come out and dance for you.
Wow.
Yeah.
So like, when I was little, I went to Peter Piper Pizza
more.
Did any of you guys know or anyone in chat either know Peter
Piper Pizza?
It had a dinosaur instead.
He would have loved it.
Uncle.
He was a dinosaur instead of a mouse.
So if you pay enough at the Chucky Cheese wedding, can you
get Chucky Cheese to object?
I mean, I bet if you ask him to.
He might, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
like a whole drama wait i don't see it oh i do see him oh
he's cute isn't he cute he's so cute but he's like barney's
long lost cousin you know he's so cute yeah i think he would
have pizza pizza piper pizza okay peter piper what a
terrible day why would they do there better be peppers on
that pizza he'd make the pizza how many a paper pie pizzas
did Peter Piper bake?
Oh.
Peter Piper pizza peckle pizza peckle peppers pizza peppers
how many pizza peppers pizza peppers how many pepperoni
it's me Peter Piper Piper Mama Mia on the pizza i
thought that was the third accent i love we are sorry in
advance to any italians please i'm so sorry you understand
we are let's do that we can do the beat we can do the beat
oh yeah yeah let's try it easy easy apparently easy easy
mode okay here we go oh there there okay skelly
Moon, moon, moon, moon, moon, moon, moon, moon, moon, moon,
moon, moon, moon, moon, moon, moon,
moon, moon, moon, moon, moon, moon, moon, moon, moon, moon,
moon, moon, moon, moon, Spoon!
Spoon!
All the sun there is.
Oh my gosh, that being so soon soon.
Spoon soon.
I like spoons or moons or balloons right
now.
I didn't Peter pipe this pickle for pepper for you, idiot.
But for vodka?
Like, I like.
You or anything.
Babaka.
Good.
Oh dear.
Mama Mia, my crush is right there and I'm angry about it.
I'm a red like a tomato.
Oh.
How do you say sorry in Italian?
Hold on, sorry in Italian.
Scusa.
Scusa?
Go mena scusa to our Italian temples.
I'm denti.
Go mena scusa.
My tummy hurts.
Me too.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Who's going first?
I'll go first.
Go Phoebe's and do it.
I wanted to do that all in an Italian accent.
but I kind of couldn't.
Yeah, I'll try.
I'll try in an Italian accent.
You'll try.
You can do it.
I can do it.
I'll try.
Here we go.
Muna, Muna, Muna, Muna, Muna, Muna, Muna, Muna, Muna, Muna,
Muna, Muna, Muna, Muna, Muna, Muna, Muna!
You
sounded more like a Dracula.
It sounded more like a Dracula.
It's Dracula.
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
Blah.
Blah, blah, blah.
Four spoons.
I just turned vampire, sorry.
Blah.
Is that the fourth accent unlocked?
The Dracula accent.
I don't think so.
Okay, I'm gonna try to try a different one.
I'm gonna try a different one.
I want to...
I want to say the word on beat, please.
Yes, yes, yes.
A baguette.
It's okay, it's okay.
And you?
Yeah, I'm in.
Yes, I'm in.
Yeah, I'm in suffrage.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Baguette.
Farre blue.
Fibi, go, go, Fibi.
Yeah.
Hi, I'm called Fibi.
Hi?
I'm called Fibi.
I love you.
I love.
Okay.
Here we go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Zu yo, bass.
Okay, okay.
Moon, moon, moon, moon, moon Soon, soon, soon.
Yeah.
It's very, it's very difficult.
It's very difficult.
Moon, moon, spoon, spoon.
No.
I... I... I... I... I'm... I'm... I'm... I'm... I'm...
I'm... I'm... I'm... I'm... I'm... I'm... I'm... I'm...
I'm...
Oh, it's disgusting.
French, French, French, French, Italian, Denchi, we love
you.
Thank you.
Yes, thank you for putting up with our silliness.
Yes.
First, animals, now languages.
Very educational.
Very educational indeed.
Yes.
Let's try the next one.
Let's do it.
That was basically clear, obscure, though.
That was Expedition 33, right?
Yes.
Yeah!
This was our Expedition 33 stream.
Thanks you guys for coming.
Uh-oh.
This one's impossible.
Oh.
Uh-oh.
I'm excited.
Let's see.
I'm gonna play it.
I'm playing it.
Okay.
Oh, it's slow.
Whoa.
Sorry.
This biscuit.
Oh, it's my Ochi Biscuit.
We love you, Biscuit.
Biscuit.
Very cute.
Very cute cat.
No.
Oh, no.
We're going to deal with this.
Okay.
That was so good.
It's happening.
I think we could go to the next one okay got a few more oh
oh god what is this what is this hold on what is this what
is this what is this oh okay here we go is this yours feby
let's let's take a look at
I have a few.
This one, I was told not to look at it.
It has been, it has been, it has gone through approval
processes, but I don't know what's on it.
So, this one is so creepy.
You say that, but I'm not even the one that submitted this.
Okay, here we go.
Okay.
1 2 3 go I'm
with I I'm gonna move on from this I'm gonna move on from
this I'm gonna move on from this Oh my god The stream is
crashing You guys You guys Oh, Miku.
That last one was targeted, and I'm not humoring it right
now.
I'm not humoring it right now.
Okay, this one, this one, um, is a vocaloid one.
Oh.
For the weebs in the chat.
Are there any weebs here?
Any weebs in the chat?
I wonder if there's any weebs in the chat.
Anybody know B-boy?
Does anyone know B-boy?
Katsune Miku?
No?
Who's that?
No, no B-bebs.
Okay, well this one might not hit then.
And we might not... I don't know if we're gonna be able to
do it either.
Oh gosh, we're flopping.
Oh, what's it?
We're flopping.
Let's try.
It's so hot!
Greenland!
Oh my god!
It's so fast!
It's really fast actually.
Okay, who's going first.
I love the memes in this one though.
This one's good.
Let's see.
Who first?
I'll go first.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
There we go.
It's so cute though.
It's super duper cute.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
This is that blue-haired girl from Fortnite.
Favorite Fortnite character.
Yeah.
All right.
Here we go.
.
Nice.
Okay.
Would you like to, would you like to go next, Vicky?
Gambarimasu.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Okay.
Here we go.
I'm ready.
Woo.
Meeku, meeku, meeku, meeku, takeo, takeo, takeo.
Meeku, meeku, luke luke, meeku, meeku, luke, luke.
Meeku, one, two, tigo.
Ring, ring, len, len, len.
It's too hard to pronounce these Japanese names.
It is too dangerous.
Yes.
Oh, geez.
Sorry if we end up butchering this.
Can I just call her Mike?
Mike?
Yeah.
Can I call her Mike?
We're far too American and British and Italian and French
to...
pronounce these so yeah so sorry so my i'm probably gonna
end up butchering it yeah okay tim
mike mike mike mike mike takeo takeo takeo takeo mike mike
look mike mike mike mike mike Luke?
Ryan, Ryan, Len, Len, Ryan, Len, Ryan, Len,
Ryan, Len, Ted, Nerd, Mike, Ted, Nerd.
Ryan, Len, Luke, me, Ryan, Len, Luke, Mike.
Taito is so good.
Nerd.
Yeah, that's the four kids localization right there, you
guys.
Taito?
Friendship ended with Miku.
Mike next, Oshi.
Yeah.
Guys, we have just one more.
One more!
Yay!
That's what I know, right?
I lost chance to prove ourselves.
Okay, yeah, this is the finals.
The finals.
Final countdown.
Oh no.
What do you mean it gets cursed at the end?
I think the whole thing is cursed probably.
I think the whole thing is cursed.
Let's have the most glorious end off, shall we?
Okay.
I won't do this though.
I'll be solo though.
Let's go.
I think it's a pretty safe bet.
We know what's going to be in hair maybe yes there's quite a
bit of brain rot out there now let's see
oh my god oh i was
laughing okay
well what was that the italian brain rot i don't really know
it but the kids know it but the kids know it nowadays oh the
whispered six seven was there a whispered six seven in there
yes it was a big no
what do you mean oh of course not no no no no oh we learned
so much today i i genuinely feel like this was an incredibly
educational stream i felt like i i felt like i did like all
different lessons languages, animals, what would that be?
Biology.
All that stuff.
All in one thing.
And I feel very educated.
Apparently also cultural studies, I don't know about the
brain rot memes of the children these days.
Can someone, what, what is Italian brain rot?
Someone in chat explained to us.
Because I've seen it.
They've seen the tongue, tongue, tongue, tongue, so I don't
really get it.
I don't get it either They're very scary looking though
They're kind of nightmare feel That's kind of what like A
sleep paralysis demon Might look like on a bad day Like
Bombardilo Crocodilo Yeah I don't know what is that
Bombardino Capuchino I don't know what is Bombardino
Capuchino It's an Indonesian meme That one is Indonesian
actually Oh Really?
Oh, interesting.
Italian rhymes with the air generated movies.
Oh.
And the kids nowadays, they...
Did you know?
I saw the other day a tweet.
And somebody was like, oh, my sister just raw dogged an
essay.
And then I was like, what do you mean she raw dogged an
essay?
What do you mean the raw dog is...
What the kids mean is that...
Is like you're writing an essay without the use of ChatGPT's
help?
No!
That's just writing an essay!
It's just writing!
It's so over.
Oh my god.
Nothing but the pen and paper and the book and...
how do i do this help me oh gee oh but you know what all the
uneducated kiddos out there you guys are now smarter than
you were before you came to stream because now you know
about all kinds of animals languages yes yeah yeah the
animals animals they're there they're real stay in school
the chucky cheese you guys or watch densetsu.exe on densetsu
.exe channel on youtube.com yeah yeah even better watch it
while you're at chucky cheese oh yeah yeah yeah yeah school
or mvp school and mvp yes we're gonna take good idea we're
gonna go to school School?
We're gonna...
We're gonna get our education!
Assing!
No chat GPT!
No GPT!
Do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do...
Well, thank you everybody for joining us for this adventure.
Thank you, everyone.
Have we got any announcements?
Anything you guys got coming up to chat about with chat?
You know, like doing some streams or something?
I don't know anything.
Maybe some streams.
I need to wash my brain after this.
Yeah, right.
If there were any announcements, then it's just all gone now
out of the brain.
It's just all been adapted.
Oh, you've got one week, guys, left to get, isn't it about a
week to get to get the january patreon oh yes it's like
exactly a week you guys have yeah one more week so one more
yeah the checkies are very cute i don't know they're so cute
we might have we might know what they are and we know that
they're very cute and yeah you'll be very pleased yes yes
and speaking of the little uh the little uh just the heads
in the chat and stuff.
Our merch is almost done being produced.
Almost.
You know what we're waiting on right now you guys?
Just the heads.
Oh.
So soon, soon, soon, that's all going to get shipped away to
your home so you can rehome the precious little buggers and
give them a nice cozy place to live yeah okay oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah anything else i guess oh thank you guys something
you guys can look forward to on our our patreon if you do
join the fan club is a podcast we uh like not too long ago
finished recording our monthly podcast
and start thinking as well because after this first episode
we're gonna be collecting questions from club members or
like topics that you guys might want us to yapp about in our
podcast we're gonna be taking input from you guys so start
thinking about topics you'd like to hear us yapp about for
an
Well, thank you guys for joining us.
And I'm also very sorry to everybody who watched.
We apologize.
Next stream will be us apologizing.
If you have brainwrought complaints, please direct them to
densets.exeofficial.
Thank you so much.
Yeah.
We have an official website and we have a mailing address so
you guys can send us messages and gifts and stuff.
Yeah.
Today's stream, if you would like.
Please add Steiner for everything that you disliked about
today's stream and the Discord.
Only at Steiner.
Yeah, only at him.
Yeah.
You can do it individually.
Actually, nothing to do with the planning of today's stream.
That was all us.
But you know, it's still his fault.
He'll take the criticism and he'll screen it and tell us
none of it.
No!
Oh dear.
Alright guys, it's time for MV Peace Out.
MV Peace Out!
Thank you guys!
Bye
bye bye!