Hello everybody!
Hello, hello!
I mean, uh, wait.
I'm streaming now.
Whenever you're good.
You might be like, hey, isn't this a collab?
Where is the second person?
Um, she said...
She wanted to sleep or something.
Can I keep this as my profile picture?
Of course, Jack.
She's yapping right now.
Oh, okay.
She was like, give me 15 minutes or something.
And I was like, well, that's fine because I want to make my
character.
I want to make my character.
Matara was just you all along.
What do you mean by that?
What if...
I blocked Matara right now.
What if I blocked her right now?
Wouldn't that be so funny?
But it's been like, oh my gosh.
It's been like the longest time since Matara and I have
collabed.
I don't know.
Like, just getting us together is like, I don't know.
we're just we're just so busy but i'm glad that we could
play this together i think she tried it and it's my first
time playing hey hello minto and i boo's iq minto i may or
may not have received the minto cosplay in the mail today
you're about to be playing with blocks anyway what do you
mean by that We call in 10.
Okay.
Me too, it's my birthday today.
I'm going to get a happy birthday sneaking in before the
cola beepy.
Naxi!
Happy birthday!
Happy, happy birthday.
Baby Cori, thank you for the five, good third.
I think that roach on the stream before might have escaped
from the vacuum.
Ew.
It has been so long.
We got an entirely new name since Mataro was...
last year you're right you're right oh my gosh i can't wait
to okay let's make our character then because we're meeting
with matara in like 10 minutes so okay oh my gosh so how
many of you have tried this have you have you played this
i'll be honest i didn't hear of the game at all and then i
like looked it up and apparently it was supposed to come out
like a billion years ago day matara was talking about how
much of a cute you are too wait what do you mean that's a
shame what that i hate her or you're playing it right now is
it a lot of fun i was like if i really like it i might like
go for the the twin tails are so cute wait i could be twin
tail also maybe maybe we match um i was like if i like it so
much maybe i'll get like i liked the they had like an idol
outfit and i kind of wanted it it was like extra money oh
wait these are also twin tail wait oh oh oh oh b b mint of
atara's winter special yeah super chat to time out matara
con of independent uh all in favor of timing out matara con
of independent look how cute how many like uh am i even
gonna be able to see my avatar though this one's so cute
though I Ah Don't hold the drills
I think I'm Wait this kind of If it had a second one on the
side This one would be really good for me I like the twin
tails We'll go with the twin tails I And my axe Let's see
What is this?
Oh eyebrows Eyebrows You know I've always wished I were of a
round eyebrow girly, you know?
I don't mean to alarm you, but I heard they just added
dinosaurs to the game!
No way.
Whoa, look at the size of those.
Wait, can I make them like a snake?
Oh, dang it, never mind.
Oh, wait, you cannot link them.
Oh, my God.
It looks like...
wait it looks like it looks like the headband no it's kind
of awesome i don't think i i look like a grandma if i have
white eyebrows even though i actually have white eyebrows
but in the game it just kind of makes me look like a grandma
wait how do i become not red whoa oh my gosh i can become
the goat
what color am I not they're not they're like a dark blue
yeah like that large don't mean to alarm you but you're
about to add cockroaches to the game ew I want what's this
one called demonic feline reptile why did I say it like that
I don't I kind of like the goat.
Oh, I see why it's the goat because they're sideways.
We'll go with large and in charge.
Reptile.
Like a percent.
For some reason, I can't help but think a great collab idea
would be you, Matara...
Wait, Miu, Matara, Michi, and Miki playing Uno with
punishments.
No idea why, though.
Maybe.
Bye, Oseji!
birthday can I get a confirmation this is not a hot dog
moment not a hot dog moment I hope you're okay oh my gosh
it's so cute wait this this looks like almost like I had
like the maid had dress though doesn't it sorry my inner
demons oh I want to be Chuni oh my god this is Literally me!
Oh,
earrings and everything.
Wow.
I don't have earrings, though.
I'm scared.
Can I...
Oh, I'm pink.
Wait, what's red look like then?
Oh, this is my underwear.
Just kidding.
Oh, where's the option for none?
We'll do a sports bra.
What's a bando?
Vincent bando.
Wait, how do I become not red?
for real oh here we go oh okay okay i could be pink i could
be blue wait i don't want these glasses sorry i forgot to
take them off um howdy y'all how i kind of want that wait
hold on uh where was i oh yeah
a nice color.
I guess so.
It's pink.
There's a maid outfit?
There is.
Shut up.
Don't get me excited.
Is it under... Wait.
Is it under...
Oh?
My god.
One piece apron dress.
Call me what I am.
Wait, what is this sticking out underneath me?
Do I have pants on?
No, no, no.
Oh my god!
It's lit!
I don't need to buy anything!
I have one outfit for the rest of my afterlife!
Wait, can I make it?
Oh, this!
This!
I could just be naked?
Wait, why am I red?
There we go.
I don't need anything else.
Oh my god, I'm gonna show up and be like, I'm ready in my
uniform oh these are the locked ones wait is this oh no
curse breaker exclusive they had like a idle outfit maybe
it's under here whoa mark of the oh my god i get to have the
yeti arm why does she look so done with everything i don't
know wait oh wait wait wait uh edit edit edit Edit?
Okay, hold on.
I want to change my ears, can't I?
For some reason, my face just looks kind of grumpy.
My yowie hand.
Oh, here we go.
Nature.
Oh, what was I?
What was I?
Aged.
I was literally a grandma.
I was wisened.
Oh, oh.
Sunken cheeks.
makeup with the deep blush makeup with the highlights oh
this one's cute oh my god the winged eyes i'm kind of a fan
wait i'm a fan of this one this one's cute howdy oh makeup
large mouth tiny mouth what do you guys think do i have a
large mouth or do i have a Tiny mouth Matara's calling Oh
One sec One sec Let me finish my art Tiny mouth Okay Oh Here
we go Oh my god Imagine What if each outfit I just start
making my ears bigger And bigger Oh your ears Okay I'm not
an elf though Okay This one's maybe...
No!
Wait, I'm actually so cute!
I'm actually like so cute!
Oh!
Frost Warden, there was... Oh my gosh.
Oh, never mind.
Whoa!
Caps and everything.
I could wear a tree on my back.
I think I'm good.
Do they give any tactical advantage whatsoever?
Okay, and I think I'm good now.
Look at me!
Okay, let me...
Alright, I'm gonna call Matara now.
It got lost in the mix, but it's...
Coffee is birthday!
Oh my gosh, I'm so sorry!
I'm so sorry!
Coffee!
Happy birthday!
I'm so sorry!
Aw, Darko, you're so nice!
What the heck?
Oh, my shoes!
Can I change my shoes?
Oh, here we go.
And my socks.
I was already wearing the decorated thigh highs.
I didn't think I needed to change at all.
I was like, yeah, we're good.
Oh, my God.
I was just going to go out of my sandals.
Most self-aware, Minto, realizing she's cute after like five
years.
You're looking very blocky today.
I'll miss my birthday by a year.
Could I get a happy birthday from you even though I'm late?
How much is a year?
Like it's been one full year and it's your birthday again?
Aaron, happy birthday!
I wanna be in big old boots though.
I'm gonna make my ears bigger.
Wait, wrong place.
Bigger, bigger, bigger, bigger, bigger, bigger.
Yeah.
Okay.
Hair highlights.
You can do that.
No.
I don't think so.
Doesn't look like it.
There's a health bar setting.
You might want on.
What does that mean?
I'm wearing boots now.
Yeah, I want the boots.
Wait, scroll down?
Wait.
No.
There's just more hair.
Whoa, what's this one?
Oh, it's so cute.
Wait, oh shoot, I lost the twin tails.
Wait, oh my gosh, it took so long, Matara left the call.
Wait, hold on.
No, this is it.
You guys, there's no hair.
There's no hair to anything.
I'm getting one guide for real.
There's no way.
Matara gave up.
Anyway.
Okay.
I call.
I call Matara.
All right.
Goodbye, everybody.
I call her now.
I wonder if she'll pick up.
Oh.
Hello?
Oh, wait.
Oh, my God.
Mint?
Yeah.
For some reason, I was like, why am I here?
hearing a distant discord noise it was calling me from my
phone what wow that's weird yeah hi miss hi what's up how
are you i'm good how are you i'm good i was just thinking i
don't think you hate me what what do you mean by that i mean
i don't think you're like in love with me but like we've
been friends for like four years you've heard me crash out
crying about like two different you know you're still in my
life with a good sign oh no i think it's because i've thrive
off of your despair you suck it up you're like yeah yeah i'm
like oh my taro are you are you crying again the hag tears
oh yeah keeping me young can you can you call me yeah yeah
i'd love i'd love to be there for you and you're like i'm
like rubbing my hands together like yeah it's delicious
She's miserable.
Nothing brings me more joy.
You're actually like, my deepest, darkest enemy.
Oh, yeah.
That's what they say.
Who needs enemies, like, when you have friends?
Friends like me.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Give war a chance.
You still have not played that game.
No, not yet.
I know.
But, you will.
But, I will.
It's been so long since we've collabed.
I feel like you should introduce yourself again.
Just in case.
Okay, so this is my...
I recently redid my introduction because, you know, like,
it's been...
Yeah, so it's a new introduction.
Oh, my God!
Kon-kon, konnichiwa!
Matadez!
Oh, hi-yo!
I am with Taraka, Nelvin, independent, and so cute.
That's me!
Yeah!
I'm trying to go for a different demographic.
Oh, I could tell.
Do you think...
Do you think it's good?
Perfect.
All the momos are probably like, oh, that's our... Every day
we hear that same intro.
No, no, no.
It's...
Wait.
Hi, honey.
You can bug me anytime.
Matara Khan of Independent, double Ds, triple threat.
What threats are those?
Oh, fuck, I fucked it up.
Okay, maybe it's too long.
We're workshopping in real time.
You got this.
Listen, it's a moving.
It's like theater, you know?
Like things happen and you just got to go with it.
Yes and.
Yes.
Exactly.
Since you two, it's been a while, by the way.
Congrats on your band.
Thanks.
My band.
so I don't know have you talked about like the conception
like like the birthing the baby make when it was in the womb
I think so I think I talked about how like you and I were
delirious and doing it no having it just sweaty sensual I
wonder what that room smelled like now that I'm thinking
back on it awesome we were locked in for like ever we were
locked in the same hotel room both of us sweating and
delirious from covid like just what um what did you tell
them uh i think i think i can't i think it was like
basically like you know we were i was like lamenting to you
like i'm lonely my tarot and just like i was like sucks for
you too bad yeah pretty much we thrive off of each others
despair you know it's a mutual yeah but um just like uh i
was like i don't know what to do and then just being like oh
but what if i made my own group and then like how we went
how i would go how how i would be able to make that happen
happen yeah and you know that's exactly how oh no go ahead
yeah no that's exactly so um i think this is where like it
was kind of obviously it sucked that we got covet in japan
and we had to stay there extra but i think a good that came
from it from being very close friends and kind of being in
like this vulnerable state of delirium where all we had was
time yeah so we were kind of just you know that like part
where you're just talking about life and i think i probably
hate you with one of those are you happy are you really
happy what would make you happier like i i hate you with one
of those like and then i suddenly like sit down i lay down
on the couch and i'm like fold my i fold my hands together
i'm like well you know and you like pull out the notepad and
you're like okay yeah yeah yeah yeah i that's that's one of
those things that i feel when you know somebody very closely
and you're not afraid because sometimes when you're talking
to people that you don't know very close sometimes you're
like oh i would want this but you because we're so close
you're like i'm lonely i i would love to be part you're like
the happiest i was was being part of an ensemble like i love
that i i thrive off of you know my success is other people's
success i love like doing things together in and i was like
and i think i literally was like well why don't you do that.
I was like, but do it.
Do it.
Bozo.
It's stopping you.
Oh man.
Yeah.
Oh my gosh.
And so much has happened since then.
I don't know.
Do you want to, I want to hear your introductions.
I haven't heard your, all your introductions yet.
My introduction, like just how I, like I also changed my,
well, you know, I'm excited.
You have two now, no?
Two?
Or do you always have the same?
Do you always have like a solo one and a, okay.
Well, I guess, I don't know.
I don't know what to like I'm mint I'm the stinky mint I'm
the lead visual of my group I'm the I'm the nebulous soprano
I don't know I'm chief annoying in my group I'm in charge of
being annoying I think we all cover that I think we all sing
I think we all sing okay Victoria no um no I'll just say
mine I'll just be like um Okay.
Mint.
It's me.
Chits, the ghost made.
Wait, you can't just like ghost Gryllix.
That's not gonna work.
Gryllix is copyrighted, but you can't just like That's just
dubstep.
That's just dubstep.
Everybody has the same beat.
I recognized it was Skrillex though.
Is it?
Yeah.
I want to hear it for real.
I think I spat all over the place.
Hold on.
Also, for a second though, I think you unlocked a new
laughter.
You kind of went like, it was very cute.
Thanks.
Now I'm scared to listen back and hear what I sounded like.
The wisps.
No!
How can you say it so easily?
It's okay.
I say wait it best.
Wait it best.
And you say treadmill.
Treadmill.
Yeah.
Oh, wait.
I say a lot of things wrong.
Wait, treadmill is correct.
You say...
Maybe I say treadmill?
No, I say treadmill.
You do?
Wait.
Is it not called a treadmill?
No, I'm going to be used.
Also, I forgot.
So from now on, wisps, you're relegated to...
With, if I go with, that's you guys.
With, now you're spinning all over the place.
Okay, I'll say.
I want to hear your intro.
My intro is, my, my, my.
Hello, everybody.
That's it.
That's all I say.
I'm a phantom.
Hi.
Okay, I was like, where's the introduction?
Oh, sorry.
Let's be, let's be of densetsu.exe.
For those of my fans that maybe don't know about your idol
group, Do you guys have a color?
When are you guys going to perform?
What's your, if you can give us like a quick, like, what's
the happenings?
What's the happenings?
Well, we do have an original song out called Den Setsu MVPs
because I'm Mint and Victoria V and then Phoebe P. So, and
as for shows, you'll have to follow the find out.
Yeah, but from Minto with Love.
Oh, I do.
already sold out at least the the in-person ones right yeah
but there's a second show there's a second show and those
tickets are up tonight actually what time 6 p.m pst in an
hour and a half the tickets is that going to be on the
valentine's day no it'll be on the 13th oh wait that was
when the first show was yeah they were both on the 13th oh
okay miss performer i i'm well it wasn't but things happen
and we we adapt and we overcome overcome improvise yeah
survive yep that's cool i'm so excited is there anything
that you could like leak a little bit just make the withth
close their ears and just leak to us like anything happening
this year you do know they're called i boo's now right i
know but i'm gonna keep calling them with you okay that's
fine not every not everybody has accepted the name anyway so
it's whatever um it's It's fine.
I mean, our initial name, a lot of my mommos wanted to be
called mommorons.
Mommorons?
There's still a few people that are like, we mommorons, we
hold on.
We never forget.
I'm like, no, move on.
Please.
Forget it.
Move on.
You guys, it's been years.
Please, forget it and move on.
It was one time.
Okay, mommorons.
I might join your team.
Okay.
Like it was going to be Momo's, but like the bunch of them
was going to be the Morons.
And I'm like, no, we're keeping Momo.
Like we don't have to be like, you know, Momo dachi,
anything like that.
No, no, we're Momo's.
The Momo swarm, the Momo hive.
Mm-hmm.
What were we doing?
What can you spoil for us for this year?
I can't spoil anything.
My lips are sailed.
Oh, man.
You've changed.
What?
Faith has changed you.
Success has really changed.
you girl i'm kidding who who what i i don't even okay well i
don't know i feel like if i spoil something like there's
been so many things that were good to go and then worked out
yeah so i'm like i shouldn't say anything i'm gonna jinx it
all maybe could you could you give me like a very um like if
it's like kind of um not what is the fucking english word
for this sorry for my language um in your best case scenario
what would you like to do with the girls oh well you know
what i'm gonna say this because it's i mean it's like i
think this also pertains to you a little bit as well i'll
say it might look out for off kai that's all yep i agree i
agree look out for off kai
I'm excited.
I'm honestly, I'm so happy.
I was telling the MOMOs too that like something, there's a
lot of people that don't thrive in collective environments
because they're like, they get very competitive or they're
like, this person's doing better than me.
This person's this and this.
For me, if I'm having a bad week and I see my coworkers or
my peers being like, I have an amazing, um, like, oh wait,
we got a raid.
One second.
Let me finish my train of thought and then I'm going to
thank you guys.
One second.
Uh, and for me, it's like, if I'm in a big
song playing cool stuff it energizes me it like makes me
want to keep up in a positive way so i really do miss that
collective environment for that situation right what is it a
rising tide raises all ships all ships baby all right we got
okay so i don't want to like make you uncomfortable because
you're my girlfriend but my wife just raided me okay yeah
well i thought when was i your girlfriend.
I'm a stinky girlfriend.
You've never like, you know, it's just what it is.
It's just never progressed me off.
It doesn't have to be romantic.
You know, we're just girlfriend.
We're friends.
We're girls.
We're stinky.
We're girlfriends.
Lives, thank you so much for the day.
I love you so much, my angel.
I love you more, Limeu.
I love you more.
Okay.
That's not true.
You know how obsessive I can be with my friendships and like
how giving I can be and loving.
I love Limeu.
I love Lymu too.
I love Lymu.
You're bullshit.
I love her more.
Oh my god.
Lymu just came to my chat, said not to cause discourse, but
I love you, Minto.
She said, love you, Mata.
Have a great stream.
She didn't tell you to have a great stream, bitch.
She's wishing for my fifth.
She's praying for my downfall.
What do you mean?
I take my love back.
I, you know, she's also a fellow short woman, right?
Yes.
Very cute.
I love her.
You know what I love about Lyme?
She's never mean to me like you are.
Oh, that's just how I show my love.
That is true.
I'm just saying.
She does sometimes kill me in video games though and it's
always when I never expected because I trust her so
wholeheartedly that if like it's the two of us and like an
among us situation I never believe that she's the traitor.
If we did like one of those games where it's like if one of
you's the traitor I would never believe that she is and she
would be and she'd be like sorry Mata.
You also I feel like I know you don't like those types of
games and so I feel like you just blindly want to trust
everybody that is your friend anyway.
Yeah I gotta do.
but also limeu is an absolute gamer so she scares me if i'm
against limeu i think i just want to lie down on the ground
and give up this is why like having her in games i know that
if i get bullied i just like release my my pocket limes i'm
like limes go pocket lives like as a as like ferret forms
perfect pokemon i think so i think so all right cutie is
there anything else i wanted to catch up with you on and
because uh yeah i feel like a lot of my my audience knows
you i feel like some of your fans know me as well and if
they don't they're gonna oh i mean what did you make i do
want to have a i want to give a slight warning there's a
there's not a lot of jump scares in this game but there's a
few oh lately just a few Okay.
I know people are going to think I'm fake with my reactions.
I know, but I really do get scared easy.
Oh, oh, I know this.
I know this.
They might not know.
And I think, and maybe you can attest to this, I think some
people in real life also think that it's fake until they
meet me and they get, and they see me genuinely get scared.
They're like, oh, shit.
She's just like that.
She's a little moron.
I honestly can't feel how you would be faking it.
I'm not going to lie.
I'm just screaming I just feel like maybe because I've known
you for so long at this point I'm just like oh yeah that's
just that's the Tarah Conway yeah yeah some of my screams
lately have been I don't know it's been a long week oh my
god we played Mimesis or oh yeah I saw that holy shit sorry
for my language it was so scary and then I played Elden Ring
with Zen and I was getting like jump scared left right and
center because Elden Ring puts enemies like behind a crate
or behind a wall where you don't see them and then they show
up and backstab you.
Oh that's scary.
That's scary.
Yeah.
Especially for you know like I'm a little bit high
neuroticism just a little bit.
No.
That's why we get along.
These people with low neuroticism sometimes I'm like oh man
I gotta control my neuroticism.
My chat is being like headphone users beware you are you got
i saw you like retweeted something i didn't get to watch the
clip but of you and zen playing something yesterday like the
you want to open it oh god should i okay open the first one
first open the one that like oh there's more i retweeted two
of them i retweeted two of them open the one that's like
more bottom the one that i retweeted first okay i'm not
going to show you guys the screen you guys can go to
matara's twitter for that but i'll just play the
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wait, I'm going to start it over.
Sorry.
I'll be quiet.
Go back to my site for a little bit.
All right.
That's all you.
Yay.
Goodbye.
Insnared in a transport key.
Wait.
Ah!
Go back to my site for a little bit.
That was it.
Wait.
Oh, maybe I...
Wait, I think I did the wrong one.
Wait, hold on.
Hold on.
I'm listening.
Okay, hold on.
They're both very similar.
Okay.
Oh, that's a fucking bad.
Oh my god.
Okay, I'm doing the second one.
Jump scare me every time.
So it's just a little spoiler warning alert.
if we go spelunkin and things sneak up on us like turning
you down is there is there in-game audio or no do you know i
don't know uh i'm gonna stop sharing my game for a second to
join you oh yeah yeah let me do that too okay i'm gonna want
to create the world or do i want to create the world i think
i already made one so i could just uh i'll i'll jump in
yours yeah so then you're gonna give me a password and
please don't make it a mean one to stinky oh wait i forgot
what the password is oh shoot wait i think i have to make a
new world because i don't remember i don't remember okay
delete world okay all right new world so far i played a
little bit of this game um just a little bit uh-huh it's um
there's definitely a lot of similarities to minecraft
there's a lot of changes but it's still in early access
right so it hits the scratch for me or scratches the itch in
some places but not other places Although you, Miss
Decorating Queen, there's so much decoration, so much stuff
you can do.
I think you'd like it.
Okay.
I'm actually like super, you know, like I like the
decorating, but I like, I like exploration so much.
So it's like, if there's like a lot to do with that, I'm
always.
There's a lot of animals.
Animals?
Like a lot of animals.
Oh my God.
I think you can kill them all.
All right.
Let me, I'm getting into the world now.
I did.
not show you guys right now because i'm scared of the
password scared of you uh okay all right join via code all
right uh online direct connect through steam oh no oh oh
wait no i don't think so it's not a steam game yeah sorry i
for okay online play let me head out include password and
okay i don't i don't think i all right the password is i
think for the next 10 minutes we will be figuring out how to
join each other's world yes okay all right this is the
password and then this is the this is the code oh my god
it's ridiculous looking okay ridiculous it is look at it
okay so let me see what i think i have to not from my world
but from like the main menu world i think so oh wow that is
a ridiculous password okay i see it i thought server join
via code oh wow okay sure hope i don't accidentally put that
somewhere please don't oh yeah connecting to min fantomes
min tara yeah yeah where are you um it still hasn't prompted
me for the password it's loading i think okay okay wow it's
so cute really is i'll i'll let you oh yeah oh yeah i'm
punching things i haven't left the little main building
wherever i'm at okay after time and then i'm gonna share as
soon as i can are you in a seifuku yeah i'm cute i'm young
matara i'm cool young matara i like the glasses He also
looks so cute with your white hair.
It's usually that color.
Yeah.
No, it is.
It is.
Yeah.
I mean, like, it's usually like with the mints and
everything.
It's so cute.
Hold on.
Let me look at your butt.
Yeah.
Very nice.
Very cute.
And the little apron.
I know.
And just in uniform.
I'm like in regular outfit.
Why aren't you in uniform?
SpongeBob.
I will say, though, the only sad part is when you put on
armor, it hides everything.
so I haven't been wearing armor.
Oh, okay, I won't either then.
Yeah, I mean, we're not, you know, depends how crazy we get.
Dang, I'm weak.
So.
Yeah.
We can go outside.
I'll let you, I'll let you explore.
Oh, I'm exploring!
Wow!
Yeah, look at that.
Oh, berries.
So far, so far feels and looks just like Minecraft.
It really does, yeah.
Minecraft, Minecraft.
one thing though, very cool.
Okay, you know how in Minecraft you need a mod to collect
the tree, right?
A mod to collect the tree.
What do you mean?
Like, you need a mod for the whole tree to fall.
Look, look, look.
I hit the bottom of the tree.
Uh-huh.
Oh, I get what you mean.
It's a while.
Wait, there's like a big thing over here, Matara.
Yeah.
What's the big thing?
Look at that.
No.
Yeah, it's a village.
You want to go?
Yeah!
You want to go see what's up there?
Okay, let's go.
Oh, it's a village.
Oh, I think so.
I don't know.
I haven't seen this yet.
Okay.
Let's go.
Oh, there's stamina.
Oh, those are...
Wait, is there a carrot?
Oh, wait.
I don't think we can fight them.
I've never seen them before, but I don't think we should go.
Oh, I don't think we have.
Oh, God.
Okay.
They'll leave us alone, though, right?
Yeah.
And typically when I run away.
There's turkeys.
Wait.
Why are there bad guys in the daytime?
This is messed up.
Yeah, there are.
But when you go cave diving, there's less bad guys, which is
kind of nice.
What?
That's crazy.
Yeah.
I kind of like it.
Because I want to explore.
I don't want to fight bad guys.
I will protect you, my queen.
Wait, how'd you...
Wait, sorry, where?
How'd you make that?
Did you take damage?
Go into Tab.
Tab.
You've played a video game before, right?
No, never.
Oh, okay, I see it.
Yeah.
My first game ever, please be patient, everybody.
It's my first time.
Yeah.
This is actually my first day on Earth, actually.
I believe it.
Do you believe it?
What does it mean by any rubble?
What would be a rubble?
Okay.
A rubble.
Let me show you.
Come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come.
Come, come, come, come, come, come, come.
So this is like you'll see these little blocks here.
So this is like stone rubble.
Oh, okay.
And this is like, yeah.
So it's kind of like a random little block.
Look, look, look at the little mountain.
It's you.
Look, it looks like you.
Where?
You have the big teeth and everything.
Right there.
I don't have a big teeth.
Look, look, look, look.
You see?
Up there.
I see.
I see him.
I'm gonna go eat him.
I'm gonna eat him You can eat him.
You can catch him too eventually.
We can like have a little fun.
Oh shoot.
Oh girl!
You meant it.
What?
Oh my god.
Yeah, I tell you.
Who's gonna win?
Oh, never mind.
Oh my god.
Wait, he just dies there.
Oh.
What did you think was gonna happen?
I don't know.
Wait, I kind of want to kill the turkey.
There's deer and everything.
Yeah, the deer will run away though.
We gotta like... Oh, they're cute.
Oh dang, you're like going out.
Yeah, they're kind of harder to...
Kill him.
Oh, whoa, it's like Zelda.
Wait.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry.
This is awakening your fighting instincts.
You gotta eat food to regenerate your health and stuff.
Oh, that's the same.
It's like...
Wait, we're gonna kill the Skelly over here?
Oh, yeah.
I'll kill the Skelly and then I'll come kill the Skelly with
you.
Harvest the mature.
Okay, I'm gonna kill the Skelly.
One thing this game does so well is the Salis.
Like, when things die, they're like...
Ow!
I'm killing him.
Oh, I killed him.
I got his arm.
oh my god the way they just fall over is kind of sad though
oh no you did that no you did that right click the parody oh
okay oh yeah wow hit me hit me oh yeah hit me hit me oh how
could you do that ow ow ow ow stop you're hitting me stop
yeah i turned on pvp oh yeah well i'm eating some so funny
how's the sound everybody isn't it yeah um so one good thing
the enemies they'll spawn randomly but we don't have to like
really make a shelter for the night we should just because
you know but um i'm down to to make a little like small base
and and or run around until we find a nice place for a base
yeah let's let's run around i want to keep exploring some
and seeing some stuff let's just have knives do you want to
try on those goblins what if they have good stuff i mean
we're right next to spawn if we die yeah exactly that's my
girl oh yeah let's go let's do tons of blood loss yes i
wonder like i've never seen this little goblin camp i wonder
if they have good loot yeah i like the carrot it's kind of
fun oh oh shoot he throws oh wait oh oh yeah he I got him.
Ouch.
Oh my god.
This is one thing I love, like the way the character, like,
might have a little saliva coming from his mouth.
Oh god, I'm gonna die.
If you run away far from him, he, oh shit, I'm also.
I died.
Oh no!
It's okay, I'm coming back.
It's okay, I'm about to die.
Oh, I forgot to change it where you can't...
Oh, get him, get him.
I got him!
Where you don't lose your items.
That's okay though.
You lose some items.
I think if you have like too many items, you'll lose some.
Oh, I see it.
I did actually.
Okay, you're right.
Yay!
Yippee!
They'll be killing both.
Oh, my God.
Ah!
You bitch!
I can't wait to...
Oh, my God.
Wait, that's so evil.
I fucked up.
The music's kind of crazy in here.
Wait.
Oh, my God.
You don't?
Oh, no.
It's like, jump, jump.
Oh, wait.
I hear it now.
Oh, my God.
we can use their workbench let's go oh what's that oh is
that like a crafting table okay yeah yeah we can make one
ourselves too later but like it's fun to use theirs i'm
sitting we can steal their stuff you're stealing we can
steal all this stuff by the way like we now don't have to
make a workbench we just take theirs wait where's like their
stuff like i'm stealing it all here i'm like taking all
their stuff oh you're just like literally punching blah okay
yeah because then like we can
the music is so crazy oh my god the music is so cool oh nice
oh my god what happened to you i fell oh my god you know
those tracks did you also yeah help me out please i'm
digging my way up i'm digging my way up oh my god you scared
the hell out of me Oh, I'm sorry.
Which trap are you in?
Hold on.
I'm coming.
Are you in the same one?
Are you in this one?
Yeah.
Okay, I see you.
Is this the one you fell in?
No.
I'll throw you my pickaxe.
Oh.
And then I'll just make a new one.
Oh, wait.
I had a pickaxe.
Why am I seeing you, like, pick up with the block?
I was not...
Oh, well, I was, like, adding the blocks.
Are you here?
I'm coming up.
Wait.
Give me a second.
Guys, we're...
Hey, hey, stop it.
Stop it.
Stop.
I'm gonna kill you.
Oh!
I know, I almost fell.
I almost fell.
You almost fell again!
Wait, these are sneaky.
This is dirty.
I know.
They're devious.
Ah.
Look, look, look, look.
Do you see the biggies?
Biggies!
little blue guys food wait is there anything else in here
that's worth grabbing or i don't know i haven't been so i'm
just gonna like lose everything oh they have oh my god i
stepped into the fire i'm so silly there's a yeah i guess
there's nothing else oh my god did you fall in again wait
there's a under oh this is how you dug out no never mind
it's the trap but you that you I just minecraft my way up.
No.
Staircase time.
Wait.
Oh, fudge.
I'm gonna die.
Maybe, maybe.
Oh, cutting down trees.
Okay, I need some rubble.
Okay, girl.
What do you do?
I need to cook my meat.
You want a meat?
I got two.
Yeah.
I'll take a meat.
I can have one of my meat.
Oh, what are you making?
I'm making meat.
Oh, wow.
I'm gonna have some apple.
I have one of my meats.
Okay.
Oh.
so tasty it's my special momo meat oh it like didn't do
anything it heals you a tiny little bit that's the thing in
this game like stuff you need to make potions eventually i
think oh sorry it's okay this glove doesn't like heal you oh
okay okay interesting stuff heals you barely i've noticed
all right where to next princess um what was i gonna wait
this roof slogged i'm taking this i'm what there would it's
nice looking yeah oh yeah let's take all this stuff yeah
this too i'll take it beach log that's what it's called it's
called a beach log a beach log beach log b-e-e-c-h beach
that's you it's a beach log let's go to the beach beach
let's go get
falling into the hole that I dug myself and getting scared.
Wait, I want the bench.
It's so cute.
Okay, I took it.
Sometimes I've noticed when you, like, take stuff off, you
can't.
I've been taking the, I don't know how to say it correctly,
the braziers.
It's like fire.
It's like stone with fire inside it, braziers.
I don't know.
I got a boom powder.
What's that?
Oh, it blows things up.
Don't throw it at me!
Not me!
Not it!
How do I throw it?
Not it.
I don't know.
Oh, maybe you need to like evolve it into another like mega
boom powder.
What's in your mouth?
Uh, a leaf.
Ah, that's bad for you, you know?
What?
How is it bad for me?
Chewing tobacco is bad for you.
It's not chewing tobacco.
It's...
How do you know?
It's natural.
Chewing tobacco is natural.
I don't know how to tell you this.
Brazer.
What's a brazer?
Oh.
B-R-R-A-Z-I-E-R.
games there's like this fire thing that has it's like sorry
it's like made out of marble and it has fire inside it i
don't know what you're talking big you'll see them when we
see them i got some which way which way let's go this way i
see some yellow i want to go see what the yellow is i like
there's even birds and stuff there he is like think of all
the things you could kill let's kill the piggy so we can
have meat yeah let's kill the piggies they look small yeah
yeah yeah i got him you got him Kill the biggies.
Oh my god, we got short ribs.
Yeah.
Oh, I got raw pork.
Oh, is that a village over there?
It looks like it.
I actually haven't done a lot of the exploring myself yet,
so this is perfect.
Oh, there's a bear.
I think there's a bear.
Oh, bears are really tough.
Let's, um, okay.
We'll go to the village and ignore the bear.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Bears are really tough.
I'm going to kill more biggies.
More biggies.
All right, I'm stealing this person's cross.
Oops, one second.
Is anybody there?
Are they like, are there villagers and stuff yet?
I've got to be honest with you.
I haven't seen many people.
Oh.
I don't think this world is doing too hotly.
There's a map.
I don't want to look at the map.
I want to explore, guys.
Yeah, exactly.
Or, oh, my favorite is when I ask people, like, oh, can you
tell me about this?
Like, oh, you could look it up.
I'm like, no, no, no, no.
I'm asking you to look it up.
Yeah.
Oh, wait, this is a toilet.
Wait, there's a downstairs.
Did you see?
There's like a...
grilled fish there's like a hidden basement right here how
do we get down i found a hidden chest how do you get down
where hidden basement there i'm going in i'm going in you're
going in she's going in she's going in whoa whoa anything
good anything good i don't know it could be it could could
be huge this this um this candle yeah taking everything my
candle that's Hercules.
What is this song from Ren?
It's like, won't you light my candle?
I don't know it though.
I know it but I don't know how it goes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Another time, another place.
A word would only rhyme.
There'd be a wrong embrace.
He like, he sings like that.
Yeah, yeah, he like sings the way that you like how a song
sounds.
He does, he does.
We'll sing another song.
It'd be another one.
Like, you want to prove me?
Because she's like 20 years younger than him.
And he's also got the AIDS, so...
I thought she had the AIDS.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
She had the AIDS.
Maybe they all have the AIDS.
I don't know.
It's rent.
I think...
Yeah.
I think so.
Can you stop mooing, please?
Me?
That's not me.
Yeah.
Are you sure?
Who else could it be?
They're so cute.
It's not them.
It's definitely them.
Oh!
Oh my god.
Animal.
I'm... Are you a monster?
That's not very nice.
I already dug there.
There was a treasure chest.
Oh there was a treasure chest in the toilet.
I thought it was a toilet but I think it was like hiding a
treasure chest.
Oh.
I have some lettuce seed.
Oh there's a... Yeah we could plant it.
Look look look I want to go there.
There's like a structure.
Yeah I want to go there.
I think I see another village too.
Oh, look at the yaks.
Oh, and the little baby yaks are so cute.
You can kill the babies too.
Wait, this place looks crazy.
Wait, what's going on here?
There's like a statue and everything.
I'll say Robo.
Oh, you're killing them.
Oh, my God.
It's my special ability.
I have an essence of life.
I wonder what that is.
This is a brazier.
That's a brazier.
Oh.
This is a brazier.
I'm eating.
One second.
I'm just, I'm eating all that I got.
Yeah, yeah.
She's taking her time.
Oh, this just looks like a campfire to me.
But like, if you mine it, it's called a brazier.
And they're like really, really cool.
Because they're in like, wait, I'm mining it.
I'm putting it in our home.
Are you kidding me?
Do it.
Like, it looks so cool.
Whoa, this place is crazy.
Whoa.
there's like a big golem guy down here let's kill him okay
well how'd you do that special move oh after you attack
enough it charges up and you can press okay yeah yeah yeah
yeah there's a big guy down here i found an old map hello
what yeah look look look look look wait wait i have never
seen one of these i wonder if we actually can like oh my god
oh what if what if we find the the Wait, wait, that's
impossible.
Wait, how do I...
It says end to map.
How do you know?
How do you know it's impossible?
What if there's metal gear in this...
Stop making the lights go away.
It's dark.
I'm scared.
I want to look at you.
I want to look at your face.
What do I say here?
Do you think...
He seems polite.
Wait, is that a mimic?
Did that thing just move?
I think we got to get him.
Oh, that's a mimic.
Sorry, Mint.
Wait, what?
Wait.
There's like a chest that is just moving around.
Oh.
Wait, wait, where?
Where are you?
Oh, I was looting that chest.
I'm doing Elden Ring Strat.
So if he's targeting you, I'm attacking.
Yeah, he's aggroed on me.
He's aggroed on me.
Ouch.
One tap, one tap.
On me, on me.
On me.
One hit, one hit.
Oh, my God.
Armored down.
What is that?
That's his remains.
That's his inside.
Oh, my God.
We looted his body for the material.
diagonal so i could take his essence and some dirt you're
basically collecting his ectoplasms if you think about it i
am 100 wait what's his what's this then it won't let me pick
this up it's like a shard okay wait one second let me a
shard wait there's i have so much junk i know it's because
you'd be like killing everything yeah what were you saying
you're trying to get rid of or pick up there's like this
glowing green thing in the middle
um oh what the hell okay idiot have you tried turning it on
and off again no no what's the portal oh i don't know go in
okay so allegedly this game was made by somebody from the
quebec which you've been to uh-huh um and so that's why the
little people there they're called the quebec or the Quibik.
Quibik.
He can't kill them.
This is, like, the main quest area.
But look, look at him.
Oh, they're so cute.
I know.
There's a bunch of them.
They're so cute.
They wait at you.
Hello.
But they're called Quibik.
Quibik.
Like Quebec.
Oh, my God.
I'm not kidding.
This place is crazy.
Wait, so this is, like, a quest place?
This is, like, where it kind of gives you the main quest,
because it's still in early access, right?
Yeah, yeah.
By the way, I only know this because I played one time.
I played like, well I played two times, but like one time my
internet cut out, so.
Oh, okay.
Look at him.
He looks like you if you had one eye.
Why would you say that?
Because he's short and he's green.
And he...
Okay, what else?
He's short and he's green.
You're wearing glasses.
Look at your Fugi.
Yeah, but like that's...
So are you.
You're wearing glasses right now.
No.
Yeah.
He's looking at you.
I think he's in line.
with you i mean who wouldn't be whoa oh i have salt oh no oh
i see okay interesting whoa yeah you like can't pick up
anything here or kill anything here i tried oh okay you're
so cute the little guy i'm stealing this person's bed okay
i'm watching you do it i did it i'm watching you do it yeah
so we gotta talk to here you have unlocked the memories whoa
orb is blocked away so basically as you like go around you
like by touch by being around these people it like records a
memory so see they're called kwebeck if you now come to them
they're gonna have their name and they're called kwebeck
kwebeck wait like kwebeck oh there's like a little baby oh i
can't really can't get a baby it doesn't say kwebeck for me
yeah it does look look down it's gonna say like recorded did
you submit your memory to the altar um go back to the altar
and three memories.
Oh, reptile, reptile, reptile.
Wait, how do I record a memory?
You just have to like press and it's gonna be like record
one memory at the bottom of it.
Oh, I see.
Oh, okay, okay.
Click the button.
And then if you go around them, there's gonna be like,
Quebeck, bird.
Like I just collected a memory called Minow.
Wait, why aren't you called a Quebeck?
What the heck?
Because I am on the Tawa.
No, not you.
It didn't work.
Are you really?
Hmm.
Cause I'm, I'm getting the memories now from being around
them.
I thought I would say.
Oh my God.
Come here.
This bunny.
Where are you?
Right here.
I mean, I think it's a Jekyllope because it's got, where are
you?
Where are you?
Because it's got the horns.
I'm like, oh, I see you.
I see you.
Come here.
Oh, okay.
First of all, look, there's a frog.
There's a frog.
Look at his eyes.
Oh my God.
Oh, he's trying to eat me.
like he's from Bambi movie.
Oh my god, he does.
Wow.
Yeah, he's so cute.
But they're so cute and like expressive in this game.
Squirrel.
I knew you were squirrel.
Yeah.
It's okay.
The birds.
There's also a blue frog.
Blue frog.
Not to be confused with green frog.
No.
Two different frogs.
Yeah, 100%.
All right, so you're just recording things.
I'm just going around them and it's like giving me a oh mint
come here what are you okay this is you what do you mean no
it's not I know what that is I know what you were standing
next to no this looks eerily familiar it's like it really
does all alone you abandoned him it looks like he's like
rotting yeah used to be yellow and now he's like kind of
brown he used to be yellow and and plump and like pleasantly
plump yeah erotically chubby and now he's skinny he's being
underfed he doesn't have the love of his oshi no oh my god
is the music dramatic for you right now it's so dramatic
it's so dramatic oh wait it says i can't oh you can't you
really can't pick up things okay i can be your
I think you're too old for him you shouldn't you shouldn't
be friends with a little guy like dad no I shouldn't I
shouldn't everything's in whip everything's a work in
progress yeah I know oh wow you can climb that's crazy yeah
actually oh yeah yeah when you get up it like yeah I really
like that yeah nice listen I'm old was there's anything here
look this looks like a tree house Oh my god, there's more of
them.
They look so sad, man.
Where are they?
They look so sad.
We should call them Minto dachies.
Minto dachies.
Oh, I got a minnow.
Wait, how...
A minnow.
Oh, critters.
Are you ready to get out of here?
Yeah, I'm ready to get out.
We basically did like the thing we got to do because it's
still in PA, and then we got to get out and explore.
Look, it's Red Frog.
Red Frog.
So if you, like, look at something, if you...
like look at it then you get to record it is that basically
what it is and then i don't know where like the memory is if
they go to satan or something you know yeah like who's who's
taking me who's recording why does professor oak need to
have the data of every single pokemon you know i you know
that's a good that's a great question wait there's something
over here too like another room oh it's just wilderness i
think wait yeah i don't think it goes anywhere No, I fell
off here earlier, man.
And then it just respawns you back at the start.
Not at the start.
It responds you back at the portal.
I would.
Yeah, fall down.
Okay.
It responds you back at the portal.
Oh, I'll do it.
I'll do it for you.
No, I'm gone.
I'm gone.
Oh, I'm here.
I'm behind you.
Oh, nothing personal.
It looks just enough like Roblox that it's kind of like.
Right.
I've never played Roblox.
but I like it's got enough of similar wait wait there's
stairs here wait what is this oh oh no I think it's goodbye
goodbye goodbye all right let's go back yoink yoink wait oh
oh okay there we go yep right I know you said not to take
the chandeliers but fuck you you're not my real man what the
hell didn't follow what to do i'm just trying to see oh yeah
yeah yeah you don't need to see i'm right here wait you're
gonna guide me through the darkness turn left go right
scream loud this place is cool oh it's starting to get dark
out you want to put a little temporary thingy while we
explore or do you want to keep running keep running wait
there's more i see some glowing stuff in here i'm coming i'm
following you yeah Oh, it's the sky.
And that glow?
I saw the sky.
Hell.
You wish.
The fires.
There's a spider.
Oh, also, also, you see these trees?
Oh!
Oh, yeah, yeah, we gotta kill him.
Oh, shoot.
I think I'm poisoned.
What's the green thing?
It's a point.
Oh, we gotta pick it up.
This is like a upgrade material.
You got it?
I'm gonna get rid of something in my inventory.
You got it, right?
Oh, you got it?
Look, look, look, look.
see this tree because it's sideways he grows mushrooms just
like in the real world you have any food oh actually i'm
gonna try this oh sorry my bad no no no here here you can
eat my fish oh okay cool oh i have a oh that's stamina
nevermind oh thank you i gotta get rid of enjoy it's gonna
be spooky nighttime yeah i'm about to die no you'll be you
got this i have more food if you need oh there's a bear the
bear is really tough let's run the other way okay I'm still
dying.
She says running.
Wait, there's a glowing something over there.
Oh, yeah.
What is that?
Oh, it's a skelly.
He's got a door.
Let's kill him.
Kill the skelly.
Look at the moon.
I know.
Why is it so...
Oh, my God.
Why is everything so powerful all of a sudden?
They're all like shooting spells and stuff.
No, that was the memory.
That was like the memory recording.
You can sleep.
Baa.
Oh, I see it.
Okay.
I'm going to eat more of these.
I'm going to eat my berries.
Wait, how do you make like a...
Hold on.
I can figure it out.
A campfire.
Oh, I can craft it.
Okay, cool.
Yeah.
I'm doing it.
I'm crafting.
She's doing it.
She's crafting.
Oh, my God.
I'm freaking crafting.
Yeah, we're going to need the little life essences later for
crafting a bunch of stuff.
Oh, yeah.
there is so many different animals for us to tame or kill i
know very exciting
and i love how you can like put more than one food into the
thing yeah it's so handy i really like that oh there's a oh
it's nighttime hold on i'm putting it in your in your
campfire oh wow you got a whole you got a whole lot of stuff
oh you could deal some of my food i got i got a lot of food
yeah i'll be cooking should be cooking i'll be cooking i had
more i had ribs no did i already cook my ribs i think i may
have cooked my ribs i think you did i think i saw carrot oh
you can even roast your veggies you can wait that's awesome
oh my god delicious
hags discover video games here i'll keep the fire up just so
we can have a little something
pig does it last i mean while you have the fire oh my god
he's so small little bunny is that a bunny what are you baby
pig let me see your face oh no that's a hog what are you oh
that's a sheep and that's a squirrel animals oh i've
discovered mouse oh my god it really does feel like it's my
first day on earth i'm like right i'm like discover mouse
discover minnow yeah What's this one?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, I got some raw meat, baby.
Raw meat to cook.
Yeah, so you could just use any sort of like fire to light
the campfire.
Wood stick and charcoal.
Oh, oh, I left my charcoal then.
Oh, okay.
Oh, I do have stick though.
Yeah.
I'm doing it.
I'm cooking.
You're cleaning.
I definitely want to make a base like this.
too because it's it's um there's a bunch of stuff to like
upgrade and a bunch of stuff to see i'm not quite sure how i
feel about like the cave system yet i i don't love it but i
don't hate it okay well wait i forgot we didn't even need
look oh this is why i took the brazier oh my oh whoops i
turned it off wait how do you use it on you just put it like
in our house for lights look how pretty that is oh i thought
you meant like for cooking i mean like you know right now
instead hold on i have a torch i'm ready to go and i'm ready
to search oh man i don't have tree sap hold on what does
that mean i'm coming i'm coming but you need tree sap to
make a torch oh okay i see i think i stole it so we got a
workbench i stole it right now i'm like rather than like
learning the inner workings i just kind of want to explore
and see all that we can see you know yeah i'm down yeah let
me let me put this back in my inventory see skelly he has an
extra sap or no on your Um, no, I have no shot.
You have one forge because you got four when you crafted.
You got a sack of four.
I didn't, I didn't craft it.
I stole it.
Four.
Uh, you're not a whore.
Sorry.
Um, I'm just, I was collabing with Z.
I was collabing with Zed yesterday.
So, like, you know, I call her that sometimes.
We steal it from him.
Steal it from him.
No, I don't think he drops a torch.
Wait, can I put it in my second hand?
Yeah, you can.
There we go.
If you press G, mm-hmm.
Hold on.
All right.
Let me get a stab.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I see a bunch of blue light.
Oh, wait.
I have a bunch of candles.
Wait, is that a bear?
Oh, that's a moss horn.
Oh, you have a bunch of candles.
What?
Wait, I wonder if I can carry the...
Oh, it's these guys.
Oh, they scared me.
I have a big chandelier.
You ain't killing me.
You think the power of Christ supports you.
Oh.
Ooh, you want to go.
Ooh, wait, hold on.
I want to see what this blue light is over here.
here for yeah me too i'm coming yeah run toward the blue
light i'm just like a moth to a flame yeah you are a moth to
a blue light yeah it's the best part always like before you
know how to get oh yeah we can double kill him oh there's
two of them there's two of them yeah oh they're both aggroed
on me what the hell why does it everything think i smell
good oh oops where am i oh i'm back at home oh shoot you
kept some of your items i'm gonna run actually i could die
Oh, wait.
They're both dead.
What the hell?
Hold on.
I'm coming back.
Do you see me on the map?
Um.
Uh, spawn.
Can you see me on the map?
I'm going to cook the meat that they drop for you.
I don't... Oh, I do see you.
Okay, wait.
Can I... Oh, I can place a marker.
Oh, that's kind of handy.
Can you teleport to me?
Can you?
I don't know.
It doesn't look like I can.
Um, where's my marker?
Oh, here.
Wait.
Death, death, uh, marker?
No, spawn.
I'm just gonna go this way.
Oh, mint, she died as she has lived.
I died.
They aggro on me for some reason.
It's because you're stinky.
No, it's because I smell so good, and they're like, ooh, I
want to eat some of that.
I want to eat some of that, little mint.
I think I see that.
Uh, am I going the right way?
Do you want me to come run to you and find you?
No, I see.
I see the blue light, so I think I'm close.
And I see maybe you.
If you open M?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, you're close to me.
Yeah, I'm right here.
We honestly haven't gotten that far at all.
No.
No, we honestly haven't.
All right, let's go.
Let's go.
We kind of rolled around.
Is that the blue light?
Oh, yeah.
What is that?
What is it?
Blue.
blue seedling oh mine it mine it mine it oh yeah oh oh give
me the shards so we don't have to like so we can one stack
them because we both have no space in inventory i have a
sapphire as well i don't know oh i'm wait is there anything
else in here what is this oh it's chalk Oh, Chara, look.
Big building.
I'm looking.
You want to go?
Yeah.
I'm coming.
Let's go.
I'm fine.
Flesh wound.
I'm good.
Let's go.
Oh, yeah.
With all the lights.
Wow.
Let's go.
Look at that.
I see it.
It's...
Oh, what is it?
It's a little spider.
Oh, it's a little lava.
It's a flower.
Yeah, that looks like a, like a demon momo.
Like a little momo.
Yeah.
All momos are demon momos.
Evil momo.
What about the whiff?
Whiff.
What about them?
Yeah, are they not demon whiff?
No.
They're just, they're just little guys.
We're in the fens.
Ooh, uh, I like a fens.
I lost, I don't know where we are actually.
Oh.
they are they're there it's the lights are there the light
the promise of safety it's here too oh it's a big tree house
man whoa oh snake don't kill him i mean you want to eat him
or what maybe it's better to capture him as a pet oh it's
green in here look at this block it's like a light yeah
that's cool wow i want to like skin this place for our own
stuff i know wait we our home man look look look this is so
cool oh wait sit together oh my god look how cute we are oh
wait hold on let me like look at you wait why am i not
looking at you i just i'm sorry i don't want to look at you
that's fine i get it i don't want to look at you let's go
find a bed and steal this place oh it's raining yeah sorry
it's our home now oh i'm guessing like mpcs don't exist here
That's one thing I noticed.
I haven't seen like any humanoid and I almost said MVPs.
MVCs.
Yeah.
Besides the the the queeps.
Yeah, but they weren't even talking really.
And they were only in that one little place.
The queemings.
This is awesome.
This is so cool.
Like there's little boats and everything.
Those things, by the way, they're like labs.
We can rob them.
We can steal them.
We can steal it.
Wait, this is so cool.
Oh, there's a pool.
There's a pool?
Where?
Upstairs.
On the roof?
So we can, like, watch over our kingdom?
Where are you?
Oh, I see you.
Yeah, there's stairs over here.
Look above you.
Oh, hello.
Where's the pool?
Oh, down here?
Over here?
Wait, where'd it go?
Oh, over here?
It's a small little pool.
it's more like a bath oh my god it's a little sauna yeah
like oh my god we get to like overlook everything wow i know
talk about luxury i know this might be the greatest find
ever oh yep yep and no enemies too have you noticed that
yeah i do wonder oh wait i i took something and it called it
a quebec quebec lantern so that's Probably what the lanterns
are called then.
Quebeck lanterns?
So they're...
This is like a Quebeck place.
Interesting.
Quebeck.
Wait.
Any beds?
You got any beds around here?
Hey, guys.
You are...
Oh, oh, Min, there's something crawling.
What is that?
Where?
Void crawler.
Right here.
He's like trying to crawl in my skin.
These wounds, they will not heal.
I see a frog.
He's over here.
I wish it was really...
Oh, I see it.
I see you.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Come, come.
on like where i am he's like looking up at me he's so cookie
looking you see him no with his teeth no i don't see him
okay come come to where i am i'm like i i won't i won't push
you
i can't believe you believe me when i said i won't push you
i'm gonna kill him i'm gonna kill him Oh, I killed him.
I got something for it.
What'd you get?
Essence of the void.
Yeah, I don't know what those are used for yet.
We'll find out.
He was scared shaking in his booties, you guys.
Yeah, he was.
All right, let me take a look at M.
We're next to these two.
Oh, if you look down where we haven't been, there's like a
big...
Oh, there's another forgotten temple gateway.
Do you see it?
No, I don't know where you are.
Okay.
Oh, I see you now.
Open M.
I see you.
Okay, now look south from us.
There's like a big fortress looking thing south from us.
You see it?
Oh, I see the tippy tip top of it.
And then on the left, like on your map, and then on the
left, there's like a forgotten temple gateway.
Ooh.
See it?
I'm not looking at the map.
I'm just going to explore.
Oh, oh, I was going to say, let's go towards them.
Yeah, we can.
Because there's a really cool looking thing.
Hold on.
Is there anything else up in this whole?
No, I guess this is it.
Wait.
Wait, is this inside the tree?
There's mushrooms growing inside the tree.
This place is so cool though.
I know.
Oh, they're not really inside.
All right.
Wait.
Oh, there's creatures in here.
Oh my God.
Where?
At the very top.
I want to see them.
Oh my God, I want to see the quibs.
And you better get over here.
You better, oh, they have tree sap and everything.
Okay, hold on.
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming, oh, wait, wait, wait,
wait.
Yeah, you better hurry.
I'm going to kill them all.
I defrenched them.
No, don't kill them.
Don't kill them, please, until I see them.
I'm literally, I'm literally killing them.
Please don't kill them.
Wait, where are you?
Where are you?
You're up top, where?
Where up top are you?
Mind, Mind, where are you?
Are you at the top, top, top, top, top, top, top, top?
You went up from the stairs?
Yeah.
Okay, I'm coming.
what you could trade with them yeah well you can buy yum
they have like a whole little thing up here i stole one of
their beds as i made it mine yeah yeah and i stole their
goods yeah fuck you it's my bed now oh sorry for my language
but it's my bed now bitch you always apologize but you never
i know i stayed and then i apologize yeah don't say sorry
just don't do it's like hard not to do like minecraft like
you know like controls with this game yeah that's my biggest
thing is i'm like wanting to be like oh yeah like i know how
to open my inventory in minecraft and i'm like oh shoot it
doesn't work how do you open isn't it also tab on minecraft
no it's like e and so my finger just instinctually like you
know i'm just like oh yeah oh yeah oh no oh that doesn't
yeah yeah i suck so already though the exploration in this
game i'm loving it a little bit more oh i mean there's a
blue and a green sign from here come here come here where i
am wait hold on i'm just looks so cool i really hope they
add like a proper adventure mode because if they do like
come where i am and there's like where you're looking
there's like a big castle right uh-huh and then where i'm
looking there's more oh this is awesome there's like such
big cool structures to find which is like something that i'm
like super into like look in front over there where where
i'm staring at there's like a big blue thing and a big green
thing don't push me yeah oh i see it i see it and then look
to the like behind you where you were before like there's
also that big castle yeah that's what i was looking at
before oh my god where do you want to go i kind of want to
go to the right castle the castle the one i'm looking
Because it's next to like a temple gateway thingy.
Wait, how do we get down?
Oh, shoot.
Oh, we can jump in the water.
I lived.
If there's water.
Okay, Geronimo.
Oh, that's not water.
I landed like one drop outside the water.
Okay, I'm coming back at you.
I'm coming back.
Oh, it shows you where your ghost is.
Yeah.
Wait, did you spawn a...
Did you respawn a spawn?
Yeah, I think if I...
put my bed i'd respawn on my bed yeah wait how do like how
do i throw things like to the wild can you wait for me i'm
coming back give me a second okay i guess it's just like
that but like i'm so used to being able to like press a
button and like throw it you know what they say all right
i'll wait by your stuff okay if i die i left i'm i did a bed
up here so if i die yeah took a bed took a bed like take one
of their beds let's do that together let's like oh mint what
the fuck i don't know if that works you have to stop chewing
tobacco mint wait where's my stuff okay um look at your map
there's gonna be a ghost we both have to run back to pretty
much the same spot you are so funny oh no this is the water
girl can you actually fall in the water oh you I realized it
wasn't water.
I can't believe it's not water.
I can't believe it's butter, but not water.
Wait, I think I just grabbed your stuff.
Uh-oh, wait.
Mint.
It's fine.
That's what I like.
You kind of keep all the stuff on your toolbar and you lose
just like half of your stuff, which I like.
It's not as punishing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, I have to ask.
The width.
Are they very demanding when you're in a collab?
Because sometimes we'll have some mommos being like, oh she
hasn't read chat but luckily all the other memos are like
buddy she's reading mint's chat okay she's focusing on her
collab partner but we'll have like you know sometimes and i
feel bad because i'm like no baby i love to chat but i'm
fucking chatting with mint oh you know oh are you guys
lonely are you lonely oh people say i saw mint can't read
it's true i feel like they're pretty my momos are two most
of the time is just sometimes and of course probably only
one person writes it but you know like it's the one i end up
reading i know yeah and it's so frustrating it's just like i
didn't mean to but like this is how my eyes like just saw it
first i'm sorry exactly yeah also i apologize i am swearing
a little bit more than usual today are you crazy like yeah
what's happening i don't know i i think it's just because
i've had a i don't know where my stuff is oh i may have
picked up some of your stuff just pick up whatever this is
and then oh this might be my stuff here oh i think i didn't
think it was i picked up some i i accidentally picked up
some of it i'm sorry no that was your stuff oh okay wait
this is the explosion powder i want that yeah okay yeah it's
fine okay i have the bazaar that's the most important thing
to me yeah i think it kept it for you okay let's go to the
let's go let's go yeah this way this way yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah Was that a turkey?
What the hell?
Oh, they're turkey.
Holy cow.
That was close.
I know.
Oh, sorry.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
No.
Hey, you're so cute.
He's so cute.
Oh, my God.
He just cried in anguish.
Cruelty.
What is, have you seen Epic?
The music?
Oh, I know of it, but I've not seen it, though.
You should watch it.
Are you kidding me?
Why?
It's just got stuff you like.
People sing.
There's gods.
There's, like, romance.
There's, like, hot women.
I love that.
Youth looks just yummy.
That's your thing, yeah.
That's your thing.
Okay, okay, Miss Olda.
Oh, men.
Look.
Don't.
You should go there.
After you, after you, after you.
Wait, how do you like crouch in this game?
Wait.
Is there a way to crouch?
Oh, look behind you.
Oh.
Oh, wait.
Uh.
Oh, what was behind me?
If you come up behind me.
Oh, what was the heck was that?
The loveliest.
I broke the tree.
Rest in peace to a lovely woman.
what is this i'm gonna get close to it how you let me know
oh there's iron i'm gonna mine that that's kind of rare is
it really yeah i found a lot of copper but iron was a little
bit harder to find and we're gonna it's not super rare but
we need a lot of it to like shift advance oh no shift is run
oh i think i rebound some stuff actually um sure go ahead
i'll mine this iron while you yeah controls oh i think i
know wait
i did it to exactly how i crouch yeah exactly how it is when
i am in minecraft which i use minecraft don't judge me you
guys i never not judge you i like never stop judging you so
i'm always ready to judge you always yeah i want to see what
this thing is but i would need your help probably killing it
Okay.
Hold on.
This cave has iron.
Okay.
I'm sorry, Mike.
Okay, I'll just, I'll mine down to you.
Just, just go down the hole that I did.
You'll be safe.
Yeah, but we need a way back up.
We can just mine up.
How do you not play Minecraft?
You just mine your way up.
I'm making a ladder so that we can, there we go.
Oh, ladders were kind of weird.
That's one of my big complaints.
What I love about Minecraft is the water bucket and the rope
here.
It doesn't look that way.
No, I'm hoping they add it on and change things up a little
because...
Well, it's not supposed to be...
Is this iron?
It's not supposed to be Minecraft.
Oh, you missed some!
You missed some!
Oh, get it?
Oh, my God.
I, like, in my game previously, I had such a hard time
finding iron, and here there's just iron everywhere.
Everywhere.
Matara's blind, everybody.
There is a water bucket.
Apparently.
I have glasses.
No!
What?
Wait, can I send you a photo?
Wait, you have like actual glasses?
Actual, okay, can I complain for three seconds?
It's gonna be longer than three seconds.
I bought Versace glasses, okay?
Who?
And Versace, you know?
Versace.
And, um, it was, you know, it was kind of like a nice
expensive pair.
They were all special, but they were still expensive.
They didn't even come with a little rag to like wipe the
glasses from like my earrings.
Really?
Yeah.
Can you believe that?
Okay, so first of all, Bad service.
This is what I look like.
And this is what I look like.
I'll send you another one.
Hold on.
A little nerd.
You look like a little nerd.
Sorry I'm laughing so hard.
What the hell?
You look like a little nerd.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
Let me send you a real one.
I sent you a real one.
What are you talking about?
That is you.
At least in like...
Oh man, I should have taken a better picture.
I actually look like such a nerd in these shut up.
I know I know that you do Ouch, oh my god a rat That that's
me you can't say that No, I'm talking about I'm getting
killed.
That's just what I look like you can't say that man.
What the fun No, I can't Yeah, you can't just say oh my god
a rat That's so rude look kind of big we have to remember
that like wait they're cute you look so cute i can't wait to
show you i can't believe you called me a rat what did i do
it was just like a natural reaction i'm sorry where how far
are you down okay wait let me let me go back to you because
i'm gonna get lost yeah you are yeah i'm picking up like oh
what the hell is this oh what the heck is this is that a oh
it's Oh, it looks diseased.
Oh, why is he attacking me?
Oh, sorry.
Oh, you just hit me for a while.
I know I did.
My audience is saying you need to bully me more.
They like when I'm getting bullied.
Yeah, because it puts you in your place.
It does.
Wait, what's this?
I've said it before, but like, it's always, when you play
with people that you don't really know, or like, if I meet
friends for the first time, I'm not going to bully them
because it's rude.
But when it's my pals, oh, you best leave.
We know we can dish it and take it.
I can't take it, actually.
I'm sensitive.
I'm not.
Actually, I think this is also another reason why, like,
because we're close friends, sometimes, like, it's been a
bit if, like, sometimes I remember in Japan, we're like, you
tease me or I tease you and the other would be like, okay.
Not today.
I'm actually really sensitive today.
Wait, is it gone?
I think also it takes.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
She'll never forgive me.
I'm just, I'm ready to go.
You know what?
It's fine.
Yeah, anyway.
Orc invasion.
I know.
Is that that guy?
He kind of looks like a frog.
No, I definitely think he's an orc.
Oh, there's a fishy.
Look how goofy.
Look how nasty this fish looks though.
Kill it.
Wait, can we just grab it like that or do we have to fight
it?
Oh my god, it's a little piranha.
Oh, he's gonna eat you.
I'm gonna eat him.
I'm the apex predator.
Wait, where'd that thing go?
Where'd he go?
It was huge.
Look, there's so huge.
Look at them.
The little goblins.
Oh my god, they're really small.
Goblin scrapper.
He's got his teeth.
Wait, they look so nerdy.
Oh, they do.
They hit hard.
They do.
Is it that way?
And they make little noises.
Is it this guy?
Look, he's like a Merlot.
I'm telling you, it's this guy.
Ah!
He hit hard.
It's this guy, right?
What?
You were looking at?
No, no, no.
Mine looked like a...
Can you help me kill him?
Yeah.
oh shoot okay nice wait i think i see it okay i'm following
i'm following i think i see it i'm following quietly so they
don't hear us is this it are you it no wait it's like a yak
yeah no it wasn't oh it is this guy it was him wait i have a
serious nasty face He looks like a disease.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
Oh, wait.
Sorry.
He rushed at me, but I don't think he did.
I don't think he did.
I promise you he did.
He rushed at me.
Anyway, what were you saying?
I promise you.
I have a serious animal question.
Did you know that ardvarks were real?
Yes.
Fuck.
He didn't know that.
I went somewhere with Junie, and she was like, oh, it's an
ardvark.
And I thought she was, like, making words up.
I was like, like, I thought I had.
had a seizure I was like what what you know I thought it was
fake like the jack-o-lope I didn't know it's real I didn't
know it looked it just looks like an app eater no it doesn't
yeah it does I mean maybe a little but oh I made oh one
small jump for mint kind wait do you remember where that
castle is yeah uh so if you click m and then you open your
no no i'm going off of my intuition
stop stop backseating me oh my god my intuition you sound
just like my chat this looks like a door open it break it
it's not never mind i lied it did though it did right it
actually like really does yeah it looks like a structure
like an abandoned structure hold on i'm gonna look up here
see if i can see it oh wait i'm going the wrong way uh mint
i have bad news my sense of direction i was leading as the
wrong way no my intuition was wrong where are we going where
are you where are you i'm behind you i'm i'm here oh oh the
fall damage is not so bad i'm right behind you
there's your favorite idol she's right here i i need to also
talk to you because I'm going to be going to Japan with my
parents.
Yeah.
I'm going to be taking them.
Remember you tell me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you're going to be there at the same time, cool.
Yeah.
I love that because I would, I'm for sure taking them to a
maid cafe first of all.
But second of all, they're going to be down for any
experience.
They're very much like we want to, you know, embrace the
culture.
Oh.
But if you are there, I'd love for you to take us to like a
little show, like a little idol show.
okay i could totally do that but i don't think i could do
that without you because you have to like book the tickets
and you need like a phone number and in japan like i could
probably ask one of my ex like managers because there's a
lot of the really good no no i got you i got you yeah let's
go kill a golem i think this is gonna be another golem yeah
let's go kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill
kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill Ouch, oh,
ouch, kill.
Oh.
Yeah, sorry.
Oh, I got sucked into the teleport!
Oh, shoot.
Oh, my God.
Wait.
I wanted to put that.
No.
Wait.
I got this.
You don't got DC?
I show you what I got.
This is, like, I swear, I'm showing you that I got, like,
it, like, actually errored me.
Whoa, wait, hold on.
Also, yes, my PC is named after my first corporal character.
Because I got my PC when I'm...
Oh, no!
And I was so scared, like...
I'll just jump back in.
I think so.
Yeah, I think so.
I don't know why it, like, crashed me.
But yeah, I sent you what it looks like.
Yeah, yeah, I see it.
But yeah, I think it would be so fun if, um, if, uh, I just
want them to experience it.
And they told me that they're, you know, they're down for
the adventure.
They want to try the fun stuff.
Okay.
I'll, I will take you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
They might only come for, like, an hour of the show and then
leave, which is, you know, fine.
no that's yeah i'm not expecting much more even that is what
i'm soloing him i'm soloing him oh good luck are you uh do
you have any plans for japan at the moment or not really um
just a little bit but uh it's it's more free than not so oh
oh oh oh i'm okay you can change your pc name to anything so
i could be like mint stinky you could do that you could do
that oh you're back oh i can do that i'm back where'd he go
oh there he is he's like trapped i'm here yeah it was a
weird bug that i got um it literally was like i can read
some of the error log to people an index was out of range
must be non-negative and less than size of the collection
parameter index a critical error has occurred you should you
should report it to the devs oh it's too late oh i'm just
Sorry.
They gotta pay me to find their bugs.
You think I do this shit for free?
Oh, I do.
Silver ore.
Ooh, I have some already.
I can take it.
Okay, yeah, you take it.
Oh, you were fast.
Wow, okay, greedy.
That's me, Matara, greedy con.
Is this, does this go somewhere now, like new or?
I wonder.
I don't know.
Let's go, let's go, let's find out.
I don't think so.
I think we can record first village, right?
Yeah, I think we can record more memories of.
Right.
I don't know what this dot, what does a recording mean?
Oh, they're saying there's a bug in the bottom left.
Screw you guys.
Uh, ooh, uh, ooh.
Oh.
I record 30, not to, like, have a competition, but I just
record a 30 memory.
If you, oh, you get more stuff.
Like, if, like, when you unlock.
at the bottom it shows like you'll get like decorative
chests and stuff oh maximum teleporters oh okay the other
ones are whip though they're all whip wait how do oh you
you're right work in progress weep weep weep weep weep but
I've only wait what's the reptile oh that was a fenn stalker
yeah he's a reptile yeah he's a reptile you like a reptile
yeah oh my god look at the animals they're so cute i don't
wait actually they're so cute what's abyssal i want to find
those abyssal wait where where where is that the top oh yeah
let's go find some more matara let's go yeah yeah yeah yeah
let's go let's go let's go let's go let's go let's go let's
go let's go i need to cook my meat i got a lot a raw meat we
can cook we can cook our meat in the in the cave yeah what
this is wait i thought we were going to the big castle first
not here yeah we uh we'll move from it sorry this was like i
forgot oh they're right next to each other oh okay we should
do we should go upstairs and put our beds there i that's
what i did i will respond oh like in this cave uh yeah do
you see it uh do you mind
Okay, be wet.
Oh, do you have your meat thing?
I don't have mine anymore.
I'm downstairs and I'm cooking if you want to add some.
Upstairs?
Oh, wait.
I just realized I'm full health.
Yeah.
Oh, well, it's already cooking.
It's like already going.
You're so annoying.
Why do you have to be such a contrarian all the time?
I'm just a lone wolf.
I don't know what you want from me.
Why can't you just do what I want to do all the time?
I'm an only child.
I need this.
I don't know how to not be annoying.
I know.
Unfortunately, I know.
Do you have food, by the way?
Because I can give you some of these stews.
I cooked all mine.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, kick it.
Cool, then.
I'll pick mine up.
Okay, cute.
Yeah, I'll bet.
Have the fruit skewers?
Huh?
Scoers?
Oh, some skewers.
Wait, that's so cute!
Yeah, I still put skewers.
Wow.
Oh my gosh.
All right, let's go!
Let's go!
I'm gonna need to make a new sword soon.
Yeah.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
Let me make sure we're going the right way.
We came from the other way.
I'm just gonna use the map.
M, M, M, it's this way.
It's this way.
Oh, I see you.
The power of the map.
Wait.
I use my big brain to triangulate the coordinates.
Wait, what are those?
what are these little lizards oh that's a snake oh man the
thingy in the distance was i think another um tree house
another tree house yeah wait i need to go this way oh wait
it's like a fortified tree house oh wait i'm coming i'm
coming i went there i went the wrong way first and i have a
little merman following me i don't trust my intuition
anymore guys oh my god man it's got one of the signs like
the the abyss suck or whatever not abyssal but it Ah!
Oh!
There's skellies in the water.
Oh my God.
Baby, there's a skeleton in the water.
It's got what, what?
But, but.
Oh, there's like orcs and stuff here.
There's like big guys here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think this is an orc fortress.
You wanna assault it?
Oh yeah, but they're coming after me.
Oh shoot, they're coming.
Ooh, girls who do crime together.
Oh, oh, I'm being assaulted.
Like, everybody's attacking me.
Okay, yeah, I'm coming to you.
Oh, hello.
Okay, yeah, I'm here, I'm here.
I'll help all right look at him.
He's so cool.
Yeah, there's like there's like skelly.
Yeah, there's this guy too He was coming after me.
Okay, we got him.
Okay, well, let's go one at a time one at a time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah How do you how do you eat a eat a frog one
bite at a time?
Yep How'd you get up there?
I jumped Yeah, remember you can jump.
This is not like the Minecraft They make they make such cool
noises.
I know they're crazy.
Oh, you're You're, like, all the way up there.
I'll get this guy down here, then.
Yeah, I'm killing this guy.
Okay, I got this guy.
Oh, man.
I don't want to alarm you.
Come up here.
We can fight them from up here.
Hold on.
I know.
I'm getting a guy real quick.
Oh, I got him.
I see, I'm coming to help.
Yeah.
I got it.
Oh, wowee!
Oh, wow!
Oh, wow, big guy!
Holy cow.
Woo!
I'm fighting him from the roof.
I, too, will have to make a sword after this.
Oh, shoot.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, I killed him.
I soloed him.
Good job, good job, good job.
Oh, no.
I stopped in the fire.
Wait.
Nice.
The music is incredible.
It, like, it warms me up so much.
I know, it's crazy.
I got just linen scraps from that guy.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm going to run.
I'm going to run for a second.
I got to get help.
Yeah, me too.
I had to run away for a second.
Run away, run away, run away, run away.
Okay, he's gone down.
Okay.
come fight me where are you come fight me one me one i'm
around i'm going back up because like up top i can kind of
heal and oh what's this this is so cool i really hope they
like make this adventure mode like an actual thing thing you
know yeah wait this place is crazy looking there's probably
got so much loot in here oh i see you i see you i'm coming
back down to you okay oh i see you oh no yeah hi like my hat
yeah I got a hat.
You look so cute and nerdy.
You look like such a little nerd.
I'm not a nerd.
I'm a powerful warrior.
I'm a warrior.
I'm a warrior, please.
Oh, there's a guy somewhere.
Yeah, he's here.
He's here.
I waited to shoot.
Okay, I gotta run again.
I'm so dumb.
I like waited to shoot my attack at the same time as he shot
his.
Oh, oops.
Wait, where is he?
Is he upstairs?
Yeah, I see him.
I see him.
I'm looking at him.
I just had to heal.
I'm watching you fight while eating my meat.
Okay.
Yeah, watch.
Watch this.
Watch a real warrior.
Okay.
Oh, I think he's dead, but it's awkward.
Wait.
Why awkward?
Oh, what?
Did you?
Nothing.
What happened?
He like just kind of stood on my screen and then, like,
poofed out of existence.
Oh, it's probably a little tiny bit of a leg.
Yeah, I think so.
awkward it's just a little awkward guys just a little
awkward yeah just a little weird that's all whoa okay i'm
stealing these for our home these like cool braziers the
lanterns oh did you did you hear me step on fire i did if it
makes you feel any better i also have stepped in fire oh
there's a gold ore in here wait there's a helmet for you too
no way yeah this is so cool we're matching we're matching
look at us we're so cute i'm gonna steal these like little
little banners right i like the lambs i want them in our
home yeah me too oh nice i've been stealing those too yeah
yeah take it take it yeah yeah lost civilization wow well
they're certainly not gonna be found after we know yeah
they're gonna stay lost yeah losers losers Oh
No, you're the music in here is so cool Adventure oh, look
it's a key.
Oh, sorry.
Oh, we could steal this Wait, we could take this take it
take it.
Take it.
Yeah, take it.
Oh my god Torch.
It's called a trork cage like work like yeah And work Trork
I like this place.
I think we're We should bring our beds here.
I think we could probably steal new beds sometime.
Oh, my God.
The music is like, I know.
I want to wake up with the soundtrack and be like feeling
ready for my day.
Oh, there's another guy in the bed.
He spawned.
Oh, he just spawned?
I think so.
Because I don't think I saw him before.
Oh, I'm going to stay back so I'm not like accidentally
hitting you.
Oops.
I was very not strategic.
If it makes you feel any better about that.
i'll wait i'll wait here okay i think they respawn so i
actually think it will be very hard to like ah me hey me
you're sorry me that's fine i guess i'll just cry about it
oh my weapon is about to die for real though okay i gotta
make a real for real yeah i need some rebel okay i'm cooking
you some meat when you're here okay oh i have some i think i
lost some though shoot okay oh no Leave me alone.
Leave me alone.
I'm just a little guy.
I'm just a little me.
Oh my god.
No, please leave me alone for real.
I don't want to do it.
You cannot run the enemy, so just keep running.
Yeah, I am.
Running and running and running running.
I'm running running running.
Running, running.
I'm here.
I'm coming up.
There's no disrespect.
What's the move?
Break your neck.
Thank you.
Oh, I went up the wrong way.
Oh, this music, though.
I know, it's so good.
Oh my god, there's a big chest.
Wow.
I'm stealing their inventory.
I'm stealing their furniture.
Ancient wardrobe.
Beep.
Yes.
Wait, why can't I grab everything, huh?
Fake wall?
What did I...
What did you do?
I'm going to make sure I, like, looted everything.
I'm literally stealing, like, all of their stuff.
Yeah, steal.
take it from them take i want their banners you know yeah
the wardrobe be is that did you drop your weapon here or
yeah but it's because it's low it's low okay okay a new
stamina weapon i guess we should probably find another place
to live man i really do think he respawned because i was in
that area yeah and he wasn't there oh there we go okay now i
can make i don't know wait what's That lantern.
I didn't loot that yet.
Wow.
Something you didn't loot.
Come on.
I know.
You're losing your touch.
I'm going to take all their torches in.
Wait, man.
Yeah, that too.
Oh, me, me, me, me, me.
There's weapons here.
Come, come, come, come, come, come.
Where?
I actually think...
Here, here, here.
I'm jumping.
Go back, go back, go back, go back.
Oh, I see.
I think you'd really like this weapon.
Genuinely.
The crude daggers?
Yeah.
Yeah, because there's two of them.
You go like, oh, yeah, let's do it.
Oh, there's a health potion.
Let's combine some of our inventory.
Do you have any, you can grab the health potion if you want.
Do you have any leathers?
Yeah, but I threw all of them away.
And linen scrap.
Okay, don't throw them away.
Give them to me from now on.
How do I look at the old map?
Is it, is there, is there a point?
It's just M.
Huh?
It's just M for the map.
Oh, the old map.
The old map.
like a cartography thing or something you know maybe oh it's
just decoration as someone said wait if i can i like put it
on this wall how do i decorate wow wait that's a health
potion by the way okay yeah and then if you have any letters
in the leather sorry sometimes my accent i don't even do it
on purpose sometimes i have some hide if you have hides yeah
yeah yeah drop them to me it's all it's all in the chest i
put it in the chest okay because we'll need to um We'll need
to, like, tan them after, so.
Hold Control and right-click on a surface.
Control.
We've got to keep these, because they're going to look so
cool in our future home.
Yeah.
Oh, oh, I haven't looted this yet.
My sign.
I didn't even know there was more.
I think my crouch is not working, guys.
What?
Control?
I'm just going to switch it to Control.
Man, I hate using Control.
It hurts my pinky because I'm double-jointed.
join it i i got my nails done so now when i have to press
shift very quickly like sometimes i hit it with my nail and
it feels like weird it's not working the light click still
oh wait there it is you're doing it yeah oh wow oh nice my
god you look so silly with your helmet you do too it's a
little tuft of hair in the back i love it is this our only
map or did we have another one No, that's the only one.
So when you got from somewhere.
I know, but I think I lost it.
No, you gave it to me.
That's the one.
No, that's the one one.
Okay, do you see the dessert in front of us?
The bird?
The dessert.
If you open your...
Click M.
And you see there's like sand and a dessert.
Oh, desert.
You want to go?
Yeah.
Wait.
is it is it it looks like i mean it looks like a desert it's
yellow and it's got sand but it's like just one path oh
there's a bear uh we can outrun him what are you a pussy no
she scared of a little bear no he's scared of a little bear
he's scared of a little bear he's scared of a little bear
look at me little man scared of a little bear i hope it eats
your face off oh he's still coming Yeah, we gotta keep
running.
Oh, what are you?
Oh, oh.
Red!
What's the red?
Oh!
Snake!
Snake, snake, snake.
Holy cow, I like this weapon.
Right?
I told you it was gonna be your- You look so funny and like
cool with the two daggers.
Yeah!
Wait, I want all the blood leaves.
We're gonna put it in our home.
There's one there too.
up all of them wait there's same thing something here
there's one here there's one here i'll give it oh wait yeah
i can't pick it up yeah i got it i got it i'm full i'm too
yes wait i think i see a structure over here i'm gonna oh
i'm looking at the map oh maybe it's nothing oh yeah i see
it it looks like a little well oh oh you look so much
powerful with it.
Oh wait, look, there's a little guy.
Oh my god, he's running away!
I can take his bed!
We can take his bed!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, grab his bed.
Noink.
Our bed.
Oh my god, it was a little watchtower.
He was on the watch.
Oh, he's not doing a very good job.
Oh, man.
Wait.
You know, you know the lore of small girl, big weapon?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Grab it.
I want to see it oh that i see it oh my god and it's copper
so it's gonna do more damage i want to see it okay hold on
uh there's i left a bench in there if you wanted to grab it
but you don't have to uh oh it's just simple wooded no no no
we're not doing that baby these are the benches oh oh wait
wait you look really cool oh sorry
i think that wait do do a few hits not on me but like do a
few hits just in it's slow it looks fun but i think you
appreciate If you want to give this to me and then you take
the daggers, or you want to take this.
Oh, it's fine.
I knew it.
I was already preemptively blocking.
Yeah, you can have it.
Yeah, thank you.
Yeah.
See?
It's like...
Yeah.
That's yeah.
Let me...
Oh, yeah.
Wait, let me make sure I loot everything here.
Mushroom.
What it is.
Yeah, you took the blue wood, right?
Because there was some blue wood.
Yeah, I already had some, so I took it.
Wait, is there anything up here?
No.
now i'm just up on top we're so close to the dessert yes wow
i can taste it i know wow we're in the dessert the bad land
that doesn't sound good i think these guys are gonna come
are they let's see if they're gonna i hope not what are they
called like those big birds vultures look there's a little
there's like a little wait min there's a tiger a tiger look
look look look oh don't aggro it because i think Do you see
him?
There's a cactus following you.
You just ran away.
Guys, do you have any beds?
I'm scared we're going to die here.
I think these guys are bad, no?
Whoa!
I'm claiming this bed.
Oh, there's more iron.
I got some.
Salt?
Oh, I used to have salt.
Because we're going to need him.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I have venom.
I have a thing of collecting it, yeah.
Okay, I'm claiming this bed.
Find another one in another home and claim it.
Oh my god.
That way if we die, we'll die right here.
This is so...
I found one.
Mint, mint, mint, mint.
Flying, flying, tentacles, flying, flying, tentacle,
octopus, eye, flying, flying.
I just heard a growl.
Flying, tentacle, octopus.
Did you claim a bed yet?
Wow.
Are you okay?
Oh.
Oh my god.
I claimed a bed, yes.
Okay, good, good, good, good.
And there's another vent.
and I'm like, what are you?
Oh, my God.
Holy cow.
Good thing you can get in the bed.
Thank you.
Yeah, let me grab my stuff.
Oh, don't grab my stuff.
Wait, actually, it's, I'm sorry.
But it's good because now it, like, combine our inventories
for some items.
Oh, that's true, that's true.
Can you grab this wardrobe?
Because it's gorgeous.
I want, I want us to have it.
Okay.
Yeah, grab this wardrobe, please.
Okay, I got it.
You want the gorgeous, it's gorgeous.
It's gorgeous.
It's just gorgeous.
Sturdy chicken.
Oh, my God.
gumbawab log that was scary that scared me i just i was
really scared wait so where's this flying tentacle you spoke
of okay let me let me oh wait there's a tanning rack here
i'm gonna start tanning our hides while we're adventuring
what actually i don't know if we're gonna come back here
what is that oh tan oh tanning rack cool okay yeah yeah yeah
and i'll put some i'll put some of the leather like in the
chest next to you that's already tanned just because do
people live here or We live here now.
I live in that house, we live in this house.
That's so true.
My house is like a little bit bigger, isn't it?
Oh!
You see the flying tentacle?
No!
There's like little guys!
And they're fighting- Wait, maybe they're fighting each
other!
There's also a camel!
No!
I'm looking at the raccoon people!
Wait, the raccoon people?
What are you doing?
Yeah, the raccoon people!
Okay, we're looking at the- Oh my god, there's like little
ferret- they're like Fennec fox guys.
Oh my god, they're fast.
Are you fighting them?
Accidentally, I did attack him.
Oh, oops.
Oh, my God.
Look, there's like a whole bat.
There's a war.
There's like a little bone guy that's attacking the ferret
people.
What is going on?
It's an all-out war.
A copper grieves.
Okay, do you remember where my house is?
Look, look, look.
Oh, they're fighting each other at my house.
They are?
Oh, okay, well, he just killed him.
See, he killed him.
That was not me.
That was him.
Oh, my God.
There's a guy.
The creepy.
Ew.
Is that the flying tentacle?
No, no, no, no, no.
I did see a big gopher.
A big guy like floating in the sky.
Oh, over there, yeah.
Look, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I see him.
I see him.
Should we go get him?
We can try.
Let me just kill this guy first.
This guy was killing all the little fox people.
Oh, no, he was killing him?
Yeah.
Good job.
I love my weapon.
Oh, my God.
Oh, oops, my bad.
Oh, look, it's an arbor dino.
Oh, oh, this guy.
Oh, this guy attacks.
Oh, oh, he's hiding in the house sometime.
Oh, shoot.
Be careful.
I'm coming out.
Oh, you're actually going.
Oh, wait.
You?
I killed him.
I was, like, hiding, and you killed him.
Look, it's an armadillo.
Look at her.
Wait, my...
I'm glowing for some reason.
Don't kill him.
Oh, I thought you were killing him.
That guy.
Wait, where's the armadillo?
I'll show you.
I'll show you in a second.
Okay.
Let me show you the armadillo.
right here where oh here it is he kind of blended oh he's so
cute oh it's my ult oh yeah cue it like goes into a frenzy
kind of oh i'm gonna go take it out on these guys wait
there's another like castle looking area yeah we can go we
have our bed oh shoot i'm coming i'm coming yeah these
little guys oh shoot i'm guessing as we go further from the
spawn more and more like harder i could use I'm coming up.
I'm sorry.
I was getting a guy.
Are these the Fennec Fox people?
No, they're Skeletons.
I'm going to die.
Oh, I did.
Just block.
Oh, my God.
That's how you're going to die.
Just block and, like, back up.
I know.
I tried.
There's another wolf behind me.
I'm scared.
Just run here.
Okay.
I'm running back to base to get you.
I'm running.
Okay, here, here, here.
My stuff.
I'm going to give you back the health potions if you want to
put them, like, hotkey them so it's easy for you to use.
Yeah, I forget.
She's just here for the zip line.
I think you're just here to kill stuff, aren't you?
I'm afraid so.
Oh, a tiger!
Oh!
Oh, a tiger.
Just keep walking if he's careful.
Oh, nice!
Thanks, baby.
Yeah.
Yo!
This is so cool!
I love the little lizard.
I need this guy.
I need him.
I need him in my life.
you can capture them after where are you where'd you go
where'd you go where'd you go where'd you go lizard where'd
you go where'd you go where'd you go lizard where'd you go
kill him what you're gonna kill him no he's just hiding from
me what was this oh i should hotkey this you should you
really really should okay i did wait what is that is that a
gotta look at this guy he looks so nerdy with his big teeth
oh wait wait wait wait let me oh my god oh wait wait oh wait
oh wait oh wait oh wait oh wait oh wait i don't like that
they also parry i don't like that they block and it scares
me oh i'm gonna die i'm fighting my own battles sorry i know
i oh shoot oh shoot oh shoot no no this guy was like tall
i'm coming to you i'm coming to you i'm coming to you i'm
coming to yeah I'm guarding your stuff.
Oh shoot.
He's coming after me.
He's okay.
It's okay.
Oh, I killed him.
Good job!
I got him with an alt.
Oh my god.
I'm accidentally stepping it.
Oh wait.
I'm stepping into poison.
Ben, I'm gonna...
I'm not gonna die.
Wait.
How are you stepping into poison?
I'm like stepping into poison.
I think I took all your stuff.
at the bees it's okay the bees are oh my freaking god there
was like a bee flying above me but you know how gamers don't
look up yeah oh you thought it was poison oh wait i didn't
take your stuff i'm kidding it's okay it's okay it's okay i
thought i was getting poisoned by the ground so i was
looking down but i wasn't looking up oh oh i could just eat
some more meat oh my god there's so much stuff here
attacking me.
Oh my god.
I think I...
This is kind of, like, I have four things on me right now.
It's called the Badlands.
Yeah, it's not very good.
Where are you?
What is that?
Um, if you open M, you'll see my little... Do you want me to
run back to you?
Or?
I'll run to you.
Oh, I see you.
I see you.
You see me?
I'm hopping.
Oh, she's hopping.
She's hopping.
I'm hopping with my torch.
He's hopping with her torch.
Yeah, that's the only thing about this thing being a
two-handed is that i can have a torch yeah it's okay yeah i
was like over there mint and like you see how this ground is
like weird yeah like i thought i was getting hurt but it was
a bee like poisoning me from a hawk what block is this i
don't know it's nasty and I'm spoiled.
Oh, I'm a deal.
Cool.
I want to, um, maybe I want to like go when it's daylight so
we can like actually see properly.
We can go rest.
We can go sleep in our beds.
Wait, can you actually sleep?
Sleep?
Oh, okay.
No, we should do that.
It's just a bow.
What is this?
Ew, it's so wet.
Mm.
Yummy.
I'm also going to cook a little bit more meat because I'm
all out of meat since.
i lost like half of my meat is that you running yeah running
with my meat oh it's a chicken oh was i going the wrong way
i don't know maybe oh maybe open your map i'm getting hurt
by something i don't know what oh my god please i wonder if
it's like the same bee that was hurting me i was looking up
though i didn't see it oh my god oucha oucha oh my god i
have four three guys on me Oh my god.
Yeah, this area is kind of dangerous.
Oh!
Holy cow.
Oh my god, and they're nasty.
This area is dangerous, girl.
I'm gonna die.
I'm leaping.
I'll wait for you.
I wish I had three, four guys on me.
Coconuts, please.
Behave, Angel.
Oh, they left me alone for some reason.
Just go to the Badlands.
You're gonna have all the guys on you.
I know, for real.
Wait, I'm last.
Mint, I kind of, tomorrow, when you wake up from your
bedtime...
um i want to go harvest the hive soil okay um not to rush
for anything but i'm like in bed waiting yeah i don't know
where i am hold on where's home um i'm far from home and
then look for mint phantom's bed i'm going the right way
what is this void heart whoa whoa thank you guys Stop going!
Wait, I want to be a part of Gifted.
I want to gift memberships.
No, you're asleep.
You should be sleeping.
Uh, I'm sleepwalking.
No, I'm getting into my bed.
Literally right now.
I'm getting into your memberships.
No.
I'm sleeping.
Hello.
I'm getting into your memberships.
One moment.
Hello.
waiting on matara con dot dot waiting on oh god will they
attack me in my slate i don't know
go to bed why don't you take your own advice okay all right
i'm going to bed yeah i'm not bad come on go to bed i'm not
enough of you i'm not another you did you because it's
adventuring time how do i get up oh there we go how do i get
up okay grandma whoa there's a wow that's a cool candle yeah
they're every like we're looting this place yeah oh my gosh
how cute wait oh i did you hear that it went like whoa whoa
no i'm gonna steal this tanning rack so i don't have to make
one you did not hear the whoa I did not hear any whoa whoa
whoa okay you're crazy yeah speak for yourself you're the
one and that make me crazy wait why is it still so dark in
here it's the badlands okay where was your home because i
had the i was right across the street from you oh i'm right
next to you yeah but now i like lost which house was your
house you just ran past me literally i know i know but which
house was your house do you remember because i had leathers
tanning i remember i slept in there oh yeah can you show me
on the map where it was how is it um can you guide me to
your house this is not my house this is not my house this
house that we're in right now that i guided you to not my
house not my house watch out also not my house this one this
is my house that's your house this is my house okay yeah
this was the house because i left the leather tatting here
yoink oh my gosh guys thank you so much for all the
memberships thank you Oh my gosh, Matara.
Oh, you hear that?
He goes, oh.
I know.
Matara, why did you gift memberships?
Um, because why not?
It's cheap.
You have them set really, really, really cheap.
Oh, thank you so much for the gifted.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
The, uh, they're, I've awakened them.
They're like, wait, Matara can gift members.
I can give members.
No, they should be giving members to.
Oh, there's a dog in my house.
Whoa!
Wait, you brother.
Oh my God, the wolves are on fire.
Okay, interesting.
I'm walking.
Yeah, block while I kill.
Block while I kill.
I have my time and I can't block.
Oh, they're on fire.
They're on fire.
Wait, does it burn their meat?
I don't know.
But I need to cook.
Mint, we need to cook.
We need to.
We need to cook, Mint.
Don't say that.
Thank you for the gift, Mint.
Mint, we need to cook.
Oh, do you want?
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
I'm putting down mine, my meat, too.
Yeah, put your meat.
I'm cooking your meat in.
Cooking my mate.
Cook your meat.
I do have a portable bed that I will be bringing with me.
Cool.
I'm going to get rid of one of the beds from this place to
bring with me.
Okay.
And I'm also storing like, this is kind of a...
Is this your bed or no?
Yeah, this is my bed.
Yeah, I claim that.
This is kind of not a great place to live though.
I mean...
No!
It's not.
There's like lots of guys around.
And the doors, they don't have them.
They don't have doors and that's why all these people died.
the doors they don't have them look at this guy he's like
climbing right he's a turtle shell i know but i'm gonna
claim this bed i'm
coming wait i think there's wait i think the guys respawned
i think they're back here the little raccoons yeah they're
here they're back you gotta look like clinic boxes right
yeah they're so cute i want to see them oh there's a sand
lizard what where Where I'm at he's really cool looking and
there's also a little skelly fighting me But I'm seeing oh,
I want to see this.
I don't get the I see him the little lizard.
I see him.
Whoa He's so cute.
He's so cute.
Oh my god.
I'm gonna take you home Yeah, soon Yeah
There's a little guy What is this guy?
He lives here!
Whoa!
Oh my god!
I'm stealing his urchin shell.
Oh, I stole his urchin shell.
Oh, that's fine.
That's fine.
What?
He's just living in the room!
Can we talk?
Oh my god, he's smoking his bubble pipe.
Oh my god.
Wait, I need to witness him smoking.
He's smoking a little bubble pipe.
Oh my god.
my god this is so cute i can't oh my god he has like a
velvet like purple bathrobe i know he's so like sensual for
some reason one one unibrow oh and he's got a little lizard
pet oh wait i'm gonna rob him before we continue okay he
needs to fix his home proper pickaxe buddy i'm i'm in oh
nice Oh, yeah, I got a copper one earlier, too.
Yeah.
Yay, we robbed it.
Oh.
Mint?
What?
Drop down.
Drop down where I am.
Come back.
Drop down.
More?
What's up with his house?
What?
Oh, my God.
A thorium ingot?
Copper grieves?
I think he's like, I think his house is like spawned weird.
Have you, um, you know those boots where they were like
Astro Boy inspired looking boots?
Oh, do you know what I'm talking about?
I think so, yeah.
Once you see them on me, you'll know what I'm talking about.
I got the Ingrid.
Oh, you stole the door?
I'm good, good, good, good.
Look at my boots.
Oh, my God.
You kind of look like those, like, astro boots, no?
They do!
Yeah, this table, look at it.
Wow.
He's got so much cool stuff.
What the heck, little homie?
Mint.
Yeah, I think his home spawned weird because there's more of
his home.
Yeah, it's right over here, right?
strange yeah oh my god he just put a potion of stamina like
on his shelf oh sure why not where else would you put it i
want his book yeah take it and then we can put it in our
take his little bookshelf it's okay if i take it yeah i
don't think he can do much against you can he is he our pal
i mean he's just kind of chilling well he's not a hacking us
so that's that's good yeah this place is awesome this is
awesome i really do think it like spawned weird i think oh i
think this she thinks oh i just heard something oh i think
it was upstairs okay just kidding i'm gonna come back up in
just a second i want a chandelier
i want his oh my god i keep falling his little book on his
table looks divine i want it yeah that's what i mean i want
that too
Sorry, buddy.
I have the tavern chandelier.
Okay, wait.
I want to see what's up there.
Uh-oh.
I like it.
I like robbing people.
It's fun.
Doing crimes with your friends is so fun.
Yeah, he doesn't seem to mind either.
It's okay.
No.
We should do more crimes together.
It's good times.
Wait.
We should.
Oh.
Crimes are fun.
Uh...
Yes?
Nothing.
What'd you do?
No.
Would you kill?
Nothing.
What'd you do?
Be honest.
I won't judge.
You know I won't judge.
I broke his...
His uh...
His will to live?
I broke his little...
Yeah, I broke his spirit.
I broke his...
I broke his red shiny item.
Uh, the...
the glowy stone.
As long as you don't break him.
I wonder if he'll respond though.
like the orcs were respawning oh big cactus oh yeah wonder
what else was I gonna grab that was it are you back upstairs
yeah I'm back upstairs I'm trying to kill this cactus to see
it it's like oh my god it's actually cactus oh it's actually
cactus it's not hard to chop my really like bad pickaxe I
still want to chop something let's go to that nasty place
and start collecting whatever the moist Soil was.
Hive soil.
That way I can like my little bugs in our bay.
Whoa, look at this guy!
He's like a scorpion, but he's got like a skull for a face.
Oh, the skull ones are typically bad guys.
They're baddies.
No.
Oh, that's what's hurting me.
Oh, there's a hyena!
Hyena!
He's so cute!
Oh, he's dangerous.
I don't know.
I could have told you that.
Hey.
Oh, yeah, you're dealing with your own.
Oh,
sometimes I right-click, but...
Oh, come on.
Where am I?
Oh, I'm back home.
You're going to respawn into the... I'm close.
Yeah, yeah.
I know where you are.
Oh, stay away from me.
Ew, Batara.
Ew.
Oh, well, the armadillo.
I'm here.
Armadillo.
Wait, ow.
Why did you harm?
No, it's these.
It's these guys right here.
Look, Fiddy, what did Fiddy do?
Oh, you're going to love these mushrooms and flowers, girl.
Ew, these sounds so gross here.
Whoa.
Oh, the blood cap mushroom.
Take him.
You should take him.
All right.
I won't take the heart.
hive soil.
When I live in my own home, I'll take them, but otherwise,
you know.
Yeah.
Maybe you can make this your home.
Ah.
No.
Too many enemies.
Are you sure?
I'd rather live with you, believe it or not.
Oh, I don't believe that.
I know.
Desert chick.
Look, look, look.
It literally calls it desert chick.
Bit, bit, bit, come here.
And then look at it.
Desert chick.
Oh, my God.
Wait, it's so cute.
It kind of looks like it's got like teeth around its neck,
almost like prehistoric style, if that makes sense.
I get what you mean, but I don't think that's the intention.
I think that's just feathers.
No, no, no.
What else is in here?
Wow.
The desert.
I see something blue, and I'm locked in.
Yep, yep, I'm following.
Do you see the blue?
I see the blue.
I see a little blue.
Little blue, little blue.
What could you do?
Oh, they're mushrooms, I think.
Oh, I got the sound.
Wait, look below.
Wait, stop.
What?
What is this?
Okay, you know what?
It's an egg sack.
Oh, God.
Oh, you were right.
It's an egg sack.
My cousin.
Oh, God, they're hatching.
But, Dora, oh.
What?
i am okay you know what i was judging this game a little bit
because all i did was like start at the beginning area and
just mine but like no this has got some oh my god this is
your area this is your stinking area oh my god there's so
many oh my god i can smoke the pipe a little gentleman you
know oh are you are you down here no i'm fighting a skeleton
right outside i'm i can come down there and i know i just
watched one die on its own that was weird oh maybe because i
hatched it out of the egg early so it was like no i wasn't
ready to be born oh that was so dramatic do you want these
uh oh i can burst the sacks yeah yeah you can open the sack
oh wow i'm going to make this species extinct don't do
Oh my god, I am keeping the medium scarak eggs.
I am keeping them.
You're keeping them?
They're mine now.
They're my babies.
They're my children.
You can, like, mine them.
Oh, you can.
Medium scarak egg.
Yeah, if you haven't hatched them, you can mine them.
Okay, I'll hatch them for you.
Or, I mean, I'll harvest them for you, yeah.
Oh, I got it.
Are you down?
Did you drop down?
Yes, yeah, I fell down on accident.
That's why I was, like, freaking out because they were all
coming at me.
i don't know if i was supposed to like hit him with my
they're actually so cute man they got like two big eyes i
don't know why i was able to like harvest one of them but
not the other one okay i'm here i'm coming oh oh you're
dropping them they're coming at me i'll give you i'll i know
i know i'll give you all the sacks that i get once i once i
collect them you know i would I was burst in them, though.
Give me your sacks, girl.
I want all your sacks.
Yeah.
I'll give you my sacks.
I want your sacks.
Yeah.
Look at this, this, like, round thing.
What?
Is that a wood?
What is this?
I don't know.
This one.
Eels.
Nasty guy.
It's poisoned roots.
Whoa.
Oh, there's like, it's so cool that you can see the ones
that are, like, still not hatched yet.
Oh, wait.
Are they the big?
Oh, yeah, I know what you mean now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Some of them are like...
Yeah, some of them...
Min?
Oh.
Big, big, big, big, big, big bug.
Big bug.
Big bug over here.
Yeah, I know.
I've been fighting those guys.
Big bug.
Oh, these are people!
So cute!
Oh, he is bigger.
He is bigger than what I was fighting before.
Hold on.
I'm coming in.
Oh, you got him?
Easy.
Look!
Wait, wait, wait, hold on.
Hold on.
Come look at this.
Wait, unless I killed them all.
Wait.
No, did I kill them all?
Dang it.
You're going to chop the roots or they're going to hurt us.
I know.
That's what I was doing.
Dang it, I killed them all.
Ah!
Uh-oh, I'm about to die again.
This is such a spooky area.
I love it.
Oh, I keep... I don't care.
I love it!
Yeah, it's fun.
I don't care.
Okay, so if they're not hatched, the egg sack is when you
can pick it up.
Oh, what the heck was that?
I'm bringing them home.
I'm going to hatch them home.
We're going to have little bugs.
Yeah, you'll have your own little bug army.
This area is quite spooky.
Look, it keeps going.
Oh, shoot.
It goes down even more.
Did you fall down?
Oh, yeah.
I kind of don't want to go down down there.
No, me neither.
I'm not going to lie.
I'm a little scared to go down there.
Okay.
Thanks.
Wait, can we...
What about over here?
here though okay let me i'll i'm following you okay i will
need to like get more oh what's it called soon though uh
what's it called health and stuff oh oh yeah yeah yeah come
here come look look look see how it's squirming wait that's
a person in there i know but these just drop like little
decorative skeletons i know but isn't it so cool that it's a
person it's really cool it's really cool i agree i agree
it's so cool by the way you can eat the mushroom oh you can
i know it says spotted but like i've eaten them before oh
okay i trust you i trust you i don't trust her the last
words she ever spoke yeah okay i don't know how to go over
right there that's just a regular cave oh that's okay i
thought that was wood wow yeah this is oh dang it little rat
rat rat rats rats yeah the rats what a cool place what a
cool place did you want to get any more wait what's over
here i'm just looking probably come outside in one of these
oh yeah probably look at that like the vines and stuff walk
oh it's purple oh man you didn't walk through the vines yeah
yeah yeah oh you did you did yeah it's awesome oh i'm such a
fan me too i think it's the glow oh no it's the ore oh
there's like purple shards of an ore oh yeah yeah i get see
this here too oh how do you how do you oh shoot how do you
mine it though i keep breaking it um you mine it with your
pickaxe and sometimes it drops oh sometimes it drops okay
i'm collecting more sack for you thanks i want all your sack
give me your sacks i have give me your 16 of them Let me see
if you have any poison vest.
Something that we can, like, consolidate.
Nice.
Oh, oh, oh.
Mid-Mid-Mid, scarefighter discovered.
Oh, oh.
He literally just spawned behind us.
Yeah, these guys are pretty weak, though.
Literally just spawned behind us, though.
Yeah, we should get out of here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
How cool.
I know.
pretty sick.
Oh, I think there are more are spawning.
Yeah, okay.
Um, let me see if I have a block I can build.
I have, like, 19 of some, like, beach beach logs.
Okay.
Thanks, girl.
Uh, it wasn't enough.
Um.
Oh, it's enough.
I'm out.
Thanks, girl.
You didn't even wait for me.
You warm
all right now i have to like drop something from my
inventory um all right i'm gonna all right girl i gotta mine
up i think it's gonna be really annoying but i gotta do it i
think you can do that wait should i take my beach logs back
or i'll wait for you outside oh yeah i'm i'm lining up
quickly oh oh i think i'm sinking oh oh i No, I guess not.
I hear you.
I hear you digging.
I'm coming.
Oh, my God.
It's so close.
Here comes Mata.
Where are you?
Where are you coming from?
Oh, I see you.
Here comes Mata.
That was funny.
All right.
I'm here.
Okay.
Where to now?
I don't know.
Is there anything on the map?
That's cool to check out.
Wow, there's like a big oasis looking thing.
There's like fortresses.
Wait, what's that like?
It looks like a volcano.
You see it?
Let's go.
I'll follow you.
I'm not sure which one you're pointing at.
I'll go.
Where's my marker?
I will follow you into the dark.
What is the marker?
Like, I put it, but I don't see it like on my map.
I think you got a...
I don't know.
There's a parrot!
Oh!
Oh, yeah, you're right.
He's cute.
Are we, like, swimming?
I think so.
In the swamps?
We're going to be so stinky.
That's a mud bath.
What are you talking about?
Okay, okay, mister.
I like how they only aggro on one person.
I think that's pretty funny.
Yeah, me too.
Also, be careful.
There's, like, big bugs flying with green on them.
They're the ones who were, like, throwing poison at me.
Oh, okay, okay.
Oh, oh.
Okay, just kidding.
The thing that I was seeing before on the map is the same
thing that we just went inside, just like another bug hive.
Okay.
Dude, the bug hive was so cool.
Crazy.
Do you want to just traverse the desert and go through it
and see what's on the other side of it?
Yeah.
We should.
Okay.
Let's go this way then.
Oh, I need him.
I need...
Wait, is that a flamingo?
where flying there's a pink bird where it's a flamingo it's
a flamingo turn around which side east west and uh south
south oh i see you and the flamingo i want to wow it is a
flamingo
Cool.
All right.
I take it back.
At first, I was like, yeah, it's okay.
I was comparing it too much to Minecraft, but the
adventuring so far has been...
Fun.
It's been fun.
Stay away from me.
Yeah.
No, let's go to the east so we can traverse the desert.
Okay.
East.
Let's go.
Oh, look at the tree.
I think it's called, like, a baobab tree that are native to
Africa.
You see that thing at the end there?
Maybe I'm having the wrong tree name.
How cool is that?
Just the big tree.
There's palm trees!
Palm trees!
Wait, that's so cool!
Stay away from me, hyena.
Yeah, hyena might aggro, but if he does, we don't got to
fight him.
No.
Oh my gosh, how cute!
Oh my god!
It's a...
Is it a baby cheetah?
Oh my god.
Is it?
What is it?
Was it a monkey?
I can't tell.
What is it?
It's a lemur, maybe?
A mure cat.
Mure cat, I mean, a mure cat.
Oh my god.
That's so cute.
He's so cute.
I love.
Let's go to the palm trees.
I want to see if there's any different birds, fish,
anything.
There's a tiger.
You can find him.
We can get him.
I don't see.
Oh, I do see a tent.
Wait.
Help me find the tiger, please.
Okay.
Oh.
Oh, he sounded so...
He said...
I know.
He's just like, okay, boo.
What's the blue place?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I wonder if it's a block or if it's a real thing.
And I'm also gonna loot this tent.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Whoever left this tent here, your mom's, you know, it's our
tent now.
What'd you say about her?
What'd you say about mama?
Mama?
wow wait use scissors on the cocoon people i don't have
scissors i like how someone's like use the scissors but i
don't have any scissors on cocoon people so they don't break
and you can use them as a decoration oh yeah i did i did i
stole the x-axis no no but there's like i guess scissors
whoa hello this is the braziers i was talking about oh are
we gonna steal them yeah Oh, come here.
Wait, wait.
Come here and open this door.
No way.
You can take it home, by the way.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm going to take the Braziers home.
Oh, you can only hold 42 memories.
Oh, here, I'll give you mine.
Here's the Braziers.
Oh, wait.
I just took them back.
Take the Braziers.
I'll take the whip.
Oh, take the whip.
Nope.
You didn't take the Braziers.
Okay.
sorry sorry i'm coming back no come inside uh if we can only
wait that means we have so many memories darn yeah um how
far is our memory place oh maybe we could find another one
yeah yeah yeah oh this guy has a yellow shell cute oh he's
different cute wait let's go see the animals in here come
come come the other way the other way yeah yeah yeah look
look look look oh i see the deer different or like uh yeah
oh and the big turtle pantalope oh my god oh my god i love
all the animals there's so much like so much in this game i
know oh my god i'm so glad we're exploring i know this is
i'm telling you like this is not the experience i had i just
did stuff solo and dig And I was like, oh, that's fine.
I'm digging.
Like, you know, it's whatever.
It's a digging game.
I think it's because it's like there's so...
It's like it's a whole new experience.
Like, what that...
Oh, that's a scorpion again.
Think of all the, like, customization you can do in your
home.
Yeah.
Like, wow.
I'm looking at the map now.
Yeah.
Which way do you want to go, Pookie?
I'm seeing if there's, like, any...
I wonder if that's one.
I will kill this spider for you.
Okay, thank you.
I don't know what a temple looks like, to be honest.
It's not like a little whirlpool.
I didn't see any on the map right now.
Oh, you didn't?
Okay.
Oh, I see like a village though.
I could try going to that.
Or maybe like a fortress.
Who knows?
You know, one health potion.
Um, I'm out.
Uh, but, um, hold on.
I have a raw meat if you want to cook it.
We can cook the meats after.
Uh, you know what?
I have bad news.
I think we should slaughter the fauna and the flora just
because I think you're right.
I'm going to need some... We're going to need some food.
Okay, who the...
Oh, the Entelopees.
They actually attacked back.
Entelopees.
What are they on?
What is this?
Oh, those coconuts?
Whoa, wait, what they are.
Is that what fell on my head then?
Probably.
Did it hurt you?
Yeah.
Oh my god, It is a coconut and it does the health regen.
Wait, how much?
I'm just eating a whole coconut.
That's crazy.
Yeah, I'm in that coconut.
Blink it all up.
Oh, it's health regen one so it's not too crazy but it's
better than nothing.
Better than nothing, yeah.
Oh my god, look how cute the parrot is.
Oh, actually the health regen is cute.
Whoa, the parrot.
I like how he's parrying me.
I'm like, you're missing your backside, buddy.
Is that what you thought they were attacking you back?
But it was really just the coconut attacking you.
Wait, wait, wait.
Does this mean wait?
Mint?
The coconuts give really good health regen.
Did they?
Yeah, I think so.
Let's loot some coconuts while we're here.
Okay.
I have four.
Coconut.
Coconut, coconut, coconut, coconut.
Do you know the Japanese word for coconut?
Coconuts.
The reason I'm asking is because I was collabing with Hany
and I asked her the Japanese word for clown.
She said it's Piero.
Which is a really, it's like the most famous French clown.
Yeah, Piero.
Yeah, yeah.
I was like, wait, really?
Like that, the word for clown is just like a famous French
clown?
The famous French clown.
Oh, he does kick back.
Yeah, a little bit.
He's like John Clown of Clown.
John Clown, the CEO of Clown.
Wait, because this place is a whip, do you want to, like,
make this our base right now?
Sure.
We could just, like, kind of mine it a bit and, like, just
take over.
Yeah.
We can even, like, and he has doors, and I can put the
braziers?
Yeah.
Wait, if I mine more...
Uh-huh.
Oh, never mind.
Don't...
Oh, I made a window.
Oh, just close it back.
Wait, hold on.
Let's put our beds in.
Wow.
Whoa, look at us.
Do you want to close the other door?
Yeah, I'll work on it.
Oh, wait.
We need more room for the...
These beds I have are kind of big.
I think we can, like, barely put them both in, but that's
okay.
You have to.
I'm going to put my bed closer to the edge.
Okay.
Wait, where's my bed?
I'm going to put your bed in front of mine.
Okay, mine's ugly.
it's okay yours is huge what the hell i'm literally sleeping
on like a okay girl i'm also a tall bug woman okay oh my god
you're taking up i'm taking up two blocks and you're taking
up like seven but you're also like four feet ten on a good
day on a good height day you know this is best up this is um
wait hold on i have a wardrobe no i have a chest we could
put some stuff in here some of the stuff that was like in
the earlier bottle or like oh my bad see
the grimoire oh that's so cool yeah with the grimoire oh i
see it's nice cool cool and i love that it has an auto thank
you thank you thank you thank you as well hi baby oh yeah uh
did you need to i can cook some meat right now hold on let
me oh yeah i have some i have some yeah yeah yeah let's put
some meat now just so that way we can be all prepared yes do
you have another chest i think i can just craft one worst
case i don't i think we'd have to craft what we just whoa oh
sandstorm yeah oh does it hurt okay it doesn't hurt it's
just like weird
a wood on you uh yes okay give me i have a lot of wood there
you go give me all your wood girl i took it i should i threw
it i threw it oh we threw it oh you gave me sticks i needed
like woodwood oh i have beach there you go yeah that's right
give me the beach um okay i needed like 10.
oh uh sorry um let's go mine what's wrong with my what's
wrong with my sticks uh they can't we can't craft a chest
with them but it's okay we can do it next time that's what
you're trying to do let's let's leave the sandstorm away duh
i'm asleep wait let me you're the last one in you're
supposed to close the door sorry oh i do have some azure
logs but they're pretty guys i don't want to use those let's
not use the
zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz
let's go chop up some more um yeah of the coconut wait
what's in here and then i'm gonna make us another chest so
we can put our stuff in Is there a chest here or no?
Oh yeah, wait, there's a wooden chest here.
Oh yeah?
Okay, grab it.
I'm still doing cups and coconuts.
Okay.
ZZ?
ZZ, Z, ZZ, ZZ.
ZZ, that was so cute.
ZZ, ZZ, ZZ, ZZ, ZZ.
Do you know, Miss French speaker, what ZZ is in French?
ZZ, ZZ, ZZ.
ZZ?
It's a, it's a bee saying Wii.
It means pee pee.
You're teaching me that!
oh my god okay miss i eat shit i'll remember come on you've
taught me yours give me the chest give me the chest girl oh
there you go yeah let's let's put other stuff in this chest
and then explore it but then we have to come back here and
like you know i know but like this can be just like some
place that we can store stuff you know yeah we got a lot of
stuff i love that we're both job oh yeah oh yeah essence of
the void like i have this void heart it's an epic thing i
don't even know what that means that's because you pulled
the big boy wow you're so cool wait oh my sword is broken
okay let me throw this out yeah it's a it's a you can use
the other crew decor oh yeah yeah let me actually wait let
me say put the workbench outside because then oh wait i can
probably put
is any stone okay okay so you can make crude crude stuff
from here if you have rubble you can make your little dagger
again oh okay I'm gonna go get some edge grab any of the
rubble oh did you use nothing I'm fine we can even cook the
iron ore while we're here yeah let's make some ingots and
stuff yeah so we can at least get like um copper what is it
called copper um now we're playing the game guys now we're
literally gonna suit up so we can go to the harder area okay
is it a harder area oh i mean i think the bad lands are a
little bit harder than the previous oh yeah that's true yeah
um what are you neat what are you trying to grab i just
grabbed wood and i need to find any stone any stone yeah
that's what this is maybe stone let me see is it stone you
can probably dig until stone yeah oh yeah i'm gonna grab
sandstone cobble me too just so i can make it furnace wall
and let it cook cook let's see that easy way
yes and then we're gonna we're gonna wear cute tin armor or
iron and then we're gonna go i know you're saying iron
you're not saying iron
Iron...
And Irvine!
Doesn't matter my brain!
Stop copying me, stop copying me!
It sounds like you're obsessed with bait.
You're copying me!
Stop copying me!
Stop copying me, you're copying me, you're copying me!
Come!
She's copying me!
I'm gonna put the floor down.
is outside because we don't have room inside okay this tree
is like deep in the wood in the ground wow wait what's that
over there no giving me oh if you happen to have found any
copper bring it back bring it back okay i don't have any
yeah yeah we'll find some there was a ton in the in the
stuff oh i see some in the walls there's copper inside yeah
if you can just mine it for me please it's like orangey.
Yeah, hold on.
That we can do some good shit.
What is that?
Nice.
Yeah, we can actually get like really nice armor before we
continue our adventure.
Yeah.
Yay.
Can you grab the brain cell, man?
What the heck?
Ouch!
Stinking bees.
Ouch, ouch.
Stop!
Good for the environment.
Oh, I'm hiding back.
behind a tree and he's still getting me.
Come on, come on, come on.
Oh into the environment, men.
How do you kill the bees?
I'm gonna die.
It's a good thing, you're gonna respawn right here.
I know, ouch, ouch, ouch.
ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
I think she's hiding it at all.
I think she's doing it.
I think it's a bit.
I have broken things in my inventory, you should repair
them.
That's what it just told me.
I have broken every bone in my body.
Damn bee, man.
Why you gotta be like that?
I do have a bow, actually.
I do have a bow.
I'm gonna try using it.
All right.
You in?
Yeah.
I'm gonna make you real cool, okay?
Okay.
Oh, dang.
And then I'm gonna give you a repair kit for it.
So when this pickaxe breaks, it doesn't break.
It's just gonna have an X on it.
and then you use the repair kit and it's gonna be back to
full what you'll see it in a chest I'm gonna give you a tin
oh wait you won't see it in a chest because a chest is full
okay yeah I'll show you after I'll be back for you I'll be
back I'm gonna get you it's a matter of time I'll give up I
do I never give up never what never give up I give up never
what I give up never what I give up I give up Never
surrender.
I give up?
No.
You're so cute, but no, don't give up.
Please.
Thank you.
Okay, I'm just going to grab this stuff to give you.
Never going to give you up.
Yeah.
I have a gift for you.
Okay.
So you're going to grab this axe, and then when it breaks,
it's going to have an axe on it.
So it's not going to disappear from your inventory, and you
just use that repair kit, and it's going to be repaired.
Whoa!
Like those daggers, I'm gonna make you those daggers, but
like, you know, more advanced, more powerful.
Wow!
I'm gonna open up.
Oh, I see it, I see it.
Wait, oh wow, thorium and cobalt.
Adam tight.
Adam is tight.
Oh, how cute!
I'm gonna make this guy.
cool and then i'm just gonna wait a little you made us i
made us a little target practice cute i was just gonna use
you for a little target practice
here we go that is so cute actually seeing your you like
shooting the thingy oh no it weighs arrows like you can't
get them back but i think they're kind of cheap to make no
are they
I wait for wait I wait until my iron pickaxe is dead the
iron pickaxe is going to totally break don't worry about it
it won't disappear from inventory okay to like you know
trash it and then um then you're gonna use it and it's gonna
let you select the item that you want to use it on okay okay
because a new pickaxe is five ingots but a repair kit is
just one ingot ah okay okay yeah i think this is in because
this is in here you know um let me also make you a better
weapon i just need to make it on the other workbench how do
i make that other bench and then we can go back cool i'm
just like i'm gonna dispose of i'm guessing no i need the
two copper did you say you had two copper oh let me go i was
gonna get it and then i got killed by the yeah okay let me
go get it for you to get the little daggers that you have
okay i'll go get two copper two copper get a little if
there's a little bit more feel free to get a little bit
more.
Okay.
But like don't go out of your way, you know.
Alright.
Two copper.
I saw one copper at least.
One copper.
One whole copper.
I have five copper?
Where?
Oh, I do have copper.
Come back and put it in the machine.
Where did I get that from?
Unless I just had it from earlier.
Come back and put it into the machine.
The machine.
Feed the machine.
Mint.
I'm feeding.
okay which one either one this one with the sticks to the
left because it's got less stuff cooking yeah yeah yeah yeah
i'm still gonna go get more though since we have time we're
just waiting for it to cook so yeah yeah yeah yeah i'm also
gonna make you a tin axe and then we're gonna and then i'm
gonna make a few repair kits for us so that way off on a
long adventure thank you mama of course baby taking care and
making things
i bully but i also love oh i love to bully sure you're like
okay weirdo yeah i could have grandma it's time to admit um
that's probably all the momos say all the time no they do do
i want what you one armor um it might be good to have just
so we like don't die in one heat yeah i think because we're
like getting into crazier areas might be good let me get a
few more wood and then i will okay okay there was only two
copper here so that's kind of lame but it's a good thing
that you only needed two earlier because i would have only
been able to bring you two now you need more okay I can
mine.
I can like do a little strip mining and see if I find
anything.
I don't know if that's...
I think I have enough actually because I have two on me now.
Wait.
Does that work in this game guys?
Does strip mining work?
I have enough.
You do?
Are you sure?
There's a ton in caves.
I'm next to a cave.
Where was one?
Oh, I'm next to a cave.
Oh, right here.
Ooga booga.
she's next to a cave all right um where's my torch sorry y
'all but we have decided that we're sick and tired of dying
yeah wait there's not this is not a cave literally nothing
in here okay is you saying it like that because i feel like
i was bamboozled all right let me go get some wood and I'm
coming back.
Oh, wait, there's one here too.
Oh, I see some.
I see some.
Yay, copper.
Give me, give me copper.
Oh, I see some.
God, the music here is so cool.
Yeah.
With like the little like, it's very western, you know?
There's only a few.
Okay.
Let me check this game.
myself as well while I'm at it so you can eat any mushroom
or some of them are as long as it says like edible no the
poisonous ones you just can't eat them oh it seems oh my god
you little sucker come here don't call me that sorry nice of
you okay it's if I if it helps it oh there you are hi I mean
it positive is there anything else in here a little sucker
lovingly I know I feel more confident going into caves in
this game because I know there's no creepers.
Yeah, exactly.
Creeper.
And like, there is lava similar to lava stuff, but not in
the same way.
Like, you can be pretty safe going into stuff.
And there's like monsters all the time.
So I'm like, oh, it's not just me going into a cave and like
getting ambushed by monsters.
Like, there's monsters everywhere.
Yeah, you kind of like, yeah.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Till there are.
your um oh iron hatchet oh this is like a new oh nice okay
i'm throwing it in the do items despawn eventually i hope so
i'm not sure what we do with it i know otherwise i'm like
just throwing it into the desert another thing that's
freaking cool so like if you touch the stuff that's outside
of the chest area it still will like trigger the items in
the chest area for a certain distance What?
I don't know if I explained that.
Okay.
So I put stuff in the chest, right?
And now when I'm going to craft stuff, it still pulls from
the chest, even though I don't have the items on me.
Oh, interesting.
Oh, I get what you mean.
Oh, wow.
That's like so good quality of life kind of.
I know.
Wait, do we not have a cooker?
Or the furnace is only for metals, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I took my cooker back because I don't want to forget it.
Oh, that's okay.
I'll just, uh, wait, I'm going to organize a little bit real
quick.
come to the blacksmith and then let me put the ingots back
you can craft anything you want let me put the ingots back
so you'll be able to use them oh my gosh thank you so much
for the gifted thank you oh you can make an iron hand
crossbow too what do i want yeah we don't have enough for
the other stuff i think you should look at the double
daggers since you love them yeah and Maybe mace is more.
I might do the mace.
The iron.
I need four iron ingot.
Okay.
Yeah.
It pulls it automatically.
Oh, it doesn't for me.
Oh, there.
Now it is.
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh, it's because you probably opened it before I put it in
the chest.
Oh, probably.
Okay.
I have it.
And then here, here, here.
Let me draw these things for you.
So all of these is like for when your things break behind
you.
Thank you.
Like you said, it's going to have like a big...
big red X on it so you'll see yeah yeah yeah yeah I like my
I'll do a sword I'll be a basic basic girl you didn't like
your axe it's because it's two-handed so I couldn't use like
now I can use my oh yeah yeah there's a iron short bow and
then there's also a little bit of armor that we can craft as
well if uh if that sparks your your joy where do you see
that underway uh so under underwear underwear offers an
armorer's workbench okay okay we just gotta craft it oh my
bad yeah move it oh oh the farmer first no built no uh
armored armorer we need a two copper ingot oh i have more
copper ore let me uh okay cook it cook it we must cook mint
yes like enough that I get the meme but not enough to like
get all the yeah I get it I know I know like you know the
premise yeah and they literally cook in the desert oh I
think we only have enough like one big armor because we
don't have enough light letter but that's okay that's okay I
will let you pick the armor that you want to make no no no I
it's okay you you you right Can I pick the armor?
Yeah, you pick the armor.
Okay.
You do it.
It's gonna hide my beautiful body.
It's gonna hide my beautiful bosom, but...
Okay, I'm gonna put this giant statue down so that I don't
carry it anymore.
And our wardrobe that you requested.
It's a pretty wardrobe.
But they're like only...
They don't hide...
They don't hold anything.
It's just for cosmetic.
Oh, what that?
It kind of looks like my old friend.
little bit i have ears like that too oh still it looks like
my old friend doesn't look like you okay your old friend
you're so done with my shit okay okay okay i'm gonna put a
great grandma look look this is you you're the small one i'm
the big one and i'm wearing the same armor and i have a
sword oh my god it is us oh i like how you just left the
giant axe don't you like store it so just in case things do
almost it's almost broken oh is it okay whatever i don't i
don't love it love it okay oh she she hates it she hates it
you guys she hates it i need but i didn't love it love it
you know well now we have some more space yeah we do that
i'm that you're instantly okay that's fine Sorry, girl.
Okay, okay.
Okay, do something in the other chest.
I'm giving you permission.
I just want to leave the lettuce because I don't need it.
Let you say?
Let you say.
What does a chitin do?
Oh, resilient material.
We're going to be able to upgrade.
So if you come to the tanning rack and you take a look at
it, on the right side, it's going to be tier two
requirements.
Oh, I see, I see.
Make me better armor.
We need tier two.
Okay, okay.
Wait, it says out of 16.
Do you have some in...
No, no, no, no.
That's all the stuff that we have.
Oh, no, I meant like, okay, good.
I can put it, I combined it in one of the chests is what I
meant.
Because I was like, I only had seven.
So I was like, either you are holding on to some or in the
chest nearby.
What?
Six, seven?
It's like the cool thing.
I've never heard that before.
Can you make a salvager?
We could, but what's the point?
We're just adventuring.
Yeah, six, seven is like...
the cool people say like the cool old people like me we say
six seven i've literally i don't even know what you're
talking about right now it looks like you're gonna hit me
with that block you're like come here i'm sorry can you like
turn around
all right girl are you ready for adventuring did that camel
just go into that hole no yeah oh my god he did it did he
just do that oh my god wait don't kill Why are you killing
him?
What's wrong with him?
Because I wonder if he's going to drop the chitney.
You're a psychopath.
But I'm your psychopath.
Oh, whoop.
Alrighty.
Are we ready?
Oh, wait.
I want to cook my meat real quick.
You haven't cooked your meat yet, girl?
No.
Okay.
I'm doing it real fast.
Real fast.
And I'm going to take some of the...
oh wait i'm gonna take some of the stuff from the oh my god
it doesn't take half take one oh take half shift okay okay
these are for you what what did you give me so that when you
when you use your swords whoa look at my hand i know camels
well wait a second i know camels don't drop chitin i just
want to kill him i want to look at you oh you look so cool
that actually looks really cool to cook the meat that it
dropped?
Ah, I want to cook the meat that it dropped.
Oh.
Thanks.
Yep.
I just yoink your meat, girl.
Oh, stop yoinking my meat!
Oh my god!
She's yoinking my meat!
Don't yoinking my meat!
Alright.
Actually, I'll give you something.
No, it's okay.
It's okay.
Wait, wait.
Where did I put it?
blood for the blood take half i have one here you can have
11.
oh what do i have one oh my god i do see a tent over here i
want to get to it i'm just going she's yoinking a desolate
basin we're in an even different place we call my womb
the way you said i'm so sorry The way you just turned
around, I can feel the judgment from like your character.
It's just a call for help.
Oh, look at the little oasis here.
Is it actual?
And maybe you're gonna be the one that saves me.
Okay.
Guys, I'm regretting this collab.
And after this, oh.
I wonder...
I want to rob whatever's here.
Yeah, me too.
Tap the soap on.
I think more people should steal.
I agree.
Oh, did we have a campfire?
Because you can steal these people's campfire, too.
Ooh, fiche.
Yummy.
Yoink.
I love when you...
Oh, yeah.
Let's...
Wait, wait, wait.
There's two pets.
Let's take him just in case he get too far from our base.
And we're like, we need a bird to see that.
Yeah, yeah.
noise noise set it up whoa yeah let's keep going there's
like a big castle and then oh we're gonna hit the edge of
the water what's that mean oh is this the castle here means
I hope you know how to swim girl do you yeah I'm not very
well yeah yeah that's another yeah oh I see over here
structure that looks awesome swimming wait that looks so
cool yeah guys she's starting to bug me please i can bug you
anytime i know that's the that's the problem i need i need
my space you're living a regular life i show up cockroaches
everywhere i saw that clip of you oh did you hear that yeah
i heard that it was like
what am i i'm going up i'm going up oh my god he's casting
spells of me Oh, no, he's not.
I'm lying.
Shadow, wizard, money, gang.
We love casting spells.
Wait, he's not attacking me, though.
Oh, he's, like, leaving.
Are you okay?
Are you killing this man for no reason?
Oh, he's like, he's actually leaving.
I'm not touching him.
Yeah, you scared him.
He's like, oh, it's a woman.
Oh, no, he's attacking me.
He's attacking me.
I was like, it's a lady.
I'm out.
He's a wizard.
So, you know how men become wizards?
Oh, they're everywhere.
It's not a bad thing.
Oh, they're, like, making a lot of noise around here.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, my God.
Grandpa.
I'm going to help.
Uh-oh.
I'm not able to collect their memories.
Were you attacking me?
I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
There's a guy.
There was a skeleton under you attacking you.
And I was killing him.
Nice.
Oh.
Oh, did I?
Okay.
No, I genuinely did not mean it as a negative in this place.
I know.
I know you did.
But good patch.
So just in case.
Because, you know, sometimes I've always...
There's copper two-handed daggers.
Oh, man.
I just made the better ones, though.
No, you did, yeah.
I made the better ones.
I'm going to keep you here.
Oh, my God.
It's like grandpa everywhere.
Oh, my gosh.
My dream grandpa's everywhere.
God, I love the sound of breaking things.
Copper helm.
Oh, this is for my head.
Yeah, because yours is going to break soon, right?
It looks like it.
Yeah.
Wait, it says zero out of 50.
Does that mean it's broken?
Oh, yeah.
It means it's broken.
I'll just put on the other one.
I look like I look really stupid with this one oh they're
all these zombies are like a little they're agra they feel a
little stronger than the previous actually I feel like super
strong now like I'm not gonna lie I think I'm like I think
I'm like crazy now I mean I don't know how to tell you this
girl but you you no I'm like super strong I like I just
really I like unlocked a new level of power.
My power level is like insane.
But Tara, I'm at spawn.
Like.
No, did you not take a bed?
I did.
I did in our little fort.
No.
I wonder because the bed is a whip.
You know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to die.
And I'll spawn back with you and we can re-adventure.
Are you sure?
Yeah, of course.
What if you...
spawn back at your bed though let me well then we're gonna
find out if you occupied your bed okay let me die i did
occupy okay i did oh i wonder if it's because it's the whip
area no all right let me see where i respawn oh hi baby what
if we explore the other way i have i agree like this way to
like get our stuff right yeah i really do think that it's
because we um maybe because we did it in the whip whip area
oh yeah we had no idea how would we have no wait i think i
see another whip area happy little accidents right right now
we can explore a whole other area sorry but that was comedy
gold where you're like i feel not me i feel stronger i
actually feel like i'm so Take the whip.
Take the whip.
How dare this area betray us?
It was our little...
It was our little treasure.
Our little...
It was our cottage.
It was our home away from home.
It was our perfect.
It was so good.
It was where we do the heated rivalry.
Oh.
Have you watched that?
No, but it's all over my...
Oh my gosh, wait.
I actually have to send you this podcast.
Okay.
It's two guys that play hockey.
They're two straight guys.
and they're watching the show and they're talking about each
episode they're basically like going run of run of each
episode it's called empty netters it's so entertaining
watching these two straight men being like okay and then he
just you know going in i mean that's what they do have you
watched it no i haven't i i will send you that podcast just
like watch the first episode of it next time you're like
cooking or cleaning or doing something.
I'll listen, yeah.
I just know that it like...
But I don't know anything about, like, the plot.
I'll give you the TLDR.
It's kind of based on, like, Ovechkin and Sidney Crosby.
So it's, like, the number one and the number two prospect.
They're hockey men.
It's based on, like, the number one and the number two
prospect in hockey.
And basically, like, their whole thing is, like, they're
rivals, right?
so they're not and then they're also gay which at that time
in hockey like you know it's it's still to this day like
there's not a lot of openly gay players in hockey right um
because it's you know whatever whichever um i mean i think
gay marriage only got legalized in canada like less than 10
years ago or maybe 10 years ago maybe like 2008 or something
anyway i digress so then they you know spoiler alert they
kiss and do other things no no no one of them's russian oh
because one of them's the number one he's from russia and
the number two he's canadian damn no canada's got to step it
up they do they're number two number two wait this house is
like inside the ground i'm robbing it anyway i'm still gonna
steal i think they're dead so i think it's fine to rob yeah
you know what are we wait are we grave rob oh my god mint
i'm gonna have a curse just like you now yeah we're grave
robbing wait i see something over here you know yeah
genuinely as a friend but also a little bit content brained
you should find a curse breaker a curse break from the fun
of it you should find a curse break because look whether you
believe in curses or not doesn't matter but like you know
maybe if you oh my god he summoned the wolves no he's
summoning the wolves he's summoning the wolves oh oh he hits
hard oh my god the Oh my god.
I got you, I got you.
Use poison.
Make sure to eat food.
I'm trying.
Back up and eat food.
Okay.
He summoned the wolf.
I saw that.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
What's killing me?
Oh, I think it might be the poison.
I bet.
Oh my god.
I'm gonna die again.
Every time I take a bite.
Okay.
Goodbye all my food.
Oh, wait, mint.
Oh my god.
There's shoes here for you.
Oh, I got shoes!
You get cool shoes, not just any shoes, cool shoes.
Oh my god.
Dubey gets shoes.
Dubey.
Oh, there's a crude battle axe, mate.
I don't want battle axe.
Dubey gets the way of shoes.
Oh, I lost my old...
Wait, I do have my old hat.
Yippee!
Broken, though, at this point.
Oh, it's so broken.
But yeah, you know what I mean?
Like, whether people believe in curses or not, you jokingly,
you know, believe that you have a curse or you do.
find a curse breaker right like it's do you think i could
find one on fiver okay not that content brain like maybe
let's like dial it back a little bit on the content all
right guys so today i'm hiring 10 curse makers from fiver
yeah maybe not like that for those who don't know i'm i'm
cursed because my mom went to the desert and touched i think
you should tell them the story yeah Well, it's pretty short.
My mom went to the desert and touched...
By the way, I think we should start this.
I'll shut up.
Okay, okay, okay.
Call that for real, for real.
It was pretty funny watching your character just be like,
oh, yeah, we went to the desert mom touched the sand and
then they were like don't touch the sand and then my mom
brought the sand home oh my god they said don't touch the
sand because specifically if if like the sand is cursed or
like there's a curse yeah yeah they were like a sacred sand
don't touch it oh no i lost my epic item of the heart of the
void no it's back in the whip we can we can get it back oh
we could like walk all the way over there i don't know what
i'm seeing but it looks like a creeper you know what else
you could do as well you could probably um oh careful
careful yeah i'm listening probably also contact like if you
like find that tour group or those people oh this guy was
tough let's oh yeah it's him it's him it's him okay be
careful which way we can get the heart back no it wasn't him
that dropped the heart it was i think it was oh oh is it no
essence of the void how did i get that the floating guy you
killed 10 man oh shut up wow such good luck all right come
here this is like the luckiest night ever i know hold on let
me pull the little guy that's lurking behind first because
he's gonna jump up at us when we least expect it oh this guy
the tentacle guy is like hiding away so far yeah i wonder
let me try to aggro him okay okay i'm eating real quick
eating i'm eating while you fight i eat yeah Sounds like I'm
eating like popcorn, so funny.
I'm trying to like jump attack him like it's Elden Ring, but
no.
He's like not getting aggroed.
He's tired.
Don't aggro on me, please.
Aggro on Matara.
Okay, okay, wait.
I have an idea.
All right.
Oh!
Did it work?
No, but like that might be the strat.
Wait, if we could just like keep doing that.
Yeah, I think I'm just gonna like...
Yeah, wait, we just make a platform?
No, make it too taller.
We're not going to be able to jump up.
Oh, yeah, I wonder if he's bugged or something.
Ha, bugged.
Oh, I can't reach him with my daggers.
You know what?
Let me...
It's all you.
Wait, hold on.
Oh.
Just build it closer to him.
Oh, nice!
Oh, he didn't draw off the heart thing.
Aw, man.
Creeper, ah, me.
You need to, like, find, like, the tour guide or, find
somebody from the area and be like hey i need help story i
need yeah i need help all right let's go wait mint we're
going the wrong way let's go over to the blue wood do you
see it on your map the blue wood oh two m and there's blue
wood wait i see it where i see red no i'm in n okay look to
the left of i need to see what the hell you're seeing on
your stream why is your do scroll wheel to zoom out of the
map.
Ah.
You're so silly.
This whole time I'm like, no offense, but I was a little bit
like, damn, like, we don't have to play dumb, man.
Like, come on.
Why is it because you resumed in?
You're so cute.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
I thought you were kind of like play faking it, you know?
No, I think you're saying that I'm still playing dumb.
I think you're saying that I'm still playing dumb.
I just think you, sometimes you don't play, you know?
She don't play.
What the hell is that?
These guys are so scary.
I think these are the creepiest things in the game so far.
I think the creepiest thing in the game is wearing a little
maid outfit.
I think the creepiest thing in the game is...
You know you're annoying, but like the other person doesn't
even grace me with her.
They're like, I'm...
I think you're the most annoying thing.
in the game i think it's just you i don't think i think it's
oh we're going the wrong way are we yes oh i didn't i
thought that now that you had a map you know you were gonna
no i was fine wait i think i see hold on another there's
another guy yeah yeah yeah oh and there's a little oh he's
aggroed he's aggroed he's aggroed oh shoot and he's aggroed
on me he's aggroed on me okay am i gonna get the big bite
okay oh my god i'm gonna go to oh my god also the sword is
easier to not hit you because it's like oh did you get kill
him yeah i did oh damn i don't know how we got the heart
last time i think it's a rare yeah a rare drop oh my god
that background ain't got me okay uh so let's go the other
way because this is where we just came from yeah i was just
looking at this thing okay uh yeah yeah let's go i can't
wait oh you did it so good it's my secret skill big boy big
boy i need your help okay oh
this game is like kind of op if you have friends you know
because all you have to do is block and they don't get
aggroed on you if you attack them so it's like you just have
to like have somebody else attack from behind for you it's
kind of awesome all the wists are playing together i already
know all the mommos too wait there's like something oh it's
another flying blue guy never mind oh there's a couple now
wait what the heck yes because it's nighttime maybe yeah i
wonder wait try to put your bed on the floor and see if we
can just sleep here i don't have a bed oh well um oh yes i
do just kidding have a bed yeah come on put your bed
Oh, you took my bed.
Let's go!
My very important bed.
Oh, he's still spawned.
I guess they may be like take a while to do spawn because we
are- Maybe because he was already spawned in.
Oh, no, wait.
Oh, no, he's still there.
just kidding so this is like redwood and then there's
bluewood further out he's coming on me he's coming in thank
you welcome what did i say don't worry about it okay
ouchy this feels just like canada oh what do you say in
canada you say night no you don't say mate okay you say I we
say I genuinely say a a oh wait there's a little tree house
yeah there's a house wait wait there's like a hole wait I
think this is a fortress or something oh let's rob it I
think a guy is sleeping down there there's a little skeleton
defending his outpost outlander berserker oh get him okay
whoa he's like the most humanoid thing oh shit he hits hard
okay help uh maybe oh shaman oh i'm dead i'm at spawn are
you are you far i don't know check how far it is because i
can run back to you it's probably not that far because we
barely i feel like we mostly side come this way come to
where i am on the map you will see me i don't see it i think
where did i it's not showing where i died um okay so that
blue wood that you see it's the it's the further one it's
the one more up top this one right more up top of it like
there's a this one no up top oh oh i see i see i see oh my
god okay i think if you start running it won't be too too
far running running but let's maybe okay i see a bed i'm
gonna steal again and then we're gonna steal another bed
from the orcs we can do like a temporary base at the orc
camp let's get into the habit of doing it i'm so not used to
having the compass up top so i just don't look at it my
brain is still in minecraft mode but like i'm not used to
following directions nope said min that's what she said
that's exactly what i said that's exactly what i said and I
was saying that sounds my yep except for standing is like
people sitting typically because she's very short that's not
even this is not how height works no my god wait I'm going
the wrong wait we just looted here I'm gonna see if there's
a bed I have one I just you know because we picked it up
yeah we should we should always keep a bed like on a so we
can see but yeah i wish you could have more spawn points
like i wish we could be like mint bed one i know right but i
guess that's too easy too easy too easy what is that oh it's
a mushroom all right there's no beds here how did these orcs
live they're savage i think i literally saw him laying on
the ground yeah okay okay i hear the judgment in your voice
by the way I can hear it.
This is true bachelor living.
Just a mattress on the ground.
Oh, I see you.
You're close.
Yeah, yeah, I'm not so far.
But I'm afraid of the berserker.
Oh, how, how, how, how.
Is that the music you're hearing?
Okay.
It came from my imagination.
My delusions are whispering.
Yeah.
That's what Matara's like, get ready with me theme song.
oh my god that is actually such a great idea you're like all
right get ready with me everybody and it's like get ready
with me to go to war
or like oh that's you oh hi
where was it far from here uh the blue thing no it's like
right up here no but my stuff oh yeah your map i should show
you where you died no yeah i'm going to it but i'm scared
just stay close where are you wait i'm coming i'm running
i'm running i'm running i'm running stay close stay close
stay close stay close stay close on top of me on top of me
oh wait but the blue forest is right here too so it's it's
fine yeah it's perfect oh wait man man man man man man man
man look look look look look look what look there's people
and they're dressed i know that's the guy that killed me
that's the guy that killed me oh all right well you know
what let's let's go oh let's get him yeah oh okay frost
march tundra we'll behind you we'll behind oh shoot two
double
nice nice oh wait i'm almost dead i'm almost dead i know
they're hot back and up they hit hard I got him.
Good, good, good.
Okay.
Let me...
Ooh!
That was good.
Scared.
There's some more stuff in that chest I couldn't grab.
Oh, they're coming.
They're coming.
Where?
Oh, it's the wizard guy.
Shadow wizard money gang?
Yep.
He loves casting spells.
What the hell?
Who is that?
Okay, there's a spellcaster and an archer.
Let me go up and around.
Yeah.
Let's ambush them from behind.
Oh, yeah, they're here.
Oh my god, they have a revival.
I know, wait, this is so cute.
They're so, like, cottage core.
What is this?
They are, but, like, evil cottage, like, you know.
Yeah, yeah, evil cottage.
I feel like we should take their home.
I agree.
Well, they're going to keep spawning, so I don't know.
Or we could just annihilate them and their bloodline.
I love that.
I think you're thinking in portals now, with portals.
Yeah.
they're dead oh they got some chilies that's why they're so
sad there's a shield do you want the shield i want to wear
my torch but actually i could wear the shield that's
actually probably a good idea yeah give me the shield okay
okay i just almost died by falling down okay don't do that
don't do that again i also got the cobalt ore what is this
okay wait this cottage core is i told
like i noticed it very quickly because i was in the middle
of fighting but now that i have the time are you sure it's
not like volcano ash and we're about to get um like i think
it's snowy not wazuvius you know pompeyed pompey we might be
this is the ashes of the people that's literally what i
titled this the stream whatever you close it oh no i hope
that's their song name pompey otherwise i poison oh my oh
wait copper daggers hmm yeah yeah your dagger is better yeah
i made it with love wait but they're the same energy but uh
they do more damage durability or oh tin is tin is uh better
than copper okay or maybe it's iron i forget but it's better
oh my god look there's even an owl there's i know the little
owls are so cute this place is awesome give me your shield
Oh, did I take it?
Yeah, here it is.
There you go.
Whoa, did you see the poison log?
Yeah, I wanted to grab it.
I'm grabbing it.
Grab it.
Oh, and I have seven arrows.
Oh, thank you.
If you want them.
You can give them to me.
Here, take.
Thank you.
Doomed Outlander Shield Rare.
Okay, this actually looks like...
Yeah, I know.
It looks legit.
Real good.
Yeah.
Wait, how do I proper equip it?
Wait, is it already equipped it?
No, you were holding it.
Wait.
Right?
wait um but i wasn't like shield holding it wait where did
it go oh wait did i drop it did you accidentally pick it up
check no i don't have it i it's not in my inventory anymore
oh i put it in my z slot okay okay good good good and then
my where's okay this place is so cute okay yeah i have the
shield okay are we ready to go to blue forest Yeah, I'm
ready to go to Blue Forest.
Yeah, let's go.
Let's blue.
My sneaky girl.
Whoa, the trees grow all funky.
It's so cool.
Hey, where are you?
I'm in the Blue Forest.
Whoa!
I must ask one thing of our audiences.
Okay.
I want them to spin.
Momo spin.
Minto's, if you have a spin emote or any...
Oh, my God.
Spin that guy.
We're spinning.
Why did he quack?
They're spinning.
We're spinning.
Look at the blueberries.
Oh, what the hell was...
Oh, there's a snake.
It's an azure fruit.
Oh, it's these things.
Oh, wow.
Oh, the music in here is so nice.
We definitely got to chop some of these trees to take home.
Do you hear the music?
Wait, not yet.
Not yet.
It hasn't kicked in.
I'm feeling cottage core.
Oh, my God.
Let's chop some of these bad boys to keep for our house.
There's spinning.
spin i don't think we have a spin sorry guys no because it's
youtube i'm sorry
oh my god wow i was thinking the one thing that like
minecraft really does so well that everyone like is that
makes it so memorable is the music and so i was curious what
like the soundtrack would be in the game this is very
minecraft this music right yeah it's so cute it's so sweet
and the berries we can cook them too i think so you're gonna
cook very bug yeah no oh yeah actually yeah i'm gonna eat
that bug yeah eat that bug i'm glad i didn't get to meet her
yeah soon i gotta i gotta like fight to the death there can
only be one bug in your life i wish there were Who do you
think would win in a fist fight?
Me or Barry?
You.
Good.
That's what I wanted to hear.
Thank you for involving me.
Good.
Don't you forget.
Kalib, that sent it to Barry.
I think she knows.
Okay.
Oh, my gosh.
I am not a lover.
I am not a fighter, but I will fight.
I don't think there's, like, any structures in there.
this forest though okay it's just beautiful it is very
beautiful let's go to the water to see if there's going to
be anything by the water okay there's also like really tall
mountains by too oh we can go we can go oh i see the
mountain yeah the mountain is bio hear that berry i invite
you one v one me i want to see this we'll be in bikinis oh
just for you i did not ask okay we won't be in bikinis
you'll be in bikinis we could or we could not i don't know
well you already offered i think you can't go back on your
word now i think the momos wasn't sure if you were like
against it so i you know just in case you're like very prude
about it no when since when oh these aren't as tall as i
thought they would be i missed the music of the of the
tranquil forest right it's okay oh there's a white owl a
white owl oh my god they're so cute they're like little
they're just little squares with wings we can i'm telling
you later in the game you can like make a box and steal them
okay i want to see a prop there's like a winter mountain you
Click M.
Zoom out.
Like north?
Yeah, north.
Actually, where I'm staring.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's north.
There's ice down there.
Ice.
I want to see if it does something funny.
Or like if it's going to, you know like in Minecraft, when
you break ice, it's like ding, ding.
Yeah.
Aw.
No?
No sound?
Oh, it's actually kind of ASMR.
Yeah, that's kind of nice.
Oh, it's mint!
What?
The music!
I don't hear anything.
Wait till it starts.
Also, you're like sliding.
I know, so are you.
Listen to the music.
It's so good.
It's going to start for you in a moment.
It's mysterious.
You hear it?
It's so good.
It's like Harry Potter-esque a little bit.
yeah yeah but also like the nutcracker aspect yeah yeah so
let's fight this bear oh okay
i think i think i took way more damage from you than i did
but i didn't even strike yes you did okay i strike one time
i hit once are we running the right way i hit we're going
north we're going north Okay, see, this is why I'm glad I
taught you how to read the map.
Yeah, now I know.
Now I know.
Whoa, another thing.
Oh, bear.
Bear and another cottage core.
So we got to be careful that.
Oh, okay.
He's aggroed on you.
He's aggroed on me.
Kill him.
Why are you killing him so slow?
Okay, thank you.
I'm doing my bear as well.
I don't have two daggers.
I got one.
It should do as much damage.
Whoa, it's like an ice wall.
What is this?
The titans, the giants.
Oh my god.
Humanity received a grave reminder.
I'm digging up.
We're in the boreal reach.
Whoa.
One woman's trance is another woman's trance.
Hello, little owl.
Who are you?
You didn't even rob these people.
You changed.
I am in a blizzard right now.
You don't understand.
I like it's a literal blizzard.
It says you can ride like a three six.
I don't know.
I wonder if I can like it.
What's the word?
Like cold.
Ah, brr.
Ah, it's quite chilly.
I made it a ladder, but you know, whatever.
Oh, you did.
Sorry.
Yeah.
How do you think I got up here?
Uh, magic?
Wait, the blizzard stop.
Of course, as soon as you're here.
Wee!
Oh, you can hear the wind noises.
Wait, I see something over here.
Where, where, where?
I think it's a polar bear.
Wait, there's also...
There's, like, wolves and stuff.
There's special animals.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, it's an Arctic wolf.
It's gonna attack us.
No, I think that's a saber game.
Look at his big teeth.
It's a snow leopard.
Leopard.
Oh, sorry.
I did.
Yeah.
My bad.
Because we're icy.
We're slicing.
We're sliding.
Oh, it's a little funky.
Yeah.
Ooh.
The music is so, like, whimsical.
And we're, like, slicing.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
He's creepy.
Oh, he's on you.
He's on you.
Sometimes it won't let you, like, uh...
Walk?
Yeah.
It's not because I'm low stamina either.
Like, I'm pressing it even when my stamina is high.
You knew what I was going to say.
I did.
You preemptively answered me.
You said block.
That's what I was thinking.
Where are we?
We're just on this ice, icy area.
And it's so icy.
Come out, sleep, buddy.
Oh, careful.
Yeah.
What is that up there?
That's another biome we haven't been in yet.
Let's go.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, oh, oh geez.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm, are you here?
Come, come on my slot and then I'm just gonna take out.
All right.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Mint?
Where'd you go?
Oh my god, my world like...
Did you just clip out of the world the way you were?
Mint?
I like crack the game for a second.
Okay, for some reason I am on the other edge of the cliff.
Look at your map.
Oh, I see you!
I see you!
Okay, so it was like a weird glitch of sorts or like...
It was so weird.
It like glitched.
You want me to...
Well, we were going to explore over here, so I guess I'll
just wait over here.
Wait, let me see where I'm going.
Am I the blue or by the way?
Oh, I'm the blue.
Okay, you're your own blue.
You're your own blue.
Okay, wait.
I'm going to go back up and just come to you, okay?
Okay.
I think it's going to be easier than, like, running around.
That was crazy.
That was really funny to watch.
What happened to you when that happened?
It just, you just popped that out of existence, like,
nothing.
Okay, let me come to you.
It literally, like, was glistening.
It was so...
Oh!
Sorry, once again.
It was...
scary i bought my game crash at least my time guys is this
like an optimal high tail first experience like you're
seeing all these biomes we're taking you around you're
seeing everything wait what did i oh a little piglet i don't
want to be cocky but i think it's an amazing i'm telling you
i played before and i was like it's okay and now i'm like
wait this is the best i think yeah like we're like giving
you the grand tour everybody we are the experience the
experience I'm watching like a goat in the distance like
spin around.
They're really funny.
Yeah.
Oh wait, there's like a, I see if, is that fire?
Maybe not.
I don't know.
Look at these fishy.
Okay, I'm close to you.
I'm coming.
Okay, I'm taking a dip.
Oh, that could have been really bad if I died.
Don't die?
I see you.
Don't die, don't die.
oh my god the rabbits screech you guys have moved as fast
and as destructive as the mongol hordes yes so we are gangus
matara khan and gangus mint phantom khan yeah that's us
gangus matara khan just works too well no relation though
absolutely not i'm glad that it like spawned you on the
other side of the cliff though it could have been much
worse.
Yeah.
Could have spawned me in the lava.
Yeah, this is cool.
Now this area isn't named anything.
Did it pop up anything?
It didn't pop anything for me.
No, it didn't for me either.
Oh, there's like a skelly guy.
Skelly, skelly man.
He's going to shoot you.
I know.
Nice.
I clicked.
I forgot that my...
There we go.
There's another fortress up top.
We're getting close to it.
you want to go yes oh i see it yeah oh wow look at the snow
tree oh look at the snowy trees in the distance oh my gosh
they're so cute and like a billion archer skeletons yeah
these guys are annoying okay oh you had the ones on you okay
yeah luckily they died okay hey hey hey why are you running
he's like oh my god it's gangas but dark god and i can't
just oh don't go so Oh my god!
I didn't realize!
I'm so sorry!
Oh, yeah, you hit... Oh.
Do you need a coconut?
Yeah, well I have some.
Do you remember previously where we fought the guys?
We had a different banner.
They had a blue banner.
These guys have a purple banner.
Look how cool this looks.
We're just coming in.
They're like, they have...
None the wiser.
These guys are...
Oh, wait.
These are the berserkers.
Oh, shoot.
They're all coming in.
Wait, let's...
Wait, this is pretty bad.
Oh, shit.
This is pretty... Wait, where are you?
Yeah.
Let's... Wait, wait.
Let's run out and, like, get them to run at us.
Oh, shoot.
Okay.
My bad.
You're right.
We should have...
Oh!
Uh-oh.
I'm running.
Oh, I also died.
Oh, man.
Man.
What do we do?
You want to run one more way, or do you want to call it?
Let me look at the map real quick, because...
Wow.
I feel like... We can run to the right.
I feel like we've seen a great amount of it, but you're
right.
We haven't gone to the right.
it we can go to the right and then call it whenever yeah
yeah yeah okay so i did i did tell my mom was and i told you
a little bit but um i talked to somebody about a commission
and they said yes yeah and how they emailed me back and it's
like half the price that i thought i was gonna be oh no and
i'm just like i think we should follow this oh no we should
where are you we haven't gone this way just straight yeah i
think it like leads to the ocean i wonder if there's like
big oceans in this like with minecraft you know what they
say about big oceans what i don't know oh i was asking you
big discoveries big discoveries oh okay these guys were high
level yeah they were crazy yeah you guys there was a little
fewer of them we could have like one by one got them yeah
they're like they hit so hard like you definitely need a
better armor and everything going into them but whatever
we're just playing around today also there's bear traps that
you can put so we like you made them with the tin ore so you
could have like put bear traps and then have them walk into
them or like set fires for example oh my god oh yeah the
fires yeah would be good you're so cute running through the
field la la la la la la la la la la la la la la committing
crimes yeah pillaging and together looting oh wait i think i
see a new biome i had such a fun time playing this like
exploring around if you just do with the digging and oh by
the way you can ride the horse if you press f when you're
behind them the big one yeah oh well god come come come come
here horse but the only you dismount him he'll run away so
horse oh my god horse yeah you got him you got him yeah you
go you can jump on them too ah wait yeah just if you
dismount oh my god min this is amazing let's go wait whoa oh
open your map oh you see it what is this you see it what the
hell oh god this is
trees there i know you think we can take our horse oh my god
the crab there's a crab oh my horse can swim your horse can
swim do you want to go yes okay yes i would like to go to
the hot to the hell island i would like to visit take me to
that danger zone danger down wow crystalline depths I wonder
if this is where we'll find some of the like the uh the ones
like the Leviathan kind of like that or whatever they were
the abyssal type they said or something.
So I think we have to like dig up here.
Let me see around the music.
Not yet.
It's just like an ambiance.
Oh, oh, we can come up here.
Okay, okay.
But they have like a little armor there, I think or
something.
Oh, bleach town.
Uh oh.
Oh.
ew did he push me off what did he do or did i push myself
off i think you just it looked like you just walked off oh
okay he can attack me on my horse hold on can i use my
weapon when i'm on the horse no i can't i can't either let's
go around and see if there's like another little yeah an
easy way that's not being spawned by a guy i can't believe
our horses are just like swimming so funny
and then like dig up.
No, I don't think so.
I don't think we should do that.
Oh, my horse has spawned!
What?
Why did you- Yeah!
Okay, this is good that- or maybe I pressed F.
This is good.
This means I can mine.
Why did your- wait, you- that means you pressed F and you
killed your horse.
Maybe I pressed F.
Whop, whop.
It's okay, girl.
I did it so I can mine for you.
Okay, okay.
I'm looking- I'm going around.
I'm looking for like a way up.
Jump here.
Wait, where?
Where- where I am.
Okay.
around.
There was a little copper.
You'll see me.
Can we get some F for the horse, please?
I'm sorry.
I'm so dystopic.
Can we get some F for the horse, please?
Aw, so sad.
Wait, my horse can't jump up.
You can't jump up there?
Yeah, oh, let me mine the block up.
Hold on.
Yeah, make me a staircase, please.
I require a grand entrance.
You don't jump up that block?
No.
Oh, yay.
Oh, okay, one second.
Can you jump up that block?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Hold on.
Let me...
I can't see anything.
Why is it so dark?
Oh, there we go.
Alright, I'm going to make you a slow staircase.
Okay.
Yeah, jump up here.
And then here and up here and to the...
Oh, okay.
Careful.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
I'm going to try to not jump next to the water.
Don't worry.
Okay.
I'm going to dig a...
Okay, up here.
Why is the sky red?
Don't worry about it.
We'll be fine.
Do you need an extra block of height for the horse or you're
fine?
I might.
I can't get up on...
You can get up on that.
Oh, here.
Okay, come up here.
Okay.
There's an attempt happening.
Okay, there we go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
All right.
I'm right behind you.
Actually, I'm stuck again.
I need you to mine this block.
Ouch, ouch.
Ouch.
I need you to mine this one again.
My head is too tall.
You're too tall.
You're too sexy.
Nope, I need again.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right, we're almost there.
We're almost there.
I'm scared because it's dark and I'm scared.
Okay.
I need you to, I need help.
I need healing, I need help.
actually out of my cinder wastes oh my god we're in a
devastated land oh mine up on mine up in a
second okay come here i like how the horse is just making
noises is it i can't even hear it almost up we're almost up
up out you'll be careful sorry sorry okay i think we're
gonna die here
TikTok audio that's trending right now.
That's like the, I think I'm going to die in this house.
Yeah, no.
Did they use it?
Oh, I think they're close.
We're good.
Oh, yeah, I see.
Okay, I'm out.
Are you good?
Nope.
Took them out.
Wait.
Nope.
Help.
We're good.
Whoa.
Just don't fart.
Don't go too far without me.
Don't fart.
Fart, please.
Oh, mint.
There's a big guy.
Okay.
I see him.
You're definitely going to die here.
I think if we run past them, we could, like, go to the other
side.
There's water down there.
Don't.
Oh, there's guys down there, too.
Okay, I'm getting off my horse.
I'm going to get off my high horse.
Put your bed here.
How do I...
Actually, how do I get off of him?
Press F.
Okay.
No, put your bed here.
No, he aggroed on me.
Hold on, I'm going to put my bed down here.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I can jump down to you.
That is so funny.
I can't.
I can't believe that.
I have to pee.
I'm going to piss myself.
Oh my god, laughing like that.
I'm like, okay, I got to be...
Hold on one second.
I'm going to like wall myself in.
Okay, okay.
I think if you go back to the water and swim back around to
where I am.
Okay.
Oh my god.
Okay, this guy is beautiful.
I'm making some food real quick and then I'm going to...
I'll swim over there.
Give me one second.
I got to pee because if that happens again...
That was so fun.
How did that happen?
The water.
All right.
one moment okay my place is work in progress everybody um i
think i'm in trouble um um um i think i'm in trouble how did
i live i felt it like kicked me into the water i got gold
shipped
i'm in danger I'm gonna repair okay wait use repair items
will how do I use it how do I use the repair kit on my
daggers oh I see if I right-click while holding it I can
repair my iron daggers okay I'm gonna go see if it's safe is
that a guy right there waiting by the entrance for me um
it's not safe he's waiting right there do you see that where
my mouse is oh that was a bat just kidding i see like his uh
i think it's him the bats are scaring me
Not him.
No, it's definitely.
Wait.
Yeah, it's definitely him.
Right there.
Wait, no, that's a hide.
Wait, whose eyes are these?
Wait, is that a person?
I don't think so.
Maybe not.
Wait, did he die?
Did he die?
Wait, who died?
Wait, there's a meat.
Ah, it's a rat!
Ah!
Stupid.
Okay.
That about, don't say that about me.
Why would you say that?
see that about me i wasn't even here man i'm i am fighting
for my life here okay like i can come to you in a second
hold on you are you're gonna come here oh my god yay i'm
gonna come i'm gonna find you i'm not gonna lie the horse
knocking you off was was just delightful it was so
delightfully good okay you know when like you like when a oh
wait i think i can escape from here wait if okay actually
come down here into the cave I see I see the light wait I
see the light I think I think I'll be on the other side but
anyway you know when you like let air out of a balloon
that's what the that's literally what the bats sound like no
they're like they're like oh cute one
second bring your bring your bed to actually can i pee also
yeah yeah go go go go go okay i'll keep uh and i'll and i'll
find my way to you yeah find your way to me no you can't pee
well fine i'll do it right here on my chair go go go go go
um okay i'll be right back
oh man um very quick for those of you uh the the width in
minstream since she's not here she can't yell at you for
gifting her subs and i think her subs are like three
canadian dollars there's a sub.
So I'm just saying, um, if you want to just go ahead, she
won't be able to be like, oh my god, stop.
Stop gifting, guys.
Stop, stop gifting.
Stop.
She won't be able to say, like, you're good.
I'm just saying, if you have, like, a little something, um,
feel free.
Like, she won't be able to stop you.
I am giving you.
And if she gives you trouble, be like, Matara told us to do
it.
What is she going to do?
Be mad at me?
She loves me.
Um,
you know stop stop oh my god
feel free to go crazy my loves okay let me hope that the
enemy isn't isn't right here oh wow oh my god does she even
know that some of this area is like dark dark i'm scared to
die though okay she's down here
guy that she was fighting oh i think that's the guy that got
stuck that she was fighting i wonder if i can like push him
off the cliff
oh it's like a golem guy is he stuck
it's all so dark and spooky apparently there was a rat no
that's just me don't say that about her i know she's small
don't say that about her oh there's a few guys there huh
okay so wait which way is she she's this way okay so she if
I dig down oh yeah they're like here I got to push them off
otherwise they're gonna come at me
there's a few of them yeah yeah yeah yeah I gotta be careful
oh fuck you scared me okay be careful there's like three
guys down there well I'm down oh in my area oh yeah wait
what do you mean oh my god mint there's also ghost looking
things Wait, did you leave?
No, no, no, I'm here.
I'm here.
I'm trying to get to you.
Okay.
If you look at the stuff in the water, they look like
ghosts.
It's so cute.
I'm coming in.
How do I know you're coming?
Because I'm looking at the map towards where you are.
And I'm trying to get there so the enemies don't follow me.
Wait.
Because there's like a few really strong enemies.
Okay.
So you're in front of me.
Did he push you down into the water?
Yeah.
And then I just kept going down.
mint there's a flaming skull oh um yeah uh okay let me see
wait why oh it's so the torches you have your cool pickaxe
um use use it to dig oh wait what if you dig into an enemy
though oh my god this is so scary this is actually so spooky
you can do it i did it
okay so now that i'm here where are you did you where did
you swim I wish I could see and I don't know where you swam
oh my god the music is so scary I think I'm going the other
way now hmm keep going all right let's keep going okay hold
on I have to fight the skeleton oh shit there's a wolf in
here fuck okay he's like getting my health Okay, one second.
Ow!
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm gonna find you.
Oh my God.
You gotta swim.
Okay, there's totally, I have to swim underwater.
No!
Did you place your bed though?
Oh yeah, I did place my bed, you're right.
He's like right above.
Oh my God, there's like fucking, okay.
I will die and I don't have my bed up.
Fuck that.
Oh, the music.
it's so intense sorry I gotta place my bed they killed
somewhere oh yeah I got his ears oh oh my god lucky thing I
placed my bed huh oh my god why are there so many gifts
what's happening what's going on um they decided to gift for
no reason in particular okay I'm gonna leave the cave then
okay um you're like how did you how did you swim underwater
by the way did you press a certain button to go down um i
don't know i was it was an act of desperation oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah i'm in the i'm okay they said to crouch
oh the sky is red like completely yeah it's like scary red
and like there's like scary music there's scary music
there's scary fish there's scary everything yeah oh you're
like in hold on it looks like the cave entrance is like
somewhere here crouch how oh okay hold on let me see do you
see where my bed is can you see that or no oh wait one
second let me let me get back oh my god it's so dark i can't
see anything okay one second m i'm gonna eat some press i
don't see where your bed is but i see where you are you know
what i'm gonna do mint i am going to
And it's scaring the shit out of me.
Because I don't know where they're making the noises from.
Is that...
Are you fighting someone?
No.
I'm eating pretz.
You're eating pretz.
Yummy.
What flavor?
Tomato.
They were fighting each other.
Okay.
The girls are fighting.
Oh my god.
You're going deeper into the mine, you bitch.
Come back.
Okay.
But there's like a house.
it looks like a haunted house oh what's it go face is a
haunted house yeah and your mom is a haunted house okay yeah
oh wait there's more guys like coming around by me i'm
scared oh i don't know how i'm gonna get to you i'm thinking
what's the better way i'm really glad i didn't turn on the
like lose all your items when you die yeah i think it
doesn't by default because uh yeah can you come the cave
entrance it's gonna genuinely help me find you i don't know
how to get back to the cave but like you're in the same cave
right just if you know i'm on the land i'm on the land
so i think i just have to get up where okay what i'm gonna
do is i'm gonna build my blocks to where you are i'm gonna
minecraft style it okay oh i see you i see you look up wait
what look up oh my god it's you it's you okay crouch and
then yeah just minecraft block it minecraft block it okay
this is really bad i have long nails so it's like the most
not good experience oh wait i could zoom in don't don't look
at me don't look at me while i'm doing this i'm so nervous
please don't look at me i'm looking don't look at me please
there's only like a trench behind yeah i'm about to oh oh
what was that oh it was nothing okay i'm coming back yay see
that wasn't that easy yay okay follow me bad news though
this is scary place yeah this is like make another bed oh i
can make another bed easy perfect because my bed is back
over there oh yeah yeah yeah she's gonna do it like i think
well no i was gonna say if you can can make another bed too
so that way we can like if we notice no i have no plant
fiber wait i could bring i have some plant fiber i have a
bunch wait there's probably like here too um oh yeah hold on
oh my god we're doing it girl we're doing it we're mining
and we're crafting and we're mining and we're crafting and
we're mining and we're crafting and we're mining and we're
crafting and we're mining and we're crafting and we're
mining and we're crafting and we're crafting oh i'm fine i'm
i don't think why'd you go over there i wanted to explore
and then i fell where oh you fell you got attacked wait come
this way come this way come this way where'd you put your
bed uh i i can put it here yeah oh yeah let's just put them
here it's nice and pretty okay all right why don't you put
your bed next to my bed because this is not minecraft okay
watch out for this guy over to the left all right we're just
gonna avoid guys but there's like other biomes and stuff
over here yeah yeah yeah yeah and there's the haunted house
to the left oh by the way the stuff in the water the little
jellyfish they kind of look like um i didn't see any
jellyfish when you look at them what it was like algae the
trees are on fire wow that's the volcanic ash we were
getting oh it is wait can we go to the house oh shoot you're
fine you're fine you're fine are you good are you good are
you good are you far can you dig up i can dig up charred
woodlands is what it's called i want to go see scary hey
wait for me oh you're here you're here yeah come come come
come there's also those like big fiery skeletons there so
watch out oh i just got like the oh my god it's the nether
yeah oh it is the nether as long as it doesn't have gas then
i'm good with it watch out uh watch out here
Wow.
Ooh.
La la lava.
Did you watch it?
I did.
Is it good?
It's fun.
Next question.
I really want to watch it.
I haven't watched it yet.
You should.
Come, come, come, come, come, come.
Okay.
Into the lava.
Oh my god.
Careful.
Jumping, jumping.
Jumping scary.
Big jumping.
Big jump.
Wow.
whoa i'm on top of the tree and see what we can find fire
give me okay wait okay this is like lava everywhere i know
this is this is actually the nether
i'm gonna try to make a little ledge to the other side i'm
going i'm gonna go i made a little ledge if you go around
the tree like just like oh yeah yeah see here like i just
made here if you you just get up here i made a ledge yeah
yeah yeah okay it's hard to the music was like scary i know
it's hard to like not see but like determine how high i can
climb yet you know like i'm like oh like it's weird to be
like four blocks yeah i know it's weird look at the sun wait
the sun to the right hold on oh oh one second let me jump
wait wait no that's the moon i think wow the moon the It
actually feels like we're in hell, girl.
It really does.
Wow.
Uh-oh.
Oh, shoot.
Oh, oh, oh.
We got him.
It's just a dog.
Okay.
Just a little guy.
She's a puppy man.
Oh, why is my thing on eight?
Be careful.
Oh, he pushed me through.
The only thing here, too, with the enemies is like, we got
to be careful not to go too far back or too far forward.
Yeah.
Because there's holes everywhere.
Yeah, exactly.
Oh, you made torches.
Look at you.
Yeah, we can make...
I don't have too, too many.
I can make a few more.
so we can make more torches yeah yeah yeah what do you need
for torches sap fiber you can check in your inventory sap
fiber and something else okay I made some more was that you
what no oh and like sounded like it collapsed
this is another dog here okay uh-huh
oh Oh, wait.
If we get out of the fire, see, it gets, like, lighter over
there.
Yeah, what is this over here?
Ooh.
Oh, this must be an endgame ore.
Yeah, probably.
It's a cobble.
Oh, yeah, that stuff was like...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, hell yeah.
Oh, hell, yeah.
Oh, hell.
There's another dog.
Another dog?
Ow.
It's three dogs.
I think he's on me.
He's on me.
Oh, wait.
Unless there's another dog.
Oh, I guess so.
I dropped him in the lava.
Where are you?
Oh, yeah.
Sorry.
I read the other way.
I dropped the dog in the lava.
Oh, nice.
Yeah, kill him.
Oh, no.
Nine.
Oh, sorry.
Do you need coconut?
Look at these guys.
There's yaks.
Oh, wait.
I also...
I need to cook my meat, actually.
Oh, yeah.
I should eat mine too.
I need a minute.
I have a lot of meat to cook.
I have five.
Oh.
There's also some stuff in front of us, too.
There's, like, a little guy in front of us.
Do you see it?
Like, the little...
Oh, yeah, there's a little frog-looking guy.
And there's a little blue guy jumping.
Yeah, what the heck?
Oh, this is so exciting.
I'm going to go...
Oh, and I have 15 arrows.
Here, I'm going to drop them for you.
Okay.
I'm going to go...
The music is so cool.
I know.
Wait for me.
Don't fight the guy because I'm still cooking my music.
I'm not going to fight him.
I want to go see the yak.
Okay.
Little yak.
I think it was also dark.
I can't think of it as dark as it was.
We were.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
I thought you were friends!
Oh my god- I think he's a zombie cow.
I think he's a zombie!
Oh my god.
No, I thought you were a friend!
You're a yak!
He betrayed me!
I think everything in this area is gonna attack us.
I think so probably, oh.
Look at the frog.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, look at him.
Okay.
Let's make a pack that every time we see a hole in the
ground, like we jump over them because it's usually not
regular ground.
It's not.
Regular ground, yeah.
Holy cow.
I brought my shield.
Oh, he like brought me close.
Oh, the guy is staring at us.
Uh-oh.
Oh, it's fine.
Oh, he's blocking.
He's blocking my dude.
Oh, dang it.
Come on.
This guy!
Ooh, you got a cool item.
Essence of fire.
Nice.
Oh, what is this?
Oh, that looks like a wizard.
I'm a dark magician.
oh big attack oh yeah he's so cool okay i gotta back up now
because i don't want any more stamina oh nice okay i gotta
heal yeah wow dark magician boy why is the frog so scary i
know everything here is scary i know with our baby items
with our literally tier one wait there's like another thing
down here what is this i know we're like we'll slow go slow
everything here is so strong let's oh i don't know if we can
find that yet oh no no don't go there's frog man Oh, okay.
Oh, I see him.
Okay, he broke my shield.
He broke my shield.
I got a heal.
Oh, heal, heal, heal.
That looks like a, like, wait.
I don't think so.
What the hell?
Demon horse?
What?
Oh, I wonder if we could ride it.
I wonder.
Try, try, try, try, try.
He runs away, so I don't think he's, you know.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm also scared.
We're going to, like, die to our death running after him.
Go to the slug.
I'm going to the slug.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Let me heal.
Let me heal and I'm coming.
Okay.
Okay, let's go.
This guy can't be that bad.
Let me aggro him first.
Wait, I don't think he's hurting at all.
Oh, yes, he is.
I'm sorry.
Yes, he is.
Wait, no, that's you.
Stop!
Don't hurt him!
No, he's hurting you.
No, that was actually you hurting him.
Okay, sorry.
That was not me hurting him.
Oh, my god, he looked so silly.
Here, grab my essence of fire.
Oh.
Actually, no, I have enough room.
We're fine.
Okay, okay.
Wow, what a spooky place.
Oh, another skele.
Skele.
Oh, my God.
Nice.
Okay, we're killing it.
Literally, figuratively.
Is that a little guy with a gun?
Oh, my God.
Look, he's got a...
They've got guns now.
Like, it's like a revolver.
Yeah.
It's a musket.
He's loading it.
This is so funny.
Wait, oh, my God.
Wait, out.
Sorry.
Not out.
Ouch to you.
Did he have to like reload his musket every time?
Aww, wait, he dropped something.
Cinder cloth scraps.
That's so cute.
Wait, there's like a...
There's a flame dog too.
Oh, haunted house!
It's a little scared!
Well, haunted house, I'm coming, I'm coming.
No, it's over towards you.
It's over towards you.
This way.
Oh, let's go.
It's the haunted house.
Oh, wait, stop.
That's...
Okay, be careful.
Yeah, be careful.
um so what we could probably do is we can like oh okay wait
yeah this is gonna be rough don't don't run in don't run i'm
not i'm not i'm actually going around okay yeah yeah let's
do that great idea yeah you're so smart so cute i know look
at the trees here they're like they're so pretty i know i'm
sorry i can't get over that he was like reloading his muscle
let me let me aggro this i think there's a there's a zombie
chicken too Oh, yeah, there is.
Okay, my shield is broken.
My shield is broken.
I gotta kind of evade run him.
I got him.
Okay, good, good, good.
Good job.
Let me heal.
Zombie chicken.
Zombie.
This does feel like exploring an oblivion gate.
Oh, my God.
There's definitely an enemy.
Don't run into it.
Oh, oh, shoot.
Sorry.
It's okay.
It's good.
Okay.
Oh, these are like the berserkers, I feel.
Let's keep, like, kind of running away from them.
Yeah.
Every time they swing, just, like, run back.
Nice.
Okay.
Oh.
Is he on you?
Look at his hat.
I know.
He's so cute.
Wait, he dropped his weapon.
No, that's awesome.
Wait, did I get it?
Maybe not.
I might have gotten it.
Let me see.
That's okay.
Let me just...
they're so cute at you I know I got his weapon oh nice let
me drop it to you here they have doors they're so civilized
I know okay it's an ancient oh it's a rare crossbow yeah and
there's a right yeah yeah check it out it's probably better
than your crossbow because it's rare I wish there were stop
running why are you running whoa oh my god they're so cute
man we're doing it We're in the scary zone And we're doing
it And we're killing it We're kicking butt Oh there's a guy
up there Where Up here up here Up here I'm gonna get him
They're so cute They have like little question marks On
their face When they're running And looking for like A way
to get you Okay the music It's like Epic epic Maybe for you
No I'm not That's okay though Maybe for you Yeah maybe for
you Sto-Bum Yeah It's not epic for me.
The bed's here.
Oh, my God.
Oh, we're stealing.
Or we were sleeping.
We're stealing.
We're sleeping.
Ancient steel greaves.
Okay, that means we're stealing.
Yeah, they're rich.
These guys are rich.
They're so rich.
And you know who's rich not?
Oh, they have an iron mace if you want to try that, too.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, wait.
I have an iron sword.
Actually, give it to me because my sword's going to run out
of...
Wait, come up here.
Come up to the second story.
What the hell is it?
Why did you find the stairs for the second story?
Um, I just climbed.
There, I don't know if there are stairs.
It's fine.
Like, where are you?
The windows and stuff are so ritsy.
I know this place, they got money.
I got money.
Oh, I'm up here.
Yeah, money.
Hold on.
Look up.
Yeah.
Wow, look at the bookshelf.
Oh, map.
I climbed from the outside.
Oh, I do.
Oh, it's a two, the mace is two-handed.
Ah, never mind then.
Check out the underground area here.
It's super cool.
Yeah, there's like an underground.
down here there's like an underground we can go together
in here oh my god yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah in here wait
where'd you go oh and down the stairs i'll change mine wait
i don't i don't i got a super chat about it i don't know if
they mean like underneath the actual oh
i don't know they meant deeper deeper deeper like the caves
in here yeah what do you mean explain yourself my love oh
done done how do you what is it control oh yeah I heard that
too but I'm not seeing any of them you might be stuck in the
walls oh oh I saw this okay there's actually stairs to climb
up oh there are oh probably like somewhere up top look for
us to shoot oh my god they have like a little dummy that you
can like so cute training dummies
did you steal a bed by the way i did okay good good good
good me too underground layers are beautiful what this is
gorgeous are you kidding me where'd you find the stairs to
go up um if you go back to the main area where we first
attack them there's like stairs going up oh like the ladder
oh maybe that's what i took the first i think that's what i
took the first okay this game's fun yeah and i noticed by
the way every different faction we attacked have a different
flag yeah so we could collect them all oh there's a skeleton
up there up top and like i haven't been able to get to him
so just be careful not to get shot okay i see him All right.
Out, out, out.
Where to next, my princess?
What a cool island.
It actually has, like, so many different things on it.
Oh, shoot.
The poor people living here.
Oh, I wonder if they meant this downstairs area.
No, I think they mean, like, underneath the ground, like,
under, under the ground, it seems.
Oh, like, in the depth of the lava?
Yeah, I think so.
Ha, ha, ha, I got that guy.
nice good job okay the music is so epic it is yeah and like
look up at the sky if you can it looks like a painting i
know it's like watercolor and like crazy yeah like a war
yeah it's time for war i see you i'm coming down hi do you
want to keep circling the island because i want to see
what's like uh on the non-verbal side i feel like we've seen
we have yeah a lot of it i'm this was legitness you what it
was legitness what legitness it was legitness oh my god i
look so cool i'm like looking at myself with my little shade
oh yeah so cool look i can even do a dropped a sword but
it's like kind of the same tier as the regular swords okay
my sword is better yeah it looks it looks really rinky dinky
i'm not gonna lie no wait i'm gonna see what my shield looks
like the music is crazy oh my god in my inventory my shield
looks blue but on your screen it doesn't i think it's
because it's like a rare one so it's like the rare like blue
yeah makes it bluey yeah i love like the oh i'm saying if
you press v you can see yourself in third person Oh my god,
the helmet.
He kind of gives me hair, if you look, because of the
little, like...
Wait, why is my...
Yeah, it does look like hair.
Wait, I look so stupid.
I know.
Wait a second.
I look cool.
They're going to add it that apparently you can, like, make
your armor not visible.
Oh, good.
I'm not going to lie.
This is a look with the gloves.
That is a look.
Mine?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I kind of love it.
I'm kind of obsessed.
Wait, I want to see what this thing is real quick.
It's probably going to attack me, but that's okay.
Oh, yeah, that's the flaming skull I was talking about.
They have, like, a question mark when they see you.
Exclamation mark.
Oh, that's so funny.
I think it's because he's about to shoot a fire.
Oh, my God, this looks exactly like a guy in Doom.
Yeah.
Oh, nice.
Yeah, good job.
Yeah, ow, ow.
Noise, noise, noise, noise.
oh skeleton horse is here skelly horse don't run don't run
don't run why is it have hair you can't just ask it why it
has hair oh oh you got him wait can he go in the lava this
is the ultimate test come on you want me to try it try all
right he can i can't although the lava doesn't kill you
right away it kills you slowly
It doesn't kill you right away.
It kills you slowly.
Killing you softly.
You're killing me softly.
We love him.
That's cool to know.
I wonder if it's because I was off.
Oh.
It's fine.
He can have him.
Oh, you can have him.
He actually matches.
He matches you.
Wait, F.
There you go.
Oh, he almost kicked me again.
Oh, no.
I won't.
I won't be.
There's another bear or.
Come on.
Mine it.
The red one.
Where?
Oh, I see.
I see.
Oh,
yeah.
Adamantite This is the best ore Oh dang okay Nice Next time
we should go exploring In the depths of this area then I
think so too I can be fun Yeah Playing today I had so much
fun Yeah thanks with ours This is so fun This was I'm sorry
to cut it kind of short I just I really Tomorrow is like my
big workday And I have gym at 7 in the morning What are you
talking about?
talking about I mean I guess short for you it's been four
and a half hours for me yeah twitch stream twitch twitch
kind of likes it when you stream long hours yeah this is
something I do miss about YouTube where you're like I'm I'm
here we're hanging out it's done but yeah I also like the
long streams did he move on his own no no I moved him by
accident okay okay all right any last words you want to say
to my momo not because I'm gonna kill you but like yeah I
was any last words he has eyes looking at me do see your v
to look at yourself in the first person oh my god it looks
like a manta ray it's so cute please please don't change
please please
please i'll change i'll change let's stop this was so fun
this was yeah um do you got anything coming up i'm like a
podcast Like, do you got anything you want to advertise?
Uh, I don't think so.
Okay, well, I actually do.
Oh, yeah.
What are you doing on February 4th?
Fourth?
I think I'm free.
Good, because it's my birthday and you're going to collab
with me.
Yeah, oh my gosh, wait!
Okay, I'm not going to lie, because your voice broke, it
sounded like you actually weren't excited.
It sounded like a sarcastic, like, oh, wow.
Oh.
oh it's your birthday oh yeah yeah i'll probably organize a
little something we can have like a little a little party
with limes and stuff it'll be fun yeah i'm probably gonna do
a long stream but i'm gonna have i told my my audience i'm
gonna have a few announcements of like permanent merch store
etc but so far nothing that's like super you know everything
is like in limbo and i hope that things are done in time oh
yeah yeah but it's not i'm very lucky that valentine's day
is right after so i could be like oh they were ready for
valentine's day yeah let's go yeah big big birthday vibes
everybody february 4th february 4th matara con channel
twitch yeah it's gonna be awesome and um yeah i love you
this was fun yeah i feel um i'm sure you also get this
sometimes where like somebody came up and they were like why
haven't you collabed with me do you guys hate each other
first of all no we're still we're just like kind of doing
our own stuff you know i like I feel like we've just been
like our free time has kind of overlapped each other or like
not overlap but like my opposite yeah exactly like I'll have
a free time and then you'll be busy and then you have a free
time and I'm busy so it's like I have a free time you're
like sorry I'm doing you know this thing that is super
important and then vice versa you'll contact me and I'm like
I'm so sorry right now like next three weeks I am locked in
yeah but that's just how it goes no we're still I'll I guess
they're my buddy buddy I guess she didn't pay me to be here
thanks for admitting that she should for my time I'm getting
older my time is really valuable I don't got much of it left
oh no yeah you're withering away you're these little flame
petals it's like you that's flakes of you just kind of I'm a
dead dying woman withering away hey that's what's in now
apparently yeah yeah all right puki i love you i'm gonna say
bye to my to my mommos and uh i'll see you around bye bye
bye bye bye bye bye bye i win bitch what
Bye.
Go away.
See it.
Say it.
Say what?
I love you.
Oh, I love you.
Yeah!
I only said it because it's been a while since we last hung
out or last collabed.
I don't want people actually thinking we hate each other.
Oh, man.
Oh, Mataro.
What?
This game is so fun.
Oh my gosh.
This game was so fun.
I hope you guys had fun.
I hope you guys enjoyed our grand tour.
Finishing off on that last island was kind of crazy.
Also, I...
So I had issues with the game when I first...
Okay, I'm gonna say something.
I had issues with the game when I first installed it.
me make like a server it like wouldn't connect to the server
so i had to like do a bunch of finangling with it but um
apparently like that's a known issue but um so i was like
going into the world i was going i'd like made a creative
world to like kind of be like maybe it's something like to
see if i was connected online and where i spawned was like
right next to a dragon
I wonder if there, if we'll see a dragon.
Kiara and Kali had the same issue.
Yeah, I think it's like a known bug thing.
So imagine dragons.
Luckily, I was in creative.
So it didn't like kill me.
Which there is like a creative mode.
Oh, I don't, I think I, I think I deleted it.
Because I was like, oh, it was just like me testing to see
like.
Because I was like, am I, how do I get online?
like is it because when you here i'll just show you if i go
back into the server the art is so cute um one second
because i was reading you had to set up the server here and
so i was like online play and i was like wait it's not
working you know whatever whatever so yeah but it's so cute
oh this game is so fun!
There's so much to explore.
And then also, I knew about the map.
I knew about, you know, press M for the map or whatever,
when I first tried it.
But I thought it was literally only that circle.
I did it, I was like, wow, this map is actually, like, so
small.
Okay, I guess there's not going to be much to... I was like,
I guess there's not going to be much to explore, but there
was actually so much to explore!
Yeah!
I'm so happy.
This is so fun.
I'm...
Yippee!
It's infinite!
Oh wow!
She didn't scroll.
No!
It like unlock- the map unlocks as you explore more!
That's why I thought it was so small!
But so far, I think, um...
I would say it's...
I mean, I think it was like what, seven years ago or
something that it got announced and then it like...
And then the team disbanded, and then it was cancelled, and
then it came back, and all this stuff.
And so, I think, though, I think they've definitely put in a
lot of stuff, or, like, a lot of thought into everything so
far.
So, it looks so pretty.
It really does.
It looks so pretty, and there's so many, like, little things
you can grab, like, skulls, like, just falling into that
bug's nest.
Like, oh, my gosh, so cool.
3d terraria it really is it's so fun so so fun yeah
crossbows don't look miserable to use getting kicked by a
horse into a cave and I heard dinosaurs are getting added
like actually I know there's so many animals I want to zoom
and like We didn't even touch so many aspects, like the
building aspect and the...
We just kind of explored, which I'm okay with.
Like I said, this is a new game.
I want to see all that I could see of it.
And then I can build.
But like, we could settle down and have a little cottage and
a farm and some animals and everything.
Dinos are already in!
I missed them.
I did not see the dinos.
What kind of dinos are we talking about?
What are we talking about, anyway?
That's our dino.
Hopefully, iguana dines.
I sure hope so.
I sure hope.
You have to dig down.
Then we'll get them next time.
The version, actually, the version from...
Wait, interesting to think this is actually the version from
five years ago.
Publisher.
Makes you wonder how much more they need to recreate now.
Matara, kind of.
Matara's our dinosaur.
Yeah, is there Ketzel Coatlas?
That's a huge question.
Very big question.
Very, very big question.
This is so fun, though.
Matara's like a great person to be explored with.
yeah i had a lot of fun i hope you guys did too i am so
hungry i was just feeding on some pretz do you guys know
pretz they're so yummy right if you've ever had them they're
like pocky they're like pocky without the chocolate and it's
like a biscuit stick but flavored and so this one is
flavored tomato they're so yummy yeah savory pocky yeah yeah
yeah except it's not like you know a coat of stuff.
It's like seasoning.
They're tasty.
Tasty, tasty, tasty.
Tomato.
Never heard of tomato flavored.
It's not a pretzel.
It's called pretz.
P-R-T-T-Z.
Pretz.
I think they're even made by the same people that make
pocket even.
Pizza one is nice too.
Yummy, yummy.
Oh, guys, what should I have for dinner are kind of hungry
it's a little late but i want some i should have something
light what's this like japanese cheesecake something that
i've been hearing lately does anyone know about that it's
like i see it's like involves like a a bisco cookie and
yogurt tacos i'm always in the mood for tacos hot dog The
yogurt thing?
Yeah, yeah.
Abyssoff cookie.
And I think it's...
I guess from what I see, you then crush it into the yogurt.
Also, I saw my second show.
Shh, shh, shh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh,
sh.
It...
No more tickets!
I think so.
Gotta be MVP ticket, it's a good day.
Thank you!
Let me see.
Oh my gosh, I'm so...
What the heck?
A whole second show.
I will do my best for both.
Yippee!
Thank you!
Oh gosh.
I hope that I could do well two shows one night, but I'll do
my best.
To make them both very well.
fun and exciting and awesome so yeah yeah yeah oh wow hold
on let me do in the discord uh i'll do gongnam neko arc
gongnam style
yay yay yay yay oh my god wait second minto with love
showing sold out in minutes
but thank you thank you very much everybody I hope I hope
everybody who wanted to get a ticket was able to get one
going to need a national tour holy moly
craziness what the heck how do you have that Steiner he sent
me a big gif of Gangnam style Neckalark.
But yeah.
Thank you guys so much for hanging out with me today.
Hanging out with us today.
It was so much fun.
Oh my gosh.
Gotta teach me again how to raid on YouTube is what Tara
just said.
L-O-L.
It's kind of confusing though.
Did you guys...
Did you guys here that there's right now is like a huge like
solar storm going on so there's like crazy crazy um what's
the words uh aurora is happening let me see if i can if i
can raid you guys i can raid you into one of my favorite
aurora cam do you guys want that it might be they might get
mad at me though they might get mad at me let's see if
there's a row oh no it's cloudy right now so you can't see
it no it's cloudy though you can't see it hang on why would
they be mad sometimes the mods are like why are people here
it gets like i mean it gets like a lot of people it gets
like 300 people max usually from what i see but oh but it's
cloudy i think but it has a v it has a hold on let me check
it i'm gonna turn so you can't hear it real quick so that i
can see if you can go back in time and okay there we go it
has like a nice like soundtrack oh yeah if you go back like
a couple hours you can really see it wow wow wow i don't
know you think they'll get mad at me just don't be
disruptive aren't don't go in and be like raid message
they're normie people everybody they're like absolute
normies so I'll raid into it but don't like yeah don't spam
the chat or anything you can just watch if you want but
right now it's cloudy but if you go back like a couple of
hours even like even if you go back an hour you can see some
of it there's just a little bit of clouds I watch this
camera daily but Silent raid.
Yeah, silent raid, okay, everybody's silent raid.
But, yeah, definitely go and enjoy the Aurora that's
happening because of the storm.
What's it called, like a geo... Wait, hold on.
It's a geomagnetic storm happening right now.
It's the largest in over 20 years, so there's a lot of cool
cameras that are doing, like, Aurora.
you can you can you could probably go outside or go to a
good place you know and see it it's only for like I think
it's like yesterday and today so yeah yeah yeah yeah so
definitely check it out if you can go outside and see okay
silent raid everybody thank you so much Ate Bito Thank you
so much for hanging out with me and my daughter today.
I hope you had fun and I had a lot of fun.
I'm gonna go get something to eat.
I don't know what yet, but something.
Thanks for the stream.
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you!
Oh, it's a bit, oh, it's a bit, oh, bye-bye.
Bye-bye, bye-bye.
See you.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Aurora is coming back.
I'm gonna raise you guys over.
The clouds are clearing up.
It's like green.
It's crazy.
Okay, I'm gonna send you over.
Bye-bye!
Woo!
Silent breed, silent breed, don't say anything, viewer.