Oh everybody hello hello welcome to once human so um you
guys might notice that uh tension is muted right now um
because we found out that uh we can't instantly play
multiplayer we have to do like a little uh we have to do a
little tutorial first like um in the first 15 minutes so So,
because of that, we were like, okay, I'm going to meet you
when we're done with a tutorial and when we find each other.
So, like, what you guys see, like your first time seeing
Tengen will be my first time seeing Tengen in game.
Because he was like, I don't want to show my chat what I
made.
So, so we're going to see that together, guys.
The first hand reaction together.
And that is why he is muted at the moment.
see each other we unmute so once human apparently it is a um
the newest third i know i wrote like at first i thought it
was first person and i realized it was third person um so
then i had i like edited my tweet like three times because
like the first time i edited it was like grab my mistake the
second time i edited it i was like oh it's a shooter game
and not an fps game
I tweet multiple times.
I kept making mistakes.
Anyway, so Once Human is the newest shooter game.
Newest PvE shooter game.
Extraction shit or whatever.
And like today we're going to figure out.
This is launch day.
Launch today.
I've always seen a lot of trailers of this leading up to
Once Human.
And like you know it finally launched today.
And judging by the reviews.
judging judging by what the reviews were saying it doesn't
look it doesn't look uh too promising we it does have pvp
and pve but we're going to be doing pve because tension was
like he was scared of getting like stream sniped and killed
lots of times so like okay he didn't say that But that's
what I assumed because he didn't choose I let him pick the
server and I was like pve not pvp And he's like yeah pve so
he's a little bitch
So he's a little bitch boy and doesn't want to risk playing
uh pvp Um yeah that's what I heard in my head when he was
like we're doing pve
anyway um most likely um it's free to play though like once
human is free to play so that's like the great part about it
it is free to play but like um it has mixed reviews right
now so i don't know apparently a lot of it was because it's
like cosmetics like a lot of stuff is like locked Like,
that's usually what I expect from free to play.
Usually in free to play, it's, you know, a lot of stuff is
locked behind.
Um, locked behind, uh, behind stuff.
So, yeah, um, we'll see.
We'll see.
I was gonna, like, go, I went in.
I was like, okay, we're gonna go in.
Oh my gosh.
Why is there like zero bars?
Anyway.
Alright.
And then there's server issues apparently too, where people
are waiting for a very long time to get into the server.
But I sort of expected that for a game that came out on
launch.
There's a hand.
Whoa!
Our world is broken.
Stagnant.
Fallen into the abyss.
But everything is born from darkness.
Even the universe itself.
Alright, I'll turn up this.
The spark of life still burns.
Alright.
And evolution forges a new way forward.
I raised it a bit more.
What's the lore that we're never going to pay attention to
after this cutscene?
Yeah, I was going to say, it feels like Kingdom Hearts.
It really does.
Once you move beyond death.
Once life returns to this world.
This feels like...
Where's the door of darkness?
Oh my god, this is the Keyblade Cemetery right here.
You might be on that path.
Keyblade, but with guns.
Kingdom Hearts should add guns into its game.
That's how it's going to improve.
The reason why Kingdom Hearts 3 was not as good as 1 and 2
was because the audience grew up and now they just want gun.
Change my mind.
Alright, oh my god.
Okay, this is like...
It's net ease, right?
So, yeah, this looks like a net ease game.
Bro, man.
I could tell, I could tell because like you can tell when
like certain games are made like whichever company made
whichever games due to the fact of like the faces.
So like this is this is the net ease style.
I can tell or next and yeah is either net ease or next and I
could I could recognize the faces like each company has its
own very distinct like uh customization when it comes to
like humans i'm like yeah that looks like a net ease or
nexen game all right can i make me okay oh this is retro
dokey right there uh well i don't know i don't know all the
faces are like true to the Can I say that?
I feel like they're all like, so are the guys, too.
All the faces are very similar.
All right, let's see.
Okay, face.
All right.
Oh my god.
It's, okay, like these games have like insane customization
as well.
like because what the fuck oh my god okay we need like a
really small head oh my god there's too many things forehead
tempo hairline jaw jaw jesus christ am i playing in like mmo
is this an mmo right now all right guys the smaller the head
the smaller the the hitbox
guys believe in me the smaller the head the smaller the
hitbox this is our you can't even tell is it the hair?
okay let's get rid of the hair and just see like does it
make a difference?
it has okay all right okay we'll fix the hair later I just
want to know if there's like any if I could is there any
difference?
like I can't tell I can't Actually, I can't tell if I'm
making any, oh my god, the head is a little dented here.
Like,
oh my god, what are the changes?
Oh, here, I see it.
I see the change right now.
Oh my god, okay, there's a little dent in here too.
Holy shit, okay, all right, at least, you know what?
All right, there we go.
Oh my God.
You know how, like, when you wear headphones, there's, like,
a little, like, the gamer dance.
Yeah, like, I wear the headphones the wrong way.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
It's so bad here.
Okay.
All right.
Let's see.
The tempo.
Oh, no.
No.
Okay.
we should not do that actually all right tempo size okay yes
the smaller we gotta minimize the we gotta minimize the the
hitbox as much as we can guys as much as we can okay all
right there you go uh oh she's mewing
okay i should like that successful mulling right there What
the fuck is mulling it's Yeah, for the Like it looks maxing
Okay For those who don't know it's basically the newest term
that Gen Z has invented It's it's like you know how like the
sig the Sigma male with the with the cheekbones like that so
apparently there's a new fad right now for Gen Z where
they're like we gotta like um we gotta like uh but yeah we
we gotta have like the cheekbones and that's what they call
they call it like muleing I don't I don't know why it's
called muleing I'm just being hip with the times, you know?
I'm just relating to the children, to the kids.
Or is it Gen Alpha?
They sort of, oh, Gen...
I like how the Gen Z people are like, we don't claim this,
we're not that cringe.
And I'm like, oh, you poor...
Gen Z.
You were already cringe.
you might as well own it like um all right let's see cheek
angle okay we gotta put it here uh oh my god the fucking
okay the chin oh okay let's see all right we gotta have
small chin and then no chin oh maybe like thicken up the
chin a little bit and then okay oh yeah okay all right okay
uh we can keep that here oh jawline jawline i want okay
let's see yes oh my god wait actually maybe not as big okay
and then oh yes the butt chin yes Oh my god!
You can have the butt chin!
The fucking butt chin right there!
Okay, and then, uh...
I think that's good.
And...
Oh, no.
I want more of the butt showing...
Popping out.
Oh my god, the Peter Griffin.
I'm making Peter Griffin.
Okay.
Alright.
Uh...
Jaw.
The muleing!
It's...
We're getting...
guys uh we're actually getting we're actually getting there
okay uh think like here all right there we go oh my god wait
that's okay Thanos you're right okay now okay we don't have
to care but honestly like um eyebrows is like fine with me
unless oh i'm always like huh i'm always like always
surprised and then okay we're uh dent it a little bit more
eyebrow foot eyebrow tail oh this part okay yeah i don't i'm
not the biggest eyes possible actually the smallest eyes
possible i just never find this is this is a lot better i
actually like that a lot
Alright.
Ooh, big nostrils.
I want huge nostrils so I can smell them better.
What's...
Nostral...
Okay, I want to be able to smell better.
So I can smell my enemies.
Nose...
Wait, can I extend the neck?
No, I can.
Alright.
What do you see with your tiny eyes?
the eyes okay wait i should wait i like that okay okay i
actually think the the pigtails the it looks so good it
looks okay wait um let me double check wait i think the
pigtails is actually perfect for this I think it's it's
actually really really good okay let me let me double check
let me let me make sure if the pigtails is uh what I want in
the end all I'm saying is I think the pigtails I think the
pigtails is perfect for this um it does hide the dent though
the gamer dent a lot so it's like I worked really hard for
that but like it's okay it's all right i think it's actually
really good i think it's really good okay um all right okay
body short so all right so we gotta have like uh this oh
okay we gotta be like a little hobbit if possible the
smaller oh Nice.
Maybe like...
Yeah, there we go.
There we go.
Small head box!
Small head!
Okay.
Smaller head.
Smaller head hit box.
Alright, waist.
I think we don't have to care about that.
I'm pretty sure.
Wait, chest size.
Okay.
Wait, what does it look like?
Oh my god.
Like the upper body.
Okay.
holy shit the only hitbox that
right let's see arms and okay what about like if I make like
everything else like super all right there you oh okay yeah
the tall waist length and then uh arms and legs uh oh wait
where's the legs there we go holy what did i create there no
it should be like up this is like the only uh boosted part
of it
the body should not be able to hold this okay there we go um
all right nice that's actually that's good that's good i
think we're looking good we're looking good here body paint
what would it okay no no absolutely now we're not having
body we're not having a random hand there like what it was
to add on there all right all right uh i think we're good i
think i think we're really i think we're looking really good
guys all right name character um oh wait is this like
staring hair tied oh wait what oh hair tied hair down wait
what why is this hair down staring look around what does
that mean all right okay let's see name this is gonna be my
character all right you will be named your name will be peak
dragoon that's that's you guys dragoon
We don't claim her
Alright Okay, how about this?
Alright, instead of that Alright, we will do
Once a dragon
Alright, there we go That's gonna be your name Once a dragon
All right, end to game.
What do you see?
That's us!
95.79 Celsius.
Physical movement or brain function, not detected.
You guys are good maxing.
Stable.
Dagger still stuck in the sheath.
Inspection 481 complete.
I wonder what tension made.
Whoa, we have magic powers.
What the fuck are we doing?
Dragoon, what are you guys doing?
Why are shoulders so wide?
It has to carry the assets.
What do you mean?
How else do you carry those assets?
Oh.
What the fuck?
What's that in, you guys?
What?
Okay, remove.
Wait, I have it.
Oh!
Oh, it stopped.
okay I'm sorry the legs definitely do not match the rest of
the body use the activated you're so beautiful guys I'm not
coping this is you guys not me I'm not okay Sorry.
Like, your body...
Okay.
Alright, let's grab the...
Let's clean the wall real fast.
Alright.
What is this?
No, this is an adult human.
Okay.
Alright, we don't care about these guys.
I finished the tutorial, though.
Access code for Chrono Cage.
Update the code after completing today's experiment.
Okay, this is the code.
Uh...
You guys are a Dorito.
Yeah, you guys are.
All right.
You won't last long if consume food and drink to increase
your energy and hydration.
Oh, no.
Is this a survival?
Open your backpack to check your inventory.
Uh, most of the ingredients and dishes have a durability,
which gradually decays over time.
Once it's durability reaches zero, the food.
Oh, okay.
This is a little fast.
This is a little fast for me.
Okay, we got eat.
And then we got a drink.
Okay, I'm fully hydrated now.
Is there anybody in here?
No, it's just me.
Okay, mouse4 is melee.
Okay, melee, roll.
And then there's flashlights.
World unlocks when the Eye of Evolution is completed?
Alright, what's this?
Input password.
Oh, shit.
I read it, but I didn't read it.
Give me a sec.
Let me read the memo again.
Is it 0728?
Okay, 0728.
I got it.
0728.
7, 2, 8.
Yay!
I can read!
Yippee!
Oh, hey, there's a dead guy.
Hello?
Wait, did I kill him, too?
An intact cradle is recovered with those used.
Energy stored within the cradle shows unused signs of
activity.
Has been placed in a separate room for safekeeping.
Am I the cradle?
Where is this the cradle?
Find the access...
No, okay, no.
No, we have to find the access card.
Who killed these guys?
Did I kill them?
Did I kill these people?
Will me?
But I'm so innocent.
Look at me.
Wait, is there...
I'm just wondering if there's certain, like, physics.
No.
Okay.
I was just curious.
Oh shit, okay.
Whoops.
Did I break my leg?
Wait, you can break your leg?
It's okay, I'm fine.
My shins are like a little bit rickety.
My shins are just a little rickety right now.
Oh, what's this?
Med kit.
Okay, we gotta get all the meds.
Item crate.
Food.
water.
Just water?
Where's like the tea or soda?
Deviation of unknown level detected in the research area.
Deviation appears to consist of multiple floating
butterflies.
Floating butterflies.
I don't know what that means.
There's like floating butterflies in everything.
What?
What's that?
How's the game sound so far?
I don't know where to go.
How can I already be lost?
There's, like, nothing here.
Okay.
Uh...
What's that sound?
Um...
Do I have to go downstairs?
Find the access card.
Where is the access card?
Go to the waypoint.
Did I get the access card already?
Oh, no!
My foot!
it's okay just i'm it's okay i just twisted my ankle a
little bit how can i like the peak human being if i get like
a twisted ankle there's fall damage this is bullshit why is
there fall damage in my video game i'm
once human i should not have fall damage also me oh my god
is this like death stranding where i have a baby in the
backpack whoa bro what's this crow doing here bro talk to
this strange bird well it's good to see another face i
thought i was on my own who are you and you're a metahuman
too i'm metahuman
What do you call you know, what do you call me a metahuman?
I don't know who you are But I know what you are Why am I
you awakened at the cradle?
And that's something only a metahuman could do Yo, whoa Do
you remember who you are?
Hello Bro, you already finished the tutorial?
I'm I'm I'm I'm making my beast you're you're what I'm
making I'm making my base you're what I really I literally
just met the bird I just met the bird I just met the bird
I'm making a base spoiler alert no don't worry about it how
far am I how far am i from the beast from the crow to the
beast um not that far actually oh not that far okay okay
that's good okay all right i'll catch you on the other side
soon don't worry i'll be i'll be making some okay once you
got here i will have a home you'll have me i am not homeless
there's a base i thought this was like i gotta give instance
i thought it's just like an extraction shooter or something
that's your butt i don't know i'm i'm there's a home
building yeah i'm making a base i was laughing the whole
time you said beast i thought you spent like there's like a
fucking companion no i'm making no oh my god okay at least
okay you're gonna mooch off your house then i'm like oh yeah
sure i'll just find where you're not homeless all right okay
i'll be there soon i'll be right back i'm still talking to
the crow okay okay ah oh my god he already has a house wait
what happened i already forgot what he told talked to me
about.
It trapped me in the cradle.
It could have wrapped you of your memories.
Oh, we used to be best friends.
Me and the crow.
You can call me V.
It seems that our interests are aligned to Meta-human.
Wait, but you're a talking bird.
What are you talking about?
You're a talking bird.
I used to be like you were.
wait when we die we become crows but it's a long story and
now is not the time no i have lots of time what do you mean
just tell me now all right i came to secure a deviation a
paper butterfly but i think something must have scared it
deviation now though we need to move there's so much lore
for a game that might die in a month but only if you help me
complete my mission all right all right all you have to do
is listen to what i tell you okay i'll be right here in the
cradle now let's go all right here we go whoa oh this is the
cradle okay uh we have to explore this press q to use space
time to search for items oh my god you just snap your
fingers
We'll have a machete now.
Oh my god, just snap your fingers.
Wait, what the fuck?
What the fuck is that?
Deviant has been infected with Stardust.
Deviant has water?
Ever since Starfall.
Ordinary humans can't take high levels of Stardust exposure.
They end up just like that thing.
But you're a metahuman.
You should be fine.
Oh, so that's what the humans turn into.
You might even be able to use Stardust to your advantage.
Okay, give me that gear.
Oh my god, I get a hat!
Oh my god!
Nice hat.
Same hat!
Snap.
Oh, there's stuff here.
Wait, there's actual stuff here.
I was just snapping for fun.
Wait, where the fuck did you come from?
Holy shit!
Get out of here!
This is a tutorial!
Alright, let's see.
What's in here?
Ooh, a Molotov.
Snap.
Okay, the snapping is a little addicting.
Whoa!
Okay, there he is.
That's fucking right!
You're in the wrong neighborhood!
Okay, let's grab this real fast uh oh i got shoes now guys i
got shoes after image women oh
where did where did female take me oh okay let me raise up
the volume a little oh my god what the fuck what are all
these what the where these extra wait self-destruct what are
these extra settings all right let's see i'll turn down the
sound effects and then i'll turn up the game okay let's see
yeah all right game has been turned up oh spiritual often
cause anomalies in time allowing past needs to be witnessed
once again Activate Space Time to locate Spatial Theaters
where events And people from the past may reappear And
potentially reveal hidden truth.
Snap.
Whoa!
Is this me?
Don't
monster.
Oh no, this is a girl with Defying.
My father and everyone else.
They're gone.
Yes, you killed her.
Yeah, that's right.
It is your fault.
Try and stay calm.
Yeah, you kill them all and you're gonna live with that
guilt forever.
Oh shit, I'm a bit thirsty.
Not because a woman.
Just what?
No, but this is the military.
We have to use you.
You're not a monster.
In fact, you're very, very special.
That's right.
You need to learn how to control your power.
You can help fix this broken world.
We can do that together.
Yay!
Okay, we gotta drink water.
Oh, I can summon V?
Hey, shit.
Hey there.
Leave.
Okay, goodbye.
Never mind.
I thought I could, like, I don't know.
I thought he would want to talk to me.
I guess not.
Hey, let's see.
Snap.
It's flying.
Oh, that's a butterfly!
Oh,
you can create butterflies?
That seems pretty useless.
Hey, I know, like, Tendon's waiting for me, but I'm gonna
loot a bit.
I know he's, like, waiting for me.
for me after finishing the tutorial like I don't know maybe
a couple minutes ago I'm still in the beginning but like
this is more important we need something powerful whoa she
can fly and I think I finally found it you hey we can see
you're special we can use them to forge a new path and bring
about true evolution this will be the Mayflies mission this
is why we'll fight Mayflies that's right mayflies small yet
invincible humanity may seem puny now but we'll prove we can
endure oh okay let's loot this crate there's so much lore
wait where do i go from here snap did not loot all this is
my no i did snap where's the door oh there's the door okay
snap oh shit
Oh my god, what the fuck?
Okay, the monster designs are pretty interesting.
Like, I would admit.
Alright, nice.
Now I have gloves.
Where do I get down from here?
Am I gonna break my legs again?
Is there, like, an easier way to get down?
Is there gonna break my legs?
Okay.
This guy right here.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Legs slightly injured.
It's okay.
I can get better.
all right not really a huge threat yet to be fair like I
feel like I'm faster than them it's a hitbox oh I can throw
oh shit wait what what the fuck okay approach and attempt to
capture it oh shit how do I throw this away how do I
Oh, discard.
Okay.
Wait, that's so cool.
I can have, like, I can use their, like, heads to fight for
me.
What's this?
Wait, touch.
Wait, but what about my...
No!
My gun!
Whoa.
I love it when my cutscenes are five frames per second.
wait that's it wait i'm wait no my gun i mean i'm at like
you have left victor victor's territory wait i'm at a house
now what is this like the original fortnite like what whose
house is this wait there's like there's what is what there's
like a horn is there gonna be a horn mode days to die?
Like...
Oh, hello.
Isolated securement unit.
Oh, no.
No, it's mine.
I'm not giving you it.
I'm not gonna give you this.
Me.
You made it back.
Yeah.
Yes, and look what I found.
A meta.
Only just woken up.
enough to activate the cradle and set oh my gosh still don't
have pants so weird shoes gloves and shoes gloves and hat
but no pants still thank you meta human your help means a
lot to me you can call me mitzko i used to be a meta human
as well rosetta did all kinds of experiments on me wait used
to until v saved me what happened after special fluctuations
in the stardust it's thanks to her that i was able to take
refuge in this place after starfall you're still look you
don't you're not crow yet wait okay are we all rosetta's
experiments that's what rosetta does at first they just
locked deviations away but then they figured out that
deviations could be harnessed to make humans stronger that's
when they commenced
as a result they created metahumans like me and you you
still look like a human sentient you're covering no sentient
covering it up for you guys and they're not wrong metahumans
are mankind's last hope we were created by Rosetta but we
don't take orders from them anymore we left we call
ourselves the mayflies now and we do things differently
What?
What the fuck is going on?
About 20 years ago, Rosetta triggered a major Stardust
fluctuation during one of their experiments.
As a result, some great ones slipped through, entering into
our world.
They brought increased levels of Stardust with them.
That poison has seeped into every corner of our world now,
spawning countless deviance.
Oh, these are the ones that we have to kill.
Okay.
Yes.
The butterfly is an emissary of sorts.
Yeah, this is like Lord Dumping Time.
The recent fluctuation must have startled it.
The important thing right now is to secure it and ensure its
safety.
See that thing in the center of the room?
It's a device for securing deviations.
This makes them more useful and safer to be around.
Okay.
So we have to give them the butterfly.
That worked so hard!
All right, butterfly time.
The butterfly is recovered.
All right, I think it likes you.
Deviant power owner.
That's us!
One's Dragoon!
Deviations can be very dangerous if not taken care of.
They can radiate stardust, which can lead to all kinds of
unpredictable consequences.
This is why we created the Mayflies.
and securement units to keep deviations contained we're
finding ways for humans and deviations to live in harmony
this is our best chance of cleaning up rosetta's mess so
what exactly are deviations no one's exactly sure what they
are just that they're not bound by the physical laws of our
world they came from another dimension something don't worry
gamer if our game survives another month will tell you what
they actually are.
So what exactly you're trying to do?
Some deviations are friendly, like the butterfly.
But others, like the ones inside monoliths, are extremely
dangerous.
It's not practical to secure all of them.
we can learn more about them maybe we can find ways to live
alongside them that's the goal you must be prepared the
stardust just keeps spreading and we aren't sure why oh
they're coming we're here for the butterflies horde mode
time be careful that must be a siren a siren they must have
gotten through come on meta a deviation from another world
just entered this space and it won't go a fight take the
butterfly with you it can help oh god okay i'm gonna take it
how do i do this uh withdraw all right it's in my pocket now
all right no endurance weapons oh okay now we have a jacket
armor we have armor now where where is it where the fuck
where's my armor is this oh there we go all right we put our
armor on i know i know guys We're gonna put, I know, I know
you might not want, oh my God, Jesus Christ.
Do we still have no pants?
Okay, all right.
Don't need no armor.
All right, is this pants?
Am I finally gonna get pants here?
Is this it?
Oh no, it's fabric.
Apparently not.
It's still not pants time, apparently.
Oh shit.
somebody's diary.
Who cares?
Alright, let's see.
Are there any pants here?
I'm just wondering if there's any pants at all.
Oh, there's Medkit, though.
Alright.
I already took the thing.
Synchroize.
Attach wire.
Building feature is locked.
Wait, what?
I took the butterfly?
Uh.
Wait, what am I supposed to do?
Interact unit to view details.
Oh, I have to view it.
How do I view?
Oh, okay.
Based at its auto attack, sink the cradle.
Combat deviations are a special type of deviation while
aggressive.
We'll take instructions.
Oh.
The dormancy threshold of a combat deviation cannot be
adjusted to false to 100.
After sinking, you can summon it to attack.
Oh, the butterflies will fight for me.
Oh, I see.
Target attack.
So they're like dangerous.
They're like dangerous butterflies.
Use green light and mood recovery speed increases.
All right.
Oh.
What?
This is what tension means.
We're in here.
All right, guys.
It's Minecraft.
It's Minecraft!
Guys, it's time for Minecraft.
We gotta cut the trees.
Because we have to cut...
Okay, equipped a gathering tool before you start collect.
It's much faster than doing it all barehand.
You can craft gathering tools at your campsites or supplies
work.
Okay, this is a lot different from what I saw on the
trailers.
I'm just gonna say this is...
The more advanced, the more...
This is not what I expected from the trailer.
It's not gonna lie.
Or time!
I think I'm playing Arc right now.
Guys, we tricked ourselves into playing Arc again.
Well, we can't get scammed if it's free.
game free arc guys free arc all right we gotta cut some
trees and we always come back to Minecraft this is free to
play arc guys free to play arc it's in the description you
guys know I don't read I just watch videos the videos I saw
once human was like people shooting monsters that's like
What I saw, so I was not expecting this.
I saw, like, I guess they, like, skipped the building part
of this game, so I never noticed it.
Alright.
Alright, let's see.
We need more ores.
Oh my god, there's so many ores around us.
Alright, don't worry, we're almost here.
Now I know what he's been farming.
Now I know.
Alright, here you go.
let's see we're almost there yay i just set up a campsite
okay i'm gonna live next to i'm gonna live next to the i'm
gonna live next to her all right craft a bare hands in a
campsite to craft basic gear tools and dishes these will
help you survive better in the wilderness guys i don't
remember which is the stage where i get to actually interact
with real people craft with bare hands okay uh items
including gathering tool and wait do i not have pickaxe
already okay yeah shouldn't i have a pickaxe or what all
right toggle between the tables oh okay crossbow pants all
right guys just for you guys i won't craft pants uh do i
have a i have a crossbow ready right okay i don't I mean,
that's gun.
That's sort of like gun.
Alright.
Oh, I need to create arrows.
There you go.
I don't think I need like more than five.
Alright, nice.
Open survival to view crackdown attacking deviance.
Are they coming over now?
You're a bit thirsty.
Okay, let me...
Collect water.
Alright.
Collecting the water.
Oh, there's a butterfly!
Do you see it?
So, like, instead of a child, there is a butterfly in my
backpack.
Alright, let's see.
Uh, I want to...
I want to...
Wait, how do I boil water?
Oh, there you go.
Boil water.
Nice.
Yay!
And then I gotta drink my water.
Oh my gosh, I have so much water.
Stay hydrated, guys.
I'm not hungry yet, so we're fine.
Yeah, this is like the original Fortnite.
Alright, I'm ready.
Fight.
What was that?
Is this like plants versus zombies, too?
Oh my god, it's like plants versus zombies!
They're here to attack my butterflies.
It's everything I've ever wanted.
RTX on Plants versus Zombies.
It does look like Siren Head.
Oh, shit.
What the fuck?
That is a lot bigger than I expected.
Oh, no.
We're...
How do I use it?
okay weapon create open the weapon he's coming over uh uh
where's my arrow you have entered what you mean what do you
mean why can't i do i not have equipped okay uh click on oh
no that's not what i wanted no no i don't want that okay uh
all right equipped arrow oh i hope this pauses
Okay.
170 HP.
Does he have a head?
Am I headshotting?
Am I?
Oh my god.
Auto attack.
Do your thing.
Okay.
Oh shit, the turrets are automatic.
Oh, what the fuck?
My butterflies are so strong!
Bro, why am I wasting my arrows?
Wait, I'm just gonna wait.
It's just standing there menacingly.
It's so strong, guys.
What was that?
Festering gel?
What did I secure?
The deviation escape?
No!
Alright, let's see.
That was easy.
Oh, talk to me.
Damn, it escaped.
That was a difficult fight.
Just driving it away was enough.
And it's all thanks to you.
All right, I opted a little bit.
You're tougher than you look.
That's twice now, you're sorry.
Tanya's just waiting for me in the town right now.
Ha ha ha ha.
Yes.
Mitsuko created this Rift Space.
A refuge from the dangers of the physical world.
Or so we thought.
Do you think that deviation will come back?
What if it returns with greater disruptions?
It's possible.
We can't just sit here and wait, though.
Meta, will you go back to the physical world with me?
All right.
Sure.
Wait, that wasn't even the physical world?
There's...
Oh, I thought...
Oh, yeah, this is a deviation world.
That way, I can lend you some of my strength.
Hopefully, we'll meet again one day.
When the Stardust is stable enough, it looks like this is
goodbye.
All right.
Good luck, Meta.
Goodbye.
All right, time to leave.
It's time.
We can finally, we can finally bump into tension.
We finally did it.
Oh
my gosh.
I'm dropping down Oh
My god fortnight Where am I going look at that 20 years
after starfall and the world is still infested with star
dust It looks like the monoliths here have been reactivated
to They might hold the key to all the star dust pollution
where wait where where do I go?
Is this it?
where's like where's where people would like hang out like
where do people hang out where are we dropping oh okay okay
okay all right i'm not sure i don't do that i i don't make
sure oh no it's dark it's dark and scary find a suitable
location and press b to place a territory to Terminal?
Wait, maybe he lives here.
Maybe that's where he is.
There's somebody house here.
Who lives here?
Oh, this is glitches territory.
Okay, that's, I don't think that's...
Okay, forms and defies.
Okay.
Alright, we gotta meet up with Tendunel.
Hello?
Hi, how are you doing?
I'm finally here.
You're finally here?
Yeah, I finally made it.
Where are you?
I'm...
Don't worry about it.
What do you mean?
Which world are you in?
We're in the same server.
What do you mean?
It's an MMO.
There's different worlds and shit.
We chose the same server.
There's in the chat on the top number six.
Is it the donkey?
What?
Someone sniping us.
Ten is in world six.
Where am I?
I'm world five.
How do I get to world six?
You gotta find a teleportation tower.
Teleportate.
How do you learn so much?
Yeah.
What do you mean?
Teleportation.
Yeah, teleportation.
Where the fuck is that?
What the fuck is a teleportation tower?
I wouldn't know, bro.
I wouldn't.
I'm like, it's right there.
i mean i'm how did you learn about the teleportations
because i'm near one okay um how do i open that map okay um
there is somebody oh i found it i found okay okay i need a i
found it okay um how do i how do i pin this okay track place
pin okay there we go all right i figured it out I'm heading
there now.
You figured it out?
It would have been a lot easier when I was in the sky if I
knew that.
Yep, probably.
Oh my god.
There's like some deviance in front of me.
I'm going to outrun this.
I have a gun.
How did you get a gun already?
What the fuck?
Just to let you know, I have a goddamn gun.
You have a gun?
Also, like, okay, you've seen the trailers for this game
before, right?
Yep.
This is not what I expected.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I thought everybody was playing this game, and I was like,
oh, that's cool.
Like, they're shooting monsters.
It was like, what's that game called?
The other, um, the other, like, Dark Souls-like game that's
like for shooting?
What is it called?
The, um, it's like shooting Dark Souls.
Right.
Remnant some Yeah, yeah, I thought it'd be like remnants It
would be like remnant That's what it looked like If someone
gave play from others Then it looked like remnant So I was
like I'm like making a house I'm crafting I thought it'd be
like Remnant
Oh my gosh We should have played remnant instead We should
okay let's i'm heading up to the tower i'm heading up oh
we're running oh my god yeah i met some few people i turned
on voice chat just in case there's a lot of people that i i
met actually oh you met people already how did you meet
people like what were we doing i was just going around and
they were like oh they were showing me stuff oh they were
hearing you they were boosting you no okay i i stayed away
from people because yeah but you said they were helping you
no they're just approaching me i don't want to be approached
okay i'm i'm here i'm in the i'm in world 6 where are you
are you at the i'm at the teleportation tower i'm at
69405041 what six nine five five one okay just follow the
road what the is this map did you scroll back from the map
yeah what the there's like some there's like level 30 like
the level 32 zone do you have okay i have a question do you
have a pants no i didn't i don't have Okay, like, I could
have wore pants, but for the dragoons, I did not wear pants.
I don't care.
There was a way you can, you can, like, you can make pants,
but I decided not to make pants.
I did not have a pants.
All right, uh, wait, where are you?
What do you mean, follow the road?
There's so many roads.
Wait, where are you?
I'm at the teleportation tower.
No, you're not?
World 6.
All right, world 6 too.
Is that you?
There's multiple- That's you, I see.
Where are you?
Oh, there you are.
You're so lucky there's no PvP.
Yep.
What the f-
What do we do in this game?
I honestly have no clue.
I don't know.
Trade, add friends.
Oh shit, yes.
Okay.
Hey, this is free.
Fight the team?
Yes.
No, no, wait.
Is it the other way around?
How come you have your butterflies?
Where my butterfly died?
I think my butterfly died.
What the fuck happened to my butterfly?
Where's your other butterfly?
Where did my butterfly go?
He died!
I wouldn't even know where your butterfly is.
There's no air holes.
Oh, shit.
Is it the other way around?
I think you should actually you shouldn't.
All right, wait.
Why aren't you fighting?
No, it's okay.
You use your butterfly to fight.
Okay, no, you know what?
Transferred leadership.
No, I don't want to be leader!
Why?
How did you do that?
Wait, my butterfly's still dead!
It doesn't do anything!
What?
My butterfly's still dead!
Oh no, what happened to him?
Make a base.
Wait, we're gonna make a base?
Okay.
What we're gonna do?
Alright, you fight that guy.
Did I just headbutton?
Yeah, you did.
I'm gonna loot your shit.
Alright.
Rest in peace, butterfly.
you're not that's my base welcome wait is that your base is
that your base over there what the fuck this is my base okay
give me a second i need to beat this guy up i know i want to
waste my air is this their base oh my god yeah yeah this is
my base what even oh you have entered tangents territory oh
it's because you have your i didn't put my thing i didn't
put my uh terminal
Oh, that guy shot you.
Oh, I can't build it here because you own that area.
Okay, this is my base, too.
This is my area.
You're building it there.
This is my...
But seriously, making a base is not what I expected in this
game.
This is not what...
This is not...
I told you, it's ARC.
It's free to play ARC.
Oh, my God.
Hello, neighbor.
Ah, hey.
You got your butterfly?
Wait, I need to get my butterfly.
Okay, a used facility.
All right.
Yeah, okay, my butterfly is here now.
Yeah, there's my butterfly.
There he is.
Yeah.
Okay, tab to open the function window and select Creole to
enter the metric screen.
Open the...
What the fuck?
There's so much information in this screen.
That would be metric.
Oh, you can, like, upgrade info.
the fuck yeah yeah there's like what yeah there's there's
some stuff what there's stoves what the fuck am i looking at
rainwater y'all might as well let's grab rainwater i can't
water is important what the fuck oh my god this is this is
definitely not what i expected um i don't know defense but
no this is like seven days seven days to die plus arc
because there's like defense stuff against the the deviant
slash zombies the copyright free zombie zombies hell yeah
they're smelting oh my god i'm getting overwhelmed here i'm
actually yeah there's so there's so much this is a lot more
than i expected i saw how much more more do i have i bought
ammunition okay all right i used up all everything uh okay i
used up all my upgrade stuff i did it and unlocked the
disassembly bench oh shit i did not unlock i did not unlock
the thing that they want me to lock i oh shit there's a
disassembly well i have a disassembly to unlock the
disassembly bench and i was like no no okay um i don't want
this okay all right there you territory upgrades i can have
more territory i think gather gravel territory expansion
what the fuck what is even happening okay uh facilities this
assembly bench okay oh i don't have gravel wait where the
fuck is gravel it's it's in the rock it's in the rock okay
take me to there what i don't even know right there is it
these these rocks the bigger ones yeah these when do we
fucking kill that's what I like to know when do we get to
shoot shoot where are we fighting some bosses and do shit
you know I thought we were gonna fight bosses I thought this
is gonna be remnant bro so it's like it's pow world all over
again oh my god you kitten that first escape from powworld i
need copper they're forcing me to build tension wait i can
share my stuff wait we can share you can share yeah what do
you need okay oh we can like share stuff so if you have
stuff and then we can share it to me oh my god it's powworld
without the paths guys we can't just suddenly switch to
remnant tangent has to download something for two plus hours
At least this was free.
Oh, wait, there is copper.
There's a lot of coppers.
Yeah, there's so much coffee here.
Where the fuck are the people?
You don't want...
You don't want to talk to the people.
You don't want to talk...
No, I just want handouts.
You just want handouts.
Any sniper is in the server and then we're willing to give
their stuff.
we'll take a gun we'll take a gun or two like yeah yeah yeah
we just want handouts that's all we want so we can go
straight to so we can go straight to the bosses we just want
to have the boss fight this is the only reason okay alright
disassembly you got the stuff um how the fuck wait I need
copper ingots what the fuck i need to make ingots i need to
smith it i yeah i have a furnace if you want to use yeah i'm
gonna use your furnace can i use your furnace i don't want
to waste my i i think you can wait what the oh i can oh my
god how the wait how do i put my ink it this game's stupid
how do i put my you have a chest already
making a base and i'm not even lying how do i put my ink
it's in your inventory i can't do it wait why are you two
furnaces because you can only for you know smell one items
at a time we didn't i need you need a charcoal i think i
need charcoal how the fuck put charcoal in it right now what
the fuck well i dropped oh i only have one charcoal yeah put
it so I can start crafting there I'll just 20 seconds 20
seconds no I don't see no do I was it cuz like I have to use
my own I don't know this is I was tempted to craft a fishing
rod I don't know I was just like maybe I'll do it Just for
old time's sake.
Let's see.
Oh my god.
I don't even have it unlocked.
It never told me to unlock the furnace.
Wait.
How do I share?
Okay.
How do I share this with you?
I need to unlock a furnace.
I actually needed the furnace.
I need to reset this.
Smithing.
Did you get this from the chat?
all right oh yeah i'm gonna i'm gonna build i'm gonna build
a furnace now uh where the fuck is the furnace where is it i
thought i bought oh there it is all right use the furnace to
refine raw materials you could reset them more practical oh
thank god okay oh yeah okay i got yeah you need
Like, I need, I can't use yours.
I have to use my own.
Wasabi wants to do, who the fuck is Wasabi?
Is Wasabi gonna fucking boost us?
I don't know.
You know what?
Fuck it, Wasabi.
Get in here.
You're level 10.
How do I get glass?
Wait, we have to fucking, you're, like, ahead of me.
So, you're, like, we need glass now.
I'm like, what do you mean we need glass?
Don't worry about it.
What do you mean we need glass?
I need glass.
What do we need glass for?
You might not need it yet.
I need glass.
Oh no!
Okay, I need to make 10 copper ingots?
Oh my god.
Okay.
Just keep crafting.
You have nothing to worry about.
just keep crafting just keep crafting keep doing it i was
just spamming ones and i realized i could just craft all
okay give me all right and i can craft more oh my god all
right wasabi wanted to join our team and then wasabi wasabi
left us that's funny no No one wants to be.
Why does no one want to be on our team?
I don't understand.
We just want to get carried.
We just want to...
Escape Social Hive, create a guild for sure.
We just want handouts.
We need to make a guild.
Is that too much to ask for?
Customer support.
We just want handouts.
We just want handouts, yeah.
Yeah.
We don't want much in life.
Just handouts.
to share base it needs to be the same guild oh okay you make
the guild tension you learn how to make a guild i'm gonna go
fucking loot shit i want to loot shit no what you learn how
to make a guild right now it's okay we have number six
number six is gonna number six was the guy that was like
You're at the wrong world, Doki.
Number six is going to give us handouts.
Do you want handouts or not?
I definitely do want a handout.
Number six is the chosen one.
Number six.
Number six, give us handouts.
I love this.
All right, let's see.
Am I crafting?
Chat, Abel, Abel, help me.
All right, am I good to go?
Okay, I can finally build a disassembly thing.
All right.
Hell yeah.
Is that a deer?
You die.
You're going to kill a deer?
What do you need deer for?
We have enough food.
Wait, we have number six to give us handouts.
What do you...
Bro, I nuked still.
Bro, A.F., but I'll work hard.
But, well, at least show us some effort.
I'm sure I build a disassembly thing.
I'm sure you did.
Okay, let's see.
I need to build this assembly.
Oh my god, we're... I'm always like so confused when I'm
building.
I have no idea what this is even for.
Building in these kinds of games gets me overwhelmed
sometimes.
Yeah, no, there's so much stuff.
Yeah.
Like I unlock one stuff and then there's another better
option.
and I was like, ah.
Wait, this assembly scrap at...
Wait, this is like...
This is...
This is Rust.
Wait a minute.
You're right.
Wait, this is Rust.
You're not wrong for that.
This assembly thing is Rust.
But, uh, honestly, I've never played Rust.
Oh my god.
This is...
So I wouldn't know.
This is everything.
God won't do much against those deviants up.
claim rewards though yeah the people in chat is like it's
been rust this entire time it's been rust this entire time
maybe the rust was us all along it was us all along okay how
do we make a guild guys we want to make a guild press you go
to give oh oh wait a hive there we go create hive What do
you want?
That's what's called?
Hi.
Yeah.
What do you want?
What's the name?
Uh, Dragoon.
Give us handouts.
Oh, free handouts.
Name it.
Dragoons.
Free handouts.
Dragoon employers.
Oh, if you...
Shit.
What's a good name?
Give me a good name, guys.
Dragoon Incorporated.
Dragoon.
dragon ink dragon dragon ink we're striving join our guild
join our guild dragon ink please is it free please tell me
it's free it's free yeah recruit me i want to join dragon
ink uh shit drawing dragon ink today so you can provide us
guns and we can fight a boss instantly how do i invite you
to the guild oh fucking no geez maybe you have to search it
wait how do you how do you find the guild uh press you and
then there's like five uh and then there's Oh, fine hive.
Yeah.
Dragoon.
Okay, let's see.
There is a lot.
Okay.
Dragoon.
I like how there's like one was like no game.
There's no.
There's no dragoon.
Dragoon.
Okay, drag.
There's Ethan and Jake.
We should join.
Who the hell is Ethan and Jake?
I don't know, but there's a hive called Ethan.
There's a hive called Ethan.
I want to join Ethan.
Ethan Who the fuck is Ethan and Jake?
I'm going to apply Ethan and Jake's hat.
Why did you apply to the hat?
I didn't, but I like Ethan and Jake.
Invite the hive, there we go.
I sent you an application.
You sent me an application.
But Ethan and Jake!
Ethan and Jake looks so cool.
I'm going to transfer you the leadership.
No, stop transferring me the leadership.
Because it's not my shit.
It's your name and the company.
I wanted to join Ethan and Jake.
What?
Ethan and Jake looked like they were having fun.
Shh, shh, shh.
Wait, what?
Enter flight mode.
There's flight mode.
There's flight mode?
Okay, what do we do now?
Now that we have a guild?
I honestly don't know.
Wait, what?
You're the one that suggested the guild!
My chat says to get the guild that you can share buildings.
Wait, number six has like a cool shirt and underwear.
Does number six even know what he's doing?
I don't know, actually.
Hive review.
There's no hive history.
Our hive fucking sucks.
We're just here.
I bet Ethan and Jake in this place is cooler.
Give us permission.
Where is it?
We should join Ethan and Jake.
Come on, let's apply it to their guild.
Let's do it.
Apply to the guild.
Apply to Ethan and Jake's guild.
It'll be so fun.
Maybe Ethan and Jake will carry us.
How can I report my own guild?
No, you can't even report?
Wait, what do you mean?
I can report my own guild.
That's funny.
I made the guild and I can report it myself.
That's so stupid.
Oh, shit.
let's see yeah i can't report it i can just leave your guild
i just leave it what the fuck is warband oh that's like the
guild leadership oh they're like the guild uh rankings yeah
yeah the leaderboards oh my god oh my god hope i saw easton
and jake are having a good time i hope all right let's let's
figure out our first mission Go into the monolith ruin to
search for supplies.
Did you go there yet?
I went there, yeah.
You already did the mission?
I did that, but I have not done the next one.
What's the next one?
Okay, I have to do it.
Where is it?
Where's the monolith ruin?
You come with me!
What do you mean?
Yeah, alright.
This is a collab.
Yeah, yeah, I'll follow you.
I don't even know where the fucking place is anymore.
What do you mean?
Oh, hey, there's number six.
Number six?
There's number six.
That's the guy that's in our guild No, what who's no, who's
this that's the guy that was like after image That's the guy
that was that's number.
Yeah, that's number six.
What do you mean?
There's nobody there What the heck?
There's nobody there There's no put these there What did you
see?
I don't know, bro.
I am gonna raise the volume a little bit little bit more see
all right all right yeah wait how did you do that i i have a
whole emote list wait how did you do that what's the list uh
where is it what button is that uh it's probably in the same
menu as the mimetics okay uh okay i need to go to what the
fuck it's So far.
Is it this?
It's not.
You can...
There's fast travels.
Don't worry about it.
There is Yeah, you can fast travel through the base, but I'm
not sure of going there though.
Where the fuck is the fast travel?
Teleport?
I know, but where?
Where did...
Which one did you teleport?
No, not the mission, but I can teleport to the home.
Oh, you go there and then you teleport back.
Is that what you mean?
Oh, okay.
Well, I still have to go there.
Okay.
yeah let's go lead the way uh all right it's this way uh you
can glide yeah that's what i'm gonna do i think i thought
i'm pretty sure all right it's this way i'm trying to figure
out the movement yeah you're actually challenged no because
like the track the map tracker thing makes it look like it's
they make you follow the road instead of like the shortest
way like they're trying to be like Like, you have to follow,
like, road safety laws, you know?
Like, yeah.
And I'm just like, yeah, no.
I do not care.
I just go straight through.
It's not like that you have cars or anything.
I'm assuming there is cars.
Yeah.
Oh, there's a guy right in front of us.
We should have done PvP.
No.
You're right.
They would have killed us anyway.
They would 100% kill us.
All right.
I can't believe it.
There's people in front of us.
all right let's i'm almost there i'm so smart with my
gliding thing oh my god this is rust all right guys if you
guys want to stream snide of us and give us handouts feel
free to join our server feel free to join our guild i can't
believe this is like an mmo as well yeah i was thinking
something else like no i was thinking of i used i thought
this was remnant i literally saw the trailers and it looked
like remnant it literally looked like remnant well honestly
i can't trust anything nowadays yeah i can't trust things
anymore like you know i watched like gameplay videos too and
it was like it reminded me of remnant and like the other the
other extraction shooter the the one with like uh with like
monsters the what's it ashes whatever it's called ash um
gosh i'm gonna try to remember what it's called i haven't
really kept up with any games like upcoming stuff because
basically everything has been a disappointment yeah that's
so true i played a beta it was really good was beta like
this i don't was the beta like this like somebody was like i
mean i I mean, I wouldn't say the game sucks.
I guess it's just...
Bro, this guy's a motorcycle.
What the fuck?
How long has he been playing this game?
He has a bed.
He's level 9.
Bro, wait, I can...
Number 6.
I can use their bed.
You're level 2?
Crazy.
Oh, my God.
It was always advertised as a survival.
It just...
When I watched the trailer, it didn't seem like a survival.
Bible game.
It had more combat.
You do your stuff.
I got the thing.
Look for, wait, look for Rosetta supply.
Oh, we have to, like, look around for more supplies.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
I'm going to start snapping.
And then you talk to a lady and then...
Oh, and then...
Okay.
Wait, somebody's house has, like, turrets and everything.
Well, it's Fallout 4.
Yeah, it's...
no it's rest another settlement needs your help no all right
let's grab this another guy all right here are they good
friends are they good people i mean they can't yeah they
can't yeah they can't fight us anyway i need to collect six
discarded items nearby wait these oh okay go to the entrance
of the monolith what the fuck oh it's over here yeah
Mary hello Mary oh yeah I don't see your name on it bitch
you're pretty cocky for someone who doesn't even have a
weapon quite impressive to be honest since you can fast
travel I'm gonna go back to the base for a while just to
give it a little bit of a modification or I thought I was
the only oh this guy's a meta human too I'm Mary it's a good
thing I met you oh now she's nice to me his fellow maplies
we should be able to help each other out I came here to
investigate a deviation that's been causing issues I think
it's connected to a recently reopened monolith nearby that
there uh I'm chasing nation as well don't tell me you're
going to try and take on a powerful deviation bare-handed
even an ordinary bow tear you apart right now yeah she was
like oh no you don't you don't have anything yeah i have a
bow we have a guild trust me yeah we have it's not as good
as ethan and jake but like we haven't come find me in
dudsville it's the nearest survivor settlement we can I did
not make this or...
Two heads are better than one.
Then I'd never turn down help.
Okay.
Oh, wait, she gave me a gun!
The huntsman!
So another Mayfly survives.
Insufficient permission.
Why?
This is my territory.
Oh.
I can teleport back home now.
How do I move the shit?
And where are you doing?
with my stuff that's my question i put your house check your
memetics and start by building a gear workbench the
disassembly a store you take objects you've scavenged why do
you store it you don't want to be my neighbor no i want to
move it to a better place what do you mean you chose this
area the only reason why you got there the only reason why i
lived here was because you live there and now you're gonna
disassemble i see i see now How did I move next to you?
You're going to move away.
You're saying stuff.
I see.
Unlock the gear workbench.
Why do you want to move?
I need a flatter surface.
This is flat.
Dude, I live next to a cliff.
What's wrong with that?
What's wrong with that, damn?
okay i need a gear workshop all right shit oh i got a
baseball bat too whoa i have all the materials guys uh gear
workbench i need more copper oh my god i need more copper
what the yeah i love these copper ores i miss i miss having
handouts not to play the game for real The structure cannot
build near a strong...
How do I move?
How do I move my shit?
This is stupid.
I forgot what it was like to actually play a game for real.
I...
God damn.
Back to the mines I go.
Relocate.
Time to actually ride.
No.
I can't people enable me.
Oh, I can't move territory.
Okay, that's how you move territory.
All right.
Okay, let's see.
Is there any flatter surface than this?
There's a lot of people's homes.
I can't believe you moved away.
Look, just move away.
Did you move to?
Hold on, hold on.
This is still your territory.
I'm trying to move it.
I'm moving my territory.
No, you're not.
I need a flatter surface, man.
Yeah, but everybody claimed everything.
It's just like my Minecraft server.
Oh, yeah, you have a Minecraft server.
Yeah, yeah.
Like, I logged into my Minecraft server, and literally
everything was claimed, even the oceans, that were around
me.
It's just, it's like...
Because I have, like, a...
I'm slowly hiring, like, a moderation team for the Minecraft
server.
And, like, one of the mods that we had...
Like, new mods that we hired to do the Minecraft server.
They were crying in the mod chat being like, There's nowhere
to build my home.
All the dragons have taken all the land.
And I was like, I was like reading the chat.
And then I got in the server.
And I was like, all right, let's find you at home.
And we literally rode the boat for, like, like, hundreds of
blocks that were surrounding me.
Like, in the ocean.
Ocean that surrounded the territory the land was claimed
We're on the boat for like an hour just trying to find an
unclaimed land And then I felt bad and I just like I was
like okay, you can build on my land You can build on my land
I
Overlaps with battle unit.
What does that even mean?
Are you still trying to find land to claim?
I'm literally watching you from here.
I don't get it.
This is crazy.
There's so much prerequisites to like, fucking build a
house.
I'm literally still watching you.
This is the only game where I can have a fucking affordable
housing.
I'm still watching you try to find a place.
Holy shit Holy shit.
I'm just gonna watch you.
I'm watching you.
Oh my god.
Oh my fucking god.
It does not auto build.
God damn.
This is stupid Is there?
Is there V?
I summoned V to talk to him.
Well, I can open the Wikipedia.
What the fuck?
Wait, the crow is like a battle pass shop What the fuck?
He crawls the fucking shop!
Oh my god.
Okay.
He's still there.
He's all the way there, guys.
He's all the way there.
I'm making shit, bro.
I'm making shit.
Are you still...
Your house is still here.
You haven't even moved it.
What do you mean?
Wait, did you move it?
Oh, you did.
Oh, shit.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe you moved away.
That's so fucked up What okay build mode.
I need a build a I'm gonna stay.
This is my area now.
I'm not gonna move Here you see my home.
I think you'll move no, that's fine because you know, we're
not gonna play this on day two I just want to have a house
This is the only time I can have affordable housing
was not like this okay all right I'm fucking trying to get
my copper in yeah at least it's free guys it was free okay
nice do I have enough I don't know if I haven't okay let's
see all right I'm thirsty am I oh shit I am okay Yeah, you
need to eat and drink in this game.
I forgot about that.
At least, like, the eating part is not like...
You don't have to worry about the eating part a lot, I feel
like.
Because, like, the eating...
Your stomach doesn't go down as fast.
I'm out of materials.
They said I have enough.
What the fuck?
Who told you that?
Guys, I got Bout Pass plus one.
Goddamn UI applied to me.
I don't have enough.
i like how whenever you uh craft something successfully it
gives you a plus battle pass i still need two more coppers
are you kidding me okay uh all right get all 10 get in there
all right what happened to number six he disappeared number
six give me a gun that's not i don't think number six uh
Give me a gun, number six.
Alright, let's see.
I'm gonna chill here.
I need to wait for my copper to construct.
When does the multiplayer in this game kick in?
Like, I'm...
That's what I'm curious about.
When does the multiplayer kick in in this game?
Alright.
got all my crafting material and then is there the gear
workshop?
Okay, finally.
Finally, I have made the gear workshop.
I only took...
Oh my god!
How do I make gun?
Insufficient material?
What kind of material do I need?
What the...
What the fuck is all?
this oh my god there is like a lot of materials you're
supposed to gather to create a fucking gun apparently uh and
build a supplies workshop what's the supplies workshop what
the fuck i need more copper everything is copper are you
oppressing the rights of me making my own house okay never
mind number six i need give me all your copper I don't I
don't need gun anymore.
I just want coffee There's an alligator in front of my house
There's an alligator kill him for material Kill him for
materials Okay I'm gonna cut this tree.
Oh my god the tree grew back Nice That's what I needed I
needed more trees Yeah it stopped raining i don't understand
remember like people were make the mixed reviews people were
complaining about how there's too many people queuing up for
this game and i'm like what just pick different servers
all right let's see i think this game could be fun if like
if it's like with people that you know if i made like a
dragoon server it could be fun as well But like I have a
house You should come to my house.
All right.
Give me a sec.
I'm crafting right now You should You should you should uh I
got my chance like no it wouldn't stop coping It could be
guys.
Okay, I'm coming over to your house I have affordable
housing.
Hey, where are you?
Where the fuck do you live now?
Oh, there you are?
way to get handouts here yep hell is yeah all right here I
come we haven't found a single person with a car yet wait
where do you live is this your house you built that it came
with the blueprint wait what the fuck did you build this it
came with the blueprint did you steal somebody's house Or
did you literally just build this yourself?
I literally just built this.
How did you get this?
What the fuck?
How did you get that?
Affordable housing.
Where did you get this?
What do you mean, where did I get this?
I got the material.
Where did you get the blueprint for this?
There's a blueprint.
It comes with the blueprint.
We have it.
Which blueprint?
What?
Yeah.
Okay, wait.
wait a minute just just press v and then right click okay on
the right house blueprints and then there's presets for it
apparently what i saw i was like i saw an exquisite villa
and i was like oh shit oh my god wait you what the fuck how
do we wait how do i i made this i made this Oh my god.
Wait, what the fuck?
Wait.
What?
Oh my god.
You can actually build a house?
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Alright guys.
Well now I know.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm sorry man.
This is just a madly urge.
This is time.
I need affordable housing.
I can't.
I can't believe they hid this from us.
Guys, I need his free real estate.
Guys, now I need...
Now I need a house, too.
Now you need a house, huh?
Oh, man.
Wait, I want the truck house.
How do I get the truck house?
I think you need a truck, though.
You need a truck for a truck house?
It doesn't give me a...
It doesn't give me...
give me the truck okay there's like there's like three
different garage that's up that the truck isn't included i
can't believe it why is the truck not included i don't know
it should be included i have the materials but i just
everything is just overwhelmed all right well i know where i
want live where's the permissions friends permissions access
to felts just look these in the structure cannot be built
near a road what do you mean exactly that's why that's why
i'm trying to find some flatter areas all right that's it
i'm moving it's moving time yep yeah i know right i'm
fucking doing it you bitch that's why i moved as well it's
so you didn't tell me you did not give
it's a surprise i made a house you said nothing of course
i've been like i don't want to move if i knew if i knew you
couldn't okay how did you how did you did you like did you
like disassemble dimash everything or like i is it's like b
and then z b and z b and then z to move territory you just
have to walk over an area oh my god what the The chat teach
you your more people played in more people on your stream
play this game Honestly, I don't know My chat's like I don't
know what to do Look man, this is southeast Asia.
We play anything that's free I swear all right okay let's
see
relocation has a 10 minute cooldown yeah that's fine i'm
fine with that all right it's time uh let's see build how do
i still not able to build this house yeah it's annoying
right god damn I found it.
Why don't you make the shack?
No, no, no, I found it.
You found it?
I found a place.
What are you building?
I found it.
Is this a tower?
Are you building the tower house?
Ah, you're building the tower house.
Oh, no.
Holy shit.
The little John sits in the corner.
My building now.
Yeah, you know, that house reminds me of those.
You know those memes there.
Galvanized square beat No, why can't I build where's the
fastest way to do this I wish it's instant I have to like
move and look every fucking are you fucking kidding me but
but but I think there's flight there's flight There's flight
the the flight cameras uh on the left I don't know let me
fucking oh my god do I have to like deconstruct this No.
It won't let me keep building.
No, no.
No help build.
Did I fuck it up?
Oh no, I canceled it.
Do I have to redo this?
Oh no, I don't.
No, no.
It exceeds territory range.
What do you mean it exceeds territory range?
There's like a white border.
Oh my god.
I have to move my house closer.
Did you build it outside?
I didn't know.
Yeah, this game is so clunky.
This game is clunky as shit.
Wait, why can't I build my door?
The door is in the territory.
What do you mean it exceeds territory?
It's literally in the territory.
How does it exceed it?
I mean, if I look at the fucking square, some parts of your
building is like outside.
How does it exceed it?
I don't know if it's dead.
more trees I need to move the territory better please I need
I need my tower house killing a whole deer family here I'm
cutting I'm destroying the environment fuck the trees we
don't need oxygen well we need a house grows back instantly
yeah the house is more important affordable housing Exactly.
All right.
Like, would you rather die in a nice home or just die in the
fucking street?
I would rather die in a nice home.
I want a house.
That's all I want.
Yeah, we didn't see, we didn't even care about the fighting
game.
We just want to build.
How do I have insuffiction?
I have 300 fucking wood.
Well, you need like a thousand four hundred.
Yeah, but I still have the wood.
good i still have it though i don't know about that can i
help you build yeah can you help me you don't have
permission wait how do i give you permission uh you go to
hive and then click my name right okay give me a sec i'm
moving my house a little bit better here okay how do i yeah
you go to hive give me a sec i've left my territory
permission okay there you go no i have to wait okay go to
hive and then uh hive okay wait i need to this is the
hardest game ever yep okay what do i do go to hive and then
what click my name yeah and then what there's like friends
permission no i can delete oh there it is okay uh enable
enable enable you use it to storage stuff too okay let's see
can i build okay build my home yeah then there's your door
that's your door that's your door that's your fucking door
wait what the how could you do that and i couldn't holy
that's funny how were you able to do it but i can yeah you
have a door that's unreachable congratulations i have an
unreachable door no i can look see hello you can yeah you
can go out but you can't you can't come in wait wait this is
an issue wait this is an issue because we can't go out into
the house oh shit oh shit you can climb we know you can't
wait can you climb wait yeah but then the door has to always
be open or we can unlock the door yeah well that's not a
problem yeah yeah yeah this is the safest home this is the
safest home the most fucking we have to unlock the toy here
and then go up like this yeah no one can raid it yeah nobody
can raid my house Close the door and just log out there.
Just no one can go there.
Alright.
Nice.
We're so good at this game.
Ha!
Okay.
Alright.
I have like six more minutes before I can... I'm gonna go
crash at your house.
Let's see.
We don't even have beds.
Yeah.
Furniture is just a concept to me.
We are just an empty house.
Yeah, my house is going to be taller than your house.
Yeah, three floors.
Yeah.
We haven't bumped into, like, a single boss type yet.
We've just been building a house.
This is more important, chat.
This is a lot more important.
Remember, affordable housing.
This is so much more important, guys.
You don't understand.
Okay, let me see.
You guys wouldn't understand, guys.
They wouldn't get it.
You wouldn't get it.
the most important part in the video game trying to figure
out like which place can like guarantee that my house is
like uh it's like okay it's like I don't know I've been
trying to find stuff but then I found out my house area is
like swarmed with alligators so I'm like yeah but what are
alligators gonna do we're gonna do nothing I haven't seen a
single alligator that's like near you yet it was there so
many of them please adjust the height did you kill all of
them probably yeah i didn't see any of the alligators yeah
right here right here here here here i just saw i can't wait
really wait i'm sorry i'm trying to figure out my house
still there's a alligator holy oh my god i'm trying to
figure out how to where can i put this Where can I put
There's nothing Oh, wait, wait, here Oh, my God Oh, my God,
okay Did you get it?
No What?
There I have a minute still Okay, I gotta wait here I gotta
wait here I didn't realize the top right corner Is my
cooldown?
Oh my God Oh But honestly, game's not bad.
It's just...
Yeah, look, okay, the moment we finish building our houses,
we'll actually fight for real.
We'll fight.
Look, we need a home first.
This is the end game, basically.
We're speedrunning this game.
Exactly.
Guys, this is like, we just wanted to find a house first.
This is much more important than fighting.
they're shooting our guns okay guys this is like i don't
care if those are nice gear they're like they have nice
house i surely do okay oh my god one minute left one minute
left and then i i can finally put down my house oh it's
because i'm moving my i'm moving my tower at the same time
is that oh my that's why that's why i was struggling because
i I was moving my towel.
How do I move just this?
Dude, dude, I thought...
Just demolish it.
Just get rid of the blue frame.
Get rid of the blue frame.
No!
Well, never!
I'm too lazy!
I'm too lazy.
Isn't that all of us?
I don't want to move my thing.
It's too much work.
I don't want to move.
I have to demolish the house I'm sad I have to demolish the
house Goodbye door Goodbye You were a great door Did you get
rid of the blueprints?
The blueprint's still there no fucking way Wait is it?
There's no way No it's not The blueprint is still there No
it's not I don't see it Wait, it is.
What the fuck is it still doing there?
How do I demolish the floor?
Here's the hollow terminal.
Wait, how do I get rid of it?
The weird ass camera.
There's nothing I can do.
How do I get rid of it?
Oh, cancel.
Okay.
Nice.
All right.
There you go.
It's gone.
Nice.
All right.
Now I can move this.
Number six, just gathering resources.
All right.
Okay.
I need a...
fucking do my stupid tower okay here maybe here whose house
is this oh this is number six all right confirm he has a bed
number six has a bed number six has a bed how did he
progress that far i feel relaxed ah yes this bed okay very
nice guys we will get there the tower is gonna be made okay
all right i'm figuring this out very slowly okay my tower
there's still hope just don't put it over the edge of the
territory bro what the fuck how do i not do that just when
you press me there's like a white like a white square it's
so hard to make this stupid i'm fuck i'm i'm going insane
with demolish everything fuck this i'm like i'm going crazy
i'm going to demolish I did that I fucking fucking go crazy
I already went I already went through that phase Fuck this I
don't need this I don't need this at all Like, you know
Alright This tower is much more important Okay Alright There
we go.
Where's the, where is it?
Oh no, I can't put my, what can I?
Overlaps with battle unit?
What the fuck is the battle unit?
I honestly don't know what a battle unit is.
Okay, there we go.
There we go.
I did it guys.
I did it.
No way.
We did it.
Let's go build.
It's time to build.
Your door is so long.
Build your door.
Oh my god, we did it.
Oh my god, I finally...
We figured it out, guys.
Okay.
Oh shit, I made a stairs.
Oh my god, you made my stairs.
Okay.
We're gonna go up, up, up.
Building formula left.
The door works.
Do I not have materials anymore?
I can't tell.
I can't tell when I stopped having materials.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
The door is finally accessible.
We can finally, like, go through the door.
The door is actually functional now.
Why is the door gone?
I made the door and it's gone.
Wait, is it?
I took it away.
Oh, you took it away.
You took away the door.
How do I put the door back?
I put it back.
Just put it back.
How?
It's gone!
Oh my god.
You took the door that I gave you.
The door is gone!
Put it back!
You put it back!
What do you mean?
I have no material.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying!
What does it mean when it says we don't have material?
Yeah, then we're out of materials.
Then get some trees!
Get trees!
It's a goddamn woodhouse!
Okay, I'm fucking chopping.
Guys, we have to keep building.
six perms to chop trees okay enter enter tell number six to
join our guild you're the leader oh yeah invite him to our
guild oh yeah get get over here yeah get over here get over
here let me just talk to you real quick invite the hive
there i invited you to hive number six all right yeah yeah
get in here and then just get in here build my house
fortnight that should fortnight that should real quick build
my house okay dude are you in the guild yet okay number six
i think you gotta you gotta give him okay okay uh we have to
be friends with him wait we have to be friends with him i'm
not sure do we have to be i don't know just okay i don't see
the option to give him the shit all right number six but
he's like in our what's the point of being in our guild that
and we can't know my friend get my friend says like in a
guild but like oh yada yada all right you get the lucky
opportunity i'm gonna remove you after the stream i mean
you're so evil you're so evil i need for my house my house
is very important to me
build my house right now number six just try to do what you
gotta do holy this guy this guy's the man this guy's the man
go build the house i will supervise this guy's the man is he
gonna put a door back on oh my god he's building look at him
go oh my god look at him go why were we doing work when we
could have had number six do all the work for us he was
collecting materials door number six give me a door we need
a door we lost what happened to her door i actually took it
off i don't know put it back on i know i gave you a door i'm
gonna know what happened what happened to my door i don't
even know what happened
i took the door but where did i take it
I don't know like it's gone.
I can't even put it back on Like it doesn't tell me how to
like give my door back.
Oh, I accidentally destroyed the door Guys, we don't need a
door In my inventory There's no doors in my inventory though
what happened to it i don't understand what i did oh my god
oh my god he has so much materials what the fuck look at
that hey you have a house not yet i don't have a roof yet
it's like 40 yeah well you have three floors does it yeah i
want my house had to be yes it does because like i require
my house to be the tallest of everybody so i can
overcompensate oh hey there's a guy here wait he has he
killed a deer yo that guy's high level he hasn't he has a
sniper oh my god this guy's gaming he's like looking at our
house hey there man he's like look at what we are doing he's
actually progressing the game yeah well well we're
technically are as well yeah different aspect yeah what are
we missing in our building just a little bit of a
foundations and such well you have a you don't have a roof
yet yeah i don't have a roof yet all right while number six
is building the rest of our house we go find some monsters
to kill you want to do a deadsville mission yeah let's go do
a mission number six can we leave this to you is that okay
no you don't ask you don't have to ask them it's expected
it's like powwow they're my pal they're my pal leave it to
me he oh shit he's the man he's the man you take it to the
man okay do we teleport there wait which one that's fill
that's bill okay wait yeah uh that's bill is it your mission
yeah uh huh where is that like what is it it's called
welcome back uh is there tp or do we have to walk there
recommended of teleporting they said but i'm not sure where
is it you want to walk just to see what the is going to
happen yeah let's go I'll follow you behind you one one one
kilometer.
Are you not on the same mission?
No, because I still have to fucking build I haven't finished
building yet top left.
What the fuck is your mission?
Go build mode and build the gear workbench That's my
mission.
I'm still at the gear workbench.
I'm gonna kill this deer because I'm angry Build a
workbench.
I don't want to build I'm tired of building
i why did it shoot stuff yeah yeah shoot stuff oh wait this
is the wrong way god damn stupid roads all right i don't
have my butterfly to help us because my butterfly is my
butterfly is crying my butterfly was like like i had to
disassemble my butterfly remember uh you can use my building
no it's fine i'm too lazy oh we don't need the butterfly we
have your butterfly oh it's good to have two butterflies
what's over here it's a zombie boy there's literally a
zombie there's literally zombies so white exactly i missed
like the tutorial had cooler zombies this is like the
tutorial not even zombies just zombie did you uh had a hard
time fighting the the tutorial box the tutorial box oh yeah
no it was so easy i was just like yeah yeah yeah the the
fucking boss was like oh that was a tough fight yeah what
what do you mean i didn't even get to do anything he just
stood yeah he just stood and then you're and then your
butterfly killed him yep all right i'm following you.
We're in Micah's...
Hey.
Hey there.
Person.
Goodbye.
Pretty sure he just started playing this game too.
He has nothing.
Alright.
I'm right behind you.
We should play Remnant next time.
I should not have played Remnant 2 yet.
I tried to, but I kept crashing.
There's a second game.
I don't even know.
Yeah.
There's a second game but i kept crashing so i just stopped
thing is i might need a new graphics card and i'm trying to
save up if i keep buying games i can yeah but the steam cell
there's a steam cell right now yeah what's the point of
buying games when i can't even launch it but you cannot not
even you don't know you can maybe they have a 20 series man
yeah but maybe they fixed it oh yeah never mind my chat was
like no my chat was like no they're like no to you no i have
a 20 series what can i do with that huh all right where the
fuck is a boss we want to fight oh shit wait he actually
dropped wait he dropped something watch this what the fuck
wait what did i do what is that it's like You kill them and
then he dropped this.
What is that?
It's like a weapon.
Can you throw it?
I must be thirsty.
Wait, oh, there's him.
Wait, I want to see if I can kill this guy.
No, you can, but like, it also kills people.
Oh, it like beams them.
Gee.
Oh, what?
That kills them.
What the fuck?
Yeah.
Wait, where did I drop it?
Oh, there it is.
You can try it.
It's right here.
What is this?
Do I just aim it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
just aim it and then it beams.
Yeah, but there's like a limited ammo.
Oh, hell not.
I'm not using this.
I have photosensitivity.
You want me to use that?
Crazy.
Alright, I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna use it.
It's RGB time.
I gotta wear sunglasses.
Where even?
Where's your fucking mission?
Oh, there's him again!
There's another one of those.
Oh my god, I'm so slow with this, though.
I'm gonna use it on the actual boss boss there's like a lot
of items around us oh he's beaming me yeah he's beaming me
i'm beaming them back i think it's like a rare drop no it's
like a it's like a rare drop type deal that'll it'll just
drop it probably where the fuck is your mission tangent it's
called welcome back it's yeah but where is it it's very far
told you my god wait this is not even the air no okay i'm
fucking okay i'm fucking uh running over to you i thought
that was the area so i picked it up it was not all right
here i come was there stamina where's the stamina bar like
right there the muscle oh the muscle okay i see it i see it
now you you gotta eat and drink yeah it's okay i I feel like
we have enough food on us, right?
Right.
Yeah, I have like seven.
You should be lost in the old damage boost.
I have like seven things from the tutorial.
Tutorial?
Yeah, the tutorial gave you so much free food.
What the?
When did you have a gun?
What?
Since that lady gave me the blueprint.
That's why you make the gear shift.
I was not paying attention.
you did not you did not have a gun i was too busy building
my tower
right this should be the area this is okay i have a bottle
of soju what is that i'm gonna eat too i run so fast now i
run fast oh you drank alcohol yeah there's a there's one of
the there's a player here yeah there's a lot of players here
wait is this oh this is like a town yeah oh it's like a safe
zone yeah it is we should build we should have lived here
yeah we should have lived here speak to mary oh wait we got
compensation oh my god yeah look at the mailbox they gave us
free stuff
oh oh my god yay they fucked up so we get free stuff buy
something you have something we have butterfly die we have
you now create based on we've originally opened up
functionality for multiple character creation you can now
create characters on any server whoa all right
we got free stuff free loot I gotta talk to the lady open
this loot box teleport oh this is where we teleport to other
worlds yay is it this woman that's a man sorry that's a man
let's see what I investigate the teleportation where's the
loot bucks speak with trader on site oh shit loot box yeah
the fuck there's loot box i got i got hairstyle i got
grenade i got emotes i got cosmetic tokens okay yeah if you
open the mail did you not open the mailbox be clear i did
what if i chat if i chat with her do i uh wait She doesn't
even have voice lines.
We don't even have a voice line.
Yeah, no, this random...
The Clare lady doesn't even have voice lines.
We both don't have a voice line.
It just feels awkward talking to them.
Yeah, this feels so weird.
Go to the man.
I don't even think I was supposed to talk to her yet.
Because I don't have a mission.
Yeah.
I'm just gonna mooch off your missions.
What the fuck is that?
what what is this what is that are you the shop who are you
look at him that thing looks dumb yeah what the fuck is that
shop oh suppressors and stuff nice when will we fight our
first boss I don't know where do you I think I think you
have to find the bosses and do it world do we have to find
ourselves alright let's see recommend the shadow someone's
over there let's go check it out someone's up ahead let's go
check it out oh there's like these exclamation points are
those exclamation point bosses you got a bike let's go to
this nearest one this one the shadow lighthouse there's a
fucking radio No shot.
They have a fucking radio.
What the fuck?
How did you get that bike?
Can you get on?
No.
Wait, how did you get on it?
Can't you get on it?
Oh, I can like...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Did you, like, talk to somebody to get it?
Yeah.
Do the missions.
Oh, my God.
Oh, okay.
Unlock the storage expansion.
How do I unlock the storage expansion?
I don't know.
Don't do the red mission.
I think the red missions are like the yellow is the green
one.
I don't want to unlock the storage expansion.
I have the purple mission, the yellow mission.
What the fuck is a purple mission?
I've never got a purple mission.
Okay, okay.
Give me a second.
I need to unlock the storage expansion.
Do I have enough storage expansion?
What the fuck is the storage expansion?
Where is it?
What the fuck?
Oh, is it basic storage?
Yeah.
I need to unlock wooden support.
To get storage expansion.
I did it.
Build any storage.
Oh my god.
It needs me to build a storage crate.
How far ahead are you?
Not that far.
Okay, can I TP to you or not?
I wonder.
Just TP to the base, no?
I know, but like, will I be able to TP to you later?
Can you?
I'm not sure.
Alright, we'll figure this out the moment.
I'm going to TP to my home and see if I can TP to you.
Why?
Why are you going to me?
No, because like, I need to go...
Because you're there for the mission.
To progress.
What do you mean?
done why did number six stop oh it's cuz he's still building
I think I'd like put too much stuff yeah I definitely I
definitely picked the house too big oh my
big it's too fucking huge way more than mine actually oh
shit I accidentally discard oh there it is okay Jesus Christ
there's so much stuff to unlock oh my god you see someone
chaff that was like I am Asian girl you see that
insane good to know man um what the is furniture basic
furniture oh i i couldn't build doors and windows because i
never unlocked it build a bed you never built a bed i never
build a bed no how come i can't progress your mission what
but because it's i'm i'm not doing the optional I don't have
any other mission it just says build a bed just look at your
task what the fuck do you have build a bed why did I didn't
even have I didn't even tell me to like build a bed or some
shit what happened to my missions why am I building a bed
why do you have to build a bed okay I don't know I'm
confused I'm just as confused is you why am i supposed to be
follow the star dust is that what your missions are oh wait
untracked why did you untrack your main mission i don't
attention i don't know 90 of what's going on right now i was
me neither dude i just i'm goofing gear work bench holy shit
okay gear work bench built alright what else does it want me
to do go to build a supplies he's someone's name is I like
Asian girls no
no no no Oh my god.
Holy shit.
Free to play games experience.
Oh my god.
No.
Okay, basic gear.
We're getting there guys.
We're gonna be able to get there soon guys.
Give up this power through.
I don't have enough cyphers.
What kind of worthless shit do I have?
Oh, I'm gonna reset this.
That's my worthless shit that I had.
okay i got the gun it's time to craft the gun which gun is
it this one the d50 bp it's the pistol d50 p oh okay is this
one i have insufficient materials uh click the crafting
materials the plus ones i don't get it why do you need to
make that shit but explore the oh i need to disassemble the
scrap oh yeah disassemble the scrap i have a disassembler
yeah i'm just going to use your dissembler wait did you give
me perms to use your stuff yeah okay like last time you
didn't have it
all right let's see it's like they're trying to combine a
lot of stuff into one yeah yeah he's gone and then i agree
like holy it's like everything all at once yep i'm gonna use
your gear too might as well it's like right here yeah how do
i still don't have enough what do you need oh
excuse me oh i got it never mind jk i just can't read yeah
well honestly i got a gun i got a gun i did it i didn't
assume so i craft any ammo in the supplies wait how much
ammo did you craft oh you do have a fishing rod there's like
a cup there's like oh it's like 40 bullets holy shit it's
like 40 bullets for craft wait what the fuck when did you
get here just notice the teleportation this is my home i
have every right to
That's what we're talking about.
That's insane.
She's kicking me out of my house.
Holy shit, how did you get here?
My house.
What the fuck?
That's insane.
She's kicking me out of my house.
I'm sorry, but I mean, my house.
Can she do that, Chad?
No way.
I just did it.
She just did.
insane can't believe we walked over here when we could just
tp yeah tp has cooled down right now wasted wait tp has
cooled down yeah this was the quickest way to bring you here
these towers are even supposed to let you travel between
worlds but i haven't been able to figure out how this
building is half can't build the stairs i'm glad that
merchant over by the old truck looks like she gets around oh
my god when do i get my bike apparently the longer we follow
the mission the further the closer we get to the boss i hope
i hope they're right i hope okay yeah we don't need to know
that we literally did that already okay speak with the
traitor did you went there you went there yeah i'm doing
that oh no I'm doing the mission now.
Oh, you're at Dead Spill.
Anything that catches your eye, I'm always open for
business.
Affordable housing.
Livable housing.
I'm just looking.
Oh, she's talking now.
Claire's talking.
I know.
I could really use some help.
My name's Claire.
I like that so many people are naked in this game.
Yeah, nobody's bothering to put any armor on.
They're just...
just building like some goods for me but they never came
back it's possible everyone's just doing this and this guy's
fully geared as shit this guy's level 10 and then not even
wearing pants what level are we i'm level six okay so they
just played like two more hours than us yeah probably i
suspect there's a deviation behind it you get the bike
though oh yeah i'm still talking that well-dressed gentleman
oh my god how many people that to talk to he should be able
to tell you more there's no question that guy stands out i
can cut that very bad good luck oh and i'll happily pay a
reward if you can recover my stuff for me i'll mark rotten
manor on your map make sure to stock up on ammo before you
go all right what the gives you the bike this guy the guy
after that guy oh the guy low low guy after that guy the
girl with the Ada Wong yeah Ada Wong Ada Wong but brunette
Ada Wong gave the bike Claire Redfield Claire Wong I like
how this is like um it's like cut scenes within the game so
you can see people walking around affecting this area.
I think I just saw you walking around in my cutscene.
Can you still see this?
Wait, wait.
I'm looking at him right now.
I don't have a POV of like outside.
You seek keys with which to unlock the dark tower.
It's like the guys talking to me.
I don't worry of what else you might open up.
Do you always speak in my...
Now it's at 801.
Merely setting the mood.
The world still deserves something poetic.
Oh, man.
What are you doing?
I'm emoting.
I don't see you yet.
It's a close-up.
If you stand next to the campfire, I'll see you.
I'm at the campfire.
And now tell me, where do you think those anchors would be?
Wait, what?
No, you're not there!
Oh yeah, I'm at the campfire.
No, man.
I'm looking forward to seeing what you can do, Mayfly.
I'm sure it will be a remarkable story to share.
By the way, I feel bad for the people that wrote the story
because they clearly put a lot of effort in writing this
story.
I had to talk to Mary again.
Mary, what do you want?
Now that we know what to do, let's split up to cover more
ground.
I'll find a way to hack into the monolith.
Why does she have syringes of blood on her?
Like, what is she doing with the syringes?
Who knows?
Gone for an hour and still no pants.
Yep.
This game has no concept of pants.
Nobody wears pants here.
Like, I like the fact that the tutorial gave us armor, a
hat, a glove, a shoe.
Yeah, I gave us everything but a pants.
Yeah, I think it was everything but a pants.
Holy shit.
What is wrong with the devs?
this hey there guys paditi ap did oh there there's a bike i
got bike too i got bike too where's your bike i just dropped
it i can find i could summon it wait how do you summon it g
g oh okay okay it just taught me that yeah well we gotta go
gotta go to rod and fanny Where's Ryan?
Okay, here we go.
Fuck your bike.
Oh, fuck your bike.
And I was fucking over somebody else's bike.
I'm ready, let's go.
Yeah, I follow you.
Okay, okay, let's see what's the closest way to get there.
i'm not even gonna ride on the road fuck the roads okay but
there's horns beep there's a radio oh yeah is there actually
radio yeah old x i don't know oh there it is
before exploring danger wait what before exploring dangerous
areas press t oh make a camp We're fighting some shit.
I don't know if I can join you Wait, can you not join me?
Where are you?
I see you Wait, wait, wait.
You rode ahead of me Can I go over this?
No Okay I had to jump over this I mean, you could summon
your bike again
I love that we just materialized the fucking bike and that's
it.
No Okay, there it is wait what the fuck investigate oh
you're gone holy shit you're gone too oh
okay oh no I should have brought the butterfly I should have
brought the butterfly I should have brought the fire shoot
the head shoot the head I should I fought it with a goddamn
butterfly definitely should have brought the butterfly lie i
know that i fucked up wait i don't even have oh my god i
didn't bring my gun oh wait i did bring my gun okay um i
hear it growling at me outside okay i realized that like
when you're on the pause menu you're not actually paused by
the way no yeah it's an mmo what is your I expected to pause
for me.
Who the fuck?
It's a solo anyway!
That's true.
Where's your head?
Where the fuck is the head?
It's so tiny.
There we go, I killed it.
Jesus Christ.
The rift anchor.
Let's take a closer look I'm just gonna lay back enjoy my
coffee and just you're already finished Yeah, I did that.
Oh shit.
I'm gonna cut scene.
Oh, wait.
Hey Oh, piddity's here.
Where's you?
Okay.
There's you are
How do we do like the bosses together then?
You gotta find it A lot of people are fighting in some
places I heard.
Oh, okay hopefully we'll find the other rift anchors there
all right you lead us you seem to have more knowledge than
me you lead us i i can't read the chat but people really
boss boss boss boss you come on where is it tangents chat
where's the boss no not not the chat like the the game chat
oh like everyone keeps saying boss boss wasn't all like
someone said you we can do uh dungeons Where's the dungeon?
Where's the dungeons?
Which one's the dungeons?
Yeah, that's what I like to know Which one would be the
dungeons then?
I'm curious now like whoa What did dungeons even look like?
Am I getting shot at?
Oh shit, we are We're just looking at her map.
We're looking at the maps.
There's a guy right behind us
We're like where could the dungeons be?
be.
We have to do these.
The welcome back.
Oh, we do that.
Oh, we do the dungeon after this quest.
Okay, we have to go to the other ones.
And then we can do the dungeons.
Okay.
I guess we can do the closest one to us.
Like this one.
Do you're in your 41?
Sure.
Oh, shit.
That's what the fuck did you...
What did you do to my bike?
Why?
You pushed me over.
You pushed me over first.
You pushed me over too.
When you unlock the rift anchors, okay.
Apparently with the...
Oh, there's dogs!
There's like demon dogs.
Diamond dogs.
Yeah, there was a demon dog in front of me.
I wish we can go like faster with the...
Yeah.
With the bikes.
There you go.
Activate.
Activate that.
This is not my bike.
Activate.
Wait, there's so many bikes.
Whose bikes are it?
Where's the guy on?
Why is there a random bike here?
Whose bike is that?
I wouldn't know of it.
Okay, next one is...
Where's the next one?
What the fuck is that?
What is that?
What the fuck?
Is that the boss?
Oh my god!
Affordable housing!
Is that where everybody's going?
I think everybody's going there.
Holy shit.
Are we fighting that thing?
Wait, is everybody there?
Wait, there's nobody here!
Can we get close to it?
Oh, I'm getting close!
Oh shit, oh shit.
What is that?
I'm gonna shoot it.
No.
No, you can't even shoot it!
What is that then?
Wait, can I shoot the hands?
What is this?
Wait!
You can't even shoot it!
Shit!
Wait!
Their friend, it talked to me.
Wait, did it talk to you?
It talked to me.
Oh, it didn't talk to me.
I shot it.
He's friend.
What the fuck is that?
I think he's friend.
He's friend.
Oh my.
I mean, I mean, he doesn't have a mouth.
Could be a friend.
Yeah, how did he talk to you?
I don't know.
What does it do?
I honestly don't know.
I don't know what this is.
I wonder if like we can get on top of it later.
Pales moving out.
Something steers from the middle of the ground.
Crush the murals and find a hidden miniature.
Oh.
hails moving house not even everybody's confused everybody's
shooting you know what i will not mess with the mystical
force apparently like people are like saying that uh uh we
have to find a way to access the secret for this it's
apparently a secret All right, there are faint noises coming
from following them and finally found the third conscious
what what I?
Huh, when did we do that?
Hey, what what what huh?
It's down.
Wait, how did you do it?
What what they did it?
Oh my god, they did it the fuck.
Oh my god.
We mooched we successfully mooched We mooched them off bro
can we yeah we're looting this oh holy we did it guys we
don't even have the mission we got a disco we leached let's
go what what the did they do rewards can only be claimed
once a week please come back next week i'm not going to come
back what did we even get like that's a nice stuff
Yeah, I got a disco ball.
I don't know what that does, but...
I don't know what it does, but we did.
Yeah, how the fuck did they do it?
I don't know.
Where's the leech?
Where's the leeches?
It's just like Diablo all over again.
Wait, it like became part of the environment.
Wait, the house?
we got this shit oh my god I can't believe it treasure and
then leave this place well I'm leaving it yeah I'm leaving
it too ow okay I need to get my bike too we gotta go to the
other unlock yay we did it Tanger we got a disco ball yeah
we did it hell yeah for some fucking reason I don't know why
we needed a disco ball it's good to have oh shit whoops all
right i i fucked up give me a sec i got off the road and i
fucked up i'm going off the road okay i'm heading over now i
left my loot there it's all right i got the disco ball
though
holy shit this game's physics is funny i am just happy with
the disco ball.
Apparently I only took one thing.
Seriously?
It's alright.
I was just having the disco ball.
I don't even know what I just thought was there.
I just like claimed the disco ball.
Oh shit.
Okay, I got the...
Got the rift.
Yeah, I'm heading for this one too.
Where's the other one?
Where's the last one?
next to our base it is we might as well just fast travel if
it's next to our base sure i'm fast traveling oh yeah
yeah holy yeah i still don't get it they just decided not to
give us pants i am gonna check my disco ball what is it what
does it do what does it do i have no clue oh it's a
deviation so i can have a disco bot in my i can have a disco
bot in my backpack is that it i see about that i'm gonna
check number six is still going at it go number six go i'm
you're 72% who would who would win us finding a boss or
number six building this house i would just go it's a
crafting it's a crafting shit not a combat it's a different
thing but it says a deviation i know but it's like a
crafting so i can't put it in my i can't put it in my in my
backpack hold on oh somebody broke its leg no you can't no
what's the point it's not a combat What's the point?
It's not a combat deviation.
There's an alligator in my door!
What the fuck?
It's in!
What?
Wait, wait, what, what, what?
There's an alligator in my fucking door.
Hey, the disco ball's in!
I put the disco ball!
It's not in my backpack, but...
Wait, wait, wait.
But it's there, but it's just not...
It's in!
That looks so nice.
no that's all i'm adding this is the only thing this is the
only thing i looted but i got the disco ball holy i don't
need the butterfly just with the disco ball oh my god i got
it it's super dumb okay we gotta go to the last which way is
the last one here it's over here that way you said my
motorcycle even though oh my god guys we actually can't wait
you like drove over it even though oh my god broke my leg
even though even though it can't be in my backpack i'm i'm
still satisfied with it just
yeah with disco it's a fucking disco it's a disco ball it's
the only the only thing i looted that's all i care about oh
shit oh shit oh shit is that boss oh shit oh shit what level
is it he's level eight we can do this we can do it this is
what we train for he's he's not taking that much of a damage
man this is what we train for this is I need your help, man.
I'm literally shooting him!
Use your butterfly!
What's his weakness?
Is it that the little- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Use your butterfly!
I have a fear of butterflies.
Okay.
Oh my gosh, I should've made more ammo.
I should've made more ammo.
Oh, wait, wait.
It's all gone.
He's stunned.
We're supposed to shoot his?
Shoot its vagina.
Yes, shoot the flower!
Oh, what?
I mean he does He died He's dead Oh
Okay Okay Okay Oh my god Okay That's That's good Yeah Well
Well To be there It's launch day You know It just launched
It's The ragdoll is so...
The ragdoll.
Holy shit.
I'm heading over.
Okay, it's done.
What the fuck?
Obtain a tier one.
They keep wanting us to craft shit.
I'm tired of it.
They love crafting.
Oh, meet Mary.
No, we gotta meet Mary.
Meet Mary?
Yeah.
it says meet mary what does it say for you obtain tier one
armor craft one wait what that doesn't say that for me
what oh okay i need any kind of ammo i hanging back with you
maybe i need maybe it's because i need ammo why does it say
meet mary free me what Maybe you filled the requirements and
I didn't.
It says, welcome.
It says, meet Mary.
Welcome back.
What?
I'm a tier one armor.
Crafting on the top.
What?
Okay, that's weird.
Uh.
Day one game.
Yeah, it says, meet Mary under the monolith for me.
What?
Maybe I don't have enough ammo and some shit.
Well, I have like, literally have like...
Oh, there's another phone call.
Moshi Moshi.
My sister stumbled across a huge toy rabbit downstairs.
What the fuck is this message?
What the fuck?
Alright, I'm gonna go... I'm gonna meet Mary.
You're gonna meet Mary?
You gotta cross the street.
And then I'll see if I start crafting after.
It's weird that...
You don't have the same thing as me.
I feel like you should.
I should, yes.
Yeah, we literally did the quest together.
Like...
Like what?
I'm heading over.
Wee!
Alright.
Ooh, somebody lives here.
Oh, Mary lives here.
Hello, Mary!
I need...
I need what?
Adesive.
I don't have adhesive.
Where do I find adhesive?
Oh, I don't need this.
What am I crafting throwing daggers for?
sounds tough what are you doing all these things and i'm
just meeting mary you meet mary and i'm doing tier one shit
and i'm like what i was told to craft stuff and then they
just like told you to do that and i'm like this is i find
this highly oppressing yeah i get to pre-guess the plot and
you don't the uh what the is this this is not fair and meds
for us as well oh she has ammo and meds you had the craft
she's giving me ammo and meds oh shit my bike vehicle is
damaged please repair in garage what the fuck you i lost my
bike congratulations wait you destroyed your bike yes that's
funny that's pretty funny i know follow the guidance and
explain how did you do all that like i still have my stuff
Oh, apparently I have a boss fight here.
You have a boss fight?
Yeah, where are you?
There's like everybody has their campgrounds here.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, what?
Where are you?
Everybody's here.
Hold on, I'll find some stuff.
Is it because you established your campgrounds?
I don't know.
Did you do that already?
Maybe that's why.
Yeah, maybe that's why you already established your
campground.
So then like it just told you to go back to it.
Hold on, hold on.
I need to make some stuff.
This is the thing.
I'm going to wait.
I'm going to get it.
I'm going to wait for you at the top of the mountain.
Can I TP back to the home?
You TP to me?
There's a boss fight apparently up here.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Guys, not wearing pants was a choice.
It was a choice.
For my attention, I'm waiting for you.
I don't have a bike, though, man.
Just TP!
To where?
Me!
I have to do my shit first.
I have to craft my stuff.
Oh my god.
God damn it.
Alright, let's see.
I need to...
Oh my gosh, I need to hydrate really badly.
Don't worry, I'm drinking.
I'm hydrating.
hey stevo wants to join our team all right stevo come in
here stevo yes stevo get in here all right uh i'm radiated i
gotta cure myself you're ready what did you do uh i jumped
in the water where the did you do where even are you i
jumped there you are you're back home yeah i'm walking home
because i don't have a bike you can wait don't you have fast
travel there's teleport or cool down oh well all right
goodbye fuck you oh my god everybody's campgrounds here oh
get oh stevo left our team stevo hates us stevo hates you
what how dare he hates me I'm a lovable person.
What the fuck?
Alright, Z, you go first and kill everybody for me.
Whoa.
Go do it.
I'm mooching off this guy.
I'm mooching off.
Don't worry, I have somebody else to do everything for me.
He's killing everybody for me now.
Let's see.
There's an alligator outside of my house.
Whoops, I alerted him accidentally.
There's an alligator outside your house?
Yeah.
Go, Carrie, go.
Go do your thing.
No, don't make your pants.
Pants are for cowards.
They told me to make it.
That's the thing I can't progress if I can't make pants.
Wait, why do you have to make pants?
I don't know It never told me to make pants I'm just playing
the game Go Radden Guy go That's a shit ass pants It's not
even a complete pants Oh my god I almost shot the explosive
tank Go guy with guns Go
Boom Boom
That's right.
That's right, Wilo.
We're doing it.
We don't need 10.
What?
What are you actually doing right now?
Are you fighting a boss?
No, we're just walking.
There's like a area where we have to go through.
And like this guy coincidentally was also going through this
area.
So like there's like a lot of enemies.
enemies too oh there is loot here nice yeah
so like it I was lucky because like he was also going
through this area too okay I made I fucked up I I was trying
to I fell from a really high place
Yeah, I think that was karma.
This game took two hours to make pants.
Wait,
there's like elite monsters here.
Where can I put my garage?
Wilo.
Wilo, what do we do?
Wilo, what are you gonna shoot?
I put the garage in the weirdest place possible.
Jesus Christ.
Don't worry, Wilo.
I'm here to help.
Mobility, basically.
don't worry why though how do i fix it repair irons i need
our irons all i'm saying tangent by time you actually do
this mission all the monsters will be dead oh there we go
it's normal okay yeah that's just okay so the the pants is
now done now it says meet mary undermodel jesus christ why
did i need to make no idea i didn't have to make pants i
just progressed what the fuck no That's stupid, dude.
Why the, why did you do that?
You're so, don't be dumb.
Alright.
Okay, I got the stuff.
All the monsters dead, by the, like, majority of the
monsters are dead, so you don't have to worry about it.
Alright, I got the shit.
Can I TP to you?
Oh, can you?
How do I teleport to you?
No, I'll just go to Dead Spill.
Oh yeah, no, no, you have to TP to talk to Mary first.
And then...
Oh my god, that's not what I wanted to do.
I wanted to grab loot the item.
Alright.
Oh, I got so many mats.
Alright, let's do this.
Okay, what's this loot?
Come on, the way I'm going to talk to Mary, and then I'll
go...
Yeah, the moment you talk to Mary...
uh then you're like at my quest area right hello why the why
are you doing what are you gonna do
what I can't read that he said he said there's one guys
somebody translate I can only read like half that sentence
and he's trying to talk to me he's actually this random he's
trying to talk to me I don't know.
Did you turn on voice chat?
No, he did chat.
The wild guy.
Oh.
That guy.
That guy is.
I don't know if he's trying to talk to me.
Oh, there's a level 5 big one.
Okay.
Alright.
For the dangerous area.
Okay, I'm going to make my campsite.
I don't have a log.
You're in such a mess right now.
You don't have a log.
No.
I lost my carry.
Oh, he's over there killing more people.
Don't worry.
I'm coming over.
Wait, he respawned?
Yeah, because he...
Oh my god.
The one of the big guys respawned.
But I need...
I need the carry.
I need the carry here.
Wait, where did he go?
Wild!
Hey, I need you to protect me.
Oh, oh, you don't eat something.
Wait, what?
Oh, my gosh, I can't read.
I can only read half of it.
Yeah, well, it's better than none.
Wait, I think he's not talking to me.
I think he's talking to his other, his other clan mates.
I think he's talking.
Yeah, pretty sure he's talking to his buddies.
Okay, I'm here.
I eat food.
Where are you?
All right.
I'm on top.
Holy shit.
What is that thing?
What the fuck is that thing?
Are you here?
Oh yeah, I see it.
You see it?
You see the big boy?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What the fuck is that?
Oh shit, I didn't see this guy.
Oh my god.
Whoa.
Jesus.
I don't even see oh there you are yeah, that's the big guy
Look there's the other guy that was my friend That's my
friend over there.
That's his that's the fuck is that?
This is oh god come on you right behind you behind you Okay,
yeah Okay, don't worry I'm shooting him Oh there nice nice
nice okay we have to go to the main quest line see i told
you i wait for you right i waited for you right oh he's
right surely that wild guy he's he's nobody make it easier
wait that's not wild Oh my gosh, Pete Diddy!
Yeah, no, it's Pete Diddy.
Yeah, wait, Pete Diddy is still doing this quest?
We were like fucking around.
We saw Pete.
What was Pete Diddy doing?
He was probably fucking around like us.
Oh my god, where did WIO go?
Oh shit, oh hey, it's our favorite.
Oh my god, Pete Diddy just like ran across from him.
I'm shooting the legs.
All right, you should drop down now
Holy shit.
That's like 700 damage through a slice.
Nice.
Yeah, I'm not I'm trying not to waste too many bullets yeah
I just realized and I I kind of All right, there it is boss
fight.
Oh my god.
Somebody broke their bike as well It's probably PDD The
Molokai's leftover public crafting facilities available I
recommended to team up first supplies and discard oh what uh
and catch a glimpse locate the rip uh is recommend team up
first are we teamed up yeah we are oh this is like we can
get materials before we go in for a boss fight grab some
shit press q okay just to see shoot hello mary a lot of
stuff i'm gonna talk to mary i knew i could count on you
you're quite good at handling deviance aren't you i have an
amplifier hat how does a rustic a rustic hat how does that
work how i mean i'm gonna i think i have enough ammo oh i
wonder if i can craft can i craft better guns uh let's see
oh i can never mind i'm literally missing waste plastic i
must have waste plastic here i just need some rusted parts
actually then i'll get a better gun okay Okay, let's see.
Assembling.
I think I can...
I'm going to make a shotgun.
You're going to make a shotgun?
Yeah, I'm going to make a shotgun.
I found it.
What do you mean, how?
I need...
I need rustic material.
Let's see.
Do I have enough?
Oh, I don't...
I don't have enough waste plastic.
Do you have waste plastic?
how much is where's the waste i need two waste plastic it's
a waste plastic i don't know i don't know how to get it see
maybe i can find extra waste around here waste plastic i
have 13 but i think i might need it though let's see if
there's extra equipment here a snap is there any stuff snap
i keep snapping around i was no Oh, wait.
There's med kits.
Okay, I don't need med kits, though.
Is there a waste plastic here?
What if outside?
Oh, that's true.
Football.
Football should be a waste plastic.
Snap.
I keep snapping around.
Alright.
Let me be.
I'm going to assemble this football.
Waste plastic.
Come on.
scraps adhesive rubber shabby yes i just got waste plastic i
need rust oh my god i just got the two i needed oh my god i
was so like i got a shotgun you got a shotgun yeah yeah yeah
hold on i'm still looking around because i need rust apart
you need rust apart so you disassembled everything
the unspinned shotgun.
How many bullets do I have now?
I have 106.
Yeehaw time.
What do you need?
The metal thing.
I don't think we can find any.
The rusted parts.
Yeah, I used up all my parts.
I found a kettle, so let's see about that.
Please.
No!
What was it?
Metal scraps.
I need rusted parts.
It's too late.
Tension.
We got Agilin.
Do you not have rusted parts?
I can check.
Let's see.
Please.
Rusted parts.
I'll be honest.
I just need one.
I got metal scrap, adhesive rubber, gunpowder, copper, ore.
Oh, I do.
I do.
I just need one.
How do I give you one?
How do you give items, though?
This is the thing.
Control X.
Okay, there.
You just need one.
There.
I discarded one.
Next to me.
Oh, that's it.
Junk.
Alright, thanks.
It's time to make a better gun.
I'm gonna say I need a heal.
I just realized.
The moment we defeat one boss, we can leave.
We'll be done with this game forever.
I mean, it's a good game, but not for us.
Not for us.
I got a gun.
All right, let's go.
Better gun.
We're like remnant players.
Yep.
We just want to pupe you.
Oh, wait, I forgot to speak Mary.
Oh, you forgot.
I just skipped.
I'll just skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip.
All right, go.
All right, let's go.
It's time.
Go.
How do we get there?
Where are you doing?
Why did you jump?
Why did you have this?
There's stairs.
It is a...
no stairs stairs bad all right i'm in are you do we do you
go in with me yeah you have to do the action also please
select the correct difficulty oh i don't know wait all right
you ready yeah how do we get in uh wait do we not do we not
just go in oh my god the level 50 and 60.
60.
They're committed four plays.
Oh, wait.
It's because number six, we're going to kick you out for one
second.
Okay.
We need to kick number six out for one.
Number six.
Okay, we're going to add Motoko in here and then we're going
to kick number six.
We will give you, we'll kick, put you back in soon, number
six.
Okay, well, we need to do this.
the rift okay there we go oh yeah
i don't i don't even know what we're fighting but it's
fighting some level 10 monster oh what
the it's like some stranger things you know it's like
stranger things they're on the other side Let's forgive us.
Right.
You are truly a great one.
Oh my god.
Even without their submission.
Oh.
We are still legion.
Oh, what the fuck?
Yeah, it looks like it's Souls game boss.
Oh, there he is.
Oh.
Which one's the weak point?
The head.
We'll fuck around about that.
It's the head.
Whoa!
About the blue parts of the leg.
It's still the head.
Yeah Just to get in take cover I'm doing more damage on the
side than it says The fucking critical point Oh my god I
want to hit the head with a shotgun but like Oh shit Oh my
god Wait are you Give me that
Wait, where did he go?
Where did he go?
He has another minigun.
Eliminate the spawners.
The spawners?
What does it look like?
It looks like an egg.
What is it?
Shoot the spawner, shoot the spawner!
I am.
Oh, he's got, we got the other spawner.
Oh, there he is.
He's back.
Oh, what the fuck is TPing?
can't catch me oh yeah he caught me oh my god I'm behind him
that's fucking right no I'm thirsty no this is the wrong
time to be thirsty I need a hydrate it does more damage on
the melee all right give me that
I'm gonna melee melee melee It's huge damage
Holy shit I'm so fucking slow Oh my She has a different gun
now Holy shit Are you using the mini gun It destroys the egg
Holy fuck that's so fast He's in front of you He's in front
of you he's behind us he has a different gun now oh it's
it's a rocket launcher holy explosives don't you're just
taking everything oh my god mona no you're gonna die mona go
yeah you're crazy oh my god you reload oh my god shift oh
where do you go He's almost dead though.
Boom.
Okay.
Call his RPG.
I want to shoot it.
I'm trying!
I'm going to shoot that fucking RPG out of his aim.
You want to shoot the RPG?
I'm shooting the arm!
You know what?
I'm going to use a fucking axe.
I'm going to use the axe.
I'm going to use the pickaxe.
the pickaxe this guy's gonna die with the pickaxe yeah i
killed you with the pickaxe all right uh okay i want control
max gain whoa that's a lot of stuff i got an ak oh wait
what's this chance to secure okay do i get it i got it it's
a new deviation i got a new deviate do we get a new yeah
yeah oh shit okay Motoko thanks for oh I did oh my god it's
so cute it's like a frog it looks dumb yeah it looks so
stupid all right uh gee are you ready to leave wait I'm
gonna snap my fingers just in case all right I want to see
the oh my god you're like one HP yeah oh you too Motoko left
honestly this is a decent game yeah i think when you get to
play the bosses the dungeons is actually pretty decent it's
it's fun it doesn't feel well it depends on how you play it
because it you know games nowadays just kind of feels like a
chore instead of like playing it and just this is depending
on how you fucking play it i guess but yeah the start is too
slow i agree the start to
wrong with that i thought having no pants was the best part
there's sanity gummies about how uh what does it do oh
there's sanity levels where's my sanity levels it's for the
uh what do you call it the radiation oh yeah because you're
getting radiation all the time it helps you all right find
chrono cage and a monolith of greed in the basement on
what's oh is this investigate investigate i'm investigating
right next to you
yeah the the part part where we actually get to shoot our
gun is fun oh what the i didn't expect there's you yeah i'm
here with you hey mr girl you did it i did you could i don't
know why commissions okay thank you it's a call really means
a lot to me the fluctuations in Yes, I did.
Yes, I did.
And I feel stronger now.
The more deviations we contain, the more the world will
stabilize.
And the more Mitsuko's power can grow.
We still have five more monoliths to shut down.
Until then, the physical world remains too dangerous for
Mitsuko.
Yes, but this is already a huge step forward.
Yeah, for chill, for chill game, it's all right.
Yeah, it's a nice like chill hangout game with friends.
what about the other demon what's that thing called no no no
no the first descendant have you tried that the first
descendant i heard it's like uh warframe and destiny
basically destiny shit is not the only threat out there the
great ones also covet mitsuko's power i mean i feel like
like if there was more dungeons i think people would like
the dungeon part is like fun in general it is yeah you can
see especially when you get like take their guns i thought
that was oh wait we're back here loot time chat is there
like another dungeon we go straight to if there is another
dungeon we can go straight to like i don't mind doing one
more dungeon yeah me too i just need one
just if the story is horrible i do not think we are playing
this game for the story we're just here to goof yeah we're
just here to we're just here to shoot our gun snap we're
supposed to go to unlock the bronze crafting okay we need
bronze i did that and then i have to go back to the personal
territory um bronze and unlock the garage garage where's the
garage already the fuck how did you have all that because i
don't know my bike broke i need to make it oh secure for
starting journey securement unit can i have two secure me
secure me hold on and unlock everything and then you unlock
open and unlock the garage more than two that's cool and you
open the garage where the fuck's the garage hey my garage
i'm a I'm still thirsty?
Why am I always thirsty?
Why am I still thirsty?
Okay, there's the garage.
This is going to be shared some new memetics with us.
Okay, back to the personal territory.
Okay.
I'm just gonna... I'm gonna TP.
You know, shit.
Yeah.
TP time.
Alright.
Alright, number six.
back in here number six number six get back into the team
number six oh my god 97 we're almost there number six you're
doing great okay let's see i don't know how many glass okay
i need 10 glass Okay, I'm gonna mooch off your furnace.
Yeah, 97.
Okay, we need to invite number six.
You invite number six into our group?
I think you can.
Oh, wait, I have to do it?
Okay, hi.
I invited him.
Okay, nice.
Alright.
I need to use your furnace.
I'm too lazy to make my own furnace.
What do you mean?
What the fuck?
fuck you have a furnace so i need to use it right you might
as well we're sharing this uh-huh okay i need like nine
glass you can i won't put the other guy i won't put the
slime guy i'm in my backpack we is there another dungeon
that's not story related that we can just like run to there
is it in there why don't i Come on, God it is.
I see him.
Oh, my God.
He's so ugly.
Look at him.
I don't see him.
What?
Come on.
He's so ugly.
He looks like he has googly eyes on.
What an ugly little guy.
Look at him.
Ugly baby.
Baby man.
He's in my bag.
Wait, I want to see.
I want to see you.
What does it look like?
Oh, my.
What the fuck?
he looks so stupid he looks so stupid i'm gonna put him in
my backpack too look at that baby man
okay what of the other one uh yeah put the disco ball yeah i
don't see it why is it not like visible what the fuck all
right well there you go what does he do upon being thrown
and knocks back oh i can throw it what the oh it like blocks
attacks apparently look at this turn off world chat this
whole fucking time why would you want to turn off world chat
he makes a wall and it heals when you use him oh that's so
good that's good i like how somebody was like i don't want
to join your team all right is there like a dungeon that uh
that we can go without having to do the story guys there is
a tangent i can do it right now where was it anyway was it
monolith of grief was that the one we did the monolith of
greed that's what we did so it should be like anything like
monolith related is basically like the dungeons yep there's
one that's level 15 the monolith danger zone where i'm not
even level 10 yet you know
like i know it's crazy but i don't i'm not even level 10 yet
i'm thirsty oh we have to activate all these monoliths to
access one of them oh i get it so you see like remember when
we're activating monoliths and stuff and then when you
activate all of these like like these anchors like the rift
anchor it summons one monolith to do a dungeon i see oh i
see now yeah yeah i don't think i'm gonna do that i don't
know i mean we had a good time we played this a lot longer
than i thought yeah we lasted three hours yeah we lasted
three hours that's pretty good for us yeah for an fbs person
who has a very short attention span yeah like yeah honestly
not bad honestly yeah let's check out numbers kind of
mechanics number sixes work i'm on a tangent let's go is it
done i'm pretty sure it's 90 97 you know what no it's almost
done it's good enough it's missing a beam there i fixed it
98 98 and then it's missing a window it's missing one window
or something it's missing yeah it's missing one window on
top oh it is wait do you have it i don't have a glass no
none of us have glass literally two percent it's missing one
window and he just he he because the stair okay essentially
it's done since the stair is bugged and cannot be built he
built a different kind of stair look at this oh he made a
different kind of stair that's smart that's we did it yeah
it's just missing this window right here guys we did it guys
we finished the game the world is beautiful when It's
fucking daytime.
What the fuck?
Number six did it!
Oh, it's good.
Congratulations, number six.
What did he get?
He gets the pride of having a finished house in a game that
might, may or may not die in a month.
You could talk about that.
It's...
It's net ease.
Come on, dude.
It's gonna live at least like two centuries.
I say the things you want to say.
Yep.
I'm publicly saying stuff correctly.
You just speak my mind and it's fine.
You have the power to fight back.
I don't.
What do you mean?
You're Indy.
You want to see, you want to see, you want to speak to the
alligator?
You're Indy.
What do you mean?
Oh, there he is.
He's supposed to see an alligator.
Oh my god, look at him.
Why does he have like a backpack?
What is that?
Oh, no, it's not.
It's just like, hello.
Can I?
Chill.
He's so chill now.
Ow!
Oh, he's not chill now.
Are you scared?
Tangent, why are you scared?
What are you scared about?
I'm not.
Just speak your mind.
Uh, I wish I'm happy.
Ow.
Speak your mind.
Sorry.
Speak your mind about this game.
Speak my mind about it.
honestly again it's it's it's okay but i don't know if it'll
last long let's just be honest there we go it's not too hard
all right goodbye goodbye alligator goodbye you die now
we're gonna eat you up yum yum yum yum yum you ever had
alligator meat uh no i don't wait have you are there
indonesia i had wait there's alligators in indonesia
crocodiles yeah that's not alligator well it's the same shit
is this i want to build okay i summon them look at him oh my
god look guys it's called duty holy shit oh my honestly this
guy i can see he's more of a pvp i can see he's more of a
pvp dude he looks so dumb he looks so dumb i should have
gone He looks super fucking dumb.
He looks super fucking dumb.
Wait, someone yours!
I don't have...
Oh, I'm not using that shit.
You know, you don't have...
Oh my god, why does this guy exist?
Like, oh my god.
It's Call of Duty.
Because I was like, he's so cute!
Alright, let's see.
Securing.
Flawless fortification, build fortification.
I don't remember which one I threw.
I threw the one on the right.
Oh my god.
There we go.
The face is here.
Whoa!
You can throw him.
Yeah.
Yeah, you can throw him.
And then I can be like...
Oh.
Oh, and then he's gone.
It's gone.
It looks so dumb.
I swear he is so dumb.
Oh my god.
Yeah, it looks like a good for PvP.
That was fun though.
That was fun.
Like, I'm glad I did not do a solo.
you didn't have to suffer again i think if i played the solo
i would not have made it to the boss you would not have
figured out the game yeah tension has helped me figure it
out the game ggs tangent three hours of sleep ggs oh yeah
that's true you were you were using your head more than me
even though you had three hours of sleep you know i remember
correctly you asked to play ex-deviant i don't know what the
fuck happened to them oh yeah yeah because like because like
you know ex-deviant was uh ex-deviant has already died so i
see that's funny so i was like yo let's just check out this
game it's launching and it's free too you know ex-deviant is
also free yeah but like this game is new it literally
launched today
just launched not today but like but like eight hours ago
guys when was the last guys chat when was the last time you
watched a streamer play ex deviant don't lie to me you know
what you're so right dude like i i can say this with
confidence there's more tarcoff streamers than ex deviant oh
whoa despite the tarcoff and the tarcoff got cancelled it
still has more players that's a little sad that's honestly
if x deviant had a better server probably
wow i mean a lot of games are basically if they have better
servers it could be good true yeah it's just you know they
just didn't put enough resources into it but even then i
don't think there's been we haven't had a game that's been
like that's done well in the last four years I think five in
the last four to five years we haven't had a shooter game
that's done well that was gonna be like the next big video
game I'm pretty sure what was the last one I think Apex was
the last one and then Rebel Royale almost was like the next
big thing and then they killed it the rem royale was at the
same level as apex at one point and then they killed rem
royale because watch is pretty huge i guess right now she's
been around for so long that's the thing now yeah but it's
been for a lot oh wait valorant valorant was the last next
big yeah valorant was the last game kind of dying i'll be
honest i haven't even touched that game because the valorant
is mostly about cosmetics it's alive because of cosmetics
and the esports scene fucking bumble it's fucking e-date app
okay where you find yeah and that's why that's why Overwatch
was so successful Overwatch walked so Valorant could run
Overwatch Overwatch for the e-dating scene so Valorant could
fucking sprint to the finish line Overwatch created the
e-couple pet names for accounts what was it What was it
kidding and uh, I don't remember the mercy players would be
kidding and then the the DPS player would be like daddy It
was like They would have You hate it because it's true You
hate it because it's true
that's just no guys it started on overwatch it did not start
on discord i mean when was overwatch 2016 um 2016 i think so
yeah yeah you know like overwatch and then they did the
workshop thing and then people did the Overwatch workshop
and then added Tinder on Overwatch.
I'm tired of this.
This is stupid.
Oh my god.
People would be like, ew, Valorant created the cringe
e-dating account names, but it was Overwatch that started it
with the Mercy and Flash DPS duo wasn't wasn't there a
certain website that's like overwatch has the most searched
fucking result yeah yeah yeah because of like sfm yep that's
insane honestly insane holy way to go community used to
believe it runescape did it before runescape was like was
like a what's the word um runescape was more of a niche but
overwatch made it main stream i'm just a merchant like the
e-couple dating scene in runescape was a niche but in
overwatch it was a lifestyle like it means you're good at
the game kind of shit la mao
the fucking lfg look mercy main looking for dps play oh my
god the blue chat Oh, the LFG.
Oh, the LFG.
Stop reminding me of global chats.
Fuck.
Oh, man.
Oh, fuck.
There is a global chat in Overwatch.
I forgot about that.
No, the LFG, not just the global chat, but the LFG section
where people were like looking for players to play with.
And then they would do like LFGs for like the DPS players,
like top 500.
a dps player on smurf account looking for mercy pocket oh my
god
everybody blocked it from their heads because they don't
want to remember but i will always remember the dark times
of overwatch oh my god i already forgot about most of it my
ptsd is resurfacing
Oh, shot, though.
That's why when people let you, Valorant is so cringe
because it was the e-dating scene and I was like, you guys
don't remember real cringe.
Overwatch had it a lot worse than Overwatch created the
nightmare.
I feel like I just relived the life that I didn't have and
turns out I had it and it's just there.
Holy shit.
Fuck.
Oh my god.
I saw the cringe.
Enough YouTube for today.
That's...
I saw the cringe being made since day zero.
I was there at day zero when the cringe started.
Oh yeah, the Genji and Mercy.
Before then, it was the Genji Mercy duos.
That's what made it worse.
genji main yeah that's what made it worse fucking shit hell
bro genji main looking for a mercy duo but is overwatch
worth to play again though like yeah it's worth to play
don't take it seriously it's not as competitive anymore it's
not as competitive more so i would have to pay a few dollars
to change my name that's uh yeah yeah you did I mean, I'm
still on that name.
Yeah.
I'm working on it.
Don't worry.
I had to change several accounts.
I was like, I'm trying to change it.
And I was like, oh, shit, I got to pay this.
Yeah, you don't have your free one because you used it
already.
I used it years ago, man.
I was there on day one as well.
Fuck.
It's okay.
I believe in you.
right you just know okay uh you could just put streamer mode
on and then you never have to change the streamer mode on
changes your actual name the name of the account you just
put streamer mode on and then you don't have your name will
always be like different every time oh but i want to oh shit
yeah but yeah i hope there's i hope there's a new game soon
but I think Valorant was the last the last like big
competitive FPS even now I'll be honest Valorant the mis
like the direction is kind of weird so and I mean I don't
play that I mean it's mostly like I said it's caught like
it's from what Riot and Riot is like mostly like cosmetics
and like they put a heavy focus on cosmetic because that's
where the money is and every time yeah because like Riot
loves having cosmetics and stuff but like i don't know it's
just i feel like uh uh other than that uh i don't really
know what other like shooter game has been out there it's
been decent shreenova guys shreenova it's in it's
interesting but like it's also a tactical shooter so yeah db
knows and how was it actually trinova the Paper mechanic is
really interesting.
Right.
But like, um...
Um...
It, like...
Okay, I think Shrinova is easier than Valorant.
100%.
Because I learned the abilities.
The ability to use this faster than Valorant.
I still don't know how to use the abilities in Valorant.
But like, I know how to use the abilities in Shrinova.
But I think, like, Shrinova...
I think the main...
Biggest issue of Shrinova is just that fact that, like...
It's just the mechanics itself is like a little weird It's
like the paper mechanics is like really weird to handle
Because you can use the paper mechanics Gotcha games It's
not a gotcha game because I know I'm just bored I'm on that
gotcha games right now Jesus Christ Yeah I think like
Shrenava the biggest issue with Shrenava is that The
hardcore gamers that like the FPS gamers Shrinova because
it's anime Right Yeah because like I saw that Shrinova is
like Really popular amongst like you know people who are
Into Genshin Impact and like Gotcha in general Because like
a lot of people that are playing Shrinova were mostly Just
like Who the fuck cut that tree The tree fell on top of me
But like Shrinova It was like people who were playing like
Who played it were people who played like Like just like
Genshin Impact and stuff like that and they're like oh i
love chinova because it's like um it's like a game that is
different from genshin but it's like an fps game or like not
fps tps but like i saw like in general like not a lot like
act like not a lot of like the uh competitive scene like the
the uh the yeah the osu players and the genshin like the uh
gacha players love chinova but like if you talk about like
competitive like uh the competitive of shooter fan base, I
barely saw anybody was hyping it up.
So I think that was the biggest issue.
Because the fan base were shooter games, especially in the
West.
If they see anime, they're just like, ugh, you know?
Yeah, no shit.
Because there's a lot of normies there.
So normies are like, normies are like, ooh, anime, you know.
They'll be like, yeah, Call of Duty, Apex, Battle End, Call
of Duty, uh uh battlefield but like when they see anime
they're just like even if it's a good shooter it'll just be
like oh anime it's true when i was like when i got invited
to the tournament i literally had like um like you would i
did i did not see like shroud play shrenava i did not see
like um you know like timmy or shroud play shrenava and like
you know like shroud would play like every fps like every
shroud will play any shooter game but i didn't see shroud
play trinova so i thought that was like you know that
basically sort of tells you like uh the what the normal
player base like would want to watch mm-hmm oh yeah deadlock
fucking valves upcoming games something like that oh yeah
yeah deadlock yeah uh that's okay deadlock uh is deadlock
the newest valve upcoming yeah yeah yeah it's wait i i don't
remember what i'm allowed or not allowed to say what insane
that's insane that's insane i think i think you just said
something you shouldn't say but okay i guess that's all i'll
say there you there you go chat No way No shot Yeah Yeah By
contract Holy shit Oh my god I didn't say anything I just
said Deathlock is That's all I said Right Right Right right
right right Interesting Totally totally i can back that up
yeah she just she just said that and that's it she didn't
say anything of it interesting yeah we heard nothing guys
that that's funny whose house is this what the house yeah
who the fuck built their house above uh oh where did this
guy come from oh wait it's this guy's house hey without
their permission oh my god he doesn't have pants either wait
he's literally in his underwear just like us wait no take
off your pants right now what everybody else has no pants
except you at number six because the goddamn shit that has
told me to not wear any fucking uh to wear what do you call
it you gotta join the crowd Look, I can be naked naked.
Wait, what the fuck?
Can I be naked naked?
You can do that?
There's like pants underneath the pants?
Yeah.
Oh my god, wait, you're right.
Wait, how do I un-equip it?
Oh my god.
Holy shit.
It's possible.
Oh my god.
I can't even put pads back on it.
Holy shit.
You can go beyond.
What the fuck?
We're chilling.
Oh my.
Oh my god.
Yeah, I do hope Trinova does do well in the future.
And like the Normie shooter people would enjoy it.
Because it is interesting.
I feel like if the Normies tried Trinova and are not like,
oh, anime and stuff like that, I think it could go really
well.
Because the game and mechanics are pretty interesting.
And like, I hope they have the Overwatch mode as a ranking
too.
Because the rank game is Valorant.
play is overwatch which i thought was pretty silly like i
feel like both the overwatch section and the quick and the
valorant section should be its own thing um they shouldn't
make like one as quick play and the other is rank um oh yeah
and then the apparently the overwatch mode was like super
unbalanced too because like it's like uh defense sided which
i agree when i played it it was
uh because it's so hard to like uh play d attack on the maps
yeah i saw a little bit of game plan yeah oh marvel rivals i
hope marvel rivals does well honestly oh yeah yeah i got you
in marvel rivals yeah yeah yeah you got me in and i didn't
play that much since the server is only available in na yeah
because it was it was pretty unstable for me holy shit but i
enjoyed it so far especially in the training yeah holy fuck
i hope city of the heroes oh i uh do you hear it the next
beta test is next week right just aria next week or in two
weeks i think yeah next beta test i'm definitely gonna try
it again for the next test um i definitely had a lot of fun
with marvel arrivals but the official game comes out in 2025
that's still a long way yeah so it's we gotta wait until
2025 to play the game yeah welcome to our like impromptu
podcast guys sorry like for not for me it's normal because
every game is just basically free talk for me yeah legit
from here alligator's get away yeah i hope i hope i hope uh
marble rivals is also successful because like we need a new
game for the shooters we're just so it's just been like
we're all bouncing between Like, we're all, like, bouncing
to game, to game, trying to find a new game to play.
Like, for me right now, if it's just stupid FPS, it's just,
again, Tarkov.
The fuck, it's just Tarkov, Apex, or Overwatch.
And then for, and then if you're, like, a tactical shooter,
Valorant.
Look, I'm just, like, I don't care.
Whatever it takes for someone to get back to their lobbies
or me to my back at my lobbies.
Yeah, I'm sorry for those who are, like, what about csgo
guys you know or csgo 2 guys you know cs is cs2 is only
alive in europe you guys don't lie it's alive in eu and asia
yeah but i don't know about na no it's it's dead it's like
almost dead in na because the only thing i do in cs2 now is
just To sell and buy items.
Like how I used to.
And yeah, I'm up like $300 in CS already.
Yeah.
I haven't cashed it out.
Don't people like use like CSGO and CS2 like skins and
knives to like...
What's the word?
Like...
What's the word when they like use it for like money?
Trade money illegally?
RMT?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
There's like a word for it for those who trade money
laundering.
Yeah a lot of people use money laundering Yeah, do you know
that a lot of people use like CS go and CS two skins for
like money laundering That's why like sometimes knives go
for like in crazy prices because they use it for money
laundering You know that.
I mean I heard so I heard like man The most expensive thing
I had is just like $210 and that's it.
Yeah, yeah, that's what I like i know like they do that as
well because like um they used to do that for like art
galleries so like in art galleries uh some art pieces go for
like you know millions of dollars but it's usually a money
laundering scheme like you see like very expensive paintings
being sold at art galleries but it's not really they're not
really selling the painting they're just using it for like
money laundering so they do that but with like csgo skins
too or they still do they still do but it's like another way
to do money laundering but like you know they won't if you
were like we can't confirm or deny that or like tax evasion
yeah I guess too I love tax evasion huh oh and you said I
said something that could be potentially legal but you just
said I love tax evasion
no no no no I pay my taxes Do you?
I buy cigarettes.
That's a huge amount of tax.
It's crazy.
No, but, but actually, oh yeah, I actually quit smoking.
I'm trying.
Wait, you quit.
Oh, you're trying to, right?
I'm, it's like my, it's like my second week.
And I'm- Your second week?
Mm-hmm.
Holy shit.
Are you okay?
No.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, how long have you been smoking?
How long have I been smoking?
like the whole 12 years 12 years oh my god good luck man
yeah i believe in you especially like for like like um like
an asian guy like it's so hard to quit smoking yep yeah
because like it's like sort of like uh what's it called like
a culture sort of type deal yeah the reason why i'm quitting
is not because of health reasons because it's getting
expensive yeah and not just that not just that not just that
but they'll hide the number one for me like i honestly if i
if the taste is all right i'll probably still going but the
taste is and they charge more so i'm like what is this you
don't taste like you used to well fuck you i'm buying this
i'm mad so it's like a boycott it's like a boycott for you
oh good luck man i believe i think you can do it if you like
dedicate and then you should also like look at how much you
save just to motivate yourself too is it is it bad that i go
to coffee instead now because like um well like uh they're
drinking excessive amount of coffee is not healthy but well
no no but it's healthier than smoking it doesn't up your
lungs it just fucks up your heart well yeah well i don't
drink that much of a cop i mean i'm starting to learn how to
brew itself and grinding it oh yeah that's that's pretty
good yeah what the what is that cover it's another crocodile
jesus christ this game is freaky just the crocodile that of
nowhere yeah like as long as like you know um it's like
healthier than than smoking and i think like if you track
down like how much money you spend like there are save each
week from it i think it'll motivate you even more yeah yeah
for me right now i i don't even buy like those nicotine
patches right and so yeah so it's like yeah holy gold cold
turkey you're just yeah and then i'm thinking what if i buy
like what do you call a vape but like the juice is not like
without the nicotine you know yeah but vaping is also like
similar though it's just going from one addiction it's just
the nicotine the thing is the nicotine's fucking me up and I
yeah but isn't vaping more expensive because you're buying
like refills honestly yeah oh it's cheapier okay I was
thinking like I know like vaping can become more expensive
but like especially there's no nicotine like so it's not
taxed yeah but vaping is also bad too everything is bad like
yeah but caffeine is better than vaping right that's true
Might as well do, like, caffeine instead of vaping because
it's, like, it's, it's, like, healthier.
Well, I mean, like, quote-unquote, healthier.
It's, it's the healthier addiction, like, to, like, go to.
Yeah, the lesser of all evil, the lesser of three evils.
It's pretty— All in moderation.
Yeah, yeah, Chad, we know that caffeine is bad.
Number six is so real.
But, like, if, um, if, like, he has to pick between
caffeine, cigarettes, or vaping, I'd rather you just Yeah We
had Like Cause like I don't think Tension can Like He could
try But I feel like It's better to just Like swap to like A
lesser Harmful addiction Than going like Full on cold turkey
Cause that's also not good For you To just Completely stop
For the For the four First four days When I sleep My leg
just Yeah Tremble so Fucking much And I woke up With a sore
leg Because of like The excessive Shake in his Like Yeah
Yeah Like going cold turkey like quitting suddenly all of a
sudden is really really bad too so it's better to like do
like in moderation and like less yeah and like less
stressful than just like stopping altogether and then like
and then if caffeine gets pretty bad you're then like he can
slowly try and stop that and then you can swap the tea after
your coffee um i i do tea sometimes oh yeah that's good tea
is also pretty healthy i'm more of a i'm more of a both of
worlds it's just that i need the more of a little bit more
of a kick because either way for me tea or coffee i will
shit them either way i think that's for everybody that's
what caffeine does like it's it's the same for like my mom
especially she buys like high caffeinated tea leaves and i'm
like jesus man like i keep insisting drink less or something
like this like blue tea or stuff you know oh yeah we need
those extra like the kung fu tea you know like yeah yeah no
people were like don't start smoking it's very hard to no
that's true that's true uh it's very hard to quit smoking
because it's just going cold turkey is like really like not
cold turkey but like but like just stopping it and it's like
like i know like in like for my family like uh majority is
like uh like my uncles my my uncles my dad my grandparents
they all smoked because it was like like uh bonding thing
you know i don't know it was for you but like for like my
family like they would like share cigarettes and stuff for
like a bonding thing and a talk while smoking and stuff like
that definitely normal yeah social smoking is a thing yeah i
might just do that um yeah so it's like very hard to quit
and stuff uh yeah it's like a huge uh cultural thing too um
so i like grew up around uh like a family that smoked a lot
just yeah i mean same yeah so it's hard to quit especially
yeah yeah like it's really hard too because like it's hard
to quit just because like like you know your entire family
smoking as well so it's like it's like you know like you're
surrounded by a presence of smokers so it's like hard to
suddenly stop smoking just because you know uh just because
like you know it's awkward so like yeah it is yeah yes so
but like and and the other reason is that why i'm stopping
smoking because apparently i'm the only one left who still
smokes oh yeah yeah because everybody slowly stopped smoking
for your family like all of my cousins has got married and
they have a son and a child now so yeah stopped and i'm like
What the fuck?
My dad didn't stop.
Your dad didn't stop?
Oh, same.
Same.
Yeah.
My dad didn't stop smoking.
My dad didn't stop.
Yeah.
But he stopped.
I don't smoke though.
I don't smoke.
He smoked for more than 30 years and he stopped like 2014 or
13.
My dad's so going.
He hasn't inhaled Any of those in years.
It's crazy What the fuck?
Hey, did your dad also stop smoking too crocodile?
But yeah, no, no, I was growing up like my dad would like He
would like I think like he wouldn't smoke in front of me,
but like I could smell the smoke, you know, and then the
worst Probably for me is when we were going on a trip He
smokes while driving and it just opens the window.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, yeah.
That feels like 2,000 Asian dad right there.
Hell yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
No, my dad, he would just like go outside like the balcony
or just go outside the smoke.
He used to like just like go to like, like the bathrooms to
smoke just because like he didn't want to bring the in.
the house and stuff yeah because there's a fucking exhaust
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah um but i remember like uh
because like i remember when i was really young because like
you know i was raised i was raised in canada and then you
know they're like smoky's really really bad like it's so bad
i mean it is bad but like it's like in your face more so
than like um like it was like it's like so in your face so i
would be like stop smoking and then uh and then I don't know
if you ever seen, you know, like those museums where it's
like it's like those like human body museum where you know
what I'm talking about?
It shows like the body of a smoker.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then they're like, this is the lungs of a smoker and
this is like the lungs of a person who doesn't smoke.
And then I would point and then we would visit those museums
and I would be like, yeah, that's you.
These are your lungs.
I used to do that.
And then I became a smoker and I saw it and I just laughed
and then oh my god
yeah I mean like yeah I don't like he used to when I was
younger I noticed it more but like I think as I got older
like he my dad does like go outside like try to hide it more
in front of me then but he hasn't quit yet yeah honestly for
me as a kid I didn't get what the fuck why is he smoking
it's just wasting money even though it was so dirty cheap
back then it was it was 50 cents oh yeah like indonesia yeah
yeah it's like 50 cents and then now it's like two dollars
it's still cheap but holy fuck it's expensive in indonesia
taxes or just like trying to make people stop smoking it's
both and either way there's always a cheaper cigarettes yeah
but my the one i smoke it's like two dollars and yeah like
yeah it's just a lot of money to spend.
That's like a whole meal for the day.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh yeah, I understand.
Well, I hope it works.
I hope it works out for you.
Yeah.
Because you would save a lot of money and also be healthier,
too.
Oh, definitely.
I started to make like every time I think maybe should I buy
a cigarette, I will just straight up open my mobile banking
and just deposit to another saving for the same price of the
cereal.
That's smart.
That's really smart.
yeah yeah that's good for you i have in there saving let me
just yeah that's really about 48 dollars holy since you
started when did you start like like stop smoking yeah a
couple of weeks for now a couple of weeks oh my god okay
it's been yeah and it's like a pack right two dollars a pack
so i think it's almost a month oh my god that's a lot yeah
that's that's i remember because like i remember you you
used to smoke a lot too yeah so like so like i hope like i
honestly hope it goes well and that you can like you don't
fall like it's good that a lot of the people also stop too
like you're the people around you stop to stop since
indonesian cigarettes are really good and oh my god it's so
fucking hard to stop yeah and all but it's also good that
like the your relatives also stop smoking so like it's
easier to like you don't get like influenced by others to
like stop smoke you know to like start smoking you know
because it's not in front of you and stuff and as long as
you don't go outside you don't see the people smoking my
only problem is that i don't know how to say it in english
but like indonesian people tend to like just smoke they're
bored yeah no i get like they don't have anything to do yeah
and they don't want to think over so much stuff they'll just
go outside and just light up one that's me that's what i
find it hard right now i am i'm very bored sometimes yeah
that's why we have exacid on here that's why we have our
podcast yes i am especially with three hours i just like had
a coffee and
I hope I hope it goes well to everybody else who's also
trying to stop an addiction I hope like you guys are able to
handle it and like being able to like you know at least or
swap to it like an addiction that's like a lot healthier and
stuff ever heard of ever heard of opening loot boxes I just
work
my free time is just work now so like I don't have I don't
have time to be addicted to anything I wish I could.
I literally have no time to be addicted to things.
You know what I'm glad?
The thing is, I live in Indonesia, right?
Gambling is illegal.
Holy fuck.
I would probably jump in that.
Yeah, holy shit.
I'm glad gambling's illegal.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm banned in a few casinos, but hey, man.
You're banned in a few.
What did you do?
Did you count cards?
I win.
You count cards, don't you?
You count cards.
No.
then how do you win yeah well math you count cards no oh
it's math it's counting cards like like math is it's numbers
i was like uh give me give me your id to like i was turning
on my chest and then they're like oh can i see your
passwords are okay i don't understand how counting cards is
banned because it's just playing the game better like it
literally just a smart person playing a game better.
I don't understand why I don't even need to count it.
I already know.
It's not illegal.
It's just you don't want them to win.
That's basically it.
Well, I don't play poker.
That's the thing.
I play chess.
You don't want you to win money.
Yeah.
That's why you need to count cards and then win a little bit
of money and then leave and then come back another time at a
later date.
So you don't like you you can you can still you slowly leech
money off of them yeah that's why they didn't kick me off
but then when they asked asked me for my passport i was like
hmm you're banning me aren't you yeah because it's a private
property they own it so it's like of course they can ban you
they're banning me that's why you play yeah but and that's
why like uh and you can't even do like online poker like
online gambling regarding like counting card using counting
cards because it's all an algorithm it's an algorithm it's
not like you can actually like out you can't really out game
the algorithm I want like 800 700 dollars I think like yeah
it's not that much but they're like stupidly counting it
like what the fuck yeah we go oh what the fuck there's a
hundred don't what What?
You got an Aka?
Someone donated a hundred.
That's...
Yo!
Who is it?
Rita.
Rita, thanks for the Aka super.
Thank you, thank you.
Dude, what the...
What's the message?
What the fuck?
What was the message?
Tengen.
Right now, and so I wish I could watch the whole collab.
Oh, she's traveling and she donated a hundred.
That's crazy.
Oh my god, thanks Rita!
Rita surpassed you in the rank, by the way.
Oh, they're surpassed me?
Oh, nice.
That's insane.
Attack.
Good, thank God.
You can't do this to me, man.
You can't do this to me.
That gave me a hard time.
Drawing your Oshie.
Having a headache.
Filing your taxes.
That's good.
Good for you, man.
I'm glad you're getting that money.
Yeah, you get to keep 100% of it.
that yeah not 100 people i mean oh yeah 30 sorry wait paypal
takes like no oh no you do stream labs so it's like yes you
know uh so it's like what was it it's like five percent or
some five to ten percent right yeah yeah yeah oh hey i got
an akatu that's insane oh my god arch thank you for the
akasupa thank you thank you i wish i could watch the whole
collab that's what that's when you That's why you were going
to watch the VOD later.
VODs are there.
Don't worry about it.
Yeah.
The game is goofy.
Guys, yeah.
You guys got to watch the whole VOD so you can get the
podcast section too.
With number six right here.
Like, hang out with us too.
Number six.
You know what?
That goes to my new powers of playing graphics card.
Oh yeah.
The moment you get new graphics card, we should play
Remnant.
I hope I can get that graphics card too.
Yeah, that's fine.
I mean, it's always going to be there.
It's all pricey.
It's going to be there.
Okay, just wait until the 500 series comes out, and then you
buy a 40.
Oh, yeah.
You know what?
You're so right.
Literally just wait until the 500 series comes out, and then
fucking the 40s are going to drop by like 50% or some shit.
You're so right.
Holy.
Oh, it's going to come out eventually.
When did the 40s come out?
I'm not sure, actually.
It usually takes like, what, two to three years?
for a new card right it's a year are you no it's not a year
it's like two years i feel like i just i just need that
encoding yeah because because just buy 30 most of my
indonesian viewers are watching with like their mobile data
and it would be a crocodile we're having a podcast it's
crazy go crazy for mobile data oh shit yeah or just buy 300
series after they announced the five the five like the 5000
the 3000 does not increase that much of my performance and i
guess waiting for the 4000 to drop price is better yeah just
save up for the 4000 i yeah somebody said the 3090 should be
a good deal now i don't know if that'll increase a lot i
can't find a 3090 that's the thing oh like most of people
who bought the 3090s mining stuff yeah yeah yeah i mean yeah
and i can't find a good one yeah for mining bitcoin and yep
and nfts like show pal thank you for the super chat good
luck on all the drugs thank you and bill yeah that was a
nice podcast that we had the random in the random podcast in
the middle of uh in the middle of the wilderness what's it
was great i had a great time tangent and number six thanks
for building my house um number six the mvp he's the real
guy he he you know what was the mvp part he knew i was never
going to come back to the house but he still built it like
he knew i was never coming back to this place but he still
did it for us yeah he he's real that's a real dragoon right
there what a legend not a fucking legend yeah this place
shall be a monument i don't know if the thing will still be
yeah i don't know if they do wipes or anything but remember
this place guys this will be the newest tourist destination
historical moment yeah the tourist destination where where
doki and tangent had their first day and only day wants you
the first and the last days of doki and tension they'd be
like oh my god it was like a tour like those like tours were
like historical tours and like and here folks is where doki
and tension had their pot their one hour podcast right here
on that back right here
ggs man ggs i have a great time it was great hanging out
with you if you're looking for a friend to collab with or
play stupid games i'm honestly i've been looking for some
stupid games instead of fbs yeah of course team together oh
my god i saw i saw the stream i saw that stream you did yeah
it's it's honestly it doesn't make me mad it's just i'm
tired of laughing in that game all right i'm gonna go talk
to my dragons now what do you do my leg you see what i'm
seeing that's what the fuck oh my god all right i am oh my
god i see now i know what you mean yeah now i know what you
mean oh my god all right i'm gonna go talk to my dragoons
now but it was nice hanging out man yeah man appreciate it
for the invite yeah of course of course i'll see you next
time dude Yeah.
Yeah.
All right.
Chee-chees, chee-chees.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
Oh, wow.
I did not expect to stream this long.
We had two back-to-back collabs that went on for like, for a
long time.
But it was fun.
I had a great conversation.
We had our impromptu podcast and everything.
And I had a great time just hanging out, you know, just
chatting.
and hang out with you guys as well as with uh tension and
number six uh that was a great time honestly it was it was
fun collab uh i am tired but i hope you guys enjoyed like
the stream um i know that the game was like you know it was
not what we expected but it was still fun though um And I
hope you guys had a great time.
You guys rest up a lot.
You had two very long back-to-back streams and everything.
So I'm going to call it here, guys.
As always, everybody, stay hydrated.
Posture check.
Get up and move around to get that blood flowing.
And if you stayed up for me, head to bed.
Because you deserve it.
I'll see you guys next time, everybody.
Bye, guys.
Bye.