It says you're checked in.
Okay, I hope I'm not jumpmaster.
It says check in now.
Okay, go to tournament.
How do I check in?
Oh, you're checked in.
I'm checked in.
Don't worry, guys.
I'm so checked in.
Like, why is the message?
Why is this overlooking my messages?
Why is this gigantic?
I have no idea.
Like, who is your avatars are so big?
All right, I'm warming up, guys.
I'm warming up.
I'm doing the thing.
We're starting on Storm Point.
look my trios matches in stormpoint as well oh okay
i checked in i see i'm checked in as well oh i i i it says
i'm checked in i don't know do i have to check in too but i
don't know what my email is and stuff like this no you don't
have to check in it's fine oh thank god one one one person
checks in it checks everyone in oh thank god we're learning
so they'll give us five minutes
real quick one sec all right i warm up my chat's not gonna
see this until 10 minutes later all right guys this are you
gonna use the bathroom wait wait if we're storm playing am i
still caustic or am i watching i don't i don't know man i
don't even know what i'm playing this is something we needed
to figure out earlier no we can figure it out as we go i'll
be watching Even though what am I?
I don't even know what I am.
All right, does this open up my game?
What the fuck are people?
I want to shoot.
Yes, yes.
Okay, so now...
Let's, uh...
Oh, fuck.
Oh, I did.
Oh, I'm still wearing my fucking...
I forgot to adjust my stuff.
Yeah!
dashboard i forgot to turn off my karaoke stuff i was like
wait a minute why am i oh i'm so tired from from it that's
for sure i hope my guy dies so i can't uh i need to turn off
a lot of my karaoke stuff okay off off my guy's still alive
bro what the oh my god he's rising me bro what the bro oh my
he fucking lives and he wins bro i'm not i was not ready for
this are you in a game i'm in a trio game i mean the trio
they warm up the guy actually won the fight i was trying to
literally the worst timing my landlord mentioned about rent
and something having on my account literally worst timing
ever oh no i don't know apparently they didn't get my
fucking payments for rent it like what what i understand are
you gonna kick you out i hope so i hate this place anyway
i'm done renting out for this year i'm 100 buying somewhere
oh yeah i've landlords are scams you are not an entrepreneur
you're a scammer you're all scammers does he know your
stream i don't know know i live in a big-ass building bro
it's a multi-billion dollar corporation of course the ones
that scam you the hardest you don't become a billionaire oh
yeah no no no no oh yeah yeah like the corp you're you're
renting from a company yeah yeah yeah i'm writing the
fattest yelp review about this place bro and i leave i'm
airing this bitch out on twitter everything this place sucks
all right where do you where do you live where do you live
tell to everybody where do you live where do you live where
do you live jack where do you live on stream right now on
two on three different streams where do you live i'm fucking
weak what is your apartment number jack yeah what is it well
well now you're oh wait we know your first name we'll just
find the the why is my camera my camera's been black and
white this whole time ten minutes later ten minutes later i
see why my camera's black I went, what the fuck?
Oh, Chad, I clicked video call back then.
Oh, Chad, well, you just got a really interesting version of
me for a little bit.
That was dope.
Oh, yeah.
That's fire.
All right, cool.
Oh, my gosh.
Why did my guy have to win this fight?
I wanted to queue up for the next game.
I will never, ever, ever be paying rent ever again after
this year.
I fucking hate it.
Yeah, but then you're going to have a mortgage.
I would rather pay a mortgage every day of the week.
To be fair, mortgages are actually good for you or your
credit.
Oh, yeah.
But not like too bad of a mortgage.
If you don't get a too bad of a mortgage.
Yeah.
The more you pay off your credit, your mortgage, the better
credit you get.
Yeah, 100%.
Because it says you're a responsible homeowner.
Responsible.
Apparently there's an earthquake in LA.
I didn't feel anything.
There was.
Apparently.
The earth is dying.
Where my friend lived.
Honestly.
This is why he didn't live like, you need to live away from
the ocean.
So you don't have to worry about the water sucking up the
land if there was an earthquake.
Yeah, live in a landlocked city.
Oh, New York City, seriously.
Is code out yet?
You're always asking if the code is out.
I'm freaking out, dude.
I'm freaking out.
Is the code out?
When does my fucking stream go live?
Waiting for the fucking...
No, I'm waiting for the YouTube thing to be like, go live.
Oh, my God.
10 minutes is so long.
10 minutes is actually so long.
It's such a long delay.
All right.
Who the fuck is?
I guess it's because, like, you know, like...
Cheater mans, hacker mans.
Because it's like, that's how long...
It's like too into the game that at that point, they can't
do anything in the stream tonight.
still pretty fucking long
i'm so locked in i need you to like micromanage what
upgrades to get if it's a character i don't know what um
what's this ping an item please what the does that mean
bro i'm multitasking here i can't ping shit for you my
random teammate i don't I'm so fucking I'm trying to fucking
I'm trying to figure out how to fucking stream I don't know
but YouTube thing doesn't pop up and be like go live wait
does YouTube can you add 10 minute delay you have to be able
to there's no way you can no I have done in the past I just
rarely added delays before but it's like the option to go
live isn't going live oh wait wait guys i got good news and
i want one two three four five six what's the good news one
two three four okay good news is we have 15 teams in our
lobby so i'm guessing a lot of people didn't click check in
so they got removed from the tournament oh bad news is we
have zone davis in our lobby oh really that's good that's
good oh okay so we we just let zone davis kill everyone
exactly make sure we avoid him but what if yeah okay does
anyone know where he lands and screams is it no idea i need
to ask look at his bots look at his bots and see where he
lands yeah yeah yeah and then we just land the opposite side
yet though uh i'm still waiting yeah look at his i'm meant
to create the lobby we're so shocked look at the bots oh my
god i can go live
I can go live now!
Fucking...
10 minute delays, man.
D.
Davis.
Where does he land in Scripps so we can avoid his ass?
Videos.
My god, my guy's killing everybody.
I'm just existing at this point.
No, all his stream titles are Smiley Face.
How am I supposed to know where you land in Scripps?
It's time to watch all his streams.
Did you put the code in the chat, Timber?
Yeah.
I didn't yet.
but i will when it comes out oh it's still not out bro what
the fuck i'm tripping out bro i want to get in this goddamn
game i'm so ready i'm not i'm not gonna lie i'm not i'm not
ready i don't feel ready i shot i shot my gun like once in
this trio game and i have 77 damage.
Oh my god.
We are so fucked.
I am not ready.
We're so fucked.
Don't worry, viewers won't find until 10 minutes later.
Alright, she lands checkpoint and checkpoint and fissure, it
looks like.
Fissure.
Okay, so we just avoid that.
Just go the opposite side of that.
Sorry, I just had code in chat.
Oh, it codes out?
Yeah, but I need to warm up my charge rifle.
You though?
You really need to warm up your charge rifle?
Tell
me when to join the lobby, because I'm still in this goddamn
trio's match.
I can't leave because this guy has tried so hard to carry
me.
He knows you're a streamer, he's like...
he's done so much for me all right codes out baby w let's go
tempo thanks for code let's let's not get round one no no
one i mean bro i'm gonna be honest if we get round one that
would be so funny that'd be funny in a very bad way that'd
be so funny don't worry our viewers won't know delete oh
right uh 15.
say 15 yeah oh my god bro my aim's not not doing so well
just so you know honestly if we're being real we probably
should have changed our names for the first like yeah we
should have changed i'm not kidding so we don't get a stream
snake so some people won't know how much lobby we were in
they would definitely throw our game for the content
I'd would.
They probably don't even stream, so there's no play.
Yeah, no, they don't need a stream.
It's the satisfaction.
I'll use stream snipers.
I'm turning on the mode thing, the mode that doesn't tell me
who killed me.
So none of you will get satisfaction.
None of you will get satisfaction.
Not if no one can see it.
All right, my chargeback goes on my duck.
I'm ready to go.
Apparently, you're so quiet while I figure this out 10
minutes later.
No, I can't adjust the volume because I have to fucking
fight.
Oh, wait.
I'm gonna pull up a map so I can figure out whatever.
Oh, shit.
What the fuck?
Oh, my God.
Nice wig.
High wig.
Yeah, we're fucking shocked.
I blame Whig.
It's all.
This is your fault, Whig.
This is your fault.
If we get fucking landed on, it's all Whig's fault.
All right.
We'll just say where we're going.
Where are we going, though?
Because actually, we don't know what we're doing.
We haven't discussed that at all.
I know.
I've been waiting for this discussion for a while.
What you mean, you just woke up.
I've been asking.
I was like, whoa, where do we go, guys?
What do we play?
I've been asking this for a while.
Where are we going, dude?
What's going on?
Um, I mean, where are we going?
Yeah, that's a good question.
I mean, I feel like, I don't know.
It's also only 15 teams, so.
Harvester would be pretty good for us.
Wait, where do we, what, um, what placement do we have to do
to, to like, top 10?
Okay.
We just need to be better than five teams.
That's it.
all the way through so all we ought to see it be better than
five teams yeah which is really easy or should be yeah
there's already teams contesting each other so this is great
this is good for us all right yeah bro oh my god what the oh
my god oh my god you know harvest snaps baked green pea
snatch you ever heard of this what snatch what yeah baked
green pea snatch what the fuck is that i'm so good i'm
eating right now i'm so not locked in from off this too i'm
so not are you eating oh i haven't even had lunch yet okay
guys this is even breakfast i didn't even eat eating yeah
more of your aim so bad all right wait all right all right
what's good all right harvester is not open okay what is
open uh in the middle or you're surprised surprisingly Sky
West Trials is still open I think we should go Sky West
Trials okay Sky West Trials and we can go if we want to
actually okay I want to be that guy we might struggle the
Sky West Trials our loot unless unless what I got less what
oh no wait no wait yeah we want to avoid Scott actually we
want to avoid Fischer because that's where Davis lands so
okay Big Mod Stacks we just need to avoid fissure let let uh
davis's team kill everyone and we'll just keep collecting
free just collector boxes yeah collector go next badge yeah
wait actually the thing about when we're going wait i'm
freaking out okay i don't want to go landslide that's for
sure staging not really either what's taken what's taken um
fissure staging harvester siphon tree geyser that's taken
yeah and then overlook and epi survey so stacks is available
yeah mod and stacks are still open we should take stacks i
think okay and now what about stormpoint stormpoint the
middle pois that are open are a cedo barometer pylon oh cedo
takes us happy to be here i'm gonna say cedo stacks wait
wait wait um what davis lands in checkpoint uh joe can you
feel like getting the game today or tomorrow what are you
thinking wait what you want to get the game anytime sooner
what's going on the code out oh oh yeah oh yeah i did it hey
guys i'm coming in yeah great awesome i'm still locked in
i'm not guys i i was just listening in i didn't realize we
were in
wait we're missing team 10 too yeah and two teams are
missing zone davis is bro zone davis is gonna run at us man
we should never mind zone davis is full here yeah team 10
and team three is missing a player is just gonna run it at
us land wherever we see a duo land all right so are we
running kp yeah but what if they're landing where zone davis
is Then we kill them and run away.
I think you're way too confident right now.
It's called.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's do Ceto and Stacks.
Those ones should be free.
All right, Ceto and Stacks.
I don't remember where either of these are.
Wait, so should I...
I should go Watson, right?
Because they're on Stormflight.
And then Caustic on World's Edge.
Okay, but where do I go?
What do we yeah, I'm about to say what do we go here?
Yeah, what do I?
Oh, yeah, Wigs on Blood.
Yeah, yeah, because you're the roller.
We were, we're starting.
I'm playing Blood both maps then.
You guys cool with that?
Yeah, okay, wait, what do I play?
What do I play?
Bang?
I mean, on this map, Bang probably.
Okay, I'll do Bang.
Okay, you guys gotta like micromanage me here.
Oh, you're good, you're good.
I'll do my best.
You're good.
I'm locked in.
Here's our IGL.
Yeah, you're gonna micromanage me.
I always turn my brain off when I rank.
I can't lie, bro, no Valp though.
we need make sure we just prioritize evac towers we find one
literally just say something like immediately get an evac
you're like hey got an evac it's gonna be a super important
comm just because we don't have a valve to get in anywhere
agreed uh how do we loot cedo um okay so cedo station i
think one should land the bottom side near jurassic one and
then one just lands in the middle and one goes big building
on the right side it's pretty simple i mean we could go we
could stretch bean and just maybe see if there's someone's
going bean but i think we just don't get greedy here because
i don't even know oh my god we have hot zone yay whoa
that'll be too we don't even know if we're gonna land on yet
but that no one could have said anything and they can still
land here we might get a contest just watch out we just
chill we just chill yeah it's like here's the play if we're
gonna get tested make sure we just group up together at some
spot on seo station go from there yeah yeah no one has
dropped from this plane no there's like one team here i
don't 14 squads we just got to be better than four squads
this is it we got to be better than four squads to be fair
announcing where we're going is actually probably worse for
us just because of people wanting to land on us i know
that's why i was like i don't know we should talk about we
should have typed this out uh timberland middle and then
i'll land a beer yeah you're good okay i'll land the side
there that's on here yeah dear thing you're good all right
so i mean Whatever guns you guys want to take, feel free.
This first round doesn't really, shouldn't be that hard for
us.
I got an evac.
Hard rifle.
Nice.
Good call.
Look at us.
Look at you.
We're doing so well.
Let's fucking go.
We're off to a better start than we ever thought.
We got an evac on the first drop.
Let's fucking go.
This is better than Twitch Rivals.
Oh, that's way better than Twitch Rivals.
I think actually anything's better than Twitch Rivals.
Twitch Rivals never happen.
so painful how do we have zero beacons oh just like twitch
rivals we had to we had to fly somewhere else to get a
beacon yeah every time every time i mean we could just this
zone actually might be ending near us i think it's gonna be
barometer but we can just stay here for right now and just
play for the next zone i think we're just chilling barometer
side or uh chill towards uh see that far yep i don't want to
use a car there's also this year i haven't seen a vault but
I have it, but you want the vault.
No, you're good.
You're good.
I'm actually going to take this energy.
Oh, hey, vault, vault.
Oh, nice.
I'll take that over here.
Guys, I need a target.
Am I trolling tempo?
If I do that, you think, or what?
No.
No?
Okay.
There's another gold mag there.
There's a 6x here if you want, when you get the tri-drifle.
There's another Evac!
Guys!
Nice.
I can take that one.
I found a vault, too.
Nice.
Oh my god, there's so many vaults.
Yeah, I'm not going to lie.
After I said that, I just found like so many.
Yeah, I'd found like two votes.
Holy shit.
Is there any evo caches that we could farm up in the way
too?
I mean, it's just going to pull towards the outside side.
It's just going to be right side area.
So if we can get there quick and do one of those buildings,
we're good to go.
I doubt we get sent on.
We might get sent on, but I'm going to be honest.
I'm pretty confident in our 3v3 ability.
We might not play it by all time, but I think we're better
than the average player in these lobbies.
I think I'm on like 100 frames.
Oh, no.
Performance.
No, no, no, no.
Okay.
No, we're okay.
I think we're okay.
Okay.
Are you sure we're okay?
I don't know.
This does not feel like 240 frames, but like, maybe it's my
mod today.
We're good.
All right.
You guys ready to rip it out or what?
No, we're okay.
We're okay.
I'll play this one game on less frames.
That's fine.
Where was the other evac out, Doki?
What was it?
It was like in one of the buildings here.
Oh, gosh.
You might be able to find it in the one of the buildings.
I have an evac as well.
Oh, okay.
I mean, we only need two.
We're not going to do that.
three to get into zone should be fine i think i'd actually i
found it okay now i should start ripping the end i think
yeah yeah we're good okay they would just start the rotation
in let's go we're gonna rotate through the jurassic side
let's go through here yeah chargeable all right oh i follow
my hammer point one team died one team died oh don't forget
we already get a poison point just from being top 15.
yeah zone davis kill everyone okay don't forget If we're on
my Evac here, we're going to start right at the end.
Just continue my Evac.
We're going to get into Barometer front side if we can.
I'll go first and I'll just tell you guys where to land with
the ping.
It's okay, so my landing's awful and I'll just tell you guys
where to go.
Do we want to try and get that?
What, the Evo cache?
Yeah.
We probably should.
What?
You good?
Hello?
I'm okay.
I ran into a tree.
Okay.
Do I get the tactical cooldown or the ultimate cooldown?
That's up to you.
I mean, I would probably say...
say tactical cool down personally but it's up to you all
right i got the tactical cool down yeah just i don't think
we're going to use the ulti how much here all right okay i
got my ulti here too we can just keep bumping in i want to i
guarantee those two buildings are going to be taken here i
would want to get there but i think both are going to be
taken for sure is anyone top barometer no i don't think
anyone alluded they just they just took barometer right now
they missed the top wait you want to put your evac down too
can you come here put your evac down yep oh they just took
it from us from right next to me you're good though there's
no one in this left side building either we can land on the
left side building okay guys all right we're gonna go for
this we're gonna land for this left building okay guys and
we're gonna start immediately lead the way cat yeah yeah got
you got you yeah lead the way there's no one on the height
so we should be free let's just make sure that we're free
let's see okay we're good there's no way they hit those
right we're good yeah no one in here we're good to go yeah
we live here now i can't but don't put gen down yet because
there's no one across when i scan i'm like we're gonna go
there there's no one one there.
I think we should take the, eh, no, let's just stay here.
Stay.
You can start setting up 10, but we're good to go.
Let's go, baby.
Look at us.
We just gotta make sure we live.
Jen down here.
Jen down could be like up on stairs, right?
Like here could be over.
I don't know.
You can put it anywhere you want.
Honestly, there's nothing that's really safe.
I'm gonna look west side.
I'm looking at west side.
Okay.
Yeah, do your thing.
We should be fine.
I don't think a lot of teams are going to rotate.
They're not like a team up top here.
Yeah, they're going to be top barometer.
right yeah they're up here oh what the fuck you can see me
from here that's not fair we are we have a lot of Watson Jen
so we should be like we should be fine on the passive
feeling to watch this towards our passive feeling right
tempo I swear it might be to be honest but I feel like there
I feel like they're gonna play more aggressive because they
just know they're better than a lot of people here yeah I
mean one team's already gone so I'm pretty sure yeah dragon
also said hello coches if we need help so nice that's
actually huge for us yeah i want i want to go to the other
building but i feel like it might just pull to the nut sack
and i feel like i've always been better so they would just
stay here all right well we'll know it oh that has to be
davis oh that has to be davis one bloodhound just killed two
people two more teams guys let's go guys i need i need to
shoot someone is it three is it three games or four four
four four okay it's four rounds or like four wait or four
games per round oh okay games for round three rounds okay
four games is not too bad i thought would be like six games
no wait where is uh everyone i want to shoot someone uh no
one's rotating this down there is people above us if you
want to shoot them there's people uh on that side you want
to shoot that there's just no one here to shoot no one's
gonna rotate this this first round usually pointless to be
honest yeah i mean we can have oh does that mean i can like
fix frames right now?
No, of course.
Yeah, you're so good.
If we die, it's not my fault.
I just said I could fix my.
Okay.
Should I look?
Tempo, were you on the roof?
No, you're in the hole.
Never mind.
Tempo, if you go on that goddamn roof, I swear.
You're literally Watson right now.
I forgot I did that with drops.
Okay.
How did you forget that?
Can I tap out?
Oh, yes.
You're so good.
Oh, yeah.
Even if he goes, hey, no one's going to send us.
No one's going to send us.
What do you mean?
What if it was Zone Davis?
Even if I get knocked, I don't think we get fought, to be
honest.
Oh, someone's fighting somewhere.
I can't see because...
All right, I'm going to fucking double-check my monitor just
to be sure.
Oh, my God.
How do I tap to my...
You guys, I need to figure out how to get my...
Oh, my God.
We've almost dead.
Wait, what?
No, we're good.
Wait, why are you sitting on a roof?
Oh.
I'm not.
I was first floor.
Okay, no, I'm on 280 hertz.
My eyes might...
just be tired.
Are you fucking kidding me?
My eyes are seeing 100 FPS.
There is no fucking way.
I still have eye boogers.
My eyes will just be tired.
It's okay.
I'm on 200 frames.
It's one of the craziest.
Sorry, my 200.
I wonder 80 hertz is so many fucking frames.
You thought you were on a hundred?
My eyes just haven't booted up yet.
It's okay now.
eye bookers are covering everything oh you 98 guys i'm
hungry
the poor girl is ep and hungry that is why where where where
where where he wants to know where you got shot at like of
course uh i die i got shot from like oh my god he knows
where he got shot Yeah.
You guys are giving the purple.
I'm just saying.
The hell no.
They would need so much damage to get purple.
It's insane.
I would just keep putting your gen downs too on cooldown
too, Tempo V.
Adam.
Well, fuck, I'm using charge rifle because I'm in the lobby.
No, Tempo.
No, other people also use this charge rifle.
Yeah, I love you so much, but that's definitely not the
case.
No one uses charge rifle.
It's not just you.
I'm going to use these cells because I want to get this
pack.
Wait, someone's landing.
Yeah, just hold strong.
They're going to another building.
We're going to the other building.
Yeah.
I kind of want to get this pack, bro.
Am I trolling?
If I do that, I think I probably am trolling.
We're in this building.
Yo, stay still so I can charge my body.
No, should I risk it for this pack?
You maybe die or no?
Um, what pack?
Right here.
A care package.
No, because the team above is going to fucking kill you.
I can smoke.
Go ahead.
Yeah, yeah.
I want to smoke up top for me.
Oh, okay.
I'll smoke up top too.
I smoked it.
I'm going.
I'm not one guy.
Actually, wait, wait, wait.
I need to wait for your next smoke.
I forgot to drop my weapon.
Oh my god!
My next smoke is gonna be like in 19 seconds!
No one's gonna get it anyway, bro.
They're baby dog bitches.
They're good.
Yeah, but now you have to wait for my next two smokes.
That's fine.
We're gonna smoke double height.
Smoke double height.
Okay.
All right.
You gotta have to bet on the fact that I'll, um, if I hit it
or not.
You'll miss one.
Yeah, you're gonna miss one.
Oh, they smoked it.
They got a fucking Kramer.
Oh, I told you.
And they got a Kramer.
No!
How are you not you you were you were fucking you're not
locked in you're not I did my smokes.
I did my smokes man I Fuck fuck fuck fuck.
How are you not locked in bro?
Got him guys.
Just my apologies.
My apologies.
I had bunked him only one only 10 more shots and then I have
all right this guy has a creeper now so like just be We got
knocked here.
It's actually bad.
Oh, that sound pull by the way pulls back to barometer so
you got bamboos a little bit.
a tad bit bamboozled all right there's no one in this house
though we could just which house this house but what if it
pulls back yeah i don't know they would just stay with that
sound show it goes we always make rotates to be underneath
uh middle of barometer if we need to team nine yeah that's
right yeah somebody got eliminated by the ring yeah
motherfuckers yeah one more squad and we're top 10 we could
just if we get top 10 consistently every game yeah there's
no way
there's new placements I love guys this is the I love ALG so
much it's so easy but that means like round two and three
like people actually it's gonna be a full lobby right
because like they made it to the full lobby I hope like I
hope like our lobby is filled with like us by the way i
don't know guys huh i hope like our lobby first if we make
it the second round is filled with like teenagers so like
their parents would be like we'll be like get off the pc oh
yeah just kick him out yeah yeah yeah like mom i'm in a
tournament like it doesn't matter you gotta you gotta go
yeah you gotta get the off it's my turn on the pc you got
calculus homework yeah you got homework to do fucking nerd
it's past your bedtime yeah tempo take my armor and
passively charge this up please can you do that actually no
right can you do that anymore the evo charters no you can't
cringe dude cringe cringe cringe oh wait should i throw
another one down uh yeah why not right now we wait until the
next until the zone pops yeah we're just on pops it does on
pops team going underneath bridge by the way okay that's an
ass team that is probably zone davis no it's a blue armor
there's no headstone davis yeah there's no way
i almost pegged him in the head your big ass is in my way
sorry i got that a lot actually damn i didn't think all
right we should take we should take bottom of middle
barometer right now i'm gonna scan what's that i'm gonna
scan make sure we can go all right i gotta grab there's no
first floor you guys ready can you smoke height we going
down below yep all right go go go that was smoked nice good
double smoke skis a double smoke but still got hit i might
be dead okay how are you getting hit that is incredibly oh
good i'm holding for you you're chilling yeah i'm fine i'm
fine i'll be here i have no idea where it got shot i was too
scared i didn't want to look at it fence up everywhere bro
and gen everywhere well gen one place but you know what i
mean i'll lock this door up just in case somebody shows up
here that's push up here just until until the fences show up
yeah and get some fences in the zipline room to tempo if you
can so they can't jump down you're good that buddy take your
time you're vibing the team's gonna be on bridge bridge is
still still in too 10 squads i'm trying to think what we're
gonna do after this is that a care pack what's okay we got
top 10 it's fine honestly we're doing pretty good yeah we're
doing pretty well i would love to hit a shot right now and
then maybe get a kill but you know Do we really need a kill
though?
We need to stay alive.
Bloodhound 5206 and the 9304.
Oh, triple red school.
I'm fighting in the back.
We know that.
That's great.
They ran away from us.
It's great.
It's huge trust.
The one's going to keep pulling back then.
That's Davis right there.
Well, I see the most risky play you guys are seeing.
It's made a fucking battery in this crafter.
That's what I'm talking about, baby.
Let's go.
Damn.
You're gaming right now.
Oh, yeah.
Oh my god.
Non squads.
Let's go.
Let's go guys.
Oh my god.
Most fucking.
I'm looking.
I hate around ever.
What are they doing?
Oh my god.
That was a horrible play.
Glad we're not those guys.
Wait, what the fuck?
Who are these bloodhounds?
I never seen those names before.
No, thank god those guys fucking.
I look out this door.
See if I can shoot anyone.
I'm not gonna fucking risk anything right now.
No, you're good.
I'm gonna let it keep rolling forward and just see if I get
any KP for us.
Any points.
There's a team over here right here See anybody who's
rotating in from behind?
Yeah, we're good right now.
Wait, there's a- There's a team right behind us!
They're not in my door!
Yeah, they're on my door.
Yeah, yeah, they are.
They're going through the house.
They wanna fight us right now?
I don't know.
They're like running back and forth.
Like, really dumbfights, to be honest.
There's, like, a guy on the stairs here and the guy to our
right.
I'm trying to look.
I'm just scanning.
A whole three-man.
Yeah, I'm sure.
They're getting away from you.
Hopefully men have a witness play.
Look at this way.
South East.
The tree man.
Yeah, you have a grenade here.
I'm gonna get a grenade Those guys out.
Yeah, I do yeah.
Yeah, you throw 100% I'm already done.
I've already burned one of them I'm burning someone on
purple.
Yeah.
I'm burning people.
Oh, there goes the other door Second, but it's so weird.
What are they doing?
Yeah, one is not the same as their They're coming out.
I'm gonna ult you.
Yeah, we're in a third party though.
So dumb I was swankled one 137 I'm looking for you.
I'm covering you coming here.
Yeah, you're good.
Keep covering.
We're gonna have to walk out here soon Yeah.
I don't know what they're doing.
I don't know why they want to fight us.
I don't make any sense here.
This fight makes no sense.
Hold on.
I can now too.
I'm just fighting.
I'm batting.
They're dying.
They're not from a top now.
Okay.
That's good.
I'm batting.
How are the other guys in the house not shooting these kids?
What the fuck?
What's this green name?
Come over to me.
We're going to walk in.
We're going to have to walk forward here.
Stay healthy right now.
We're going to move forward here.
Hey, I'm staying healthy.
I have no ulti now.
This is so ass.
an ult you want me ult somewhere oh they ran already ran the
fucking way with their own here in the in the what are they
doing oh she won this you win this one okay yeah you're good
you're good you're good just look left to try to get your KB
just get your full wheel up nice to die or not his own these
guys are more yeah I'm gonna yeah yeah Red army crack I
corrected my crackton it's the last one if you get him yeah
yeah take that look that 100 you go really kill oh shit i
thought i was fused he's guys now move up to the left side
just keep playing left keep playing more left top but more
left your left you're good you're good nice guys good put
your gen down to the av one depo yeah jeff i'm gonna alt
left just cause i i know you know we behind us what the
There's a guy behind us.
You're good.
I just live.
Just live, tempo.
Did you live?
You lived!
Yes!
You're good.
Stay there.
Just stay there.
Don't move.
Top five, baby.
Top five.
Just stay there.
Don't look.
Don't look at them.
Don't even look.
Yeah, they won't see if we don't move.
I thought that works.
Yeah, yeah.
It's like the dinosaurs.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, And we got top four.
Let's go.
We got a few kills.
Nice job, guys.
Let's go.
We got the kills.
We got four kills.
That's right.
Suck a dick, whoever Bangor 2942 is.
Yeah, whoever you are.
Good plays, man.
That's, I mean, that's probably enough for us to call
already.
Yeah.
I think we're fine.
We can just chill now.
Yeah, we're good.
I'll play.
I'll play next game, man.
That's a nice point.
We're good.
That was awesome, bro.
Are you doing it?
Good job getting the KP.
We needed that pretty much.
Yeah, we got four KP guys and four plays.
No, we're just no way any team's gonna chase up to us now.
Oh my god, this is the creeper team.
Let's do it.
That could have been us way good.
That bloodhound holding that creeper.
That could have been...
What a fuck did that team push us just to get...
I mean, I'm gonna lie.
I re-peaked without scanning and there are just three men
sitting in the back.
And they're in a bin.
But they have like purple and reds too.
So it's like they could fight, obviously.
Oh, they could.
He's like.
I'm hungry.
You are 20 something years old.
You are not hungry.
You're hungry.
I'm hungry.
Oh, man.
I'm not gonna lie.
We were done a better job with the Kramer here for sure.
Yeah, that could have been you.
Yeah, I mean, I would have hit at least at least one more
shot than this guy.
Oh, oh, maybe it was like a blessing because then you
wouldn't whiff in front of everybody, you know?
Oh, my God, that's so true.
I just three men swung a team.
I just swung a three man into a bin, though, and died for
it.
That's pretty embarrassing as well.
But it's good that you died so you could IGL us better.
You're so right.
Yeah, I feel like my comms really just improved there,
actually, so much.
Yeah, yeah.
The moment you died, your comms were...
got your igl and just got so much better your show right
your show right bro what the fuck is going on what is this
fight what is this fight i was watching okay there we go all
right nice guys let's go good dude we got that that's all
right we did it we did it automatic automatic round clutch
probably that's a round qualification right there well okay
how many points is that 9 or wait 12 9 9 yeah wait do we die
fourth we die fourth we're fourth place yeah yeah yeah
that's nine that's crap that's definitely that's a lot of
points right there top 10 is top 10 you're gonna need 15.
oh okay we just need four uh six more points and we're in
okay team 11 oh team 11 is it wait that's not even zone
davis who the fuck is team 11.
they got 12 kills hey why Why did Zone Davis die?
Zone Davis died ninth!
They only got three kills!
Wait, don't tell me we're getting a new code every time!
Oh, uh, I don't know.
I'm refreshing the page.
Oh my god, Bro, Zone Davis fell off, man.
They let this random Team 11 get more kills.
Guys, we're in fourth place with nine points!
Oh my, look at us!
I guess we are getting a new code.
I don't...
I guess everybody's fucking leaving.
All right.
Um...
code every game this and then go to tournament okay yeah i
mean so this is like 10 minutes later okay yeah we're still
waiting for the code okay so my chat this 10 minutes there
but house of volume we already got through it's already 42
minutes deep but like house of volume guys yeah yeah was
that like really bad for y'all or like how many viewers did
we drop in the last 25 minutes guys can anyone let me know
guys know like has the volume been okay after 42 minutes
just has not been there at all just like oh i got food oh
food i got food because my mom gave me my food food i'm no
longer hungry i'm still epee though you're hungry epee and
your mom gave you food i'm like a tomagachi i've never been
so jealous ever in my life
Tamma, put that new code in when you can.
Yeah, I'm going to drink my soup.
I am also making food.
Right now?
How are you doing that?
You need a toilet break, too.
What?
You got a wireless headset?
I have a, I have a, I have a, fuck, what do you call it?
I have a camera on top of my stove.
So I can see the, I can see my stove from my, from my room.
so I know when my food is cooking and then I can just run
over you're run over it's the most modest tempo shit I've
never heard of my life do you have like a dog camera on your
stove do you have a dog camera on your stove wait to look
over what's going on on your stove when you're an AFK like a
baby that's fucking awesome I gotta see if my water's
boiling and now I can run over like a baby monitor your
kitchen's your fucking baby you have a baby monitor minus
tempo shit i've ever seen all right the codes in the lobby
we're ready for round two let's go yeah yeah well
technically round one but yeah yeah round two round one i
was just doing the right game we're doing it guys we're
doing it now if you really want to get crazy here if we
really get like a good game here i'm all i'm saying is we
can just have a fun time for the last two games i'm not
against it it would be pretty if we had a fun time and then
somehow that would be so great even though we thought we
crawled yeah that would definitely okay maybe like we should
have our fun times at the last game not the third game as
well because you know jordan we're in fourth place yeah
bitch sorry yeah is that really something to flex about when
there's only 15 teams
i'm pretty sure jordan could get top four by himself
you wouldn't even need two more players like he's good you
know what i mean uh watching blood bang and then probably
plastic blood bang on the other map yeah thanks for the raid
thanks for the ray bro he can can jordan coach us i'm not a
beginner streamer can jordan like coach us live yeah testing
in a 15 team lobby is crazy someone definitely could yeah i
saw some contesting yeah you'll visualize easy work
i wish they had that like one the new thing they're gonna do
for split two for i think so yeah yeah yeah someone someone
definitely he doesn't make the next round that's a w for
like actual two people that put north pad or something and
then two people that put like
thing and everyone's just landing on each other and i said
okay i will not tell anyone that they are landing on each
other wait we shouldn't say what our pois are or they'll
start landing on us we should type it out like all the pros
they see that we're already qualified so they're scared if
they land on us we have nothing to lose anyway we gotta we
gotta stop saying we haven't we haven't guaranteed what do
you mean we can literally die last every time like hey we
still get one point that doesn't mean that doesn't make 15.
that's that brings us to That brings us to 12.
Yeah, that's three points short from qualifying.
So let's go kill a team.
And then we're solid.
All right, let me...
I mean, I didn't expect a full three man in a bin, bro.
What?
No, this guy said, why did you swing solo?
I had to kill you.
I said, I didn't expect a full three man in a bin.
Wait, we're all three just hiding in a bin.
In a bin.
What the fuck?
I mean, that was hilarious.
wait did you did you see that uh did you see that uh i don't
i don't know if it was a glitch or if it was a hack i saw i
saw a tick tock or if there's something on twitter where it
was like uh someone opened up a bin and three people
actually popped out of the bin they like glitched themselves
in in behind a pill and then someone opened the pill and
just three people popped up and then he died that is
actually unreal that is fucked up This is the question I'm
asking everyone in today.
I'm asking everyone and every lover in today, this exact
question.
Like chicken parm or meatball marinara subs more?
Every TFT game I play, that's the first thing I say in the
chat and I don't say anything else.
Wait.
I judge a human based off this answer, to be honest.
Yeah, I do.
What if I don't like either?
It depends on the quality of the sub, man.
If the bread's not good, I need my chicken.
I mean, dude, it's just chicken color.
It's just so much better than me blowing air or something
funny.
I think like chicken and brie is much better.
Chicken and brie with cranberry.
Ooh, that's a very fancy taste from you.
I respect that.
Oh, wait, I see my stream now.
You're a woman of class, huh?
You can't afford this.
You can't afford my brie, my puppy.
You can't afford this sandwich.
Oh.
said we can't afford this all right guys game just ended on
our 10-minute delay all right yeah my whole chat saying
let's go tempo tempo goat and when i died they died my whole
chad just said actually washed foot feeding washed so i tell
you the top one is the fucking goat when your chat starts
cheering for tempo you know something's wrong you know you
did something
I'm real, bro.
Holy shit.
Hello.
Whoa.
You just want to straight answer more on me.
I kind of like that.
Wait.
One minute.
Oh, do I type no.
No.
No, it's crazy.
No is crazy.
I respect it though.
But they stopped.
for me, am I important enough that they'll stop for me?
Hell no.
It's like match starting.
Not a fucking chance.
I think we fixed the mic issue.
Okay, wait.
So am I playing the same thing?
I think so.
Yeah, I'm down for that one.
I can still eat then.
I don't have to pick anything.
No, you're good.
You're good.
Eat up.
You're chilling.
I mean, if your eyes are still not seeing 200 ADFPS.
I need you actually maybe to get on mic.
48 fucking milligrams of caffeine right now 180 milligrams
of caffeine oh that's not me that's not what i'm playing i'm
playing this i will be honest with you guys i'm not a great
butt on here as you can tell so like i'm gonna try my best
you know wait wait did we people scan uh no not once oh i
mean we didn't have anyone anywhere that we could do that
okay yeah yeah we had to go all the way to bean but i think
that was a dumb road to do that scanning got us into the
building your fucking control see my charge rifle number 74.
nice good for you man how many ranked worldwide and kills
right now no can't you look at that what's your rank
worldwide and kills for charge level how do you look at that
i think you can amen tracker yeah oh okay actually i was
number one and i was number one in uh re45 kills for like i
was number one mirage in canada we know we know
I just need to remind you guys it's very it's a very
prestigious you don't never forget it's a very prestigious
title Julie and Julie guys we're two for two on beacons man
we're rich Oh my god, why can't we have this in twitch
rivals that was like actual money We don't win jack shit.
We don't win money from this Yeah, but then we but we also
just if we don't get 14 pros trying to run us down We're
just fish food bro.
The bottom of the food chain in Twitch Rivals.
It was your Twitch Rivals too.
I can't believe.
That's so sad.
That's so fucked up.
They did that to your own headline event.
I love it.
You love that for us though.
It makes my better storyline.
You know, when I went outside after we lost, like horribly,
and we got 19th, we got 20th.
I thought he was going to be, like, laughing about it and
stuff like that, but I called him, like, a loser and shit.
I went out there and he was molding.
Because we got Oh, man, he was so...
No, you just had a hard one.
He was like, that was one of the worst events we're playing.
He should have casted.
It was a casted.
I'm not so funny because I was like, ah, you're shugged,
bro.
Good shit.
I thought he was like, laughing with me.
And I was just like, nope.
Man, this is just one's dad, man.
To be fair, it's worse because he was first picked, too.
Well, it's worse, but dude, his teammate, which I don't know
how this happened, but his teammate never played the game
before.
What?
Wait, the his third?
Yeah, I don't know.
How did you go?
Why?
I have no idea.
That's why I was like super confused.
I mean, I had to talk like, I don't mind me.
Why did Reptar pick him?
Why?
He was the last pick.
No, he was last pick.
Oh, he was the last pick.
I mean, that's the guy.
That's what it is, but I just didn't, I don't know how that
works, to be honest.
All right.
Wait, what?
Did you hit the circle yet?
I didn't.
His beacons can't what he can.
I'm going to go over now.
Yeah, you're going to do a thing, bro.
Is anyone going to grab the cash?
I'll go grab it, actually.
Yeah, if you can, that'd be great.
I'm going to run this.
our loading patterns are so fun guys my eyes are slowly
seeing more frames now my eyes turned on yeah i start
turning on oh good for us guys okay oh she no take cape oh
that's weird that guy told me have you ever seen those
cenote cave zones then we just go here that guy write the
script or what hacker man's actually though oh my god bro my
stick truth on the system there's a was always really quiet
no no no i i uh i moved my mic into my mouth oh that's good
okay good eat that mic yeah eat it up baby oh yeah and then
video then videos record it and then privately send it to
like wigs private channels you know like wigs tier three
mods yeah i mean tier three subs yeah yeah you know the mod
guys i don't have a charge rifle that's that sucks dude damn
um All right, any Evag towers?
Probably not, right?
No, I only have a Rez.
I've got Rez.
I have Evag.
You have one Evag tower?
Okay, we don't want to definitely use it yet.
It'll be tough.
All right, are you guys ready to rotate in?
Yep.
Yes.
I'm ready.
I'm ready, too.
I think we'd hit this cannon.
You guys want to risk it for the biscuit?
Yeah, let's do it.
Let's just hope Team 11 isn't there.
Team 11 is a real threat now.
They're the ones that got like 12 kills.
Where Team 11 was landing.
Let me go first, and I want you guys to know what's
happening.
All right.
you okay you guys could definitely take it you're good okay
there's no one even close it would be so funny if they're
just hiding like behind that rock i can't lie i'll be a
great really oh just drove by us with a china it's all good
it's all good they won't they'll ignore us they got out oh i
guess they won't ignore it they're walking up we're good
we're good we're good they're walking up we're chilling let
them walk up and actually see where they go they're gonna
have to they're gonna get the package and then they're gonna
probably just rotate into cenote yeah we're i see them they
ran away behind us just in case oh i shouldn't shoot them um
no you could shoot them for sure i'm gonna shoot them i want
to put up maybe an evite tower down here just get into
cenote you want to point down yeah put right here buddy just
get in we're gonna try to just fly into this way right we're
gonna just take a building in there and see how it goes
we'll get richard in from there okay just follow my path
thing okay we're gonna go left Actually, follow my prophet,
guys.
Follow me!
I'm not going to hit a tree this time.
Follow me to your imminent death.
Let's go, guys.
We're going to land right on this one.
And we're going to keep on walking in.
Yay.
Just keep swimming.
I'm going to look at my scans.
We are.
We're always doing so good, guys.
I believe in us.
If we do so well in this game and get, like, top three, then
we can fuck around.
Oh, yeah.
Now we can easily fuck around.
All right.
gonna take this building for them.
We should like contest a team.
I'm sure.
We should do it for Joan Davis.
Okay, not Joan Davis.
We should grief him.
I mean, he's gonna qualify anyway, so we might as well grief
him.
He definitely qualifies in no matter what.
A whole team across this building.
Okay, watch out.
Whole team staring at my door from across.
Team on this building, too.
West side.
White armor.
Get shit on, kid.
There's a team on the West side, too.
These scads are.
Yeah.
We're gonna be just full three men in the airs the whole
time we're gonna get spotting zone actually keep pulling
back that'd be a pretty crazy boba does it peek me peek me
peek me yeah peek her peek her guys peek her man i want to
show my god i'm zero damage it's like as you're eating you
know i can eat actually i'm gonna i don't know you can take
damage why didn't you push me while i'm eating they're gonna
find out 10 minutes later and i'll be done eating all right
i don't know i feel like you're a very slow eater am i right
okay maybe all right yeah i feel like you definitely are i
get the vibe from you that you take like 45 bites and you're
like okay it's because like i watch a show while i eat i
love it i mean it's a healthy thing to do adjusting slow
yeah that's true because like you can it meets you like eat
less i did math we have 12 things 12 what i'm like the
opposite literally destroy food like it's not healthy for
your stomach if you eat too fast it's really unhealthy
actually i said that yeah that's why you disappeared last
like two days ago no i fell i fucking knocked out for like
eight hours i was dead i didn't know you could shoot to this
this is crazy that's what i'm looking oh okay well i shot
him or anyone he already knows i shot him with 121 let him
know we're here yeah
I honestly, guys, this is pretty fun, dude.
We had a way to spend six more hours with all of you.
Guys, peeks into crack so I can shoot you.
Yeah, a lot more to go.
Once the games get harder, it'll actually be like way less,
way more fun, to be honest.
It's kind of easy games are a little bit boring, a little
bit more boring.
I think it says there's not a lot of teams, so you don't see
a lot of fights going.
Yeah, and also like, you know, you know, you're good,
probably no matter what the fuck you do, unless you're like
really, really struggling at the game.
Yeah.
You can shoot through that crack, by the way.
You can, yeah.
I had someone for like 130.
It was crazy.
I wish we could still farm armors for each other.
Now we actually have to contribute.
And that's another game more boring too, like rotating this
out and you just can't farm shit anymore.
It takes so much damage to do so.
Now I can't coast.
Now I actually have to farm with you guys.
Yeah, you need to also run a sniper.
Now we have to run triple sniper.
No, I don't think we should do that ever.
I have a purple R9.
I have an R9's fucking ass.
I don't even know if it's going to be good for us.
I have a blue R9.
I mean, I just have a...
I rather just use a bolt at that point.
I see someone's gun.
Should have honestly.
Nope, I can't shoot a gun.
Shoot his gun, bro.
Take the fucking barrel off, kid.
Mad, Maggie!
Man!
Okay, I kind of like that, though.
That's on Davis.
They're fucking around now.
Yeah, he might be a...
Yeah, he's number one, right?
He's number one.
Keep a lookout to see where number one dies.
Yeah.
All right.
I'm done eating.
I'm not hungry anymore.
Let's go.
I'm just EP.
You're still EP though?
Go take a nap.
Five minute nap.
Yeah, I'm going to be right back at it.
I'm going to go sleep.
Just tell me how we do.
Take your power naps, bro.
You put the fucking feet up and then you lay on the floor.
It's actually so good for you.
Tembo takes power naps for sure.
Oh, shit.
Look our door.
Piece of shit, man.
So Tembo, I don't really know when Tembo.
How many hours of sleep do you get daily?
Oh my god.
He knows.
I don't know.
Sometimes I fall asleep on my desk for 20 minutes at a time.
Bro, what?
Do you not take actual sleeps?
Like...
I don't think so.
Oh, I slept yesterday.
Team 11 dead.
Oh, Team 11 dead.
Oh, that's the team that ran over everyone.
That's the team that fucking fights everybody.
Maybe they WK Davis.
Let's go.
see there's put him down or what that's not good for us
though i want to see davis out respectfully all right all
right uh doesn't qualify yeah he's just a threat you know i
just that would be so funny that's why we contest that's why
we contest him contest them oh who's who's what the what
we're just trying to make sure they look at them yeah i
literally don't know where people are uh also tumma make
sure you just keep putting your uh gen down on uh on
cooldown so we're not leaving anytime soon yeah we are
living here now for a little bit at least yeah for sure
there's like a team oh i see a team if you guys want easy
shots here yeah i was sure okay yeah i'm trying to shoot
this team no but i can't see them oh no yeah he's just he's
running back and forth wait they're all the way up up here
what the is that oh he's on this rock all the way up here
yeah that's what i'll see so high why is that allowed i
think really bad zone i can't lie well i have a thingamajig
uh oh yeah i think there's been a few bomb pulling bro evac
uh yeah yeah i know i'm gonna be gonna take any back oh my
god what i just came with oh ow ow geez oh geez dudes what's
going on that's not a person that's a really oh yeah suck it
be it team nine dead nice guys nine nice two more teams two
more teams i headshot at him he got scared and ran away Bro,
this guy's the best player in the world or what?
Oh yeah, you can't outsnipe the sniper master.
He's gonna break, he's gonna break your fucking gen.
That's a really good view.
I can't lie.
How's it not?
He knows the angles.
Our gen still has a little bit of HP left.
Yeah, how is that even possible?
I don't know, it's been hit for a while.
Yeah, what the fuck, man?
I know you do fucking stuff, bro.
The fuck?
Wait, they smoked us.
I mean, if they push us the morons up, they'll do that.
so funny watching a team down here i mean we've been able to
kill him in two times i'm kind of down for it they're funny
across no just preparing shots i'm just gonna troll them i
mean yeah why not fuck it i'll troll this one team and just
smoke them every time just block their one ls oh wait you
can't even you can't even get damage for that anymore what
the smoking yeah now yeah is that crazy Wait, I think they
left the house.
Wait, I don't know, actually.
No, they smoked me, never mind.
He smoked me.
He's still here.
Yeah, they are still there.
Yeah, well, team's back here.
I mean, taking the top, so like, if we need to, we can go
across the top left side.
Team Southwest.
Take the top house.
Watch out, Wig.
The guy behind you.
Whoa!
It's our coach.
Our coach came into my room.
Wait, can he coach us too?
Yeah.
Do we just have the entire TSM coach us?
yes they're all watching from behind the screen we need that
we need that we need that we need every help we can get yeah
tell him to hit up destroyer real quick tell him to reach
out of destroyer give it to wig he's too likable for people
to hate him for using hello hello i'm trying to try to start
aimbotting a whole 360 spray people just be like oh silly
wig that's
We're still a little guy.
Oh my god, look at him.
Alright, come on, give us the phone.
Nope.
Okay, this is the zone.
What the fuck is this zone?
Bro, what?
We need to take the height of this building, to be honest.
We need to.
Is there anything, any rocks that we can play out here?
I don't know, bro.
Do we just, I'm gonna be honest, guys.
I don't think we can survive this in any way.
Do we go to the back of this house and just rip an evac
tower and say, fuck with it, what happens?
Or is that what happened?
We don't have an evac tower.
Evac tower next year.
Yeah we don't have it.
We just have Resbeacon.
We're so dead guys.
I'm gonna put Res Beacon Out.
Wait, wait wait.
Having a Resbeacon is good.
We can go into the water, put two Resbeacon's down and hide
behind it.
Wait, these Sony's...
What am I watching?
All right, we need to get the height of this building.
Can you smoke these windows, Doki?
Yeah.
Right, we need to climb this and get up in the building.
Oh that was awful smoke.
It's okay.
We got this.
That was a great smoke.
Yeah, yeah.
We're gonna climb this, just get up.
Just take the heights we can actually play maybe a little we
can see what's going on.
Yeah, yeah, cuz like they're fighting down here It was a
great smoke cuz we lived I cracked you over here.
I might knock one I'm looking for you.
There's someone here with us.
Yeah, I just I'm just trying to look to see what the fuck's
going on Where we get we can we can't play over here.
They're fighting.
They're over here.
Oh, there's nothing.
I got killed got killed All right guys, okay, wait, you guys
keep doing that.
I'm gonna look to see what we can play
gen uh oh i'm definitely not safe here i'm safe here too
definitely not safe here either we're gonna do what we're
gonna do you guys listen to me yeah yeah we're gonna jump
off and go left side over this rock i'm blind there's a team
right here you're listening okay we're gonna go whenever all
right we're gonna have to smoke our back when we jump off
the height though because this team's gonna shoot us okay
we're gonna we're gonna we're gonna swing left we're gonna
swing that we're gonna jump down and then you smoke our
middle here to cross over the rock okay here we're There's a
smoke middle when we cross the road.
Okay, okay, yeah, right.
Full heal first.
Full heal before we do this.
Y'all can't help.
I had to smoke this now.
Yeah, you're good, you're good.
I'm watching the team over here.
Yeah, you're bowing.
I'm okay now.
I can go.
Okay, okay, ready we're gonna do it now.
We're going to cross now.
Go, go.
Jump off, slide left side.
A ton of meat, a ton of meat.
We're gonna go to this rock.
Look at that smoke!
We're good.
Nice.
Good fucking smokes.
We're good.
We literally vibe out here.
Just shoot behind us just.
Just focus your back guy right here.
Yeah, yeah.
over here yeah yeah i can steal this to kill nope i can't
fucking i missed every shot okay we're good we're good oh
yeah shoot this kid shoot this kid bang all this bang all
this we have it okay i'm begging yeah and grenade spam if
you have two i only have one grenade left uh i have three
out of three i could drop you one nice i always i fucked it
up too we're good yeah dropped uh dropped a name for you i
didn't i didn't flesh somebody's flesh over there i should
we might want to wipe this to be honest can you move up a
little bit on this or no Can you smoke our mid or now?
Oh, we can't.
We can't.
I think we just let them.
Yeah, but they're gonna angle us out probably.
Hi, Arc.
I hit one.
Hey, you guys did that.
You guys did that.
You guys said that.
You're good.
I'm waiting for a scan to get on.
Told me a duo.
Can you guys come over here and wipe this with me?
We're gonna push them and wipe this.
Okay, okay, I'm gonna call.
Wait.
No, no, no.
They cornered away.
They cornered.
We're good.
Back up.
Bro, we're just dead.
There's actually nothing to do with this zone.
What the fuck is the zone?
I mean, we actually have nothing to do.
This is crazy.
I'm literally going to try to run this zone and bring it in.
We can just mile run.
Let's just let them kill each other first.
Yeah, we just wait for more people to kill each other, and
we make that run at the same time.
Yeah, I can try to smoke them from here.
Right here, right here.
Yeah, I'm going to move right to the middle.
You guys stay there.
I'm just going to move right over here.
Wait, wait, wait.
He portaled back to here.
Oh, he did.
What a fucking moron.
All right, we're gonna move.
Let's move up.
Oh, look up front if we can donkey trying to.
Oh, I hate him 70 red Nice good smokes.
I'm gonna try to literally just put a fucking mobi res down
and sit behind it What is that?
Wink shield, Wink shield, Wink shield
Bro that is so not red.
What is that?
Wait, wait, wait, we got we got our three points.
We're at 15 now That is the dumbest fucking shit I've ever
seen in my life.
I gotta kill for us too.
Bro, what is the zone?
Bro, that might be one of the worst.
There's nothing you could do there.
No matter what, unless we're a Newcastle team, we're
literally dead.
Bro, that is fucking crazy.
That was the craziest zone pull ever.
I'm not kidding.
That might be the worst zone I've seen ever in ALGS.
I've never seen that zone before in my life.
Put that in the ALGS Discord so we can get them to remove
it.
That guy in our lobby is hacking.
He literally said, have you ever seen those sounds?
And it just happened.
Wow.
Destroyer's in your chat.
He's in your chat.
Bro.
What's his name?
Let's ask him.
Ask him what the next zone is.
Yeah.
Hey, bro.
You got a little inside on with the next zone.
Yeah.
You know what the next zone is, bro?
Come on.
Give us a little.
that ring was fun
that's actually just the dumbest thing i've ever seen my
life i can't believe that was i can't believe that was real
that was a crazy i want to see my chat's reaction to that
bro it'd be like what the is that what the actual fuck is
that it's okay it's okay no way it could happen again no way
we're gonna get a really good zone this game i got a kill i
got a kill three and then donkeys kill oh so four points
yeah we need one more point and we fucking no we need two
more points and then we qualify well no we get two more
points just because there's only 15 teams in the lobby now
no that's one point that's one point that's one point well i
mean one point for next game and then one point for last
game true yeah so we can no no we we fuck around the last
game what if like all right yeah last game we still need
something here last game are we connecting davis we're still
down yeah we are we are in sixth place we're in sixth place
almost waiting for oh no it doesn't feel that safe though
for six plays yeah it doesn't it doesn't feel safe it's very
it feels very not safe i mean it feels like pretty scary we
always we just got the words down we need we need zone davis
and team 11 to just roll everyone no bro we just we're going
to wait i'm caustic now oh yeah zone davis and team 11 if
you're watching the stream 10 minutes later kill every team
but our team agreed so then you can get content more from us
you can find us for content if we get the same game it came
zoom out simple let me know you put the code in yep so
geyser siphon and tree should all have someone okay and
harvester what's the code that's in that direction code just
came out let's see there we go okay guys i'm in i got in
before wig did i am hacker man i'm in i'm out all right i
mean we're locked to in now i'm like so locked in possible
world's edge is really easy right all i needed was what were
we were we uh where are we landing on world's edge stacks
stacks stacks still playing bang blood um i don't know i
really want to that i think it's a common cost yeah we
definitely want costa here for sure so what should we play
then fuck zone davis is going stacks okay wait wait who's
who's tart man no idea fissure launch site was anyone
countdown wait if he's going stacks oh he said siphon he
said siphon he said siphon he said siphon i mean
motherfucker zone davis banning you from pro league scrims
after you make it into pro league if you land on no we'll
prevent him from making into pro start burning that use that
to our advantage big dog honestly zone davis band from a lgs
tournament you'll never get into pro league if you kick us
out if you land on us yeah i'll also gatekeep i'll never
have your pov up it's it's not a threat it's a promise yeah
i don't i don't make threats i get even i'm i don't make
threats i'm realistic You know, I actually have to say I
admire how optimistic we were.
We're going to make it across that water.
Honestly, if they weren't focusing on us, we're good.
I think it's because someone shot, who shot at them?
Who the fuck shot at them?
Definitely not me.
No, that was me.
Yeah, I was going to say they didn't know we were shooting
at us first.
They were shooting at us.
No, I was literally watching.
They didn't know we were there until somebody shot at them.
I was like, what the fuck shot them?
They were not paying attention.
100% shot us.
I was like, oh, you want to play this game?
Okay, to be honest, that rock looked a lot closer than it
actually was, because it looked closer when we were at our
rock.
And then as I started running, I was like, it looks like
this rock keeps getting further away.
That's so true.
I was like, wait a minute, I'm running, but it's not getting
any closer.
I was confused.
And then I was like, I'm going to run back and then it
didn't work.
yeah all right so what come do you want to run mega lore
again i don't mind running whatever i can do whatever or
should we run yeah run bang and i'll run blood again fuck it
all right wait why were you hesitating then well because
like valve is just so good like that i don't know it's just
so tough we don't get evac towers that's why in wedge and
i'll go or i'm blood and you could go valc um yeah let's do
that yeah okay yeah people will think i'm you and it'll get
scared exactly yeah like oh controller run away yeah better
than me anyway yeah because obviously people put the
controller play on blood so they'll be like that has to be
wig like i don't want to get close to them i mean i can't
believe that was a real sound that was insane that was
actually i'm gonna be honest about that situation i'm
leaving you guys behind them 100 just send me in there oh
someone just said we should have grabbed a car and we could
have put the car in front of us as we run up yeah but that's
hindsight though like we're weird like he didn't we were not
close to any cars like where we i don't i don't know where
any of our cars were so far away oh it's time for candy i
got i got worm candy guys damn zone davis got the zones on
lock but damage nah oh wait that's his teammate yeah
Oh shit, Team 7-9 are duels!
Dan
is logging over.
Had to install Origin.
Come on, Dan.
What the fuck, Dan?
Poor Dan.
I can't believe how crazy that was.
I'm hungry again, bro.
You too.
You're hungry?
I mean, now I'm hungry, but not eating.
Call your mom to bring food over.
Yeah, I'll make her fly in from Florida.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm on the horrible.
My dad.
I'm on fucking.
It's fucking terrible.
It's being like, mom, bring me food.
When you move here, I'll be your in-house chef anyway.
So we're good.
Oh my God.
You're like his maid.
Oh, shit.
So about me moving to Texas.
Motherfuck.
You're not moving to Texas?
No, probably not.
Yo, taxes.
I know, bro.
But like Texas.
Yeah.
What's wrong with Texas?
this week no it's a great place and why don't you move there
yeah it was so great i might need roommates man i was gonna
say a very very uh very political joke i'm gonna never mind
we we know i'm not smart enough to debate this i know where
my intelligence stops and where it starts wait what do you
mean you might need roommates soon yeah what the fuck's that
mean tell me yeah what does that mean like like our we tsm's
not paying for the house anymore oh no so you guys are
broken firm that's crazy that's so crazy you guys heard it
here right here from my stream if any news article want to
quote quote it from dokeybird from the dokeybird stream
ready be ready to tag dokeybird yeah yeah make money and tsm
doesn't guys exclusive uh exclusive news drop from dokeybird
stream i think every esports org is just broken yeah that's
uh house isn't how house isn't being covered so everyone's
got to figure out what to do um which is everyone's
splitting up well evan and evan and jordan are gonna play uh
play from home so that they don't have to pay rent i mean
that's right but i don't want to go back to canada so hell
no yeah i didn't shoot them first i just saw my vaude i
don't think i think we got shot from the right side the
whole time not even the left left side shot left side shot
us and then i just shot us and then and then i just returned
fire and then i hit them for 70.
i thought the i thought you shot them first because they
weren't shooting yeah you know they they shot me and then i
was like oh you want to play this game and then and then we
died and then yeah and then they're like yes yeah yeah i
played bloodhound where's Where's Valc?
Where's Valc?
Top right.
Oh, God.
That was so scary.
I got the blood on lock.
Wait, who healed in the open?
My favorite is me, bro.
I was like one HP.
I was like, one HP.
I don't know about that.
Bro, trying to heal in the open.
That's my favorite one.
Chad just, like, sees that zone.
Like, bro, you could have made that if you just popped six
batteries to 360 times per tick, bro.
I heard about people who might go three asked for to make
that one.
1hp is a bloodhound crossing open water what the fuck you
want me to do
honestly we might be able to grab big mod too if no they're
seen there they called it what they called in the chat a
team really yeah the cut name's like simple or something
like that that's okay um all right i'm gonna i'm gonna go
land uh i'm gonna i'm gonna take like these buildings so i
can grab the beacon let's make sure just stick on me right
now just in case we
are you okay so that pink team is going mod why does it seem
like they're very short that pink team to our left is very
short they're going geyser i don't see anyone near us for
mod i don't either um if you guys want to go mod you want to
go to mod temple i can go i can go no no no i'm gonna i have
to go here because i need the beacon yeah i'll go mod and
just load it up you guys go over here if i get late landing
i'll just scream Yeah, I mean, oh, we cannot craft everyone.
It's going to be like, we can craft you.
And I was like, no, we cannot.
No, we cannot.
I guess we run as a deer.
No, we find there's no near.
I did find this though, first Ben.
Wait, I can't ping it yet.
I'm scanning the beacon.
It's okay.
It's going to be here, buddy.
He's going to cry.
No, he's going to cry.
Okay, I figured out where it is.
Here's a 6x2.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, it's down.
Okay, not great for us.
That's for sure.
If we landed sky...
Sky West, we would have been losing the fam here.
moving solid that's right we got about also make sure to
take your fucking take your goddamn eval towers please if i
can find eval towers i have 45 purple flatline purple this
is pretty fucking dog actually we can just we can just pick
up like a million uh evo harvesters on our way and just be
red when we go into zone that's true yeah except for on the
complete opposite side no that's probably the right call i'm
new ting i don't have a good gut i mean i've never nemesis
alternator but I prefer double R9 I feel rich I am scout
flatline I want to two times I'm gonna drop it over here uh
keeping it yeah I got you yeah all right I guess our nemesis
I guess I'll run it actually this is a little far I'll be
excel in my pocket too just in case we need it I have one as
well grab as many heals as possible since we don't have uh I
got I stick drift is crazy I didn't I didn't loot this if
you want to loot this uh tempo I didn't loot this building I
have a purple heavy mag for someone I'm not running one and
a purple energy mag for someone oh I need that oh yeah you
can take that oh another purple backpack over holy shit I'm
actually finding crazy loot over here we're so rich I can't
lie this big mod has a lot of stuff where you guys need
there's a vault tier two yeah is there an r9 in there yeah
there's a blue one it's pretty ass but like i don't even
know what i'm looting anymore definitely better than nothing
if you need an r9 definitely take it yeah i'm already
running a nemesis i don't think i'm gonna have another
enough oh there's another there's another uh actually i'm
gonna run you saw the heavy mag temple or no yeah yeah okay
i'm gonna run uh uh flatline then okay instead of a i'm
dropping a put for you kidded alternate stuff open yourself
yes okay i'm good all right i'm gonna about and start
walking forward to the uh paintball i grab that evac tower
i'm gonna grab that 2x and also that backpack i want to grab
that charge rifle that's over there and then go for it man
make sure to remember to we're driving part of zone and the
zone is coming in so don't forget that we have we cannot
craft like we can usually do just remember that yeah how
many miss can we stay in zone before we die five five and
three are automatically timed out yeah okay there's no way
we can fuck that up right yeah no shot guys no way right
guys another evac here okay i actually should take that for
sure how did i miss that i'm an idiot oh fuck it's pretty
bad thanks buddy i think it has to do a scan should i still
Where are we trying to run to?
Like, we should probably go through a side-by-side, yeah.
Yeah, we should grab something for...
We should grab the evos.
Yeah, for sure.
We should definitely pad their way to, like, get evo-cashed.
That one?
Yeah, 100%.
And they go through, like, the fragment side and do that as
well.
Like, Monument, right here, for sure.
Would it be funny if I alt it just to run faster?
It would...
I don't know.
Funny might not be the word, but...
I would giggle if you wanted me to, like, I would giggle for
sure.
and then there's just a team right here i would definitely
giggle oh balloon yeah we'll take this balloon and get in
we'll just get the eva tower or the evo cash holy there's
two bed kits here i'm gonna grab one i'll take that oh i
need a sniper oh wait do i hear is that are those shots or
is that just the evo harvester that's no it's the evo
harvester because i don't it's just shiny oh shiny all right
don't forget we're gonna go off this choke too i'm going up
i'm gonna fly up i'm coming with you it's okay don't think
i'm a controller player uh do i get odin's glare or raven's
blessing wig oh which ones which one's which i don't
remember what it is the raven's blesses the 25 alt when
activated yeah or double the duration of the attack i would
say the raven one just make sure you scan your raven to get
your ulti back faster okay so the hot and then honestly yeah
you could if you want to
naked all and so we can we could charge a Raven's want to
get this evo yeah I'm gonna go get it for us we're going
we're going to go this way we're gonna go through landslide
or actually nah fuck that we shouldn't go to landslide let's
go through the top side of Skyhook all right i think i think
it's gonna be we can do a ring scan too yeah yeah when you
guys are grabbing that then i uh yeah yeah do a ring scan
and there's there any beacons we hit yeah it's gonna top
grandmas after this and hit a beacon as well for you duggy
so we know which way to go if we want a path towards
countdown we want a path towards skylights to which ones
less congested there's only 15 teams though so uh two teams
die too two of them die oh 13.
yeah i realized Too dead.
Contesting when there's only 15 squads is really fucking
dumb.
I can't lie.
Yeah, I can't wait to do that for the look.
For the last game.
Yeah, it's so fucking dumb.
Anyway, you guys.
We're doing a good game here for the guys.
I also didn't ulted.
Oh, geez.
Start scanning stuff when we don't be seeing anything.
Did we grab that evil harvest already?
Oh, yeah, we did.
Yes.
Oh, so there's a team over here.
Okay.
It's okay.
People find out 10 minutes later.
True.
It's okay.
All right, bag trials, bro.
That is ass.
Wow.
We don't see anybody, by the way.
They're so cursed, bro.
Did we do the people skin?
No, we're gonna do that.
We're gonna do that.
We're gonna do that grandma's right now.
There's a glow gold light mag.
I'm good.
I better take that.
My mom's in chat laughing about how I said she's a horrible
cook.
Which is very, it's very true.
It's very true.
I'm waiting for you guys.
I'm worried that I'm going to get fucking run up on.
Yeah, you're good.
I'm coming to you.
You're showing.
Let me take our time.
I'm running.
All right.
I need, I have, I have a four and eight.
I'm coming.
Okay.
Let's see.
Let's see how congested everything is.
Let's see which way we should go.
Here we go.
If no one's on top of trials, we should just evac tower on
there and then I could just charge our three evac towers.
We might as well.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
All right.
Hope no one three, two, one's me.
Yeah.
I'm sitting right after you, so if you die, I die.
All right.
We're gonna go do this guy.
Jesus Christ.
We're going with his team right behind us.
That's one, two, three.
That's like four.
That's like four things.
They're probably gonna immediately just.
they're going to probably immediately do exactly what we did
so we're just going to keep moving forward they're going to
just follow us so wait what do we where are we trying to go
are we going straight to skylock we're going to go through
skylock and probably evac somewhere but like there's no one
for us to really go this zone's pretty ass we'll have to
fight our way top side over here oh wait we can grab this
thing too while we're here yeah we're gonna do another
evocash we're good how much does a cash give us again 300
300 i think yeah yeah yeah i'll be like i'll be 150 off yeah
yeah yeah we're all we all should be 150 off we're all 150.
yeah we're any other beacons we can hit when we're here yeah
there are we're gonna be able to hit more yeah yeah and then
that'll give us purple i can't library these zones have not
been kind of us at all what what is up with us playing and
having horrible zones it was it's just life at that point
that's right life for us i guess for us at that point uh if
you guys can find charge rifle stuff yeah i picked it three
times i don't know if you took it i just found a new scope
okay i mean Okay.
Log.
Ooh, that's another bat.
Someone take.
I'll take it.
I have six or I am good.
I dropped a med kit.
I mean, let's just go.
Let's just go take this front side building.
Where the, with the post cameras.
Because I mean, at this point, bro, there's, there's not
going to be much to play in Skyhook.
I don't think there's anyone there.
So I should go.
Let's take this for free.
We'll see.
We'll just get in this building first and then move forward.
We can just scan it.
Oh, I think I hear John from it.
Are we scan?
No, no, no, no.
We're good.
The other building we want to scan is up here.
Can I get that?
beacon or no um i would if you could but if you can't do it
it'll be so funny if you die it would be pretty funny yeah
it'll be so funny i don't yeah sure scammed oh they are in
here oh they're not they're not okay i'm just gonna go up
there and break barrels for us get in the building okay i'm
chilling here until i can scan beacon yeah do your thing is
good you're on the other building that's fun i hope i don't
die it'll be so funny though i hope you don't too oh they're
I fucking set up one of the guys and chats are we good guys
we get here I have a plan all right but this zone is
terrible bro everyone hate us bro I do want to I don't know
anymore if I don't I don't I mean he's not really saying
anything so I have no idea what's going on okay good we got
the scan I'll go up north here and like play on penis I do
want no I want to play i want to play underneath raven i
think here but i don't know if there's anyone there or not
i'm trying to scale out the scenes or are you oh you guys
are here okay yeah yeah well i'm trying to go raven if
there's no one raven we should go there right now but i
don't know if there is or not because there's no one for us
to play we literally cannot do anything we got we got we do
yeah i mean i don't think we should evac though maybe we
just when we could evac do you guys want to play okay so
here's my thing do you want to play here or do you want to
go to raven side i think raven might be a little bit better
for us we actually play the game might as well go raven side
yeah but i feel like there's going to be a lot of teams
there too i do too but i don't think we can go anywhere else
yeah i don't think we can go out all right now there's no
there's a lot of teams at trial side yeah i think playing
towards raven and trying to get kp might be the play we
didn't get there wait am i getting walked up with team on me
see my way i'm gonna scan no audio nice yeah we're good yeah
behind us i will play here for right now and just see what
these guys do purple as well yeah one thirty three 180.
they're going to try to take our first floor just pressure
our guys we call tempo put traps down we can down first
floor and block the doors and stuff i'm being shot by a
fucking roof Yeah, you're good, buddy.
You're showing They're all the other bangledios for now.
We're good.
Our building isn't in so now.
No, no, we're in we're barely in We're gonna take our first
floor Let's kill these kids when they walk in.
We're fine.
I'm going to the roof then Yeah, you're good.
Watch out.
There's bangles up there.
Yeah, scanning they're running.
They're running.
They're rotating.
There's good.
Yeah, one one Until I'm gonna look at my side.
We're in here.
You know, is it our first floor, I think?
Go to Doki's side.
Yeah, go to Doki's side.
We're just up here for now.
We're still in up here, by the way.
Barely.
They watch them.
They conduit altered us.
All right, all right.
It's fine.
When the conduit goes down, we're going to ult their first
floor.
We're going to jump down.
We're going to ult their first floor and take this fight and
just kill them.
We need KP here, bro.
We're not going to be able to play this zone at all.
So you have a combo, right?
Demo?
What?
Yeah, I've cost gold.
Okay.
Yeah, everyone here.
Wait, wait, wait.
They're shooting like, yeah, down there.
There's like...
I might get away.
Wait, I think I have angles here.
Yeah, never mind.
They full died.
The team that was behind us full died.
Okay.
There's a dude.
They're like literally in this floor right here.
Wait, there's a team down here too.
Look, I can scan them for you guys in five.
Because we're going to kill these guys if they're still
underneath us or not.
They are.
I literally scanned them.
See?
Right below.
They're coughing too.
This is so bad.
This zone is awful too.
Like, what is going on?
Wait, do we have room on the roof?
Yeah, I think we should not die because it's still 12
squads.
I know I want to try to jump down here and play the fence
line and maybe just Falculti from there But I don't know
what to do because we're getting shot from everywhere.
This is so bad I think there's a team right over here or
like a solo.
You're right.
I see them.
I see them Yeah, they are.
Yeah, I want to jump down and take the fence and then maybe
Falculti late game I still don't know how we survive this.
There's like no actual chance we survive this item.
We're blue All right, so we're gonna jump out.
We're gonna go right now.
We're gonna go out.
We're gonna go on top floor We're gonna go on top floor and
we're gonna go to the fence line.
No, yeah, we're gonna go fence line first No, no, no, you're
good.
No, you're healthy.
John, just come with me.
Just jump down the fence right now.
Just come here and play the fence side.
We're getting looked at by everybody.
We're going to play from here.
Right.
We're going to, we're going to, oh, we're going to valkalty
late.
I just don't know how late we can do it.
We're going to try.
Yeah.
Tempo.
Can you look at our backside here and cost you go do this
right here on the front door?
Front step.
Make sure this gets up.
I'm scanning.
There's nobody here.
We're going to go.
We're going to hit a really risky valkalty.
Come here.
Can we?
Unattached.
We're good.
Okay, ready?
Let's hope we don't die.
We gotta kill.
We're gonna try to land somewhere.
I don't know where we're landing, but this is a really risky
ulti.
We somehow get on that penis.
Penis tower?
I don't know if we can.
There's a team up there.
Wait, I'm penis.
Let up penis.
There's only one guy.
Only one guy.
Okay.
I'm not landing there, by the way, because I fucked up my
landing.
So good luck.
I landed on him.
Okay, it's fine.
You did a good job, Tebow.
I'm alive.
I mean, there's nothing to do.
this zone is so fucking dog shit god damn it man all right
don't you play your life try your best there's really
nothing to do yeah you're gonna go to two points you're good
don't you run on this left side rock if you can i don't have
you can this is so chopped no oh no i got slowed why is this
such a hard why are we getting caught on everything all
right wait wait that's that's that's three more points
though oh my god bro i'll tell you right now these early
rounds are gonna be harder because teams just don't know
what's happening.
Like, why is that team running behind us and taking our
first four for 30 minutes?
I just don't understand what's going on.
I'm losing my mind.
Because they saw us doing it and they're like, and they can
do it.
They're like, this makes sense.
Let's do it.
This makes sense.
Yeah, okay, cool.
That makes sense.
God damn it.
You know what, talk about, too.
We're gonna play the front side of your zip line.
I'm just, I don't know, bro.
I'm just thinking that teams are gonna be playing in these
spots and no one is.
So I'm like, oh, okay.
Well, now I look, I'm like, wait, I forget we're round one.
No one's even doing anything correctly.
you so my fault wait did i shoot my gun i did oh thank god i
shot my gun i was like did i get chest to shoot my gun guys
i shot my gun it's all that you guys i don't feel safe i
don't think i play no we're fine with that was that was that
was that three points were good There's no way we don't get
at least three points every game.
So, like, let's be honest, we're good to go.
Yeah, but what do the other five teams get?
I gotta lower the...
I don't know.
We'll see.
Wait, what is what?
What is what?
The only time I got to...
The only time I got to use my all is when I accidentally
alted.
No, you're doing great.
You did a great job, though.
I'm very proud of you.
We're valid.
Don't stress it.
We're all good, guys.
we're doing it i believe in us we're doing great oh
yeah this is still in if we three hit penis oh we would have
been winning this game baby we would have won three man
landed on that car we just three man jump on the penis three
man got on this dick prize would have been good he couldn't
handle all three of us right yeah i'm a fucking nerd
you land on there oh no i didn't like it it was like land on
that i was like i'm on it i'm on the penis i didn't reach it
i don't know how we didn't reach it that's actually crazy
low-key what do you mean it sped out i don't know i i'm
joking did she just landed somewhere completely yeah but i
lived longer for him well yeah that's what i'm saying
because i just don't know what's free and not free with
these fucking guys in it again.
I don't know what's going on.
Well, there's going to be a 20-man lobby.
It's going to be so much easier to understand what's
happening.
It's just so hard.
I mean, the fact that we even got that Valkalty off is
low-key, impressive.
11 and 1.
That's the two teams that we needed to do really well, and
they farmed everyone, which is good.
Great.
Good for us, guys.
Let's go.
We're on fire right now, guys, honestly.
All right, last round.
Refresh.
Let's see.
Let's see what happens, man.
Give me a breakdown here.
We're just in 20th place.
somehow out of 15 quadrants and 20th somehow don't tell me
why i'm the customer not calling bro that would be the
funniest thing if we don't make it past round one today yeah
that would be so fucking crazy that'd be so funny it'd be so
funny though no but that would mean we improve so much
though the next one we do you know the next one is next week
right oh that's crazy it's just back to back week so it'll
be so funny if we do so well this would be so funny we just
do horrible if we if we make it if we somehow make it to
finals and it's just like oh we're in like top five or
whatever or like i think you're on too much copium right now
tim you're literally in six i'm sure now in first i'm pretty
sure we well that's because we didn't count game three i
don't think we're on six place after game three no way no
way i mean realistically it's just It's just harder to call
this shit because just no one's doing anything correct in
any way possible.
I think if we actually played a bad comp, we probably would
do better.
I'm not even kidding.
I would put money that we do better.
I have to pee a little beer, but I go pee, bro.
Hey, it's his first pee.
It's his first pee.
Good for him.
He's over in the floodgates, though, bro.
He's about to pee 47 times.
He's about to pee 49 times, though, now.
He's over in the floodgates.
It's true.
I'm going to go get an energy drink.
All right.
I'll be here to entertain your chat for 10 minutes later.
Oh, boy.
Okay.
I'm going to love that.
Trust me.
Hey, guys.
So Wigs Chat, do you know anything about, like, Twitch
Prime?
Well,
you know, you can't skip, this is an unskippable ad.
All right.
So, like, all right.
Twitch Prime is basically you can subscribe to your
favorite.
twitch streamer for free so go to the search bar and type
dokey bird go to the twitch search bar and type dokey bird
and then um i am your favorite streamer right now you can
you twitch behind me over there on my twitch channel all
right code is uh codes in oh you got the code nice i'm back
we are we are in seventh i don't know i still don't feel
safe though we're in seventh yeah we should probably play
normal yeah i feel like we should play normal i think we're
like four for fifth i feel safe but seven does not feel safe
well actually we're we're in seventh but five fifth six and
seventh all have the same amount of points oh okay yeah but
what about eighth we'll play how many points does eighth
have like how many behind us there's two yeah i don't feel
safe at all four is 4 is 20, and then 5, 6, 7 are 16.
And then 8 is 14, and 10th is 11.
Yeah, that is no.
And they can easily get, like, a points for this.
Yeah, we should just be careful.
We just play normal.
Everyone's just...
That means we're just the same rank as...
We're...
We can keep sliding by in 7th, all tournament long.
Nice.
Wait, where did Whig go?
Whig went to get an energy drink.
back oh my god wig run faster yeah wig run faster you can
hear us i'm here i'm here i'm here did you hear what i said
wig um i heard you didn't stop talking for like 20 minutes i
just constantly heard your voice while i was in the kitchen
what place do we have what place are we in 40th we are in
we're on we're on uh seventh place seven but we're tied with
five and six yeah but we're not safe at all because 10th
place is only what three points five points behind us yeah
yeah oh my god we don't claw this is hilarious bro that
would be so funny bro i mean so funny dude i should laugh so
much all right guys it's fine i'll start trying now oh yeah
now so guys before trying now i get it it's all good oh so
that's why we're not doing well
you guys realize that what uh davis is going to be in our
lobby every single time all the way until finals wait really
that's how that works that's how it works top 10 always like
stick together and they just combine with the another top 10
that's right beside them oh that's fucked up that's fucked
up man can we like move to a different lobby can we lose can
they swap us to a different lobby can we just lose and play
next week guys i'm done and make it easier i mean we can it
doesn't matter we're not gonna make it all the way to the
end whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa have a little faith here okay
we're totally gonna we're winning one game we're totally we
make it we make it to round two okay i mean no we make it we
make it to day two all right we're winning one game today
we're winning one game from day two to day three yeah this
is it this is yeah i totally believe in us oh yeah 100 this
is my believe it voice now for sure you sound so
unreal there's no way there's no way no never
did they just launch the fucking rank season yesterday
without even announcing it yeah yeah no one was doing this
like day before or something it was like the day before yeah
I think why would they not say anything that's so bad I like
it was so funny because I was looking at the Twitch thing
and nobody was, like, doing, like, rank class.
Yeah.
Like, the rank one.
First team for rank one.
It's like, you don't even fucking know what's going on.
You're like, oh, okay.
He's like, whoa, there it is.
Oh, wait.
I just turned my volume back up in game.
You're good, buddy.
We're vibing.
Alrighty, alrighty, alrighty.
We're so locked in, guys.
I'm totally locked in.
ready y'all yes let's go guys listen to some hazmat hotel
right now we're so locked in it doesn't matter i say no
they're still gonna start it ready no okay yeah they don't
care about my opinion
yo wig yeah what's up you need uh you need some kills here
yeah what's our fucking roller player i'm trying now bro i'm
trying our fucking roller player again gameplay here yeah
yeah you need you need you need four kills all right hey he
stopped it because I said that and then started it again so
yeah listen to you yeah why because I used you as an
argument so he was like no he's like I used you as leverage
I wrote no and he didn't care he still started it that's so
up chat i just don't have that killer instinct anymore chat
i'm sorry dude it's not in me that roller change man i'm
literally thorfen now bro you're literally a roller player
what happened to you i don't fight anymore i have no enemies
so you did fall off no i played basketball last night
actually got extremely competitive but i played basketball
last night i got actually very upset at the people i was
playing with are we doing a uh pickup 5v5 in la i mean i'm
down wait why balls what happened to basketball oh you mean
you mean in the beat on the beach yeah yeah i mean you love
valuable now is that the whole point that's what you love i
love yeah yeah i just built gamer anime anime girl thigh
juice all over my lap right now child gamer sucks yo use
donkey bread for 10 off wait actually do you have one yeah i
think what would you name your flavor what would you name
your flavor if you got one what would you name it i'll need
it what's a good flavor what's it oh that's a good one for
you yeah yeah that's a good one but what would the flavor
taste like though I don't know fucking ass what cheeks oh
we're not getting that okay we still get this for free I'm
gonna take these two buildings I'm gonna actually get
competitive now let's do I'm gonna lose dome and stacks,
okay?
You fucking idiots!
Scan the fucking beacon, you dumbass!
Man.
Should get hell in here instead.
The chat.
He was screaming earlier.
About what?
Where's the zone?
Why are you not popping?
Okay.
I got the carbon.
Ooh, there's a golden massive.
Does it don't want that?
I'm good, but that sounds fantastic.
I'm good.
Oh, okay.
We're good to go.
That's so easy for us, guys.
Yippee.
Yippee, guys.
Okay, I'm grabbing the bat.
I'm running carbine.
Carbine vault.
Okay.
I swear, I haven't found a single repeater.
I haven't found a single evac.
Yes, you have.
I just found an evac right now.
Yeah, that's it.
I should probably stop.
just not large right back i'm not found a backpack yet i
still don't understand how to loot this oh i found a
repeater but i already have a kidded carbide oh i could have
a kidded action we should probably rotate fast this one to
be honest i'm gonna run run a repeater decide figure out
where to grab the uh the uh harvesters from yeah we could
definitely do that but i mean i think retaining a sound
might be a little bit more important for us here in this one
just if you want to get points and the zone's like super
easy bricked all right i'm heading to you is there anything
good in the thing uh purple flat lines if you want to that
it's not bad uh i'm good i'm not gonna take the purple flat
lines i guess oh i can take no i'm running repeaters i don't
want to run double heavy yeah i would do that i need a scope
though for my repeater You could just get it two times off
the flat line if you want to.
Oh, I could.
Here's this.
Oh, yeah, that's better.
Anyone running havoc?
I have a turbo.
No, I'm running a bolt.
I'm running a bolt.
Actually, yeah, take that tempo.
I'm going to pick up this havoc right now.
Take that.
Okay.
I have it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
From there.
The smoke came from this direction.
Wait, there's two monos?
Oh, they're anyway.
Yeah, they're running.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Let them run.
Yeah, it's fine.
We want to get in front of these guys though, for sure.
we can't i have a balloon or evac i don't have an evac
make your way on over kid all right i think they went to get
the evo stuff and then yeah i did
all righty well no there's a purple backpack it's all good
just come on through i'm running i'm running wait there's a
people beacon here that we did not scan oh there are matters
bro i was so early teams like we know it's gonna be free by
the time we rotate there's gonna be so many teams in zone
compared to what the fuck we're in i'm waiting here oh we're
taking the replay oh you can if you want to i'm good that's
over here honestly yeah take it take it well not do it do it
do it do it where are we going to we're gonna go through
geyser side let's go through geyser where did that other
team go they went through geyser as well but they're
probably gonna go through geyser tunnel we're gonna go
through the geyser choke they probably balkled in the top
side gotcha choke right wait you guys want to try that
valkalt from uh uh that valkalt that goes like do you want
to try it i'm i've never done okay you don't want to go guys
i'm not safe at all like our our placement is not safe i
don't know i'm just trying to make round two you know i'm
trying to play at least eight games today yeah let's try not
to i did cancel plans this Oh, wait.
A gas trap.
We're good, though.
Well, you have that temperature or not?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
They were here 75 seconds ago.
Can we grab this thingy?
Oh, yeah.
Get the EVO cache and then we're going to Valkaldi.
Just come back to me after that.
Okay.
I'll wait for you.
You go grab it then, tempo.
Yeah, yeah.
We're going to Valkaldi immediately.
Here, I see people on the hill here.
I'm not going to shoot them because...
They're shooting at someone else, right?
Yeah, they are.
I'm not going to shoot them because they don't want.
Oh, wait.
They're right sauce.
This guy was playing the whole time.
Are we Valkalting from where you are?
Yeah, yeah, come back to me.
We're gonna Valkalty right when you go.
We'll turn back and make sure we're not getting walked up
bomb by Lava Siphon.
We're good.
I'm good.
All right, ready?
Yep.
Come here.
Okay, nice.
Huge for me.
Nice.
Turning Baron.
Are we trying to just go into like...
Yeah, we're gonna get like through the Lava Siphon.
Holy shit.
That was good.
There was team right next to us.
Yep, that was great.
It was a redeploy.
That's fine.
Oh, they're taking it.
Oh, yeah, we can't go there.
Come back.
We'll go back left.
We're good.
Go into the tunnel.
Yeah, we're going right side.
Go left side.
We're good.
We're going to be here.
We're showing.
We're going to walk up here on left side.
Yeah, I'm just going to heal.
Yeah, you're good.
Heal up first, then we'll go this way.
I'm going to start walking up to make sure they don't take
space in us.
I do.
I have 70 bullets.
I need light ammo.
I have none.
Try to see what's free right now.
Just keep moving left of me.
I am hell.
I need light ammo.
Is there anyone on the Twitch rivals?
It's fine.
There's no one over here.
We're going to take this house instead.
Keep coming.
We're good.
Nice.
Good rotate, guys.
We're in a great spot.
Yay.
This might be the exact same time I played.
Remember when I told you about the, you heard my Twitch
Prime stuff, right, Wig?
Yeah, yeah, I did.
Ten minutes later, I have a hype train on my channel.
Nice.
On my Twitch chat.
Where's my hype train, guys?
Guys.
Thanks.
Thanks, guys.
Hey, guys, where's my life train, dude?
Guys, switch prime over here.
Switch prime over here, guys.
They used up all the Twitch prime finishers for my channel.
I need to...
Tempo, can you do this a little bit differently down here?
Can you block the doors?
Holy shit, I fucking cracked him.
Yeah, which ones?
Just block both doors.
Yeah, block both doors.
Actually, block the front one.
Block the front one.
Don't block this one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I broke their fucking jet.
Yeah, fuck him.
Good shit.
And I cracked him.
I'm gonna try to get purple off my sentinel.
I don't know if I'm gonna be able to.
Same.
I also have a sentinel.
Yeah, I charged it up.
Might have ripped a little bit.
We're in a really good spot.
I'm pretty sure that- Can I play on the penis?
Uh, you said do you want to play on the penis?
Don't repeat what you dropped it to you?
I wouldn't- I would rather you not play the cock.
Because if you get- if you get knocked then we can't do
anything about it.
I think for- I think for this- I think for this zone, have a
little bit more locked in because i think teams will start
to rotate in a little bit because it was last game so i
think this game is going to be easier for us to play like
correctly if that makes sense just keep a look down on the
right side here two temples you don't get walked up yeah i'm
gonna look at south side that's fine i'm gonna keep trying
to farm up i have only 300 400 damage off my purple i have
500.
oh i closed my chat this whole time i had no idea what's
like i'm 8 50.
where are you guys getting the things for the thing what
what what did you just say i was shooting people i'm 8 50
away yeah i shot people Can you guys let me know?
He has let me know if I die.
Okay, yeah.
Awesome.
Thank you.
You're dying?
Oh, wait, well, actually?
Oh, my God.
I just fucking shit myself, dude.
I think I'm over.
Actually?
I was like, wait, hello?
That was fast.
I was like, damn, I just literally tabbed out for two
seconds, guys.
Oh, yo, thanks for the five gifted sos on Twitch, guys.
Thank you.
Yo, what the fuck?
I'm on level four hype guys team 11 died that's not good for
us guys I guess they know hype train is now uncapped if it's
still going on after 10 minutes yeah guys over at twitch.tv
slash yeah yeah we have no hype train here guys it'll be
pretty cool if I ever got one never got one before never got
one before
oh I already used my one Phoenix my one gimme hopefully a
fucking crafter wins near us just keep looking out here for
time oh you just literally cannot dive from here just make
sure get barrels on there if you want one team i'm gonna
need to build one now they're moving up moving up towards us
on the right side um i don't have it they're gonna go
they're gonna go rv probably if they go rv if they go rv
yeah you're good you're good they go rv we kill that it went
back you've got we've got like 10 nades in this building
you're good all right they can't go in the close rv they
have to go they went down below the other house we're good
oh that went inside the house we're chilling i'm gonna find
somebody to shoot at nobody's peeking anymore
I just want to waste all my meds.
I really want a crafter to come near us, probably.
I have four bats and eight cells.
Oh, yeah, four bats are.
I have three bats and five cells.
We're good.
Yeah, we can just share our heels.
Yo, peek me.
How is it not hitting?
How is that not hitting?
Oh, from there.
I was like, where are you getting shot at?
That's so confused.
Yeah.
Fuck, I tried to shoot his feet.
Yeah, shoot his toes, baby, suck his toes dry.
Whoa.
Relax, guys, chill, man.
No.
I didn't say that, bro.
Wait, where did the...
People that were playing under the penis go?
They went and saw me.
Where did that Joan, bro?
Look at that.
We've got a bagel.
We've got to go.
We've got to go now.
No, we're going to go.
We're going to back go.
Come here.
Where the fuck was that pool?
Banana phone.
We're going right back to fragment.
Maybe that pole is literally terrible.
All right.
Which fragment we're losing?
Where do we go?
Diner would be best.
What?
I don't know if it's going to be fixed.
Don't we want to play a building that...
Oh wait, diner does have doors.
Diner has doors.
Yes, he does.
Good job, buddy.
You can't wait.
How do you get in?
Wait, wait.
And it didn't have doors.
Come on.
I think there's people in that building.
We're going to land right here.
Land right here.
That's what I'm saying?
I'll leave the same one in here.
We're good.
Oh, that was close.
Diner has doors.
Diner has doors, big.
A lot of these buildings do have doors, correct?
Nice.
Give it a take.
If it now pulls back somehow, I will be very sad and
extremely disappointed, but it's all good to life.
Tim, okay, I have one battery, please, sir.
Uh, I dropped that here.
Okay, nice.
Oh, wait, we don't have this floor.
What the fuck?
No, no, no, no.
Wait, we're going to just play a little bit.
We're playing a little bit spastic right now.
We're just going to play a little bit of 12.
All right, I mean, I have two shield cells.
Tim, do you have extra shield cells or no?
Uh...
Guys, they're going to try to push us here.
Let's just stay focused here.
They're going to try to push us.
So we're going to hold the top side, and we're just going to
play on the second floor.
Second floor is probably up.
All right.
Let me block off as much of this bottom floor as I can.
Pebble, do you have extra shield cells or no?
Yeah, I have 10.
Yeah, I have two.
Can you give me just three?
Or two, just two.
Oh, wait, you're right here.
I'm talking about here.
I'm dropping an eight.
When you can, can you get more barrels on the second floor?
Just because we're going to get a push probably.
Just trying to pluck off all of the first floor.
No, you're good.
You're good.
This zone might pull towards no name, but I'm pretty
confident it's going to go towards us.
We'll see how it goes.
I do.
Oh, I don't have all locked off.
I'm going to go top floor now.
Yeah.
Yeah, do your thing.
You're good.
I was like 12.
Why do I have eight nades?
Bro, what the fuck?
Why do you have eight nades?
A lot of this pool is pretty fucking crazy.
All right.
In 10 seconds, we'll find out.
Well, suit happens.
I mean, I mean, Jesus Christ.
All I know is.
rotate got me a charge rifle so we win okay okay the zone is
getting smaller so i don't know all right well there we go
sound pulls no name it's right we back tower into like one
of the no-name buildings can you no can we can you scan this
uh rv here real quick or no i don't know if i can reach it
i'll try i think we can all right reach this team might look
ridiculous they're leaving or not there's one guy in there
okay i mean i don't want to go there early but i do want to
kind of go there.
Could we break out left?
A little bit.
I don't know if there's anyone.
I want to wait a little bit longer.
If you're next scan and see how it goes.
Because this team and this team behind us on top side,
Diner's going to try to fight us.
But I want to try to get to this if we can.
I don't know if we can though.
We can play inside.
Do you want me to scan the RV again?
Yeah, yeah.
You're going to scan RV just yet again.
There's two people now.
It's two.
But like if we go up there and cost gold, it should be
fucking free.
But then the team behind us is going to.
No, I know.
we lose anyone we're gonna have to fight something there's
no way we get in there for we try to run that side and then
evac from behind this big ass rock no because there's gonna
be a team on cliff that's gonna probably shoot us out
there's definitely a team up there no no no the team the
walton fence over there that team moved down i just saw it
so we should be fine then yeah i think we do drift left side
then a little bit let's He's a bat.
He's a bat.
Want me to give you the point?
I can put an evac right now.
I don't even know if we can land anywhere.
Try not to evac.
Try to evacuate.
Let's see.
Okay.
They're double red inside here, too.
I mean, we might just be able to land on one of the
buildings to be.
If we're getting shut off, just get off.
Okay.
Just keep coming.
Keep going.
Keep following me.
I'm going out of the world for this.
We're going to land.
We're going to land for RV.
There's no one in RV right now.
We're going to go RV, okay?
Get in there?
Right here.
This RV right around.
Oh, my God.
The door just closed.
No, I don't.
Okay, we're good.
We're in a great spot.
We are big ass head.
Now we're good to go.
Nice.
Good job, guys.
Yeah, see, Liv, Tempo and I, we did it.
We helped.
Nice job, guys.
Big ass head.
It was in my crap way.
Good shit, dude.
All right, now we somehow have to...
Yeah, glass side is actually probably better here, so.
We want to stay alive.
Do you want me to scan west side or east side?
What do you want to scan?
No matter.
Let's see.
Right now, I'm probably more.
You're good to talk, guys.
You're good.
I'm so safe.
I'm very safe.
as well, we're good.
Let's keep putting those barrels down, reviving.
The grenade, those seats will really help us.
We're in zone to go again, we're good.
We're gonna literally, tempo, we're gonna get more traps on
this side of RV, okay?
cause we're gonna get sent on from this side.
So any, prioritize any traps and also any in the window up
here too.
If you can just put them on top of the windows, as well,
we're good.
And even blocking doorway.
I'm trying to get some light ammo.
Don't be afraid to block doorway, combo when we're inside
somewhere, we're good.
There's like 10 million nades down here, by the way.
One, two, three, oh my God, we are all just chinging.
Yeah, we're good.
Keep putting more traps down.
I'm cool down on the side.
Somebody was rezzing.
What the fuck is rezzing?
Bro, this is just like, these kids just don't stop shooting.
I'm going to take a chill pill, guys.
Guys, please.
Let us live.
Is there any way for me to charge rightful someone?
No, I sounds this way.
Why not?
Do you guys have any cells?
I can spare two.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I saw.
I'll take one.
I can drop two more as well.
that matter you guys are good you guys are good i'm gonna
keep the name of southwest i still have more cells so
they're robin why are you peaking me why me man just look
delicious i guess this this team has to move now my god i
get it but like it's a hard being so hot well you want to
pick me again bro i'm confident bro i can't piss him the off
i broke this door They're planning on rotating right now.
Yeah, how about you fucking peep me again, huh?
Yeah, you might get...
Whoa!
Thirst him!
Where?
Here and here and here and here.
I can't thirst for my own thing, though.
Yo, we have 10 million nades.
Bro, we're not...
We're gonna not have 10 million nades, dude.
Yeah, we probably can't get any of this.
Fuck, it didn't work.
Wait, the other team's pushing the way.
I should get it.
Oh, my God, we're just in level 6 hype train.
Thanks, guys.
I mean, right here, right here.
Right here.
Focus on my side.
Focus on the side right now.
I'm focusing on the side, too.
I'm focusing on the side.
Okay, okay.
Because I saw them before running.
Don't be afraid to throw ulti if we need to jump on the
southwest side.
Yeah, yeah.
There was someone here.
No, you're right.
They're definitely.
They're getting shot.
They're getting shot up top side.
They're getting shot up.
I'm playing outside a little bit to get some panels.
I'm shooting this team to the northwest.
This kid is still peeking me inside.
Get a job.
This is his job.
Please.
You horny motherfucker.
Got one.
Got a kill.
Nice.
Full knock.
Wait, that's not even your trap.
No, it's not.
I was getting fucking gassed by a different trap.
We're good.
Okay, so we're gonna move left side here.
We're gonna go left side rock, okay?
We're gonna break out of your left and move that side.
Oh my God.
That's your all.
Oh, yeah, we're good, we're good.
Are you pushing us?
Yeah, yeah, they're all there.
Push us.
All this, all this, all this, tempo.
All this tempo.
I all did.
I'm on me, on me, on me.
Last guy's two left.
I can't do anything.
You need to go crazy, your tempo.
Nice.
You're good, you're good, you're good.
You're good.
You're dead.
You're so dead.
We got second.
Oh, wait.
What the fuck happened?
Wait, what the fuck?
How did everybody die?
I was so confused.
Why?
It was just there.
I have no idea.
Wait.
There were five teams alive and then all of a sudden there
was two.
Well, that's what happens, bro.
Because there's just no one in the lobby to start.
It's so hard to predict.
How many kills do we get?
Oh, shit.
I got second place.
i think we got like three kills or something yeah good shit
dude we'll take that let's go baby oh we got four kills yeah
next round we're so around too bro bro 11 and 1 got 14 and
13 what the happened i'm telling you right now i'm telling
you now that would be that would act i think that's that
lobby is going to be harder than the next one I'm not even
kidding.
Oh my god.
Thank you to my Twitch chat for giving me a level 7 hype
train to celebrate.
Oh my god.
Guys, I still have a level 0 here, guys.
We still have a hype train.
Guys, I still have a level 0, guys.
If anyone wants to change that, I'm like, I was...
How do you still have a level 0 hype train after all that?
That's insane to make fun of you.
Oh shit.
Wig, even I have a level 5 hype train.
I'm just fucking with you.
fucked up bro why can't i why can't i hear my own stream oh
wait i'm just i'm just refreshing the page come on man but i
mean we definitely qualify for sure yeah i just want to see
how high we made it with that because if we got second
that's like nine yo we finished in fifth place bro we got
fifth all right how much are our next when do we how many
minutes till we play round two minutes left guys um i would
say i don't know probably fifth 15.
I'm going to use the bathroom.
Entertain my chat, please.
All right, guys, you know, listen to the chat.
I know you guys have a game.
Our game's not in.
You guys have a sub-train over at Doki Burr's chat.
But listen, man, nice week's chat's pretty rad, too.
And we don't have a sub-train.
So if you guys want to change that and, you know, change
history, that would be pretty pop.
Oh, you're not gone yet?
My bad.
I mean, guys, keep going.
Doki should get a level 100.
She deserves that.
Bro, why can't I, why can't I hear my own stream right now?
What is going on?
This is so weird.
Oh, someone like dual sense controller or what?
A phone.
I think, I think, I think Vals could be really good for us,
bro.
All right.
We're back.
Let's check the Discord.
Where's the LDS Discord?
Let's see.
Okay.
Challenges.
Check it three.
We were lobby 15.
Any announcements?
I've spooked I spilled a whole thing of gamer thigh juice or
anime thigh juice in my fucking counter again I'm not I
spilled it on my my fucking my desk now
I don't know how long we wait that was a good game bro yeah
at least shoot our guns agreed that was fun that was some
kills I can't believe I didn't recognize the top two that
happened so fast yeah no when I'm usually so attentive to
that.
Like when I went to the backside of the RV to start shooting
people, there was five teams.
And then when you were like, throw your costicle, then I
threw it.
Then all of a sudden there were two teams.
And I was like, oh, it's already over.
I couldn't believe that, like if I knew that was two teams
alive, I would have swung on the left side and just would
have fought across the tracks.
Because I don't think that was only a duo.
It's insane.
I can't believe that.
I'm usually so attentive to how many teams are alive.
And I did not believe how fast that went down.
Chaos.
literally little cash
okay my page is refreshing all right let's see where are we
now tell until our next game probably a little while yeah 10
yeah i'd say like 10 just because the because the other uh
the other lobbies have to finish too oh yo we should warm up
we can't combine unless warm up yeah we should i'm pretty
i'm recently warm to be honest But the fact that you're not
kind of scares me a little bit.
I hope we're seeing at least more than 40 frames.
Guys, we should totally we should play some trios.
Thank God that they didn't this team inside that RV did not
hit any wingman shots on us.
Oh, yeah.
Thank fucking God.
Yeah.
That would have been so bad for us.
He went like 0 for 7 on us.
This is when we when we were about to fly into the RV.
And you said RV almost flew into the wrong one.
Oh, wait, which one?
Isn't there one RV?
No, there's one on the other side of the tracks.
I was like, okay, yeah, I'll fly there.
And then I was like, oh, wait, there's people there.
Imagine you landed across, probably would have been so
fucked.
Who would have died so early if we didn't have a cost to get
that RV with you there?
Oh, yeah, 100%.
Yeah.
You're literally got knocked around.
There's been a trio pubs.
It's like one trio pub.
That's all you guys, I think we can make food, to be honest.
Oh, you're going to make food?
All right, Temple, get in here.
where are you oh i invited you let's go wait can we leave
trios and not get a penalty thingy yeah yeah we can't oh
yeah it's a pub it's a fucking pub you can't leave gun run
now i know that yeah you can i literally left my pub 10
kills what was our what was our final score like our final
placement fifth yeah we're two point two points away from
two points away from fourth i can't believe we got nine
points and we only went up two placements that's actually
crazy yeah well don't forget we had a pretty fucking shit
third game that's pretty that's true yeah our third game was
pretty rough gustav gustavs are same way same with our
second game we went to track across the fucking river of
death but hey we survived we got top 10 every time really
did good job guys that's fun i actually had to shoot my
weapon a little bit that was a good time I just can't
believe how fast that went to two squads.
I'm kind of sad I didn't recognize that.
I'm watching it.
I'm watching it back right now.
Yeah, I didn't realize.
It's like everybody just died so fast.
Yeah, and there's no reason for that either.
There's a lot of spots that are playable.
I just thought if I knew that was happening, I would have
100% told us to see it out of the trophy.
I saw us die.
I was like, second?
Yeah, I was like, six.
I was like, all right, well, six of 4KB.
We should still make it.
But I saw second.
I was like, what the fuck do you need second?
Yeah, I was like, wait a second.
all right i'll be right back real quick all right we're
playing a pub go for it are we doing the same jumping in
here are we going to do the same comp where there's actually
20 people at tempo yes yes all right i didn't know that was
like our actual comp now oh my god an alternator
yay yo there's a gold bag over here got it i got so much
gold stuff um golden golden wait why didn't not grab that
hemlock there you go wait are you in here with me yes that's
me stealing your loot here you take that because I don't
know how that gun I don't know how that gun works did you
take the scope I got scope no I got scope I think I dropped
it over here somewhere yeah yeah you don't know how to use
the 30 30 but you play sniper that's that's that's not a 30
30 no you dropped a 33 yeah but yeah yeah but oh no i mean
like yeah i don't know how that gun works that's that gun is
you lead off like it's like a like a sniper that's too much
thinking that's too much thinking way too much thinking
necessary i found another
I got oh wait the thing the thing's over there yeah oh wait
we don't need that we're playing
pubs I hear someone I'm gonna rat them yeah I hear people
too let's rat them right here
wait I got it ready there they're gonna come grab this and
then we're gonna kill him oh wait they went into the ring
they went to the ring yoink yo what the fuck they're on me
they're on me whoa they're on me yo let's go in and punch
his ass out let's go fuck that guy oh he's fucking right but
where's his teammate though
hey i fuck him up i don't know where his teammates well i
ain't got balls in the face He balled you.
Oh, there's his teammate.
No!
I went climbing to the ring.
I couldn't.
Oh, that's ballsy.
I fucking got crazy, man.
Last guy is, like, over here?
Yeah.
He's over here.
I'm gonna crawl you.
That's the way the last guy is.
Oh, that bomb fucking give you a shoe he's pushing in left
side oh all right let me refresh this oh it's out oh it's
out all right let's go we got our new lobby oh no why why
are you saying oh no he's not back yet bro wait i swear i
thought i heard him he's not back some guy
did you just put the code in no no all right this one might
be a little difficult oh why why we have like we have like
five teams i recognize all right let me go into that ailjose
discord and what what group are we we're in group eight uh
code is coming out here in a sec
oh man
is out.
I wait.
Don't you.
What?
Are you telling me that your level 10 hype train is offline?
Yeah.
Wait, what?
Are you fucking kidding?
Wait, she's offline?
I'm not.
No, I'm on YouTube.
Why does what?
You didn't know.
I thought you were streaming on Twitch too.
I reacted way crazier if I knew it was fucking offline.
What the fuck?
Yeah!
What are you doing?
I'm opening stream.
No, it's not.
It's ended, but it was on a level 10.
I had to make my fucking green super greens drink.
We got a two of them are going, right?
Yeah.
You didn't realize it was offline.
Oh, what?
It's 11.
And I turned offline.
Only you do that.
I did.
You're out of work.
You did.
Only you.
There's only one in the world that would.
I can't believe you didn't know that.
Where are we going for this one?
I'm trying to figure out where people are going.
I'll make my drink that I need after this game.
It's fine.
I've been taking a probiotic with like these.
What team are we?
Are we team 19?
Yeah.
Oh, wait.
Even I recognize some people.
We should definitely call.
We should definitely go immediately and say something.
World's Edge first.
Let's say we're going, I mean, Monument's not bad, to be
honest.
Monument would be pretty good for us at easy rotations.
out of monument uh harvester
um anyone countdown there's one team monument uh team is
already going monument no one's countdown i don't see anyone
saying countdown right by west
or you can see him conk i don't want to fight off spawn we
could but i really don't want to do that to be honest four
games and you get monetizer l rod like i i believe in
architects but just let's just say what for some reason we
do this we just one of our four games which is not worth it
siphon mill i'll take countdown if we can it's honestly we
might be able to grab mod stacks it's still open oh thermal
l rod oh but i can't lie bro we're gonna get i'll just say
stacks mod i said stacks mod fuck it harvester climatizer i
will i'm gonna go to the bathroom real quick that'll be all
right north pad monument stacks mod fissure everyone stacks
monument anyone monument fissure zeus thermal elrod
countdown zeus fissure siphon mill north pad harvester
fissure zeus dax mod guys are dumb beast zeus fissure
honest so no one is so right now uh a tree launch site dome
stacks mod it's all open that entire south side is open okay
we called stacks mod for us yeah
so that's just needs to we just needs to uh use his use his
streaming and uh bully everyone out you'll never be on the
watch party ever again but that's good they don't want to
get watched they don't want to get the cast you will you
will never get you will never get publicity you will never
watch you will never watch your stream if you land on us so
you will never get publicity that's what we threaten people
with oh my the overseeing eye of apex legends what the uh
there's a lot of really good teams in here by the way yeah
that's what i was saying we're talking about it wait where's
the thing this one we got we got uh we got zone davis we got
ferelli on his team we have easy stomps the the other team
that did really well from our lobby last time we have
unorganized okay yeah so there's like five five six teams
that i recognize maybe they'll fight maybe maybe they'll
fight each other cedo tree all right so tree is taken cedo
is taken so we can't land there on storm point um honestly
we probably can we can grab pylon our launch pad still
that's that's still open pylon launch pad yeah like okay so
barometer pylon launch pad devastated echo coastal that
entire south southeast side is open okay for your first uh
for storm point and then for world's edge launch dome stacks
mod it's all open so if if someone decides to late go to
stacks or some then we can veer off to launch okay launch
site if we need to wait so there's someone going mod stacks
potentially no no no i'm just saying someone oh someone is
going launch site okay so yeah we should have no one should
be mod stacks in dome okay what i can see okay but obviously
you never know
if we do if someone does land on us and we don't want to
fight them we still have staging that's open that we can go
to as well yeah which is not bad let's just hope people
contest each other yeah you guys all contest each other and
we'll rack up the placement points yeah we'll just we'll
just be there chilling placements oh yeah here we go this
might be the place where we no but we still have next week
though we still have next week now we still have next week
guys don't worry we're totally gonna get into pro league
guys oh obviously yeah wait if you get we get to pro league
who's gonna watch party i i want to be honest here okay
ready team two is literally just like absolute fucking early
rounds challenge.
Yeah.
So we can, we can just have them run everyone over.
That's what I'm going to say.
They're definitely going to three.
They're, they literally, they fall off after end of every
challenge circuit.
So they do horrible in files every time, but they are just
early round.
We're on a, we're on a hype train.
Oh shit.
Oh my God.
Wig, you're finally on a hype train.
Wig.
Let's go.
You did it.
I knew you It's because my hype train ended.
Yeah, unfortunately.
So they transferred over to you.
Yeah, transfer to mine.
Oh yeah, I forgot she's not actually doing anything on this
channel.
Let me just go to this one.
Oh yeah, she's actually has not even said a word yet.
Alrighty.
Let's fucking do it, bro.
What are we waiting for?
Start.
are they like ready no all right so literally just watch out
for those two that team two no joke okay where are they
landing um i have no idea we should definitely hopefully not
be near them though they're gonna probably take a really
good po off okay tempo where are they landing analysis now
see they don't care whenever i say no they don't care i'm
back if it was imperial how though they would care yeah if
it was wing that said no Do you have the way I said don't
keepers said no and then they listed after I said no.
Okay, start.
I'm going to play.
I'm going to play the same comp.
Okay.
I'll do blood.
So we should have.
Mod stacks and domes should be open.
Yeah.
But we'll see.
All right.
Well, we'll see what happens.
100%.
Let's go, guys.
Let's do it.
We have four games, man.
Whatever happens here happens.
Let's do it.
I believe in us.
Hmm.
I do too.
I think round two will be like really hard.
I mean, don't forget.
I want to also point out there's been like really good teams
that do not make it past round three.
So like I'm very proud of them already.
Like I'm very proud of us already.
No joke.
No troll.
Let's go.
Then why did Tempo say we can make it to finals?
Because he's delusional.
I think we can.
It's just going to be hard.
We can do it.
What do you mean, delusional?
Yeah.
What do you mean?
Delusional.
I mean, there's a team right to our right.
Wait, there is a team there.
Yeah.
with me here to stay with me are are those guys going stacks
then or i think they're are we getting do you think they're
stretching to launch i don't know just stay on me just stay
on me yeah they're still they're still here one's going to
mod are we getting that one team went mod okay so we go
stacks and i think that team is stretching to dome i think
so as well um yeah they are there that's fine yeah just land
together here we should be okay this team's leaving i'm
getting uh i'll get the backside then i mean that kind of
sucks bro why are these guys taking over they probably
didn't want to contest i gotta be honest but i respect them
not fighting us instead and just going to mod it's a good
call i already done the same thing all right one team dead
here we go nice not last guys not last place i'll take that
all day you think i'm kidding i'm so happy about that let's
go baby i'm happy not last yeah you have no idea about that
let's go baby huge one all right so let's see how this goes
though man um we should realistically here in this Let me
see real quick, one sec.
We should be able to get to Mirage.
I think it's going to be Mirage slash staging.
Try to be real.
So we should be able to move quick.
We definitely want to navigate like...
Let me scan this beacon while Dome is not looking at me.
We have ring scan too.
Yeah, that's going to be like really big for us.
This ring console should help us at time.
It's right there.
Okay, there we go.
It's going to be a lot of Fisher's zone.
It's not an easy rotate for us, but we can do it for sure.
Still positive.
I am looting.
I'm like carbine hemlock.
I'm the best.
Okay.
Also, let's just watch out for mod to push us or do some
stupid shit.
Because they do know it.
No offense.
They do know it's us.
And respectfully, people probably do want to push us.
We're being honest.
Should I do the do the player scan?
Yeah.
I mean, if you think you're safe right now for sure.
I'll try it for it now.
I can come up and body block for you if you need first.
Let's see.
I'm doing it.
Yeah, go for it.
Go for it.
Blue backpack here, by the way.
I need that.
Oh, they're gone.
That's a really fast rotation.
Okay, then we can go to, we can go, we can go mod and then
grab their.
Before I hit the XL.
Yeah, we should, we should definitely get the EVO.
I'm going to grab the EVO right now.
We should start rotating out right now anyway.
I have four batteries, eight cells.
I'm actually really good on meds, to be honest.
Me too.
Like, really good.
There's also this one here too.
Perfect.
Because my ass is broke.
That's fine.
Do we want to take the replay?
Yeah, we do for sure.
Oh, wait for you.
Yeah, you're good.
I want to just get anyone have evacs or no.
Do we not get one?
Nope.
I didn't grab one.
I didn't see one.
It's all good.
We can take this balloon, right?
No, yeah, we should take the balloon for sure.
Oh, wait, here.
I dropped that.
Oh, I'm good.
I'm good.
I don't have any energy.
Alrighty.
Where are we heading?
We're going to land over to lava side by side.
Lava side by the speed road down pretty quick.
Yeah, we can grab that balloon too, to be honest.
Yeah, I think we just go there and hit another balloon.
Just land on this caterpillar balloon for now.
And just scan inside this building and then we'll just hit
the balloon.
There's no one looting this whole site.
They probably just left the radio, honestly.
You want me to scan?
Yeah, scan this front side building just in this one.
Just scan it so I can run it on.
Someone res.
We're good.
All right, I was hit this balloon.
Yeah, someone did res.
All right, let's go.
Yeah, keep on moving.
There's a team right here, though.
We're good.
We're going to go left side.
Just going to keep over here.
Sectional, right?
Keep on moving the left side and we're going to hit it.
We're going to hit a Valcolty probably and try to get in
somewhere.
Time to be on middle side.
We're going to hit a Valcolty for here.
All right.
Do the player scan or no?
Oh, actually, yeah.
Yeah, might as well.
100% do it.
All right.
No reason not to.
And it gets away.
I'll watch that team.
Team behind us over at launch.
We're good, though.
Yeah.
all right i think actually at this point guys like we're
pretty actually no we're good there's teams leaving they're
over to crafting right now we're gonna we're gonna go to the
harvester we're gonna go through harvester this team's going
we're going through heart we're gonna go back here backside
yeah we're gonna go we're gonna go to this way yeah all
right that's like we kind of know where the sound's going
anyway it's gonna go towards lava fisher there's no way
there's something in front of me kind of though guys i still
don't have a back high for some reason Wait, what?
We pinged the...
Just say how?
I bought two.
It's gold.
You grab some heavy?
Nice.
Wow, that was awful.
Fuck me.
What a useless uh...
Another one.
Where do we go?
We're gonna keep walking through Harvester's side.
We're good.
I have a gold helm for...
I think you keep it right now, to be honest.
dokey right now if you can pick the gold helm dokey all
right i have also double ulti excels if you guys need your
ulti late game or anything yeah i have an old excel too
should we shoot these kids walking in okay oh i'm reloading
my stupid gun it's okay crack one crack one blood literally
one hp over there oh i missed it's not good he's still on
right here i'm gonna try to kill it when you walk when they
cross all right can we grab that evo cash to our back left
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Is there a team on fence, though?
Ah, no.
No, they were the team on fence.
They left.
You guys find sniper ammo.
Let me know.
I'll stay near him just in case.
They were good.
Oh, whoa.
There's people.
There is people.
Yeah, we're good.
We're good.
We're showing.
I'm trying to look for you, but they're far.
Yeah.
Just keep calling back to my side, guys.
We're good.
Yeah.
We're going to move through harvester then.
Fuck the evo cache.
Yeah.
Yeah, we can't.
It's all good.
No worries.
That's the team.
team top highway so they just rotated in it's all good
really worse we're valid like we're a little late we're very
oh we definitely got stalled out i mean stats modern we're
gonna be late we should probably go and actually get this
evocast right here to be honest and then we'll go in from
there we can make a play i am two and 16.
uh scan up just in case yeah you're valid nice i save yeah
we're safe.
We're good, dude.
I also need some charge rightfully.
If anyone sees a 30-30, let me know.
Got you.
I'll keep a lookout.
Ooh, Evac Tower.
Nice.
Oh, that's huge for us, actually.
One team has three Evac somewhere.
Yeah, actually, though.
All right, we're going to keep on walking in.
We're going to get height on this rock here, and then we're
going to hit the evo cache, and we'll go from there.
I'm going to take the height.
It's like five seconds behind us.
Yeah, you're good.
You're good.
I'm going to take the height of this, and then you guys
just, one of you guys just goes get the evo cache.
Okay, I'll get it.
Hey, you're valid.
I'm looking over.
We're going to scan just in case.
Yeah, why not?
We're going to go through landslide?
No, no.
We're going to go through staging for sure.
I am...
Oh, behind us.
Flying in!
Flying above us.
We're going tunnelside.
Yep, yep.
Lending on my height.
Lending on you, yeah.
We're going to fall right down.
We're going to go down.
There are.
Teebees are here, too.
Come down.
Come down to the landslide, you can.
We have no smoke.
Don't forget.
Just try to get it.
Just keep going.
Oh my god.
They're sending us.
Go through tunnel.
I'm batting.
Keep going through tunnel.
Oh, I don't think temple's dead.
I don't think temple's dead.
Motherfuck.
I'm dead too.
Just keep running down.
Okay.
I'm just going to run down.
Oh, why are they doing that?
I would just honestly, honestly, Doki, wrap through the
landslide tunnel on the right if you can.
And then maybe I might go back around if you can.
Yeah.
I'm trying to get her banners.
champion but it's all good dude what are they doing i
guarantee that's feroe and the boys i will put we i right
here and then go back um you could yeah you could just go
all around time to i don't know if you have time to go all
the way around you don't have an evac right uh no i don't i
would i would wait then here i just literally right here and
then go like maybe 30 seconds let me know when to go you
have meds i do yeah you should be fun and then you can res
us over in the staging side like the crack house over there
oh okay i have like three I have like three syringes, one
Phoenix kit.
Let me know when I should go now, actually.
I would actually start moving now.
Yeah, yeah, you guys are timed.
Yeah, only 40 seconds left.
There's an evac behind you.
You're good, though.
If these kids are routing it, then there's not much to say,
to be honest.
No.
Really unfortunate timing, though, huh?
Holy fuck.
I think, I mean, if there's not here, you definitely get our
banner, though.
You're good.
Just really depends if they're routing it or not.
And I think you go res in that shack.
You know the house I'm talking about, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, cool.
Nice.
We can go to our loot too.
We're going to have a balcony as well.
I'm going to go see if you have, we'll grab some of the meds
too.
They took the lead back.
That gets me need.
It's all good.
No worries.
All right.
They go hit that res above us if you want.
Not that one.
The left side one.
Yeah.
The one that's like that little house.
The one in the house.
Oh yeah.
Just because we don't want to fucking immediately get sent
on.
And then we can go into staging, probably scan that beacon
to see where to go next.
Do we get a point for being top 15?
yeah we do get a point which is good that's fine that's
great wow i can't believe they landed on my height in that
situation man hit a free rotate in the landslide tunnel
right over us probably thought you were solo or at least
they definitely did not trigger me i think they're like
they're just super confident in team fights i think i think
that was the really aggressive squad i'm pretty sure i mean
if you want to scope out the scenes doki you can go to the
front of staging i'm gonna look for you right now no one's
in staging we should probably just get there to be honest
all right just go staging like bottom side yeah we just go
bottom like into the glass you Definitely can get a glass if
we need to.
I'm going to go bottom side now then, because I don't have
that many meds.
Yeah, you're good, you're good.
Do your thing.
I'm not going to go get a loot time, but we probably can't,
sadly.
Yeah.
I'm right behind you.
It's definitely up to my two syringes.
Damn, I had good loot, too, bro.
That sucks.
My charge rifle.
I know, man.
Also, my ulti-xel is not going to have an ulti or an evac.
I can give you an ulti.
Yeah, we probably should, because I think my ulti is going
to be super important here.
It's going to get in the zone and see what's good right now.
Am I gonna die from this?
I think I might die from zone.
All right, don't show too much presence here.
Just play small.
Yeah.
Yeah, I dropped my ultrasound here.
Yeah, we're gonna take this.
Yeah, you're good.
Do your thing.
I'm gonna pop this all the Excel and we're gonna try to fly
in somewhere, guys, all right?
That's gonna be the play.
We're gonna try to get...
I should scan beacon, right?
Yeah, if you can.
Sure.
Let's see.
I don't give you guys...
Do you guys need syringes because I can give you guys one?
We're gonna play...
No, it's fine.
I'll take one, yeah.
We're gonna drop down and we're gonna...
Valkyledy from down below.
You should actually do it up here.
We're going to do it up here.
All right.
We're going to wait 30 seconds though.
We have to wait for my percentage to get up.
Just play small here for now.
We have 30, oh, but we have 30 seconds left.
I think I'm going to get my ulti by the time now.
By the time the zone closes.
I hope so.
I mean, I hope so too, because then we definitely don't get
a zone.
Keep moving towards me, guys.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here's the way I team fighting on that side.
If we can somehow land in that fissure building.
I want to try to get RV, you know what I mean?
Down here.
Oh, okay.
RV looks free too.
Yeah.
there the team above us is gonna be a real problem all right
we're gonna make a play here guys i don't really know what
to do wait wait you know you can buckle from here right
where there okay yeah yeah yeah i think you can i think you
can wait for it then wait for it can you though if not if
not we can just play underneath here okay okay yeah it
should be fine what's that we're gonna figure it out soon
all right well i mean this is our hell mary so yeah this is
our hell mary here all right ready come here come here come
here ready we're gonna get on immediately ready three two
one go we might die out of there here wait Okay.
Okay.
Don't you just go.
I can't even see.
All right.
Let's see if RV's free.
If RV's free, we're playing there.
Okay.
That was a scary shit out.
I would just land on top Mirage.
Wait, wait.
We need to get a better spot.
We're going to play underneath.
We're going to play underneath here.
Okay.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, bro, you're so lucky.
I called that out.
Nice.
Good job.
I have fallen and I cannot get him.
You're good, you're good.
I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay.
I'm okay.
Open the door for you.
You're good now.
Put barrels down, Tembo, put barrels down this side.
This side when we're born.
Yeah, we're gonna open this.
You're scant didn't pick it up, but I saw it with my eyes.
Why did my skin not pick it up?
Yeah, you're scant didn't pick it.
I was like, there's people.
Oh, wait, I can take this back.
I have a backpack now, guys.
Nice, great.
I'm still broke.
I'm once though.
I'm not broke.
Yeah, I'm busted, bro.
You take some cells.
Yeah.
I'm surprised that we're even alive right now.
Me too.
Okay.
There's a problem though.
We have a Krabber team here with a double red.
So like, bro, that is a problem.
We just need to literally play small tempo.
How long till your ulti gets back up?
It's up.
Okay.
Cool.
So we're going to play small, do not get Krabber.
Literally do not peek this window.
Have they push her for the ulti outside tempo.
Like immediately.
I'll tell you what.
He takes the ulti outside.
Yeah.
We're going to.
Oh no.
An ulti inside our RV if we need to.
the outside and just shoot us yeah but we have we have next
zone just gonna keep looking out for these guys okay i'm
gonna oh my god you know in purple it's okay it's not a big
deal okay yeah yeah we could all be purple yeah but yeah i'm
not wait you have what i i don't okay i can give you one
more syringe that's gonna say i actually don't even want to
cross over and get that to go it's not over here you go
thank you all right we're gonna put here tempo keep putting
these traps on this side protest aside 100 i think this is
just because you need it thank you All right, you can never
peek again.
I hear them moving.
When you old tempo, you're going to ult the outside, like
literally right here.
Yeah, right here.
Yeah, if they push us, I don't know if they're going to be
guaranteed, but they're thinking about it for sure.
He might be as small as possible.
It's just so funny.
Oh, shit.
I'm not even zone.
I'm in zone.
No, we're in zone.
Okay.
We're in zone.
I'm talking this wall.
Like when I say ulti bro, like you can ulti whenever you're
going to ulti.
think we're getting i can i can ult you right out this door
yeah yeah i wouldn't even do it yet though because they
might try to wrap our other side yeah they're ending us now
they're ending us i'm safe i'm safe tempo hold outside now
hold outside now hold outside now their side right side
right side hold the side i ulted nice good ult you can only
focus this side now they can't be going because of this yeah
i'm looking i'm looking i'm looking i'm looking oh they're
trying to come in through here that's fine that's fine but
they're not they're not knocked yeah so we got those are my
termites i can't go out i can't go out i can't either i
can't either don't pick this yet yeah i don't know i don't
feel safe They're still out there.
They're still out there.
We're good.
Let's get the barrels over here.
Tell them what we can.
I can't.
Okay.
It's fine.
They're dying.
No more.
They're dying for it.
You're dying for it.
We need to get a grip on this.
We need to get on this.
We got it.
Nice.
Good job.
They're getting pushed through.
Push through, push through.
We're getting set down.
We're getting set down here.
Wait, these aren't my barrels.
That's fine.
We're getting set down.
I have to go for this, bro.
I'm dead.
The red box is...
The red box.
You can...
I can't always run your barrel or not.
We're good.
No reason not to.
Somehow we're still in zone.
Can't tell which barrel is modulo.
The only barrel that's in here is...
I'm good.
I got med kits and stuff.
We're good now.
We're still in zone.
They're gone.
Eat some loot.
Yeah.
Eat.
Go loot.
Go.
Eat.
No, I can't.
I don't need to heal first.
Okay.
We're good.
Thank God they delivered their loot to us.
I got a Krabber, guys.
We won.
Wait, I have no loot.
Another Krabber, double Krabber.
Who wants to get it?
Okay, no, not me.
I'm horrible with that.
I'll take two Krabbers.
Wait, are you throwing?
healthy wait you're throwing wait you're throwing give me
the craver give me one of the craver you're gonna have it
because i'm definitely throwing you're definitely throwing
but imagine the content wait i need that light ammo and the
light mag and the light stuff oh yeah i dropped you some oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah they're just three minutes i cannot
believe we're still in sound guys yo how are we still alive
i don't know i don't know i mean you guys made that so good
just just just live here we live here let them kill each
other look i don't think we can We don't need it.
Does anyone have any needs?
In game.
Does anyone have?
No.
Come on, zone pull to us.
No, it's fine.
It's fine.
We're gonna play underneath.
We're good.
Oh, here's more lay.
How the fuck are we?
No, no.
We're just so good.
Thank God.
You're going.
You're going to stop three.
Top three.
Wait, wait, wait.
We gotta wait for them to kill each other.
I know.
I'm gonna try to pressure them.
They're gonna force it.
going to evac up if they fight this if they fight with you
back up okay i don't have an evac we're gonna i do i do i do
we're gonna play late though just play here late yeah we're
good i'm ready i'm actually hitting these kids too i'm ready
for them to a plus wait they knocked one they knocked one
okay it's fine it's fine we're gonna play slow wait till
they trade more did they i didn't see a kill feed oh the the
the the uh they need it they need it they feel killed nice
they focus one that's good they're good we're good we're
gonna play this late we're just gonna play late we can't
really go up here yet because we're gonna die i mean tempo
where the What the fuck are you doing?
I mean, we're gonna have to eat back up, I think, for sure.
Well, I can climb.
I'm a mountain goat.
Yeah, climb the straight side.
Oh, I'm a mountain goat.
Why did you climb this?
Oh, shit, they know I'm here.
Oh, shit.
Abort mission.
Abort mission?
Oh, I'm trying to get second.
All right, boom up.
All right, I'm gonna eat back tower.
We're gonna go.
We're so dead.
It's fine.
Let's go.
All right, ready, go, ready?
I'm going to eat back there.
I'm going to eat back.
I'm going to eat.
Ready?
We're going to do this together.
I'm doing it!
Oh!
They've grenade it!
We win this!
We win this, guys!
We win this scene!
.
Alright.
I died right out of the air.
I hit someone.
It's fine.
I'm okay with a second.
I'm okay with a second!
You may not be wind!
How did we get tall too?
We got 2!
Oh my gosh.
How did we get 2?
we were so broke i don't know how that works oh my god they
didn't finish the job i've never seen that house with that
rv in for that long that's not with the rv in for that long
ever in my life we had zone knowledge oh my god good shit
dude oh my god we should have finished the job we had one
kill we had one kill by the way yo we're in fourth place
let's go oh fuck good shit chat I don't know how y'all
wanted to fight that bro when they land top rock and we have
no horizon bro like team one team one team three and team
two are cleaning everybody yeah those are all three teams
that we we knew about yeah one two and three were cleaning
everybody yeah it was some extent they literally cleaned
more than half the lobby themselves good fucking dude all
right guys we're halfway there no that's a great play from
us i cannot believe that just happened bro i can't believe i
can't believe i know we were so lucky we had we had zero
meds and then the and then they delivered their meds to us
they amazon primed us let's go guys let's oh my god oh wait
is this code for lobby too is that our code oh i think this
is lobby too it is uh yeah let me post it in the thing all
right guys let's do it i have to pee again wow i can't oh my
gosh you got to do as many on me like that that's nuts
that's actually good to get away though no really good job
to get away seriously you saved that game good thank god
that dead slide clutched it that's 10 points that literally
is going to probably get us through if we make it i don't
feel safe man i don't know that's the most safe we've ever
been that was unreal
oh my god that's unreal i can't believe that just happened
can't believe we actually i mean and you guys when they went
in the rv like you're goaded for that bro you're actually so
yeah yeah thank god i used my eyes yeah i used my eyes there
how did how did we not How did I not scan them?
I think it's because they like came out at the last second.
I think so too.
Can you guys let me know when the game starts up?
I'm watching her vlog back.
Yeah, someone was like, respect to the Bloodhound for going
for that Kray-Rashat at the end.
That's me!
You're such a beast.
I was like, wait, I'm the Bloodhound!
If my chat's telling me to play Edge, it's like, bro, play
Edge.
Guys.
I'm pretty sure all these teams are playing.
playing edge we should want to get one kill what do we mean
play yeah we don't need a kill we just need to be in so
unreal good fucking call tempo by the way that we can ulti
out of that angle yep well weren't you the one that told me
to ulti out of there really good call and also great call by
doki to swear back to rv that's great yeah that would have
been so good we have such good you know i think i think this
is like algs material i think we got we got we got algs both
we keep on going we go we'll make it the pro league that's
what i'm saying oh
my god let's go that was a hell of a rotate oh my god i'm so
surprised we made it this far i'm so surprised all the teams
behind us die it sounds like do it for the content creators
let's pass the other round so we can make more content yes
yeah you you lgs needs more publicity we're here for it yep
we're providing it right now yeah slowly but surely we're
giving you publicity let us through to the final round give
us the content creator pass i think my favorite part of this
though is that i always tell chat how bad rvs are and our
our life has really dependent on rvs yeah we got our pious
placements when you have a caustic i mean true yeah yeah but
true all right so someone did land here and here okay yeah
here and here so we okay wait how many x's is that five six
seven eight
i mean thank god also that rampart team did not like try to
fight us too much and they went on the outside rv instead
yeah and then they got on by the people on top i mean they
wanted to but we got we got so many like fucking barrels and
stuff they couldn't they couldn't get in yeah if you didn't
tell me to line up the barrels i would have spent like three
and three but we had five barrels on that side so yeah i
mean it's the only time they can pee because the other
team's gonna shoot them the whole time yeah where the hell
is game where's uh they're waiting for someone davis okay
let me let me know let me know when we start up someone
fucking moved this guy can start yeah yeah tempo get in
there bro someone fucking move him apparently his team was
like can we have wigg over davis bro i take wigg so i can oh
we just got 10 points there i'm not trying to brag god bro
if i had any of my loot i would fucking got three kills in
this rampart team so hard i was just shooting a nomad prower
i was so
part where uh where they're trying to raid us into in the rv
yeah i'm watching right now it's so fun to watch the mod
back it's so yeah the 10 minute delay is it was like
scantoki i was like i'm scared i don't want to move i didn't
want to make any noise or move i was so scared we got this
bro let's go we're so about there's something i'll be able
to fuck oh yeah just sorry nice oh my god you guys murdered
that bloodhound that ran in i almost died if you didn't kill
him i mean i had a peek that bro because i just can't let
them get the fucking side like you know even though i died
there it was still worth it to be honest what i'm saying
like if you guys didn't kill the blood that ran in i would
have died and you would have died yeah no you guys are great
and then i'm dying to a causing barrel because i have no
idea which one's yours i was like so chaotic it was so
chaotic and i was like trying to loot some syringes and shit
and then two barrels showed up and i was like oh i don't
remember throwing those barrels there and then they just
popped and then i forgot to mention that they weren't i mean
i had to go for that though because i had no heals i would
have been a useless flesh you just be her meat shield i
gotta get something right now like fuck me all right got you
baby no did you realize we've had have we had beacon every
single game bro where was this in twitch rivals yeah what
the fuck that's a young game we're kind of getting bitter
peel eyes here
even geyser has had beacon two games in a row yeah which is
where we landed in twitch yeah we had zero beacon that was
my own tournament they couldn't let us win that's how it
goes
gets the fucking beacons okay so geyser is there mod is
there i'm gonna split off now and head to the beacon i go
loot these it's just so much fun guys they should play i'm
having a great time like i had zero expectations going into
this and like i'm having yeah i thought i was we're out
after the first round not gonna lie zero expectations that's
the delulu i love that about you though tim you're giving me
hype a little bit i'm expectations i was like i don't know
guys I don't know we're gonna make it to the first round we
had zero practice as a team other than the twitch rivals and
that didn't go so well Please don't shoot me guys.
Here's the charge rifle.
I pinged it.
I can't ping it.
I'm a beacon ping I might roll.
I had another evac too.
You ping an L.
You did it?
There's some sniper ammo too here Wait, where's uh, okay.
It's on the second floor.
Is it with the sniper ammo?
No, it's on the second floor okay i
kill i mean we had no chance to win that game we did a
really good job getting the second place there yeah yeah
we're so lucky that they decided to push each other there's
a lot more sniper ammo here okay nice i'm vote hemlock right
now i'm not that bad i have a 6x here too for you
i don't know why i'm so confused i don't know what's going
on anymore what happened what do you mean why are you
confused i'm so lost i'm just i'm just running in circles
you're good buddy
I don't think he's okay.
I hear Dougie just get stressed out whenever Tempo says it.
You're like, what do you mean?
What do you mean?
I was like, what do you mean?
Okay.
Wait, I don't need that anymore.
I just picked one up.
You did the charge rifle?
All right.
Well, I mean, I'll do this whole shot and we're going to go.
There's a 6X here, too.
Oh, I got a...
I got a...
I got a redeploy.
i love you bro at least kill one as i'm just flying to a
whole three man with pac- magnets i kill one i'm just
fucking dead of you not me just floating around in the air
yeah not me just floating around the air not knowing what to
do he's like get one yeah i find a fucking spot to land
first they don't debt one yeah i love it dude i love it so
much i think my favorite part was that we each individually
five different Gordon's yes that was fucking awesome we have
a a thingy by the way this is a horrible zone for us and we
have no evocast tool geyser so oh yeah that's what i was
about to ask about the evocaching can we people do we have a
people people thingy oh we have nothing oh we got a big mob
though we got a big mom do that yeah we're good there's a
heavy mag on that someone grab it if you need it uh i need
it yeah all right let's go scan people and then also uh the
zone over at mod hey are they still there or did they live
No, they definitely left for sure.
Unless they're routing it.
But the whole paintball side is looted.
So I would assume they left.
I could show presence first and see what's good.
I'll fly up.
And if I die, just run.
That's the chat.
I can't lie.
They looted this like fucking horribly.
There's so much shit left.
If you guys need anything.
They like fast looted, I guess.
Yeah, this team wants to just get the hell out of here
immediately.
Which I kind of respect.
It's like the right way to play.
Oh, there's Bats here.
Oh, yes.
I need a sniper I'll let people scan it Yeah, you're good
Hit the people scan And then we'll hit the console beacon
again I think we just wait Till the zone closes To be honest
Okay, you want me to scan that or wait Um I would wait I
think we just played the top mod And then scan both Then we
just ripped it in Cause we're gonna be late to this No
matter what So I'd rather know the next circle And see if
this is a crazy pull or not I don't think it should Oh Oh my
god Okay Team over at the drops Uh The fucking Evac tower I
see I see them They're taking the Evac Yeah I just want to
land it Play together What the fuck They're good We're good.
If they land on us, we're pretty close here.
They almost stuck me with an arc.
Are they pushing us?
Oh.
They are.
They're out of there.
You know we have White.
Oh, we're fucked.
We're fucked.
We're so fucked.
Oh, yeah.
Run if you can run.
Run if you can.
I'm trying to run.
I'm dead though.
I think it's out of you or me.
Yeah, you guys split.
They can't get all of us.
They're not splitting.
We're next to each other.
Yeah, I think they definitely get all up first.
No!
I'm there at great second place.
They know it's us, dude.
They know it's us.
I think it's they know that we got white armor because we
didn't have evil.
Yeah, we had white armor, yeah.
Yes, them!
Oh my god, it's so stupid.
They know we had white because we had no evil.
Just a fucking Ferelli boy kid.
Just a hard-stuck Challenger Circuit player.
Whoa!
I mean, it's true.
All he does is go to Challenger Circuit and they get shit on
in the finals.
Everybody in time, man.
how they play and they go to finals and get shit stomped
it's just annoying oh my god it's so frustrating ggs that's
where that's okay we're still you need you need five points
a game to get into top 10 so we're good we're still we're
still okay we're still don't worry we have two more games
wait wait wait wait wait wait is this is only four yeah this
is four we have two more games i think like they land dome
right yeah yeah they land dome or no they land uh launch
site dome yeah so they're they're gonna be they're gonna be
behind us every time now now we know we just got to dip the
out immediately i mean we should be we should be fine uh
next next bracket or because we're storm point on the next
one we're storm point for the next two so we're fine if
these guys in the lobby again they go long side down we know
they're gonna do that again yeah yeah for around three yeah
100 oh one second you're good bro do you think fuck man that
sucks because the right the right play for us there is to
wait to be honest 100 but they they know that that's us too
so they're like they full sent it it's not a bad play i'm
just salty but overall it's just annoying yeah we just they
know we we had white too because we had no evo yeah it's so
rough the no the no player fan for us is pretty rough in
that situation and also not having evo cash in front big mod
is tough too yeah i wonder if they were the same team that
fucking ran at us last game too yeah yeah were they i think
it was i think it was because the horizon that landed on us
yeah yeah yeah i think that yeah that was the same team that
landed on us so they'll always be like i think they'll
always be like behind uh following us and mirroring us yeah
100 without it now they will pretty sure i think we just
have to fast be faster in our rotation because like they'll
always be behind us so we'll we need it we just got to get
the the out yeah we got to dip the out the moment we yeah
the only problem is though in the next round like let's say
we do make the next round and we go to world's edge and
these guys are behind us if big maw doesn't rotate we might
also not have stacks yeah true true true let's just find out
where do we want to go for stormpoint next two games what
are we thinking i don't know i'm trying to i'm trying to see
no station i think these guys land there see those taken
yeah yeah yeah she does i think everything's going to be
taken at stormpoint but we could still make it work yeah
we'll see where everyone right has anyone no one claimed
stuff yet right now they they have uh but not everyone has
just when we like think of all the spots are free right now
that's what i'm trying to think the fucking map almost bro
what am i watching uh where's my face oh i don't have it i
didn't see w keying everything look at this is what they do
every time they just literally never make it anywhere
because like you can't double key everything right around
exactly yeah
it's okay they have the they have the sick ass rank mindset
oh he's dead
What did they die to?
Oh, nice job, guys.
Seriously, great play.
They died to an actual team.
Yeah, I'm not salty at all, guys.
No worries.
Bro, they died to...
These guys just they play like it's ranked every game.
That's, that's what I just told you.
Yeah.
They would have died to like, no, but I'm sorry.
They, they, they, they're somebody.
There's somebody.
There's somebody in someone's heart, but like...
Road life is good.
Road life is actually pretty good.
I know him.
Oh, you know him?
Yeah, he's pretty good.
Oh, okay.
Wait, am I watching the same team as you?
I think so.
No, but Bloodhound, Caustic, Bang?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Road Life is really good.
Oh, okay.
So there's some buddies.
The dad is some buddies.
I mean, compare to us, everybody's somebody.
We're the part of the game plan.
I think everybody's everybody, and we're nobody's.
Yeah, we're the nobody's here.
Yeah, 100%.
We're the underdogs.
100%.
Without a fucking doubt.
Follow for follow?
All right, revive for revive.
What do you think?
Okay, so Tempo, how are you knowing where people are going?
Are they typing in a Discord or something?
Oh, no, they were typing in game chat.
Yeah, like they were typing the, like, they were doing all
the drops for in-game.
Oh, shit.
You're calculating that through game chat.
I was just writing down I was just writing down I was just
writing down crossing out all the stuff on the map.
He's analyzing god damn thank you thanks for this is why we
have we have tempo let's just double check when we swap maps
here well that was a learning game for us now we know we got
to leave quick we don't have anything yeah let's see we just
have to make it to that we have stuff we have to leave quick
because their team that team is like they'll just be right
behind us and yeah and also no offense to any of us here
they're just going to be distributed yeah no the hundred
percent you're going to win oh wait wait wait i have a plan
they're going to beat us okay okay next round assuming no
those stacks and we do right we we hide in one of the
buildings and we rat those fucks okay and then we kill and
then we kill one right we kill one we can't lose 3v2 right
we're still we're still gonna lose i think i think i think
we win a 3v2 right same armor assuming there's no armor div
i think we can win 3v2 i think we'll win a 3v1 I don't know.
No, I think we can do 3v2.
Because they'll be...
Because, okay, this is what you do.
When we rat them and we kill one, right?
We gotta use that initial, like, two seconds of confusion
that goes through their brain and then kill the second one.
And then it's a 3v1, alright?
That's the plan.
You gotta use psychological battles.
We're gonna use the psychological battles here.
We have two seconds after we rat one to kill the second,
because they will be confused.
Unless they're...
Are we really gonna risk your one game for that?
i think we do i think i think i think we do it and then we
t-bag the shit out of them okay wait do you think that's a
smart thing to do our our two games that we have left no no
no it's next round no it's it's when we it's when we make it
to next round okay okay okay if we make it to the next round
okay yeah if we make it to the next round we take step
because we're not on world's edge anymore right yeah we make
it to the next round we take stacks we rat them in a
building then we kill one from getting ratted then we kill
the second in the next like three seconds from confusion and
then it becomes a 3v1 oh come on and yeah yeah because
they'll they'll have like three seconds of brain delay when
they're like what what when they're like what just happened
and who just read it and who's where and what right and then
we use that delay to kill the second second person yeah and
then and then it's 3v1 and after we kill them we t-bag them
oh wow you think so you're thinking like thinking like so
ahead in the future yeah yeah i was like i think also like
crazy because that's just if we win yeah if we get to the
third we definitely get one we don't like it's a hundred
percent we get one if we rat it's like it's like 70 we get
the second one in the matter of like in the in the confusion
and all the stuff the confusion again yeah that's seven yeah
we use confusion is super effective confusion is super
effective depending on who you're fighting the only problem
is i don't think this works irl sadly controller players
okay confusion confusion that this is exactly why i don't
think we're gonna win a 2v3 confusion probability for
controller players is much higher than m and k players and
that's like why i think we won't win a dv2 instead of tempo
just shooting his gun he's gonna think about how to confuse
the players yeah i was 13 damage but like bro i got them so
stumped i gave the ptsd now they don't know what's going on
bro i gave them ptsd PTSD, they're gonna be like check every
fucking building now because of us.
Yeah, exactly.
And then you know what happens when they have to check every
little building?
They get slow.
And then we can get ahead of them next time.
You're so smart, man.
Honestly, you're also so dumb.
It's unreal.
I love it, dude.
I thought I love you so much.
See I'm just dumb all around.
That's nasty.
But like Temple here, he tries to hide his dumbness.
What do you mean hide?
Hey, my brain is still here, okay?
My brain only disappears when I go to...
When I go...
We literally play Apex Legends.
We don't have brains.
Yeah, true.
It's gone.
Before your stones.
After the first two years of Apex, it's fucking long going.
You're so wrong.
You're so correct.
Once you play Apex two years, you just automatically are
dumber.
That's just how it goes.
No, that's only controller players.
Oh, you think so?
They get affected twice as hard.
I actually think you might be right, bro.
I have definitely gotten way done before when I first
started.
Wigs, like, wait a minute.
I'm a controller player.
I was pretty smart, bro.
And I'm not smart anymore.
That's for sure.
I've done some app questions, bro, on stream.
I said that streaming is like the Bimbo modification.
One of those, are you smarter than a fifth grader things?
Yeah, have you ever taken one of those?
No.
I don't think I've ever passed it, bro.
I'm not kidding.
Wait, really?
Wait, how far did you get?
Yo, if it has like geography and stuff in it, I'm just
confused.
Geography is fucking stupid.
Why do we need to know where things are?
Exactly.
Honestly, low-key spin a little bit.
If I'm not traveling, why do I need to know?
Yeah, exactly.
Even if I am traveling, I have Google.
Google?
Yeah, we have Google.
We literally can just Google where to go.
We have GPS.
Why the fuck do we need geography?
To be fair, though, when I was in Japan, I just literally
just Google Translate everything with pictures.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
to do with geography but yes exactly what i'm trying to
travel i guess i'm sorry yeah i'm learning japanese so we
can uh when we go again i i can iGL us in japan when you can
just iGL us in english like what do you well no i gotta be
able to talk japanese so that i can idea let us let me let
me talk to you in japanese okay no i thought you meant like
we're gonna be like in japan playing apex or something i was
like What do you mean?
We're still going to be talking in English.
It's too funny, bro.
I just literally take a picture of everything I need to
know.
You know what's crazy?
I worked out in Japan, like a park, and there's like yellow
tape, but like not really yellow tape on the thing that says
like caution.
Did you go to the... Did you ever end up going to the One
Punch Man place?
You mean One Piece?
One Piece Man?
Oh, yeah.
What?
One Piece Man is crazy.
Or One Piece, dude.
won't be shimmed uh what sucks okay next time we go we
definitely have to make that a priority because i want it to
go wait what happened to my nesty plushie you said you give
me a nesty plushie where is it i'll see you at land right
where is it i have it i have it no key's not going to land
no way yeah digitally gonna go to land wait who's gonna grab
the ipad and the the roller stuff i i have a tablet i just
don't have a roly thing wait how much is a roly thing i have
no clue hey You had a level 10 hype trade.
You can send us a...
No, no, wait, wait.
No, wait, wait, wait.
Don't you had a level 10 offline hype trade, okay?
Let's ask if Apex will sponsor a Roli thing for us.
It'll be content.
A Roli thing would be content.
It would be so content.
Okay, you know how in Japan, you guys were on like that
platform thing for B-stream?
Yeah.
Imagine just having Doki just zooming around in the
background and then she falls off the stage.
She's like drifting.
Imagine her little avatar has abandoned on the forehead yeah
she's drifting too hard she just eats herself off that was
so funny okay okay okay yeah they sent it while tempo was on
the roof true bro tempo you and roofs are cursed brother
yeah so you weren't you on the roof when they shot you yes
yeah that's right yeah and also you were yeah we ran up we
should just get where they were going i should i should have
just charged rifle them off the thing honestly i didn't
charge rifle them because i thought fly away true then I
should have realized it's three controller players no you're
spitting for real yeah okay okay so like who's gonna ask
apex to sponsor sponsor us for the you you have the most
cool just yeah yeah level 10 hype stream you just got a
level 10 hype train you got a level 10 hype yes but that
doesn't mean anything isn't your hype train even higher now
I'm talking like yes I guess it's unlimited now it's
uncapped oh no I mean like isn't it like higher for your
stream to hype chain compared to like a normal stream you
probably made more in that level 10 hype train than i do to
get paid to get to the b stream yeah okay hey at least
you're getting paid i'm just going there for free we could
get like apex to sponsor it which means none of us have to
pay okay yeah yeah you you go ask ea wait why do i we
literally work because you have the most pull we literally
works for b stream how do i have the most pulled as content
creators more pull wake is also a content creator i think
it's a host and caster yeah i'm a host i'm a co-host you're
not even a host i'm a co-host yeah so then you can like you
have the most pull because you literally work for apex right
guys we're in eighth we didn't we didn't we're not 10th yet
so we're good Jesus Christ Zone Davis has 43 points We're
not in 10 We're in 8th place Let's fucking go guys This is
good This is good Alright Now we got Now we got We got a
plan for round 3 Now we can't Fuck up You know boys If you
guys If you guys are listening That's right You might want
to Double check every single room And then this You know
what this is If they are listening Then they'll double check
Every single room So they'll be slow I thought we're doing
That in round 3 Yeah that's what I mean Oh okay I thought I
was we're not doing this route what the jk we're actually we
actually are here listening we actually are guys if you're
if they're listening and we are actually routing them then
now they have to check every single corner so even if
they're trying to push us quick in bigmont they'll be slower
now that's right check every corner because we could be
every yeah clear the corners guys guys check your dms check
your team all right let's go all right this is our real plan
guys Yeah, this is our real plan.
Checking my DMs.
Whoa, that is such a great plan, Tempo.
I'm waiting for them to type the thingy where they're going.
How did you write that much in such a long, in such a short
amount of time?
That is like so much knowledge.
We're so smart, little man.
I'm so proud of you.
Alrighty, let's fucking lock it in.
All right, let's figure out where the fuck we're going here,
yeah?
Ascade, Zeus.
I am a little high and the delay plus wig typing in chat is
absolutely breaking my brain.
Yo, someone fucking typed tree, and we're on storm point.
I think they've lost it.
Launch pad, cascades, C note, C note, C note.
Okay, checkpoint, and storm catcher.
All right, what's the...
Did Team 2 type where they were going?
Team 2?
Oh, no, I have no idea.
Let's get the fuck away from them, bro.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm not trying to go down with the sinking ship.
They haven't typed yet.
okay they just got in all right so we got we got pylon wall
and checkpoint still open or or our favorite poi uh i'm on
still yeah uh maybe because it doesn't around it's scary
doesn't doesn't uh don't the boys do exactly what legacy
does all the time i'm not sure why would they do exactly
what they do are you just copying they both ape everything
oh They both also land at the same POIs, I feel like.
Yo, guys, chicken palm or meatball marinara?
Chicken, brie, cranberry.
Quick, quick, quick.
You're fucking bougie.
Bougie, motherfucker, man.
And the bread has to...
would take from that guy i like that different one two three
four five six seven eight nine ten that maybe that's a crazy
thing only 12 pois are claimed i feel like there's just no
way pylon's free i gotta be honest here okay well we still
have check someone i remember someone typing wall like when
we were in world when we were on world's edge so let's just
pretend wall is gone okay we got checkpoint pylon jurassic
right there's no way somebody takes jurassic is such a place
No one's typing landing spots anymore.
No one's about it anymore.
No one's admitting.
No one's talking about where to land.
Yeah, I don't know.
It makes me nervous, though, because I don't know where the
fuck to go.
It's because your chicken palm distracted everybody.
True, true, true.
My fault.
That's in the hard-hitting questions here, making them
think.
Yeah, they're thinking they're not actually doing.
Okay.
Checkpoint, eye line.
Jurassic coast and the other coast what do I want to go are
you playing?
Yeah we're saying coast we're going coast you know coastal
and devastated coast are both still open I mean okay so
let's just we're starting so let's just go put on and if
someone's there let's go checkpoint okay down I mean that's
a really hard jump though like we just gotta hope it starts
bottom right and goes top left oh fuck me let's try it I
mean wait am I still caustic um on stormpoint probably not
no watson i would say okay okay and i would are we swapping
back like you're on blood and i'm on bang no i think we stay
valk to be honest okay i think valk's gonna be like really
important for us i think are you cool on blood or no yeah
yeah yeah yeah i was just wondering no you're good i want i
don't want you to be uncomfortable
all righty 6 45 right yeah yeah the thing is that i think
that barbecue place is like 30 minutes 30 minutes away for
food wouldn't be downtown la yeah 30 minutes okay you guys
just talking man hungry 25 minutes oh that's tough it's a
long drive for food all right bottom right top left ready
all right the ship did not the opposite of what you just
said by the way well that's not bad if we see someone going
left we go right that's not bad at all that's not bad at all
let's just see this is where we want to go i might just jump
early brown see anybody I gotta turn my audio back up.
How about your jumping, by the way?
There's one team potentially going there for sure.
I think checkpoint might be the more free one.
Checkpoint.
Oh yeah, there we go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Bandage ship, go checkpoint.
All right.
Don't come near.
It's just the archon.
I'm still turning around to watch.
I'm looking at the team chart, right?
I don't think anyone is going pylon though.
So yeah, we know now.
I think there is one team, bro.
I'm pretty sure.
There's one team here too, maybe.
All right.
What we're going to do is you guys are going to both land on
this building back just in case we're gonna contest it okay
i'm gonna land middle i'm on that middle there is it there's
someone right above us yeah yeah go over here okay yeah yeah
no we have no choice now sadly oh we are getting contested
all right we can make it work we're good we're good we're
good we're better we're better 100 i'll just hold angle from
here i think so okay i think we are for sure here's a charge
rifle for a fight that's in front of us we're good we can
just leave get your loot and then go back down below we're
gonna go down below okay i just don't want to fight this
because I just don't know who's near us or what they're
gonna do.
Just don't know who it is to be fair.
Alright, I'm gonna jump off and we're just gonna keep going
mountain right side.
We're gonna go walk towards Mill's side, okay?
Okay, I'm handing over now.
Yeah, I'm gonna start walking down Amelia.
Just steal their loot.
We might just... Yeah, I think we go pylon next game.
I think so too.
Let's do it.
It's fine, but also teams might take it now because they
might think it's free.
Just loot all this.
I'll go to the next building.
You guys loot this building, go down below.
We're gonna go.
Alright.
We're fine.
We're gonna be fine.
I picked up scope all right and there's a charge rifle here
too let us see what is free here let us see
are they lowball up there i'm good sir nice they're fighting
over in mills right now by the way there's a skull piercer
here nice i can't use it sadly but it's good all right i'm
gonna walk down here i think we just i think we need to find
a beacon We should get this Evo cache, though, on the
rotation now.
Yep.
Agreed.
For sure.
We do not want to be blues anymore.
We do not want to be whites anymore, man.
Nice.
So one team dead.
That's going to be the mills team that just died.
So we should be able to rotate and get this Evo cache over
near Cito.
I want to destroy these spiders, but I don't know if we want
to do it right now.
We really, really need like heals.
Not an Evo somewhere.
No, for sure.
One bat, six cells.
We're going to hit this Evo cache right now.
We got to watch out, though, Tempo, because this team is
another need.
fighting in there yeah yeah i think five's down and we're
good where do we want to go i don't know bro i want to go
towards cito but if this team's still here i don't want to
looted yeah i know but i don't know if they're still here
you know i mean but this would be a they were pretty early
around the rotation and cito takes a long time to loot just
play slow here and see because the cito station team should
be really good if they're playing cito should be a good
squad yeah they're on top cito right now let's get us back
up here back up here back up here we're to go back.
We're going to go to we're going to go towards Bean, okay?
We're just going to walk over here and go towards B.
We're going to path into this road.
I know it's a really shit route there for us, but I don't
really have another play right now.
We're kind of getting fucked.
It's good though.
We're fine.
We need another Evo.
Right now, this blows.
Or we can, yeah, we don't have a scanning thing either.
No, we don't.
I'm going to shield cell right now, just in case.
That's fine.
Do your thing.
You're still needing back there, yeah.
I mean, yeah, I would third party if we didn't have fucking
whites you just loot this up we're good we love this take
our time and we just have to literally just loot up to make
sure we just c-zone you can also hit that prowler if anyone
wants the damage for the eva do you get enough evo anymore i
don't remember i think you do right
we really just need we need like a hundred squads already
guys so many teams are early fighting for no fucking reason
this is great no one wants to take those there's a 2x on
that i have a 3x Yeah, I'm good too.
Let's just keep looting up.
Yeah, because teams are landing on each other, so...
Yeah, exactly.
So we should be good here, man.
Because they're not sure.
Yeah, there's going to be a lot of teams fighting that don't
know what they're fucked to go to.
Don't forget, we saw like three POIs free and we got landed
on, so like, that sucks ass, but it's what it is.
We can go get the care pack here too, maybe.
People were here 10 seconds ago.
Okay, nice.
Yeah, they got the care pack.
You're good.
They're over here now, too.
They're rotating back towards CETA, but did the barometer
have a beacon?
No, it didn't have a beacon either.
So these guys, no one near us really had a beacon at all.
Then we just wait for the zone to close.
I think we play big building over here near us.
And we just wait for the zone to close and go from there.
Let's play in here.
Put together a fence up.
And then we just go.
It's definitely not going to end near here, but it's fine.
Just stick together and show presence.
And we're good to go.
We're going to play this late.
But we have a valve for this exact reason, to be honest.
Is there any other evos that we can get?
Any other evo caches?
There's no one near.
No, none of them are near us.
So ass, bro.
The team that fucked this checkpoint sucks because we could
have got an evo cache up there too.
It's all good.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm, well, I'm 12, 3, so.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm, I'm 06.
I've, I've no bats.
I've sells though.
All right.
We're good, baby.
We're vibing the fuck out.
Just stay calm.
We got this.
I'm so calm.
I have an evac tower, too.
I want to jump this guy here.
I have a quest begin.
Someone take that back.
I'll get it.
Oh, I'm a son of, huh?
They know we're right on or two.
They're going to fight this fight.
Here we go.
They're going to go.
You're ready for a fight.
You're ready for a fight here.
So we have 33.
Keep scanning when you can.
We're gonna have to get opening damage here.
I already scanned once.
Yeah, you're good.
I might be down.
It's the window.
People window.
Yeah.
Yep.
Talk to heal.
I have to heal.
You're good.
Good.
I mean, no audio.
Super sick.
Oh, no.
You leave.
They're literally on my door.
I'm just running.
Oh, God.
We're getting fucking.
Nope.
They just fucking scan me.
i have no idea just keep running tempo they're gonna they're
gonna just land on you just keep going whoa that's them
again i'm actually just gonna be so mad it's unbelievable i
have were they ranked 41?
i have no idea oh is that them again is it their horizon it
is them they're right behind us these kids are so cringe bro
how did they get us again It must have been the mill.
Wait, is this their first, it's their first fight?
Yeah, it is their first fight.
They were probably C note, I guess.
Right?
I'm trying, bro.
I look at the zone too, checkpoint.
Oh my god.
Oh, I'm so sad.
Maybe we should have just fought the checkpoint team.
I don't know, bro.
And that situation is just so tough.
Like, God damn it.
We can't think it's them again.
We died to them again.
Yeah, it's actually just super unfortunate.
Are they fighting again?
Oh, no, they're...
I hope you guys get...
I hope you guys get day two, you motherfuckers.
Right, right, right.
We're still...
We still have one more game.
It's all good.
Like, don't forget.
One game, but we can still get us through.
The next game and we're good.
Yeah, yeah, we just need one...
We got one point.
Guys.
We got that one point, guys.
I mean, to be honest, as long as this team keeps rolling
every other team and the teams with us don't get any points,
we should still be fine.
100% bro without a doubt.
I'll be back one second.
Yeah, but our third, our last game has to be good.
We need a game.
Yeah, our last game has to be decent here.
We need to find a spot.
We need to find a spot to land too.
I think pylon should be fine.
Pylon?
Okay.
Yeah.
It was open.
Like it was open, but we only we veered away because we
thought someone was going to be there.
Well, we should have went on pylon.
Where is it?
Where is this team landing?
The team that just killed us?
Yeah.
Probably C note.
I would say C note.
Because we knew someone was fighting Mill.
And they don't have any kills from before us.
So it's either C note or barometer that they went.
Yeah, because they're like mirroring us in both maps.
It's okay.
We don't make it through.
We still have next week, guys.
Yeah, we got this, guys.
We got this.
Wait, is it literally next week?
the saturday yeah yeah the saturday i'm gonna send y'all
something don't don't look at it though on oh okay okay i'm
gonna be honest
that's the only thing i'll read that's yeah don't look at it
okay i'm gonna be honest
That's no fucking thought I did.
Because I know the first sentence you write is not going to
be anything.
Yeah, no, of course, of course.
It definitely wasn't her just reading out, not thinking.
I'd be like, oh, wait a minute.
Try guys, try, dude.
Alright, we can get it.
We can get 10 points in this next game.
And then we Gucci.
But if this team...
us bro one good game yeah this team or the other other two
teams if this one or redeem or relax just kill everyone
anyway then we actually stay in our ranking anyway so we're
good yeah we just we just now that they killed us we need
them to kill everyone else okay i mean they are sort of
killing everybody yeah but then like the thing is they're
not killing people fast enough so like they have 10 kills so
like the people team below us might just overlap us from
sheer placements maybe yeah we're getting zero points yeah
we got we got one oh we got one like oh we got we got one
okay good we got one placement point i mean if we can
actually get pylon for free though we're gonna be i think
we'll be fine yeah yeah yeah we get pylon this is this is
the checkpoint team that this has got to be the checkpoint
team that we landed with it's really unfortunate brown that
that checkpoint pulled up here Yeah, I mean to be honest, we
also didn't say checkpoint.
Yeah, sure.
To be fair, you're right.
Yeah We should just type 2 POI so that everyone gets
confused.
No one no one no one type checkpoint.
Yeah No one type checkpoint.
So that's why we thought we should be okay there too if it
looked like someone was going pylon Yeah So technically it's
also their fault too.
Definitely it's also our fault.
Yeah, they should be mad at us to be honest Yeah, they'll be
like what the fuck you type pylon.
Why are you here?
there's no one type checkpoint and we had someone was going
pylon yeah we hesitated that was team eight who was team
eight i think i actually don't know
okay one sec oh my god i got hit by four headshots yeah did
you just get rocked bro i got no audio did you watch my vibe
back if you watch my vibe back i had zero audio on a horizon
just landing right in front of me it was crazy i got fucking
terrifying.
That's okay.
We have one last game.
That's all it is, guys.
We got one more.
We already did better than what we thought.
And then next week we play again, we're only going to get
better because we're practicing.
Oh yeah, because this was our...
This is our practice session, right?
Yeah.
And now we know what POIs we like.
We know what characters we like.
We're so good to go now this next week.
We should have, you know, done some scrim or two before this
game.
But like, no, instead, this was our practice.
yeah no need for that yeah this was our practice yeah
practice for pro yeah it's only the one practice week guys
we got one more of these bad boys come on dude yeah yeah
eventually we can make it to the finals if we just keep
spamming it so we can like you know have off on sunday like
we just care about our mental health a little bit you know
what i'm saying yeah yeah yeah we're not done yet though i
don't know why we're coping we're oh don't worry i already
had i was on Sunday to be my rest day.
I fucking love this team so much.
It's fucking hilarious.
Oh my god.
Leaking TSM strats right now.
My god, please, bro.
Oh my god.
I mean, juicy Reddit post I could react to for content.
Guys, they're saying that TSM is planning on um oh here we
go you're planning on cutting hal from tsm and then yeah
you're cutting hal and they want to bring an up-and-comer i
.e dokey bird into it how is planning on retiring no no how
how is planning on retiring what wow oh my god can we get a
reddit post with dokey's name my god exclusive exclusive on
joki first channel i'm listening to what they're talking
about on temple stream right now and it seems like how is
planning on retiring and they're they're planning on um
hosting tryouts for his replacement like this week and reps
is going full-time plans for zombies that's crazy oh my god
and like uh burholz is planning on becoming the new igl for
for dsm insane i heard howe's committing to ant farms full
time he's committing on being a house wife for his girl good
for him yeah good for him actually yeah good for him he's
gonna be the he's gonna full full on full on house house
wife duties good for this guy man honestly vibes for being
honest yeah he's like he's like oh man apex it was just a
great time to retire this is the great best time he's
retiring guys peak retiring for five million dollars bro
yeah yeah good for him good for that guy good for that dude
oh man wow wow wow we you know wow we is what it is wow we
is right dude don't worry we have one more game 10 points
though and honestly it's gonna be 100% possible to qualify
for us we just need placements we need better placements we
just need fucking we just need fucking a beacon bro that's
all we need every game we have not run into fucking 18 186
what were you guys talking about what were the TSM leaks oh
where we're going to dinner oh yeah and i heard that you
guys are hiring ducky as full-time uh yeah yeah you're
signing me up yeah yeah yeah they definitely have enough
money for this after not paying for a house anymore bro why
is this guy fucking 1v3ing by by himself is this still the
same team yes he's like 1v1 1v3 away from his team they have
21 kills no for sure yeah all this bro just to go out
literally never make for a league it's crazy to go out in
day two because you just can't do this against good players
it's nuts i mean we're not saying we're not good players i
mean they can do it to us though they could definitely do it
to us probably every time they could probably beat us 3v3 99
of the time i'm i mean i'm pretty sure they could beat us
2v3 if they wanted i'm sure maybe even one maybe even one
you know i don't want to be surprised there's this one guy
that's literally trying to 1v3 by himself they're both like
all three of them are trying to 1v3 a fucking team listen
this is all just setting up a crazy comeback story if we
don't make it this week to go next week and fall the fuck
out oh that is so true it's so true dude oh it's so true i
believe it i really did too but i think we're gonna make
this next one we're gonna be good to go That's the bottom
one right now.
I think we secure a W this next game.
This is going to be the one we win.
Oh my god.
And then we can...
Do I have to get a Liquipedia now?
Now that I'm in, like, CC?
Wait, I think I get a Liquipedia.
Can I be on a Liquipedia?
Oh my god.
Are you going to get one?
I'm in an official tournament.
With zero earnings.
Zero.
No, no, no.
If they add my content creator tournament earnings.
Yeah.
if they add all my content creator tournament earnings i
earn more than some pro players i'm pretty sure i do too
okay it's not the biggest flex
unreal it's gonna be wait did they just win they just won
yeah wait what point did you guys get this game one they ran
at us bro tell who's that tell them to coach us yokey says
coach us pop in the discord and coach us yeah oh wait we're
in ninth guys we're tied with five no way teams for like if
we up this game we're not gonna be we need us we need
coaches insane oh apparently dude you guys are my i gotta i
don't play valk remind me to scan care packages bro okay
yeah that would help us with the points i think would have
had blue i just forget dude all right codes up let's go what
was that tie we're 9 10 11 12 all tied at 11 points oh i
shouldn't send that i really want to send that message i'm
not going to send it though i'm not better than that i'm
better than that i really want to send this why do you guys
suck stop running we ran every time we fought them you want
to say why are you running Oh, yeah, I thought you were
saying, like, why are you running away from the fight?
I was like, brother, he's got 30 kills.
I don't know.
All right, let's go, guys.
We got this, man.
This is it.
We're literally, they literally have a chance to call.
We just got two zero, one point and zero point game.
We just need, we literally need like good placements.
That's all we need.
All we need is literally not to die to team two.
That's literally all we need.
We just need team two, we just need team two to run everyone
else down.
Yes.
and out please please leave us alone leave us alone please
what do we do to deserve it i i scared everyone off we're
good what do you say nice bro banned from all you think you
got swing like that i don't mind this tempo confidence i
need bro i think they come to me to host the tournaments
anyway so i'll just be like oh yeah yeah yeah this guy this
team just apes everything so they're not good for good for
the tournament that's insane that's unfortunate
like for uh for actual reddit reasons that's a joke by the
way tempo would not do that yeah for legal purposes that is
a that is i'm not joking
for legal reasons i'm not joking
I can make these jokes because I'm not organizing any
tournaments in Apex.
He...
I want to say it.
I'm not going to say it.
I'm going to say it.
I keep typing things and deleting it.
You know what I mean?
We're going to say it.
We're going to say, no, type it to us and then I'll say it.
No, no, no.
They don't want you to look like, bro.
Oh, my God.
You're so smart.
Type it to me.
I'll say it.
You type it to me.
It can't say to a V2 model.
What are you going to say?
I'm not curious.
I'll tell you.
Why, Ashura?
I was going to say, all right, guys.
Don't want exclusives.
I won't say it.
Exclusive.
I'm trying to be better, bro.
I'm trying to be better.
Oh, my God.
I'm not, though.
VTuber shit talking you, bro, has got to be top three worst
moments.
Like, you know what I mean?
I will type it.
I'm going to type it.
You know, type it type it after we make it to the next
round.
Okay, okay, okay.
Yeah, you save the shit talk for when we're on top.
If we go out sad as fuck, we don't say anything.
No one will know.
Okay, how about this, bro?
If we lose, we don't make it, we don't make it past to next
round.
We go, we go like literally all black profile pictures,
everything on Twitter, and we go to our grind mode this
week.
and then grind mode yeah yeah it's like the bra and james of
basketball when he's about time he goes full black robot
picture everything it just grinds and then we'll go to wig
to to grind mode and then he'll be like i'm sleeping guys
yeah they were like we woke up like all guys we're ready for
the practice i just woke up i'm ready to i'm ready to algs
let's be honest how much would have ranked really helped in
this situation we've got to the same team three games it
would have helped so much because i would be practicing
instead of playing other game i was playing anything i was
streaming you know i'll just start underscore a game i was
playing like it's crazy yeah see what was i streaming time
is like non-existent for me now i was playing roblox yeah
instead of playing apex i was playing roblox oh you Wait,
Roblox is this the Apex?
I was playing a visual novel.
And then I was playing Halo.
I was playing a self-park game.
I was playing...
Like, I was playing everything but Apex.
The only time I played Apex was the Nessie Cup and the JP
tournament I did.
There's a tournament.
It's back-to-back.
That's true.
Yeah, for real.
So...
Start the, where the fuck is...
Start without him.
Start without...
Start without that team member.
No, what the fuck, admin?
Tilarious, dude.
We could have had a chance.
We could have.
All right, it would have possibly...
Okay, this really shows me, though, that, like, if we
genuinely just didn't die to team two every game so far,
that we could actually...
We would have made it.
Yeah, without a doubt.
100%.
Because we are literally just...
died to what one point in two games and we're still almost
swamp yeah we're good we're good we got the show let's go we
got the shit i'm ready i'm ready too i'm ready all righty we
go back again i guess too
this is it
this is the game a chat said we're hosting a podcast chat
it's not even a game anymore we're just podcasting who is
this person i'm banning them from a house chat i was just
threatening everyone bro he's all right are we going pylon
right pylon yeah we don't have a beacon we don't have a
beacon again wait wait wait but we can rotate into Jurassic
if no one goes there that's fine that's fine honestly if no
one goes in this direction i might just land Jurassic is
there anyone checkpoint this time there is yeah this team's
going to checkpoint we should definitely drop soon hopefully
these teams are not going there they might be bro if they
are we just serve Jurassic that right that right team looks
like they're going far right yeah they're going to see
though I think this team might be honest here this team
right beside us on the team above us too and the team to our
left I mean Jurassic's free I don't want to contest I
definitely don't want to leave I think of Jurassic that we
address the seams coming out of this Yeah, they're landing
on Pylon.
There's two teams Pylon.
What the fuck?
Do you think that checkpoint team just left and was like,
fuck it?
No, no, I saw them go in there.
We're good.
They're 100% on there.
It would have been nice, though, because they had double
beacon.
We went there.
We're good.
We got the shit.
Let's do it.
I can't scan yet.
No, you can.
You're good.
Yeah, we have ring console, which is literally all we need
for getting these points.
All we need.
We'll see what happens.
Well, a team is definitely going to run at us to get beacon
as well.
We don't have any like things for scan stuff.
Oh my god.
I'll give it a sound.
That's huge for us.
Yeah, I'm going to loot inside here.
It's going to end Cito slash Bean for sure.
I'm going to loot this.
All right.
Sounds good.
We really need an Evo cache.
We don't.
No, we don't.
Yeah, it's so bad.
It's all good, baby.
All good.
We got this.
Where is there?
What's the closest Evo?
Oh my gosh, there's no nothing that's close.
We're going to need you to scan like.
yeah in the boxes then yeah it's gonna be tough when i get
the care package i will but still not gonna get us enough
okay i mean well it's not awful awful i guess just the white
armor is gonna be tough for no evo fine we could rotate
through um maybe i maybe i go over i don't want to go there
now though this is a pile on team i just come through i was
gonna say i probably should have went over to nut and just
got the evo cash over there i could still do it to be honest
should i risk you think or now for what go over here to this
night cash i feel like you should at this point we don't
have anything yeah i think i do too because regardless of
what the fuck happens we're just we're gonna die yeah like
if we don't have yeah wait this guy's routing it they're
routing the evo okay i don't don't this guy was just heck
what's in the evo what the i'm coming back was that person
that had to be a person that's why graphics were fucked up
no yeah that thing's not there anymore uh yeah i just can't
buy pylon too uh we should just start rotating this i'm just
gonna see this dot i don't have an all-break cell for for i
don't excel here i have a note i'll give mine to do you want
me to hold it or you want to use it now um i think we just
do we save it we're fine i think we're gonna walk in a
little bit more we definitely need an evo i mean we can try
and grab this evo it might be hard but yeah i mean but white
armor so to the map because the team's just going to into
everything and there's cedar there's cedar station you know
they're right here too they're moving across right the white
armor is just really rough though yeah well let's just slide
down just play from here maybe try to get some shots for
first before we rotate an actual center sound because you
have nothing to fucking do wait all right all right i mean
let me come back up come back to you guys backing up backing
up the white armor is just so rough man we're gonna get
sandwich here too all right we should actually rotate down
here i think and try to get that evo okay i think you're
right joki just Yeah, you're good.
You guys are fine.
We should be fine.
We have no choice now.
Can we grab that one, blue?
Yeah, we should be fine.
At least we get blue, which is just, at this point, way
better.
That's just better for us in the long run.
Yeah, we're getting fucked over right now, but we're doing
good.
We're fine.
That's what it is.
We don't have a choice.
Let's get this evo cache, and then I think we just literally
play in this building.
Oh, I see a trooper shotgun.
They're right in front of you.
There's a team there.
It's fine.
It's okay.
Let them go.
Maybe we can get the evo when they rotate out.
I'm just going to play in this building for right now.
I'm going in.
Yeah, you're inside.
You're inside, you're out from here.
We're good.
We don't really have a choice.
This team left the evo cache, though.
But there's still a team on the left side.
I don't want to go over there yet.
Barometer team's going far.
Flying up and seeing if I can actually see what they're
doing.
I think of the evo cache.
You guys stay here, right?
I'm going to charge rifle barometer.
Yeah, if I die, then fuck it.
We can...
I mean, we have evac and your alt, use either to try and get
a better position no we definitely want to try to get in
somewhere and get a good spot for zone i got the i got the
evo by the way nice oh that's good good start should we go
to you or yeah there's a top barometer now yeah there's
showing top barometer i don't know so like here's my dilemma
guys like i want to go over there but they're gonna run down
everything from everyone yeah like even with blue armors i
still think they're gonna just fight us regardless yeah
probably purple's which is so fucked what we could do though
is we could hit an ulti side cedar right there over on the
back side i just don't know if it's going to be safe or not
i think it's not my fault i think it's better than being
here right if you want to just stay here and see more teams
dying i think you're saying i think it's gonna be better
over there for sure yeah so i think we just go on roof and
we hear my balcony okay we're here let's try it why not
right okay we gotta make a play for zone here i think we go
all right we're gonna try to get to that front spot and what
happens if there is a team in there there's a team in there
we're dead
Not anyone in here, right?
No one in here.
You don't see them.
I can't see right now.
Nothing's pinging.
Doors open.
We're good.
It's the right side of the door.
Oh, I think.
We're good.
Nice.
King's off the door.
Okay.
We shouldn't get into it.
I just want this team to run down everybody.
That's not us.
Okay.
Where's the best place for this?
Jen?
Jen would probably be like literally right here.
It's a res in front of us too.
Or back here at tempo, to be honest, right here too.
It was really good.
There you go.
That's fine.
away from what's their face yeah and if you can fence the
outside tempo a little bit too instead of inside as well
we'll find our oh yeah do you want the alt excel or do you
want to charge it up passively i think you're good i think i
started the path we're going we live here now all righty i'm
gonna shoot this oh look at us guys we did something good
job thank you for the plus 50.
good job good job good Whoa!
What the fucking shit?
You're good, you're good, you're good, you're good, you're
good, you're good, you're good.
Okay.
Show him.
Not coming down here.
Not going down here.
You're good.
I cracked my top.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I was just looking at the flyers.
Yeah, you're good.
They're white armor.
You're showing me.
John White?
Do we ape those fuckers for shooting us?
No.
We should not ape.
Where did he get shot?
That got shot from behind?
I have no shells, by the way.
Just realize that.
Hey, just, uh, I can show you some.
Yeah.
But I got, I got like...
Open this door.
How about?
all right we shouldn't be thinking too well nice yeah one
point's fine that's good nice wait we just chill yeah we
just buy the out i mean again we just literally can't get
into it on having these guys in your lobby until like the
later rounds it's just an awful experience so we're fine
here's what it is oh wait wait i can shoot those idiots up
there don't get on the room tempo you're on the room get the
fuck off the room tempo get the fuck off the rip they they
jumped off we're good okay i scared them hey fine i'll do it
in here yeah that's fine yeah gigantic football size head me
or you're ducky uh who's i don't know who's bloodhound i
don't know how do you not know i'm bloodhound how do you not
know oh yes yeah they're dirt horizons killing people so
they're right now they're just gonna feed everything all and
we're just good there should be more teams than having zero
points than us for sure which is good but we're the teams
that had who were below us i have no idea i didn't see the
name uh they were like nine and eight and seven nine eight
and seven i don't know if i saw their names yet like like
points oh no they get any amount of points that's not good
for us no no i meant like not is team is a team nine or team
eight oh i have no idea oh okay i thought you meant like no
i thought you meant you know their team numbers because i
could just look at the numbers what do the numbers say
now i actually don't even know where they are
where are you shooting from they're shooting at me yeah but
where you ping them i can look over here oh
hello open open door sesame what the fuck are you doing
tempo i was trying to level up my thingy this man keeps
going outside scare me i know you're fine i know you don't
have a lot of shields dude we have we have multiple jets
yeah we should find a chance thank god yeah thank god it's
all good though i i mean right now i don't really know where
the sound's gonna go i think it's gonna pull towards us
personally but it could pull towards bean as well we'll find
out soon
we'll see you in a little bit a minute do they have they
don't have console oh i feel like i see a lot of teams like
this way that's the scary part They have ring concert.
Oh, my balls.
I'm broke.
I have four cells and no bats.
And one syringe.
So why are we firing?
I can get purple.
Okay, how much more you have?
A thousand.
Dude, okay.
That's only 10 shots.
I have a thousand as well.
Yeah, I'm also still a thousand.
I haven't shot one.
Only 10 shots.
Don't worry.
Here, here, here's a syringe.
I dropped a syringe.
Nice.
Take that syringe, Bigdall.
Oh, you.
He literally told us he had one syringe.
I have a med kit, though.
Hell yeah, you do, baby.
Yeah, you do.
Get that med kit.
Yeah, you do that, baby boy.
This is a podcast.
Yeah, it is really.
Oh, wait.
I saw someone land somewhere.
I'm going to go kill them.
Tell them if you.
If you get an off tempo, I'm never hanging out with you ever
again.
Wait, you were hanging out with it.
Yeah, I can get this kill.
You hang out with him.
No, it's not.
I'm going to pull up and pull.
Once I actually have my building, a recon play here.
Temple, are you shooting someone over in the building?
Oh, they are.
I'm shooting like this way.
So like, I don't want to leave yet, but I can't lie.
A really good play would be taking underneath over here late
game.
Like really late.
There's also a spot in water we can take late game.
If you, I want to leave yet though.
If we go there early, I just don't know what's going to
happen.
13 squads up.
We get out angles so hard.
Sorry, I'm just waiting for your thing to charge me up.
Me too.
Yeah, you're good.
I'm not going to use any of my meds.
I don't want to fight throughout over Jurassic.
If no one comes from Bean's side to fight us, this is
actually really good.
If anyone does come from Bean, we just need to get
aggressive on the slide down from the hill.
That's all we need to do.
September, please just watch your back when you're sling
like that.
If you get killed from Bean, we're dead.
Like, we're just going to get sent on.
I can't really...
He'll scan us.
Okay, that's not good.
This team scans us.
He's going to see we're a full three men by our So just
watch out for being right now.
This is going to be a man.
That's what I'm looking.
Yeah.
That's where we all got to look and we just got to shoot on
the cross down.
And then we just get aggressive on the, oh, they slide down
at all.
Out of the door open, now I'm looking.
They're redeploying.
Okay.
They might just land on us.
Let's see.
I can shoot a lot of ping-a-ma-jig.
I'm going to try to.
Oh, wait.
Where is it?
They're going that way.
That's so good for us.
They're going to go towards that team.
That was, uh, hitting the scan on us.
Let's go gigantic.
How was this team playing top of C though and not getting
shot at at all?
Yeah, just gamers.
They're just gamers.
What can they say?
Yeah, I don't know what to say anymore.
They're just those guys, pal.
I don't know.
We don't have a word for him.
Do I want to throw another gen down here or no?
Yeah, yeah.
I would.
We're going to, you can get it back for the time we need.
And we also have all Dexcel too, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I have eight percent.
Oh, they're shooting from the, yeah, they're shooting from
that way.
They are on Bean.
This team's going to fight us, I think for sure.
Which we have no more charges.
Oh, yeah, we don't okay.
No We do we do and you're just throwing it down now.
I'm gonna I'm gonna control this door and shoot these guys
on top bean All right Watch your back Timber.
We did nice.
Okay.
Good.
That's huge.
That makes me a little bit more confident that the team the
bean team's not gonna fight What the fuck there she has to
top here.
Yeah, that one's really good.
Everyone's very good.
Everyone's very good at the game Everyone's very good at
this.
Yeah, everyone's like right now, man.
I want these guys to leave with their horizon, so I don't
think they're gonna leave.
Team 17 dead, right?
We got one point off placement.
I mean, we've already originally got one point already.
I'm like, what do you mean?
They played the top of the hill still, yeah.
Yeah, they can.
Just let me know what they're doing.
So I'm gonna stare at that.
I'm staring at them.
Look at the sound, bro.
The sound's fucking out.
Where'd we go?
I mean, there's a water spot we could play.
There's over here under the waterfall.
Yeah, we could.
Yeah, I think we might have to go there late, but I don't
know what these guys are gonna do.
They're gonna shoot our fucking falcon.
out well they can't go the other way they have to go to us
yeah i mean they get evac though so we're gonna do late
games we're gonna do late games we're gonna jump out my side
over here okay towards over here and we're gonna we're gonna
eval call the over the backside on this on this okay what's
we're gonna do i'm just gonna wait for the charge i have
zero damage yay i mean we don't have a choice Yeah, I don't
have a time to fucking shoot anything.
These zones have not been great to us at all.
They've not been kind.
All right, you're going to need a gen though?
Oh, they smoke us or what?
Can you see?
I'm going to scan a little.
Yeah, scan a little.
Nice.
Yeah, that's fine.
All right, so we have two options.
I'm just going to keep a lookout.
We're going to try to figure out which option is good.
Just stay on me when I'm flying, okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They're not dropping down.
They're just...
They have to go soon, though.
Yeah, they have to leave.
No, since we see them pop through Evac, we need to take our
Valco at these because they're They're going to shoot us
out.
And once we see those switches.
There's a sign out.
I hit one for 80.
I hit purple 80.
Can I hit the scan when you can?
Do the scan when you can?
Why are they crying out again?
That's fine.
Oh my god, I'm getting shot from behind.
It's fine, it's fine.
I'm over the door.
Okay.
I don't scan.
I want to scan.
One kill one.
I want to kill one.
Oh, I got I'm full kill.
I full killed.
On my door.
I'm a door.
Why are you killing us?
You're so bad at the game?
We're good?
Medding.
Play slow.
We're gonna be dead here though.
We have to kill these guys.
I'm trying to figure out where they are.
Okay, okay, okay, I'm here, me, me, me, me.
Slow, play slow.
Anybody else going down.
Play slow.
Don't eat the Bengali.
We're good.
They're nading us now too.
We have to go.
Go, go, go.
See me out right side.
Try to get your kills.
That's a different, that's a different.
Oh, it's a whole nother squad.
That's a whole nother squad.
What?
We got eight though.
Wait, do we get any kills?
We got one.
We got three points.
Where did these come from?
This might be possible.
It might be possible.
Three points.
I just cannot believe this team's fighting us, bro, instead
of evacking.
What are you doing?
I don't think they had an evack.
I don't know if the challenges are against.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
My brain hurts a little bit today.
I can't lie.
We should.
We definitely should have left.
We found their evack.
I don't think they had an evack.
I don't even know, but we played that.
We actually played that correctly, because we just need a
valkalty late there, and we just get sent on by a stupid
team.
Yeah, I didn't realize there was a second team behind us.
I mean, that was the top-side Seedos team.
There's no reason for them to do that either.
That makes no sense.
They died for it.
Yeah, they tied the fight.
I mean, this just proves my theory that CC is just horrible.
What do you watch, party?
Yeah.
I mean, no, final round of CC's gift, but Jesus Christmas.
Too many teams out here thinking they're Aurora or fucking
TSM.
Unfortunately, I mean, what, three points?
There's a chance, like a small chance there's a chance it
really depends it sucks that team two actually died though
because we needed them to go crazy and kill off the teams it
was because they died that teams were still alive i mean we
got eight we have a point yeah we'll figure it out here
we'll see damn if we got that valkalty off i think we could
have played that spot that i wanted to two it sucks so guys
it's okay that meant that means that we per if we don't make
it the next round we purposely through so that we could play
more to get there and next week we get round three which is
not that hard we improved yeah yeah yeah yeah we get to like
yeah it just means that we we we just wanted to spend more
time together as the besties so we could yeah we just love
each love and i just we just wanted sunday we love each
other so much wow we also did not want to stream on sunday
so that's why we purposely threw today yep exactly we didn't
want to stream tomorrow we're so smart guys i think it's not
over yet though i think we still could it's gonna be really
low i think we have to get to one place not ninth i think
like uh if we didn't get run at twice in a row that time.
If we just did not get sent on two times, very
coincidentally, by the best team in the lobby, it probably
went great for us.
The team we died to is relax.
So they're in four, so this is good.
We died to a team that was above us.
Okay.
What about the team's alive right now?
Who's Varden?
Yeah, who's this team that I'm looking at?
Yeah, yeah.
They're team four.
Varden, team 10?
no team 10 team 10 is oh i don't know what i don't know what
that team numbers are this team just moment by 30 kills so
hopefully it's a really good team you can see when you open
seven let's see and 11 and 12.
wait what happened no i'm saying we were we were we were
tied with 10 11 and 12 before we're going into this game oh
that's scary that's scary
we got 12.
we were four points away we had two games of just like two
more points we would have been fine die to those guys three
times more oh man it is what it is guys you know it is what
it is ggs everybody ban from all n a man nice wig bot gg you
say it type that thing type it i typed it those uh for ellie
boys they're all banned from all na events now oh my god i
might be a bad influence i don't know oh my god guys am i
bad influence guys oh yeah you know what i'm in next week
though actually though yeah yeah let's run it back next week
i'm in I'm in.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm in next week, guys.
We practiced this week.
And then on top of that all, okay, we figured out a comp
that's good for us as well.
We'll figure that out too.
I agree.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was a feeler.
It was a feeler week.
Yeah, we were just figuring stuff out, you know.
Exactly.
You get it.
You show get it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know what?
I'm glad I didn't have to play six out.
I know what?
I'm actually kind of glad, too.
yeah i don't worry i'll be locked in next week next week
i'll be locked in for six hours i still feel around guys
yeah yeah we're just feeling it out we didn't know how it
was gonna be also someone make my liquipedia now because i i
went and i i was in an official that was an official
tournament so technically yeah i want my liquipedia now and
anyone the person that keeps removing my liquipedia you
can't remove it anymore because challenges circuit is legit
yeah exactly we're mad okay guys i gotta head out for dinner
that was all right ggs guys yeah we run it back or run it
back next week next week i'm down isn't tell me the one on
the 13th i think so okay yeah 13 13 14 yeah 13 14 i should
be i should be able to play 100 i'm like not 100 sure i can
all right wait let's just let us know uh ggs guys i have
these guys love y'all man hey listen listen don't call it a
come back because we never left guys all right yeah yeah we
had very look we exceeded our expectations because i didn't
think we were going to get past round one i'm with you as
well i'm the same thing so we exceeded expectations all
right well ggs guys love y'all man all right ggs everybody
bye bye bye that was fun 10 minutes chat but you guys see
this in 10 minutes um you know it's
rest it's secretly a blessing in disguise for me uh but ggs
everybody i honestly i had a uh i had a great time um
playing with wig and tempo and um and we're gonna see we all
be doing it next week we'll be we'll see uh but as always
everybody uh stay hydrated posture check up and move around
to get that blood flowing and if you suffer me head to bed
because you deserve it I'll see you guys next time everybody
bye guys bye I hope I do the fucking the delay thing always
fucks me up I don't know how to do it properly like ending
this delay stuff but I hope I don't accidentally end it in
the middle of the game and you guys are gonna be like what
but we'll see you're gonna see in 10 minutes bye