Alright, we're live.
We're live now.
My YouTube, Doki Bird.
Yeah, is... yeah.
Yeah, I think that's how YouTube... I don't know.
You look up Doki Bird, that's where I am.
Not a kid's channel.
I just hope I don't get flagged as a kid's channel.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, okay.
Don't change my game to Roblox.
This is not a kid's channel.
Children leave.
You're not welcome here, you fucks.
My Roblox account got banned.
Wait, your Roblox account got... what did you do?
My main Roblox account, I tried to log in to add you and it told me that my main Roblox account got banned for a bad username.
Wait, when was the last time you used Roblox?
I don't even know.
It told me March 20th.
So like a week ago they banned me.
I don't...
What did you do a week ago?
I don't know how they fucking like sniffed me out, but they told me I couldn't have the name ass.
Okay, to be fair, how did you get away with ass?
You can't even say like... you can't even say like woman in Roblox without...
You can't say women?
Wait, okay, can you say woman with an E or woman with an A?
Not an E?
You can't say either.
You can't say... women don't ex... you're right, women don't even exist in video games, you're right.
They're so true.
So true, Roblox.
What?
Guys, you know that women aren't real in video games.
Oh my god.
Women literally aren't even in video games.
Yeah.
They're not... they're not real.
Women aren't real.
I got the censor block.
Behind every Vtuber is a man.
It's true.
With a voice changer.
They were right.
They were always right.
Everybody who appears at cons, yeah, those are hired.
Hired women who pretend to know.
Hired women who pretend to know about video games and Vtubers.
Yeah, you want to catch one and just walk up to them and be like okay, so you're a girl, huh?
You're a paid actor.
A paid actor.
Yeah, paid actor.
Yeah, yeah.
You...
Yeah.
You're a character.
What's your favorite Pokemon game in the Pokemon series?
Name three starters from Pokemon Diamond and Pearl.
In your opinion, what was the most based Pokemon protagonist?
In your opinion, would you smash your past, Guard of War?
Only women can answer this question.
Only women can really discern the popularity difference between a Lopunny and a Guard of War.
What is the... what is... which Pokemon has the egg type to...
Which Pokemon is sexually compatible based on egg type?
And if they can't even answer that, they're not real women.
Your maternal instincts should give you the answer already.
Oh!
So true.
Only a real... real man behind a VTuber can guess.
God, we've just started.
Ten minutes.
We've gone so far.
Oh, oh, oh, Doki, did you... did you learn to do the... the... the collab thing where you're like both on the screen together?
I don't know, have you done that one?
I've done that before, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I always like to do that, but I don't know...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we can do that.
You can set it up, because I'm lazy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm like, okay, I think I just need to add you on Steam if that's okay.
Oh, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, let me grab my code.
It's okay, guys.
We're...
In your digits.
Now you guys can listen to us set up this so much more professional...
You got... you got Roblox installed already, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I got the... wait, we had to install Rob... what?
Okay, well, it's like... it's like a browse... it's like a launcher.
So basically when you click play, it's just... it'll like boot up a window.
Oh!
It's not really like a program, but you do kind of have to do like a little bit of a download.
Okay, yeah, that's fine.
I have fiber.
We should be good.
Oh, nice.
She got those optic cables.
Yeah, I was like... I was like, you have to download... I thought it was a browser game.
What?
I think it used to be, but they have... they definitely have their own little like program now.
Okay, let me... let me add y'all.
I think like the saddest thing I've ever heard about Roblox was when they got rid of the oof sound, because it got copyrighted.
I forgot that that happened.
That's so sad.
That's when Roblox fell off.
That's when...
That's when Roblox went downhill.
I live in the constant like realization that like all games these days just mimic Roblox.
Like all these games, I'm like, this is just Roblox.
Like Fortnite.
Wait, really?
Like what?
That's simply Roblox.
Like, like, you know that new one that's come out?
Like Content Warning or like...
Oh yeah!
Content Warning!
I wanted to try it out.
I haven't played it yet.
Oh we should play it sometime.
I haven't played it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah me too.
I really want...
My friend linked me to... One of my friends linked me to one of the Content Warning videos where...
Where... Oh, no, they deleted the link!
Oh no they didn't!
Where it was like they were... It was... How do I explain it?
Ashley, it's nothing you explain.
I'm going to link it to you.
What does this look like to you?
And...
What does this look like?
What is that?
Can you explain?
He's the only thing about the class.
Oh dear lord!
Can you explain to the class what I sent you?
Holy matrimony!
This is what I'm about to do to you guys' wives.
Oh my god!
I disappeared because my Steam was like, we have to restart your Steam.
Goodbye everybody!
I'm gone from the screen.
Alright guys, look.
Thank god I am playing a game that's totally not for children because what I'm gonna link in chat is not appropriate.
Just so you guys know, what I'm about to link to the chat is hella inappropriate.
It's simply how the children are made.
So I hope there actually is no kids.
Cause I'd get in that.
Especially when I'm playing Roblox!
Anyway, this is what I sent Snuffy.
Enjoy!
I'm gonna be using this one for a while.
Woah!
Well yes.
Aren't you guys excited for content warning the game?
I don't know anything about it so this is just even more like how did we get here?
Apparently it's like lethal company but like what if you're doing it all for content?
Like it's...
That's what it was!
Yeah!
It was made to be a streaming game.
It's literally lethal company but like you film sh- it's like let's do it for the vine, you know?
That type of shit.
Yeah, do it for the vine!
Yeah, do it for the vine, the video game.
Exactly.
Watch your friends jump and be like, yeah!
Woohoo!
And you can die!
Apparently you can die too because you know.
You're doing it for the vine!
Alright, what do I- how do I join you?
Oh yeah, did you add me?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I added you.
Okay...
Am I not popping up on the screen?
Oh there I am.
Wait a minute, okay, welcome to the- so okay, so blah blah blah, do you use- you use spout capture?
Uh, I used... what?
Spout?
Sorry!
When you do OBS streaming with VTube Studio, do you use spout capture or do you just use like a game capture?
Game capture, yeah.
I was like, what the fuck is spout?
Maybe hide your model so you don't like show any information then.
Okay, okay.
So like if you click your little side button, like the items in the background, does that appear on your stream and stuff?
The little buttons?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I hit it.
Guys, I'm gonna be gone for a little bit, give me a sec.
Give me a sec.
You should check that out.
Spout capture.
Spout capture is fucking amazing.
Like literally, it hides all the UI for VTube Studio and it runs way better.
I 100% recommend it.
Okay, I'm gonna write that- I'm gonna rewatch this bot because I'm not gonna write this down.
Okay.
Timestampers!
I gotta set a password.
Timestampers, if you're gonna post my timestamps in my YouTube comments, remember to write this one down and put it in all caps and bold it if you can.
Just so I can remember to watch this part.
Okay.
Okay, so it should be... wait, what did I make the password?
I'm gonna add you to something and then you just have to put in the password and I think that's...
Alright, nice.
Password is empty.
Also, like, one of my dragoons was like, my favorite description of Content Warning is basically, Lethal Company, but you are Jake Paul.
Oh, gosh.
I heard he's like, boxing some- wait.
I forgot the other one.
The other one?
Okay, sorry, like- There's two of them, right?
Yeah, yeah.
I like how even you're like, wait, was there two of them?
There might be more!
How many Pauls are there?
Was it two?
Jake?
John?
I'm just naming, like, the Beatles at this point.
Paul?
Okay, to be fair, they all like, they both lured together for me because they both like, do the same thing now.
One- except for one owning- one owns an energy drink and is like, spon- like, is sponsoring a fucking basketball team now.
Prime or whatever.
Yeah, yeah, Prime.
I got Prime.
Have you ever tried it?
No.
Have you ever tried any of the, like, content creator- like, did you ever try the pink whatever or the pink juice or something?
The pink?
Pink sauce?
Dude, was that pink?
Oh, the pink sauce!
That wasn't content creator.
That was just some...
Oh.
Some- some fucking- Like, a famous person or something?
No, it was just some TikToker who tried to mail, like, sauce.
Like, you never heard of it?
What do you mean?
Like, like, okay, it was just some TikToker who got viral because she made, like, you know, pink sauce.
And then she was, like, mailing, like, the sauce in, like, just a fucking envelope to people.
Like, there was no cooling or anything.
She just mailed a fucking bottle of sauce to people.
Yeah, she just mailed it to random- to, like, random people.
So, like, the sauce was, like, dripping out or exploded and it was like- Wait, no, because I've seen it- I've seen it at, like, Target.
Yeah, yeah, and then, like, some fucking sauce company bought- bought the brand.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, they're like, wait.
I'm John Sauce and I need this on my shelf.
Wait a minute.
We- the pink sauce.
That's- that's what we need.
The booth says it just needed to be pink.
Next, they're gonna make the sauce blue so they can make his and her sauce.
So- And then- and then the her sauce is like- Gender reveal sauce.
Yeah, yeah, and then the her sauce is, like, five dollars more expensive even- because it's pink.
I'm talking about the pink tag.
Yeah, yeah.
I like the gender- gender reveal, like, barbecue party.
What gender is your kid?
Grab your his and her sauce today.
Hey.
I'm talking about my wedding and- and please make sure that the his and her sauce is there.
Yeah, yeah.
My dream wedding.
Please.
I need to be sure that the women use the pink sauce and the men use the blue sauce.
What do you mean there's no his and her ketchup anymore?
I use the Shrek ketchup.
She uses the purple ketchup.
I don't remember what- What is purple ketchup?
But I forget, like, what- We're quirky.
What the media was.
We don't- we don't- we're quirky.
We use the Shrek and- the Shrek and purple sauce.
What is the purple ketchup?
There was a purple- there was a purple ketchup, right?
There was a purple ketchup?
Purple ketchup?
I know about the green ketchup.
I think there was.
It was the easy squirt.
Heinz easy squirt.
Oh.
Wait, I'm gonna send you the picture of it.
What a great name.
I feel like it'll hit you like a rock.
Like, look at this.
What an amazing name.
Oh!
That looks disgusting!
That actually looks disgusting.
They make green and purple but not pink and blue.
It's literally right there.
Yeah, those are like the more, like, muddied colors of just, like, chaos.
Like, I don't know.
Like, what?
Oh, so guys, I'm gonna disappear again because Snuffy sent me the thingy.
But, like, what?
Who thought green and purple was, like, the colors to do when pink and blue was right there?
Like, why did they- What, you think pink and blue is more appetizing?
Like, what is the tastiest color?
Okay, and green is- okay, and green is much better.
You try to say green is- Green is like vegetables and stuff, you know?
No, you don't- Like, you don't want to have green sauce.
Like, what?
That's a fair name.
Delicious tomatillo.
Oh my god, they let some random TikToker get ahead of them.
I literally- how come you guys never invented food coloring before?
I know.
I need- I need- oh, man.
Would you drink from the, like, the cursed orange dye Garfield cup?
The Boolean?
The radioactive Garfield cup?
The ra- yes, because it's Garfield.
I mean, like, okay, it's just a little- as long as I don't build it up, you know?
As long as I don't- Don't- don't do it continuously.
It should be fine, right?
Do it contin- Yeah.
I don't know.
Like, as- you know, you- you have one.
You can, like, expose yourself to radiation, like, once or some- It's- it's like a freebie?
Yeah, like a freebie.
Like, a scratch off, like, one free radioactive explosion.
Yes, exactly.
What?
Yes.
Yes!
As long- okay, it's like a- it's like a- a Bestos, you know?
Like- Bestos?
Yeah, like, you know, when you're exposed to Bestos, you get- you know, you get cancer?
You get lung cancer?
But!
If you- you- if you don't continuously expose yourself, you'll be fine.
You just, you know, go into, like, the house, like, for, like, five seconds, you'll be okay.
Is that how it works?
You're gonna fucking die.
I'm so worried.
It's like- it's like, as long as you don't breathe in all of it.
If you breathe it in, God himself descends upon you and he's like, that's okay too.
Look, bananas have radiation!
It proves my theory!
What?
Bananas have radiation in them!
That's not radiation, that's calcium!
No, no, no, you didn't know that?
Bananas have a little bit of radiation.
No, calcium.
Wait, what?
Okay, now you're coping.
Now you're- Hey, what?
There's no, like, I get California notifications saying that everything I eat has lead in it.
Why would they not tell me if bananas have fucking radiation?
It's just a little bit.
That's what I'm saying!
As long as it's just a little bit of radiation, it's fine.
A little bit of radiation as a treat.
Yeah, it's just a little, you know, a little treat.
See?
So it's like, it's so tiny.
The drought is so fucking tiny.
But if you eat like a hundred thousand bananas, maybe it's not- maybe then it gets a bit worse!
Maybe it's a thousand bananas and then you'll die of rain.
You know, it's like- Also, how does fucking- I don't cat connect to this fucking- Wait, okay.
Let me, let me, let me, let me walk you through it.
So you click the bottom button, you click the little group of dudes, the three little men saying the same thing.
Yeah, yeah, I joined you.
Yeah, join me.
You type in the password and the name so you see, like, I have the password.
Yeah.
And then there's the person name.
What does it say?
It says- Is it loading or something?
It just says like- it just puts me in the connecting forever and I have like- Oh, oh my god, I had to like start it.
Oh!
Oh my god.
I know you wanted to talk about radiated foods, but...
My brain is fried.
I was gonna say, isn't it funny if you- if with that logic you could like sprinkle a little bit of radiation on each of your foods?
It's like a treat.
Okay, but like the thing is- It would have helped me 100,000 bananas.
I said you get one.
Now you're trying.
Well, imagine if you separate it and you make it into a fraction so one banana, you could still have like a fraction of that banana.
Yeah, yeah, for bananas.
Yeah.
I feel like you'll die by the time you get radiation from bananas.
I think- I think it's fine.
Like, you- Oh, I thought you meant you were gonna die from the radiation.
No, no, no.
There's no way- You buy before- You buy bananas in your lifetime to get radiation poisoning.
That's why- that's why I'm saying if there was a Garfield cup like that's filled with radiation, I get one.
As long as I don't- as long as I don't pass the threshold to get radiation, we're fine.
It was enough radiation to make sure it was like never sold again though.
Like, I think maybe it was a lot.
Okay, but- but that happened like a long time ago.
Did anyone die from the Garfield cup?
No.
So we're fine.
If the people back then didn't die from the Garfield cup, I would be okay.
Also, like, did you start the thing?
Cause I still can't get- I think it's loading.
Oh, it's an invalid password.
What?
Wait, so I didn't fuck it up.
You fucked it up.
Are you- did you put the password in correctly?
No, I did.
I- what do you mean?
Okay, let me- let me- let me try again.
Guys, we're professional streamers.
Snuffy has been streaming... maybe even longer than me.
My stream anniversary is on 420.
I'll be streaming for four years.
Oh dear.
I'm old.
Snuffy has been using this app definitely longer than me.
Okay, okay.
Try now.
See if that works.
Please, please.
Is everything correct?
No, it says I got disconnected.
Wrong password.
Okay, I- am I getting- What?
Are you- are you using the right password?
I- I think- Wait, there's no password in there.
Oh, wait.
I didn't put the password in.
You- I didn't put the password in!
I'm gonna force you to drink five cups of Garfield cup today.
Guys, I didn't- I didn't realize I had to insert a password, guys.
I'm connecting.
I'm in.
You just put the right password in and you're like, simply I put it in right.
And you didn't even know I put in the password!
I just put the name, you know, the- the Doki Snuffy.
Can't be wrong if I never inserted that password.
Yeah, exactly.
Can't be wrong if I never put in that password, guys.
Oh my- I'm glad, like, we're on the same wavelength here.
It's not my fault.
No, it's- it's just flip-flop between, like, who fucked- Oh my god, Joki jumpscare!
Wait, where are you?
Oh shit, there you are!
Okay.
Okay, wait, how do I do this?
Start- How do I- Ruffjohn, bring your bottle from the- Okay, so if you left click, you'll be in front.
Yeah, right- if you right click, you won't be in front.
So I can, like, maybe- Okay.
Alright, here we go.
We're figuring this out.
We're figuring- Okay.
Wait, I should be taller.
Oh yeah?
How can- canonically, are you tall?
Are you a tall one?
I'm, like, eight feet tall.
Wait, wait, wait!
Okay.
Oh wow, Joki, hi!
Alright, alright, yeah, yeah, this is- this is canon hype, by the way, guys.
Just-
Holy shit!
Wait, that means you're, like, seven feet- you're not seven feet, you're smaller.
Oh my god, I'm literally- There, there, that feels right.
Am I?
Yeah.
I'm not on my screen anymore.
That's right, this is my stream now.
Oh god.
Okay, here we go.
We're doing this.
It only took us a while, but we figured- guys, we're only 25 minutes- actually, no, we're only 30 minutes late, guys.
It's okay.
I think it's been- I think it's been great.
This is a mid-40.
Yeah, it's- this is fine, guys.
We're only 30 minutes late.
But look at the content.
Now you know about radiation and bananas.
Yeah, nice.
Watch your banana intake, guys.
Yeah, yeah.
And to all you kids out there who's watching me, get the fuck out.
Yeah, and your banana intake as well, kids.
Yeah.
It's not a joke, it's serious.
Yeah, eat as many bananas as you want, you won't get radiation poisoning.
If you see Garfield on a cup, just walk away.
No, just take one sip and you'll be fine, you get one.
Take one and drink.
We all get one, you know?
We all get to pick our radiation.
Would that be like your final?
Like if you were on like death row and they're like, you get one last meal.
I want the Garfield.
Pour me a fresh cup.
Give me that Garfield cup.
I want all the food blended into the Garfield.
I wanna know what radiation tastes like.
I wanna know the Garfield in red 40.
Okay.
You didn't- you know that like-.
The reason why Garfield- the Garfield cup was filled with radiation was because of the color orange.
Yeah, yeah, cause it was like a- I don't know which combination- poisonous color of orange?
It was like orange and green are like- you need like radiation to make- to make orange and green back then.
Cause that happened for Star Wars too.
Where like they had to recall a bunch of Star Wars cup because it had like orange and green in it.
Oh, what- we- Like- oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, C-3PO.
Was it like a C-3PO cup?
I have no idea.
I just remember- I just remember they had to recall a bunch of Star Wars cup.
Cadmium.
They're forbidden colors.
I think it's like cadmium.
I'm on- I'm on a- I'm on Know Your Meme.
Hey, guys remember that funny meme when people and kids were getting exposed to radiation?
So fucking hilarious.
This picture says- 1978 Garfield.
It's not a pretty life, but somebody has to live it.
McDonald's mug.
99,000 ppm lead causes brain damage plus 5,830 ppm cadmium causes cancer.
So it actually wasn't even just cancer.
You also get brain damage if you drink Garfield cup.
Okay, but like how many- but like how much do you have to drink though?
Like what?
What's the limit before I get brain damage?
It's really close to cancer.
Like does one sip give you brain damage or was it like, you know, several cups?
Like we didn't know the numbers here.
I feel like we should just- we can- we can just have this like test for ourselves.
Like I'm surprised nobody's like- That's who you wanted to drink.
People wanted to drink the Garfield cup.
It's okay.
That sounds like- It's content.
Content for- Yeah, it's content.
Monday's in my right.
April Fools, happy Monday.
I'm gonna drink five glasses of Garfield cadmium.
You know like those like YouTube videos where they're like taste- they're like a tier list of which cup has the most radiation.
Radioactive glassware tier list.
That sounds incredible.
That's actually incredible.
It did.
Tier list radioactive glassware.
It does the most radiation.
Come and find out as we taste each radiated cup.
I'm like swirling it around like we're trying wine like, oh yeah, this one really resonates with me.
Yeah, I can taste the lid already.
I can feel my brain like fuzzing up.
And then like somebody get the- those fucking like radiation testing machines and then like beep beep beep beep.
The Geiger counter.
Yeah, the Geiger counter.
They're like, alright, gotcha.
Let's see how much radiation this cup has.
Beep beep beep beep beep beep.
Even if it's like Fallout, we gotta have like the Fallout like rad noise of just like .
Even if it's like a wood pipe.
Like, oh my god.
I can feel the lead already eroding my lungs.
I think that's like an S tier right there.
What you think, Snuffy?
Do you think the lead tastes like it does?
Like, did you ever eat like pencil lead?
No, what?
What?
Excuse me?
Look, I thought we were acting.
Now I'm not too sure.
Is this- is this acting?
Is this- are we still- are we-
Could you- could you explain your story?
You- you never- you never- No, no.
Judging by my reaction, absolutely.
Judging by my reaction, what do you think?
I- I thought maybe it was a formative experience for many people.
You know, when you're said school and you're bored, maybe your pencil broke and you're like, oh, the lead is just- it fell out.
You know, it used to just like crack and I don't even remember what possessed me to do it, but I feel like I was like, well, let me just- let me just eat it.
Sample.
I mean, it's like eating a Tic Tac.
It was like really simple.
It was not salty.
It was like sour almost, like very chemically.
Oh my God.
People talk about glue eaters, but you're a fucking lead eater.
Sure.
Yeah, dude, I used to like lick it too.
After like I started eating it, I used to like- every time I used to start writing with a pencil, I would like lick it.
I would like suck.
I feel like you're- you would be like one of those students, my mom would be like, you shouldn't hang out with her.
I swear like I saw people in like movies.
They always like writers like lick their pen or something.
They like dab their pen, I think to like get the ink flowing, but I didn't understand what that meant.
So I would just start like doing that with like pencils.
So I would just like dab the pencil onto my- What?
I mean like, I- I- that's- but like you- you actively consume the graphite.
Don't you act- Yeah.
Yeah.
The wood do.
I just kind of started gnawing on all parts of it.
I think I got a little bit of the paint as well.
Chewing on- You know, I think you are the perfect person for the tier list.
Yeah, yeah.
We should just have like a toxic product tier list.
Where do you think we should put the- What was that?
The recalled products tier list.
The cursed consumer reports.
What's the best tasting recalled food?
Should they recall it?
I'm so in love.
I'm gonna be like- It'll be like- It'll be like- So, it will be like- By our judgment, yes, they definitely should have recalled it.
It can be one of them YouTube videos where it's like- No, you have to guess which one is which.
And we'll be like okay, this one is definitely the recalled.
I can taste- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
What- Five items are on the table.
Three have been recalled.
It is up to Snuffy and Doki to find out which three were recalled.
We'll pick one.
For containing leeeen.
You're like, I'm gonna get emails reaching out to me like, you know what, I think you'd be great for factory work.
Do you wanna like test some of our product going out?
Like you wanna be taste testing.
Like the product testing.
Quality insurance.
You get paid for that too!
I know, maybe I get benefits.
Thank god.
I like how we have yet to play Roblox.
Yeah, maybe there's cadmium tasting Roblox games.
Hey guys, you guys like this black screen?
Oh my god, we are distracted.
It all started with the Garfield Cup.
I don't even know how it started.
You know there's like, you can actually buy radiation items in like, like those like, what is it, those donation stores?
Like Goodwill?
What?
Like, is that what they're called in America?
The Goodwill stores?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, the second hand stores.
Cause like, there was a YouTube short.
I get all my information from YouTube shorts nowadays.
But like...
But like, there's this like, channel that gets like a Geiger County.
And they go to like, Goodwill.
And they like, find all the items that has like, uranium in there.
Dude, oh my god.
I actually...
Okay, so I actually probably have something that's good for this.
Because...
Good for...
Good for poisoning myself.
When I became like, independent, I was like, you know what?
A big thing about becoming an adult is, is like, owning plates.
Yeah.
So I went to like, a secondhand store to buy some plates.
And I was like, oh man, these ones are so cute.
And they're like, vintage.
That's so cool.
That should have been a warning sign.
My plates are from like, 1938.
Good.
Like, Googled it.
I was like, oh yeah, what kind of plates are these?
And it told me that like, they're at like, high risk.
Like, anything 1950 or earlier is like, do not consume.
Because it's probably filled with lead.
You know.
So I've got like, tons of lead.
You have tons of...
Wait, have you...
Wait, you've actually consumed lead?
No, no.
Well, I mean, other than from the pencil, I'm then too afraid to use them.
I feel like I'll just have to serve it to my greatest enemy.
Oh, so they're just there for decoration type deal.
Yeah, yeah.
I bought like, a whole set.
And now I'm like, too nervous to ever eat from them.
But maybe I should like, eat your right in like, a little glass.
Okay, how many subs?
Oh my god, before the FTA was even fucking invented.
Holy shit, I'm gonna be good, dude.
I'm good, I'm great.
A British would suspend you if you had to.
I mean, I would consider that like, self harm.
Like that Twitch ban on a Twitter account.
Snuffbee has been banned.
Oh no.
That'd be way better than half of the bans though.
I'd be so proud if I got banned from drinking from a lead glass rather than like, showing ass.
I'd break the norm for VTubers in school.
No, I had the first VTuber to get banned for fucking drinking lead.
That's incredible honestly.
I'm so sorry.
I'm just blowing the track record for VTubers.
Oh man, there's a first for everything and I'm here to see it, dude.
Guys, just remember, if you think you have a plate that's really, really old, maybe don't use it.
Because most likely back then, they used lead or uranium to make the glass wet.
Is uranium the green one?
There's another green one, right?
Yeah, uranium's the green one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, okay.
Because I was wondering, that's the one where they...
Oh yeah, people go to the secondhand store.
And they have like the light, right?
Have you seen those?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
They shine the light and see if it...
I did that because they had a couple of them.
And I was like, I kind of want that.
I feel like that'd be fun.
You never know when Superman might show up and you got to like neutralize him.
Yeah, neutralize Superman.
Because of the weakness.
The green crystal.
The green...
The kryptonite?
You mean the kryptonite?
That's insane.
Bro, you're right.
I didn't do anything to Superman.
It's fucking kryptonite.
Look, they might both be green, but they're not the same thing.
I thought that was real.
His dog is named Krypto.
Why would you name your dog like your weakness?
Like, gone.
Like, imagine naming your cat like...
This is like the most badass thing ever.
Because it's like, this is the only thing that can hurt me.
Okay.
Oh my God.
I mean, I would name my dog Gun.
I think that's cool.
That's cool.
Where's my Gun?
That's what I was looking for.
Gun, come here.
Spit, Gun.
Are they like naming also like people who name their pets after like, real people named?
Like, if you name your dog like Jerry or something.
That's an awful name for your dog.
You're an idiot.
Where's Jerry?
It's something you're talking about like you don't know where your stepdad is.
Aw man, where'd Jerry go?
I miss that guy.
But it's like an eight year old fucking like beagle walking in and being like...
He's like, who's a good boy Jerry?
You're my good boy Jerry, that's right.
Oh my god.
Roblox, right?
Oh yeah, Roblox.
Anyway, what's the first Roblox game you're gonna take me?
Guys, I've only managed to play two Roblox games or maybe three.
Oh yeah, I played Hospital RP.
Oh yeah, we lost a little... that's my favorite one.
That's your favorite?
I played Hospital RP, Doors, and the Warrior Cats roleplay.
Okay, okay.
So like, Snuffy apparently is like a professional when it comes to Roblox.
She has two accounts.
I have my personal account for my formative experiences and then I have my work account for my business expenses.
Business expenses.
You go to your tax guy and you're like...
And I spent $50 here for Roblox.
But it's a business expense because it was for stream.
Yeah, that's how I felt about my gacha games.
It's like my accountant would be like, okay, can I see your bank statements?
And I'd just be like, listen, if you see $500 for Cookie Run Kingdom, then like, just close them.
Just so you know, I streamed the content so it was a business expense.
This was for stream.
I was planning this for a sponsor.
It was work related.
I see.
Okay, so most engaging on the list.
So just let me know if you see a game that interests you at all.
Because, you know, Roblox is pretty fun.
I like it a lot for just being able to like hop in, hop out, be like, oh, you know, this was fun to try.
Let's try something else.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you see something that catches your interest, let me know.
We've got some classics.
Natural Disaster Survival is a great game.
Super fun.
But it's not cursed.
What are you looking for?
What's your interest?
Okay, you know what?
Surprise me.
Like, you're the expert here.
You're supposed to take me to this, like, wild tour.
Like, oh my gosh, you're like my pixie manic girl.
And you're gonna take me to like the...
Your pixie manic girlfriend takes you to raise a Peter on Roblox.
There you go.
My life changed when I met my pixie manic girlfriend.
Okay, okay.
Bro, you have the hairstyle.
You're the pixie manic guy from Berserk.
That's what I can't stop hearing.
Everybody's like, oh, nice Griffith hair, bro.
What the fuck is a Griffith?
Bro, what the fuck is a Griffith?
What is a Griffith?
The only thing I know about Berserk is the... is that scene.
I should laugh about that scene.
What scene?
The only thing I know about Berserk is that scene.
Because it's so fucked up.
It's that scene.
Everyone, people who know about Berserk knows exactly what scene I'm talking about.
I don't know anything about Berserk other than there's a guy named Griffith.
And then people say I look like Griffith.
And then somebody said my Final Fantasy 14 character looked like Casca.
That's all I know.
What the fuck are all these people?
And then Guts.
Just a guy.
I just...
I just know about the horse.
The horse.
Yeah, everybody in chat is saying the horse.
Yes.
The horse.
That's the...
No, no, you would not be laughing when you know what that scene is.
It's so fucked up.
I like horse related content.
Would this be good or bad?
Okay, what do you think?
If people are like, oh no, a horse.
What there's... where does your mind go to?
My little pony?
Okay.
That's the other spectrum.
What's the other side of that?
And what's the other...
So in the face of this keyboard.
Here you sit.
That's the fucking pony spectrum.
That's one... that's like one end.
That's the left side.
Where do you think the right side of that other side is regarding horses?
Actually, I shouldn't.
I don't feel like I should be talking about this.
Just so you know, it's not...
There's a lot of ways that I could be worried right now.
That's... that's not... it's not a good scene.
I'll just say it's definitely not appropriate for Roblox.
That's for sure.
Do not... do not search it up.
Mads, don't put me in Roblox.
Don't put me in the Roblox category.
They're not ready for me.
They're not ready.
Just so you know, we're playing games and demos.
Oh my god!
Okay guys, I know we haven't started the Roblox stream.
You know, like, Twitch contacted me to like headline one of their Twitch rivals.
Oh yeah?
And then like...
What is... what is this stat?
Cause like, they saw my schedule and they were like, yo, Doki.
Do you wanna headline the Roblox Twitch Rivals?
So Roblox Twitch Rivals is like just fucking inviting?
I was like, who are you gonna play?
Are you gonna play the shooting game?
Bro, I don't fucking know.
They were like, they were like, do you wanna headline the Roblox Twitch Rivals?
And I was like, bro, I don't play Twitch... I don't play Roblox.
That's so fucking funny.
Oh, you should headline!
That's fucking fantastic!
No, no, you know what?
You might get a lot of children from that.
That's not a good idea.
Yeah, that might be wrong audience.
When worlds collide.
I said it was screenshot.
I don't wanna play this game, but it keeps... it's on the front page and I really don't like...
The Twilight Daycare?
Wait, is this where we're like babysitters?
Are we gonna...
There's like 20 babysitter games.
Oh no.
I'll take you to the best one.
Okay, okay, okay.
Alright.
Tell me when.
Guys, the Roblox content starts now for real.
I'll take you to the first one.
This one's a classic.
I know a lot of people will probably be wanting this one.
Cause it's just so good.
So this is Raise a Peter.
Raise a Peter.
Oh, I heard about this game!
You raised Peter Griffin!
Yeah, yeah!
Oh my god, now you'll finally experience it.
If Peter stars, you lose your save.
What?
Oh right, I gotta like...
Put the game on the screen.
Hold on.
Okay, open Roblox.
How do I find you?
I think it'll prioritize friends.
Oh, okay.
So like if we're friends, it should just put us in the same world, I think.
Alright guys, Roblox content actually starting now.
For real.
Sorry, we had like a 45 minute podcast going in, but for real, we're starting.
Alright, so if I click play, then it'll go straight to you?
I think so.
Oh, I've joined you!
Yeah, you've joined us already!
Okay, I'm gonna click play before I show my screen.
Alright.
Oh wait, actually I shouldn't.
Guys, I have to select a lobby.
Wait, how do I find your lobby?
I haven't selected it yet.
I'm trying to figure out how... Oh, here we go.
It has to be a window.
That's what it is.
Okay.
Chat?
Get out of my face.
Whoa!
Quit hassling me, bro.
Okay, uh...
Can we move us a little lower?
I'm so confused.
I'm just doing my own little stream thing.
I'm trying to put the game on the stream.
There's invite friends.
Oh, you can invite me, right?
Oh, oh, oh.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
Is this good?
Okay, I think this is kind of centered.
What is this?
Oh, it's centered.
Oh no, it's not centered at all.
Okay.
Ba da da ba ba da ba ba.
Ba da da da.
You okay there?
Classic, classic copywritten free music.
Whatever the heck.
What is this called?
Copyright license free?
Copyright license?
Copyright free?
Okay, I'm gonna create...
Lobby title?
Doki...
Schnuffy.
Lobby password?
I'll have it be the same.
God damn it.
No wait, this time I'll know the...
It shows on the screen.
This time I'll definitely know how to insert my password.
I'm gonna screenshot it.
Okay.
It shows on the stream just...
Okay, I see it.
Inappropriate lobby name.
Okay, hold on.
That doesn't work.
Okay, yeah, don't... guys.
Stuffy, I literally just spent $30 on Robux.
Don't get me back.
Oh, royalty free.
That's what they say.
Stuffy, I literally spent $30.
I need my Robux, man.
Okay, surely the... wait, it just disappeared.
Look, she's trying her best right now.
She's trying... she...
It keeps disappearing every time I...
She ate graphite as a kid, guys.
Don't...
Please.
Doki, your whole name is appropriate.
I don't know...
Please understand.
Is my name a hate speech?
There's no way.
Okay, this one... this'll be good.
That works.
Okay.
I almost read it out loud.
It's so fucking ridiculous.
Okay, you got invited me.
Oh, I see you!
Yeah!
Wait, I don't know if that's the right one.
No, okay.
It should say Doki Schnuffy.
Yeah, yeah, I saw that name.
Okay.
Uh...
Yeah.
Yeah!
I'm in!
Alright, alright, guys.
We can finally show the screen now.
Yeah!
It took us... it took us a while.
I think this is it, right?
Please use windowed or... wait, what?
Isn't this window?
Are you using windowed mode?
Yeah, I am.
Okay, but I'm not sure if that's the right one.
You do slowly... oh, oh yeah.
Are you able to capture the game?
Wait, wait, give me a sec.
It says, please use window... wait.
Guys, we are going through some technical difficulties.
Wait, what's the problem?
What's the problem?
Am I not in window... oh, wait, yeah, I am!
I'm in windowed mode!
Do you have to capture it as a window and not a game?
It didn't work as a game for me.
Oh!
Wait, how the fuck do you do...
Okay, wait, we have figured it out, guys.
I figured it out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, I did it.
I figured it out.
There we go.
Now we got it.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, there's our Peter.
There he is.
He's running around.
That's our child.
I'm so happy.
I accidentally zoomed in.
He's so big!
I'm so... give me a sec.
Cause like my alt key is...
Okay, here we go.
Guys, look!
It's our Peter!
It's our child!
Let me zoom.
Okay, here we go.
Alright.
After many technical difficulties, we made it.
We're finally playing Roblox.
Hurry!
We finally made it!
We made it!
Yeah, we're playing a game!
Okay.
Peter slowly loses hunger over time.
Buy burgers to keep him alive.
You can buy burgers at the gas station across the road.
Wait.
Oh, there's me!
Guys, am I beautiful?
Mmm, head burger, head burger.
You look great!
Guys, am I beautiful?
You look like you'd be the most thirsted character on a horror video or something.
Oh my gosh.
That's great.
Oh wait, he's dying.
Our Peter's dying.
He's the...
He is!
No, he's only ten... Oh, he's slowly losing... Oh, wait, wait.
He's slowly losing health.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What do we do?
How do we save him?
Oh, watch how we're crossing the road.
The cars won't stop.
Will we die?
Oh, I did it.
Oh, nice.
What?
I died!
What the fuck?
You killed me!
I did it again.
Bro!
Okay.
Okay, maybe I should cross the road.
I took a single stab.
How the fuck did you die?
Okay, I bought two burgers.
Okay.
What?
Poor gear.
Let's purchase poor gear.
How do I purchase?
I'm trying to purchase.
Stealing is illegal.
I got one.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
I thought I bought it.
I'm gonna die.
Today is my last day alive.
I'm going to die from cardiac arrest.
How do I?
How do we buy burger?
I gotta like... I gotta like mute and like cough horrendously.
What?
Okay, wait, wait.
I got this.
I buy burger.
Burger.
Burger?
Oh, there you go.
Alright, we lost a lot of money but I bought the burger, guys.
Hey, would it be so wrong to like...
I gotta like, tinkle really quick.
Before I laugh so hard, it's not gonna be...
It's okay!
I'm gonna feed our Peter!
Oh my god.
Feed Peter.
Don't worry, I got it.
I bought... I got the food.
I'm filling it up!
Burger refills 25 of Peter hunger.
In addition to buying burgers, you can buy items from the PeterNet.
What do I do with the PeterNet?
Okay.
Let's see.
Open door.
Guys, I'm exploring.
Oh my god!
I can buy a phone!
Guys, I'm gonna spend my money because Snuffy is not here to stop me.
There are basics of Peter... Rays of Peter.
There's a lot more to explore so have fun!
Okay.
I got a phone for my Peter.
What does that do?
Peter, you have friends.
What are you gonna do?
Call your friends?
Peter...
Peter.
What does he do with the phone?
Instructions unclear!
Freaking sweet Liz!
Alright, guys.
I can't...
Oh!
I got to unbox!
Alright.
No, wait.
No, no.
Did I actually donate it?
Oh no!
Did I?
Okay, no I didn't.
Thank god.
I don't want to donate money.
Oh, is this the phone?
Call somebody.
I need to...
Gives you his money.
Oh, I can call.
I called Joe Swanson.
Yo!
Snuffy, I spent all our money.
We didn't even do anything.
I spent all our money on a phone.
Peter is hungry but the fridge is empty!
Peter is starving!
Don't keep him!
But I got us a phone!
Look!
I got Joe!
What is he going for?
He's going to give us money!
Rob him!
How do I?
Okay, I'm going to make...
Hey, Peter.
Give me all your money.
You should raise your... how much?
Okay.
Give me all your money.
Look!
See?
Give me all your money.
He now makes $120!
Oh my god!
I can buy so many burgers now!
Go buy burger!
Are you going to buy burger?
Oh my god!
Peter is dying!
He has 24 health!
Oh my god!
Okay, I'm bringing it!
I'm bringing it!
Don't fucking die from the car!
We only have a dollar left!
There's no car this late at night!
Okay, okay, okay.
I got...
Don't worry, I got like...
Don't worry, I'm going to go buy more burgers too.
Oh my god!
He's so close to dying!
Yeah, he's so close to dying!
Don't worry, I'm picking it up.
Okay.
Here you go.
I need another $25!
I don't know how to drop items!
I actually picked up a lot of items.
You robbed the store and got all of those items?
Stuffy, I need $25!
Stuffy, I don't know how to drop my items!
Oh, okay, okay, wait, wait, wait.
Peter will bless us.
What do I do?
There we go.
I clicked him and he gave me money.
Oh my god, if you click him, he gives you money!
It's like cookie clicker!
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
You wanna...
Doki?
Doki, I heard a gun!
Everything's okay.
We got it.
I'm gonna go buy more burgers!
Don't worry, I got us another burger!
I got us two burgers!
Don't worry, I'm doing it!
I'll make sure Peter grows up big and strong!
You gotta click him for money!
I can have endless money now!
Oh, it's like cookie click!
It's like those AFK arenas!
Alright, don't worry.
Oh, you can call people!
Yeah, wow, Stuffy's so expensive!
Okay, I'm filling it up.
Okay, I got another.
Give me all your money!
Ray, you should raise your income!
Okay, $250.
We need $250.
Wait, do I click him?
Yeah, just click him and he'll start shedding.
Okay, okay, okay.
We should both click him at the same time.
Oh yeah, look at all this!
The double fingers?
Oh, we should get an auto clicker!
I'm getting a macro right now.
Get a macro right now?
Get the macro?
I'm programming my mouse!
Roblox doesn't say anything about no macro!
Oh my god!
Don't worry, I'm clicking, I'm clicking!
Okay, we have more burgers!
Okay, so like...
So, I'm gonna click on the burger.
We almost have $100!
What can we get with this money?
Don't worry guys, I'm a professional when it comes to...
I'm okay.
Don't go outside!
Okay, look at you!
You're thriving!
Don't go outside!
I just see like, blowing up explosion sound effects and particles bursting into the windows.
Shut up!
Are you in like a coma?
I'm afraid to cross the road.
Pick me!
Rest me!
Step me!
Real quick!
Oh my god!
You just feaced out of the dirt!
I can't!
Pick me up!
No, there's a solution!
I can't!
Let me see if I can...
Maybe I can buy like a defib or something from the store.
I don't think I can!
Oh, I just need to jump!
Okay, I'm good.
I'm a queen!
You wanna...
We can have a drink together!
Wait, what is it for?
What are the matches and the gasoline for?
Wait, there's like ammo?
Wait, you played this game before!
Why is there ammo?
I don't know!
I didn't...
I've only like glued the game up!
Peter is hungry!
Oh god dammit!
Oh, wait.
Okay, um...
I need to buy the burger for Peter.
Are you... you're on a wanted list?
Oh my god.
I can't drop my matches.
I can't drop my matches!
How much are the matches?
Okay, okay.
You said backspace, but it's not dropping!
How do I drop?
I actually do not know if you can drop items in Roblox.
I've never... I never knew that.
I'm pressing backspace!
You liars!
It's not backspace!
I just... oh my god!
I'd win.
I'd win against the car!
Let's just... let's just say...
I'd fucking win.
Oh my trash can!
I can throw in trash!
Okay, I did it.
Is Peter okay?
He's okay.
Don't worry, I'm gonna buy more burgers then.
Yeah, he's good.
He's eating.
He's healthy.
Okay, I just realized we don't have a lot of money.
So let me throw this...
We have a lot of money now.
Look at that, 30 bucks.
Okay, but which one is the one I bought?
Gotta milk him really quick.
You're gonna milk your Peter?
Remember to milk your Peters, guys!
Wait, did I?
Oh, I already bought this.
Don't worry, I'm going through.
I'm crossing the road.
Hey, look, I made it.
Yeah!
It's just like how I know when you're coming home because I just see your explosions!
It's okay.
It's okay, Peter!
I got you with the food!
Can I call somebody else?
Wait, we should call his wife.
How much does his wife cost?
Like, his...
His wife is only $250.
We're gonna make that in no time.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, our Joe makes $258!
Okay, Peter, we're gonna call your wife.
We're gonna buy your wife.
Buy her?
You know those mail order brides?
Did you buy her?
No, not yet.
We need... Oh, we can buy it.
We can... Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That mail order bride.
Two times money and buys burgers for us.
Oh, nice!
Oh, we don't have to do it anymore!
Oh, now we're getting $2 per Peter click.
Oh my god!
Wait, how did you promote your Peter?
It's because of Lois.
It's the Lois buff.
Oh, the Lois buff?
Look at that, guys.
When you get a wife, you can make $2 per second.
$2 per second?
Minus 10 sanity, but $2 per second.
I hear you.
I wanna just click on her, dude.
Fuck Peter.
Oh my god!
Lois is here!
Wait, she's leaving!
Why is she leaving?
Wait, does she just...
She's gonna go buy burgers!
She's gonna buy burgers for us?
Oh my god, we don't have to do this anymore.
We've been promoted to just clicking Peter.
Don't worry, Lois.
We'll milk Peter for you.
Oh, hello?
Hello?
The doorbell?
Who called us?
Hello?
Who's that?
Who's walking down the street?
Wait, what is that?
What is that?
Wait, that's a prank caller!
We just got fucking... What do they call that?
Door dash?
Yeah, we got like...
Ding dong dash.
Door dash is the fucking Uber Eats.
Oh god.
We got door dash.
Peter.
Hey, Peter.
Hey.
My favorite Family Guy character.
My favorite Family Guy character?
I think my favorite Family Guy character...
Oh my gosh.
That's so difficult.
There's so many.
You remember that one...
One dog that was there?
Because they baited us when...
Brian died?
The Italian dog?
Did you see that...
Did you see that post where like some guy got a fucking tattoo of Brian to like...
Unmemoriam for him and then the day...
and then the day after like...
Brian was like, not dead.
What do you think he tells people now?
Like, about his tattoo of Unmemoriam Brian Crimmel?
Like what was that, like 2016 or something?
Oh my god That's like .
That's so smart though because like he...
Seth MacFarlane was like, we need more ratings.
Let's do a fake I'm like pretending to kill off Brian.
I feel like I felt the impact back then.
I don't know what it was.
I know, you're like, you didn't expect it.
But when I was a kid, I think I had a crush on him.
I don't know why.
You had a crush on a dog?
Well, I don't think that was part of it.
I think I liked that he was like a free thinker.
I was like, yeah, you know, I'm an atheist.
I'm in middle school.
That's cool.
He's a dog.
I thought he was cool.
Yeah.
No, no, don't say that.
No, no, no, that's not what it was.
And he's a dog.
No, no, no.
I want to give him a swirly in the toilet.
No, now you're just making stuff up.
Oh no.
You got caught.
I'm being honest with my life and you say I'm making it up.
I don't know if I should be like honored that like my stories are that like...
I'm like fables.
Well, it's not just not that is the fact that like him being a dog was not like the main one of the reasons why you had a crush.
It's like people who are like, you know, people who have like crushes on like what's his name?
Kobu from the Lion King.
I bet you were one of those kids that had a crush on Kobu, weren't you?
No, it's like you are projecting.
That sounds like you know from experience.
No, no, no.
Snuffy, did you had a crush on Kobu?
But the girl lion could get it though.
Oh, nah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What's your Disney crush, Snuffy?
What's my greatest?
Okay.
My real true like Disney crush?
I like Esmeralda or Megara from Hercules.
Oh.
Those are my Disney crushes.
Humans.
Those are my girls.
Yeah.
Beautiful women.
Women.
What about the males?
Who are the male crushes?
Disney men?
Now tell me there's a Disney man for you.
Any male characters in Disney.
Is there even like a memorable one?
There has to be.
Why is Lois not doing her fucking job?
Gaston is pretty dope.
Oh, Gaston is pretty nice.
Yeah.
Get yourself...
We have a thousand dollars.
What are we gonna do with this?
Call his friends.
Wait, we can buy stuff on the PeterNet.
The PeterNet.
We can give him a couch.
I'm buying him a chair.
And then I'm buying him...
Wait.
There's like a couch.
Oh, I'm buying him a chair.
I'm buying him two couches.
Okay, there's somebody like...
...tapes to her ceiling.
And then I'm gonna buy...
Wait, okay, now we're broke.
Now we're broke.
Wait, I can call more people.
There's somebody taped on her ce...
There's somebody taped on her ceiling?
Where is that?
Oh shit, what the fuck is that?
Oh, it's our stuff I ordered.
I ordered a couch.
Here she comes.
Here's my couch.
Wait, I ordered two couches.
Where are my two couches?
There.
One of the...
He's gonna give us like three dollars now.
Oh, nice!
Yeah, now four dollars, cause I ordered two couches.
Oh, two couches.
It's turning into the family.
Yeah.
Alright, keep clicking.
I'm gonna talk to Joe to give me money.
Six dollars.
Oh my god, holy crap.
Oh my god, Joe makes five hundred dollars now.
This is it.
Give us your money, Peter.
Give us your fucking money.
We can call his child soon.
I'm gonna...
Give us your money, Peter.
Alright, I'm gonna go call.
Have you seen like Seth MacFarlane's newest show, Ted?
The TV show?
Yes, yes.
I've seen it three times.
Wait, like, no, not the movie.
The TV show.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I love it.
Wait, you saw the TV show three times?
What do you think I do?
All I do is like...
I itch crotch and watch a Seth MacFarlane TV show.
That's what I do for like eight hours a day.
I think you're like...
Your entire personality is based off of Seth MacFarlane's show.
Do your...
Can you do a family guy impression?
Like what character do you think you can do the best impression of?
Okay, definitely Joe.
That's the only one I can do.
That's a good one.
Hey, Peter.
I called Brian, by the way.
I do it always.
But I don't... I haven't practiced in a while.
Oh, show me.
Show me your impression.
Shit, how do I even do that?
Okay, hold on.
Let me mute and practice really quick.
You're not muting.
Practice.
I did it, Peter.
Right off the bat.
You need to say practice.
That's great though.
I'm trying to try hard.
I'm like auditioning.
Are you trying to say my Joe Swanson was not good enough?
It was great.
It was great, but that's like a liberating thing to say.
Like who wants to show off as Lois?
Who wants to be like, oh man, I love Lois Brecken.
I love Lois Brecken.
Peter.
Wait, wait.
The horse is here.
Peter.
I'm so bad at it.
I don't know how to be forced.
Brecken!
Oh my god, he just shit on the floor.
No, we gotta get Stewie.
I'm gonna call Stewie so Stewie can eat the shit.
Is that what happens in the movie?
Yeah.
You don't know your fucking...
You don't know...
Oh, what?
Oh.
You don't know your fucking family.
And you call yourself a Seth MacFarlane fan.
Where's Stewie?
Stewie's here.
He's gonna eat the shit now.
There's so much shit.
Stewie, get on the fucking floor.
Stewie, do your job, Stewie.
Oh my god, he ate shit for $400.
Okay, we're fucking rich.
And now it's all over his face.
We're fucking rich now.
This is it.
We're making money.
We're raising Peter.
Okay, let's see.
Okay, we need a TV for our Peter.
Oh, I got TV!
He's only age two.
That doesn't seem very old.
Okay, we got TV.
And then...
And then we got a...
We got another fridge.
Nice!
Wait, two fridges?
Double the burgs?
Yeah, double the burgs.
Okay, let me talk to Joe and threaten him for money.
Okay, he doesn't want to give us money yet.
Okay, the TV's here.
The TV.
We're getting the TV.
The TV's here?
Nice.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here we go.
I'm packing it.
It's beautiful.
Look at that!
Our Peter's gonna grow up big!
Big and strong!
What's this other box?
Oh, the fridge!
The fridge!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Guys.
Guys, you think we're doing a good job raising our boy?
He's happy!
He's so happy!
We're giving him a family!
We're buying him a family!
If Lois worked harder, he would be even happier.
Yeah, I like how Lois was cheaper than his child.
He's at the truth, B!
Guys, every family needs a strong Peter foundation.
Strong Peter!
Hey, Peter!
Come on, check the internet.
The Peter-net.
The Petronet?
What are you gonna get from the Peter-net?
It's only $50 for a nice rug.
Why not?
Like, let us stay warm and cozy.
Yeah, but there's a- Oh!
There's a bird!
What do we do?
He's taking our stuff!
We're large!
How the fuck- Oh, he took our chair!
He took the chair!
I don't know what to do!
You're a fucking- You're a fucking policeman!
This is what I need a gun for!
There's so many!
There's two of them!
They're taking everything!
How do we buy a gun?
How do we get a gun?
We need to protect ourselves!
Our first- Is it the First Amendment?
I don't know.
I thought that was like a freedom of speech or something.
What the- That's the- You're American!
Oh, it's our Second Amendment!
I forgot what- It's our Second Amendment!
We need to get a gun!
How was I supposed to know which amendments- How many amendments do you guys even have?
Wait, twelve?
That was like a religious thing.
What?
No, like the Twelve Commandments or something?
I'm getting the dynamite.
I'm gonna go buy dynamite.
They're backward!
It's the whole house or nothing.
I got the Fortnite Battle Pass.
I'm getting matches and dynamite.
What does the Fortnite Battle Pass gonna do for us?
I don't know.
They stole our table and our TV!
Wait, what the fuck did they steal?
I paid for it!
You- $500?!
He kicked me!
I paid for it!
I'm getting robbed on both ends!
Wait, where's the gun?
Where is it?
Where's our Second Amendment?
Okay, okay.
I'm leaving with the dynamite.
I'm getting another chair.
I'm getting chairs.
We can get robbed?!
At any moment, I'm ready.
Oh my god, I can't believe it!
Just let me know.
We're going out.
I like this whole bullshit.
That's just our chairs again.
I got us chairs again.
Oh my god, this room is so scary sounding.
I got us chairs.
I got us more chairs.
Oh yeah, Mag!
Wait, they took our phone!
What?
We took the fucking phone!
Okay, apparently if you close the door, you can't get robbed.
You know, that's actually a good idea.
You can just leave our door open!
You're so irresponsible!
We're irresponsible?
This is a group effort here!
We can't have...
We are both responsible for our Peters.
He's begging for his fur, Peter.
He might wander outside.
He might walk outside and get hit by a car.
He's not...
he's not my kitchen!
How could you do this to our son?
Okay, wait, let's see.
Why did we buy a new phone?
Oh, I got Pierre.
We can fish Pierre...
We can fish now.
Somebody said in the...
In the Raise Your Peter meta...
Did you know there is a Raise Your Peter meta?
And they said that we should grab a fishing Peter.
A fishing Peter?
If we want to be very efficient in raising our Peter, we need to get a Pierre.
Just remember to close the door.
Don't worry, guys.
I'm gonna close the door.
Guys!
Do not worry!
It's not just about raising Peters.
It's not like you walked away.
Did you close like a real door?
I got the fishing Pierre.
Where the fuck is the Pierre?
Oh, the fishing Pierre!
I thought you said the fishing Peter.
I was like, we can double the Peters?
Wait, where the fuck is it?
I don't see like a fishing thing.
I'm gonna try crossing the road.
I saw it like show up on my street.
It's over here.
It's across the street.
Why is there a thing across the street?
Oh!
Oh no.
Fishing rod.
You got a fishing rod.
How do I get one?
Don't go outside.
I'm fishing.
Okay.
I don't know.
I said purchase.
Is it coming to the house?
Oh, it's getting delivered.
Oh, it's getting delivered?
Okay.
Well, I'm gonna close the door soon.
I don't want to get robbed again.
We don't have a gun yet.
We haven't practiced our second amendment yet.
Wait, what did you...
I got something.
Is it a fishing rod?
Did you get the fishing rod?
And I can get Quagmire!
And I can get Meg!
Why is Chris the most expensive?
Why is...
Why the fuck is Chris Griffin so fucking expensive compared to everybody?
Is it because...
Is it because Seth Green does NFTs?
I'm a little confused.
It says that you can buy a pier so...
So, like a cover.
So rain and thunder won't kill you.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that's what happened to me.
I like how someone's like, Chris is endgame.
Oh yeah, Chris Griffin?
Yeah, that's kinda endgame.
Yeah, that's endgink.
Oh!
Meg drives off Burglar because she's ugly!
Is this Quagmire?
Why is he a toilet?
Is he a toilet?
Oh no.
Oh, the chicken!
Oh my god, we're making so much money!
Okay.
He occasionally turns into a toilet.
Gives two times money while toilet.
Oh, he gives more money!
Wait, does that mean if I click him, he gives me money?
No, it's like automatic.
No, it's for Peter.
Yeah, it's like a Peter buff.
I mean a Peter buff.
So like, if Peter sits on the Quagmire toilet, we get money.
Yeah, he gets extra milk.
Okay, we need to get endgame.
We need 5k.
Or 7k.
5k for endgame?
We gotta all click on Peter.
I bought a fishing rod, but I can't use it.
You haven't?
No, I have nothing in my...
Do you know where the pier is?
Maybe it automatically...
Oh, maybe.
Yeah, maybe I gotta look for more interactions or something.
You go over to the... You go over and fish.
I'm gonna try it.
Snuffy?
Did you?
You saw him, didn't you?
I saw him.
I'm trying to feed outside and I saw him.
I'm not sure if it was real or not.
Alright.
I'm trying to get...
drinks, coffee for a short speed boost.
What do you need speed boost for?
Can boost your money up to four times?
Oh my god!
I have more stuff coming in, guys!
Bro!
The factory is going.
Oh my god.
We're fucking gonna...
We can finish this.
I think we can finish this game.
We can get to end game.
Give me all your money.
I don't know if there's an end game.
I think it's like a forever type of thing.
There's no way!
There's like...
It's like that...
You know that Kim Kardashian game?
The one...
You know that...
You know Kim Kardashian had like this like...
Fucking similar...
Pre-Rays of Peter but for Kim Kardashian.
I'm...
I'm getting assaulted by a ghost!
You're getting assaulted by a ghost?
There's fucking ghosts!
There's a ghost!
I can't go outside or the thunder is gonna get me!
It's only attacking me during the...
If I'm close to the fish pool...
It says like...
Snuffy accepted a quest.
Me phone's dead.
What did you accept?
He wants an eel but if I fish...
I start getting like attacked.
He's immune to ghosts.
It says like...
Me quest.
You accepted a quest though.
Me phone's dead.
Hi!
Oh my god I'm gonna die!
I can't.
Ever since I got like...
Struck by thunder...
I'm gonna go outside again.
I'm gonna be a NEET.
I got hit by thunder...
Now I'm gonna be a NEET forever.
Maybe I have to do this during the day...
Or else I'm gonna get like...
Harassed by like ghost visions of...
When has it been...
Wait I'm gonna turn on the speaker.
What does the speaker do?
Yeah!
Dance!
Ba dum ba dum ba ba dum ba dum.
Yeah!
How do I use my emote?
Why?
Is this a stereo system?
Yeah!
I bought this!
Oh my god we're making $30!
Bita!
Yeah!
Guys how do I use emote?
I bought an emote with my $30 robux.
An emote?
I think you gotta like equip it.
Did you equip it?
Yeah yeah I did.
How do I use the emote?
How do you use emote?
E dance?
E?
Wait slash r- You gotta like type it?
E dance?
I don't know how to type.
I think everybody's gonna laugh at me in the chat now.
Oh you're saying to prevent you from sending...
Guys I put...
Guys I don't have a chat cause I got scared.
Guys...
Guys... Is there a way that...
Is there a way to activate it without typing?
OH SHIT!
Oh press period.
Okay period.
Oh there it is!
Look!
Oh shit I have...
Stadium what is...
This cost me $90 robux.
Okay show it to me.
I spent $90 robux on it.
Are you proud of me?
I spent real life money.
This is where your money goes to dragoons.
I spent real life money!
I don't know what you're talking about.
I got this!
I'm gonna die!
You guys this is where your money goes to.
I have Lil Nas X Old Town Road.
What the fuck how much did that cost?
Mine was $90 robux.
Actually I got this from the live Lil Nas Roblox.
I got this from the live Lil Nas Roblox concert.
I don't know if it was like 21 pilots of like...
Nojacat or something.
I think it was Nicki Minaj.
Nicki Minaj has like Pussy World.
Okay.
It's like the Nicki Minaj Pussy World.
They actually...
Okay doggie this might be a little on the point here.
There was a world that was actually an official roblox sponsor.
But it was removed because it was still a little bit adult to them.
But it was basically like a woman's...
What to call this?
A woman's menstrual...
Informational world.
What?
You can change your character model to like a woman's tampon.
And like go down the tubes.
And all those pieces parts.
What?
And get a whole like informational...
Practically think of it as like a...
Magic school bus.
Where like you shrink down and get to experience like...
The parts of a woman.
In roblox.
How did you know about this?
Did you go there?
Did you visit this world?
I just didn't.
But it got fucking removed for being too mature.
Was this your like daily world you visit every day?
Today let's time to visit the menstrual world on roblox.
I just really like to be a tampon one day.
Oh my god.
I wish it still lived to this day.
But I definitely think there might be like a youtube video that goes in depth on like how cursed it is.
You can like roleplay being like...
Let me see.
Hold on.
Let me see if I can send you something in google that shows it.
The sex update went through on roblox?
Is that true?
Is that... Is that true?
No no.
Are there 18 plus servers now on roblox?
Oh my god.
It was called the V land.
The V land?
I don't even know.
I don't know if it's the real one but this is what it looked like.
V land.
Where you get to dress up as like a tampon.
I go to the menstrual...
Hold on.
I'm gonna save this and put it on stream so you can see.
You're gonna save?
Oh my god.
What am I looking at?
What?
Oh my god.
This is...
Oh my...
Now I know why they shut it down.
I love women.
Now I know.
I like these like thumbnails from youtube.
That if you search like roblox v land.
You just get these relics of like what could this possibly be?
You guys.
If my mod.
Don't link it in chat.
Don't link it.
If you don't link it in chat.
Let the chat discover it themselves.
Let them discover it themselves.
Oh my god.
Wolf this is so good.
I gotta save this picture.
This is so good.
I wanna make this like my fucking collab just chatting picture.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
It's so fucking big.
Wolf is not a real thing.
What?
It is.
That was 100% a real thing.
That was very real.
It's just another roblox classic moment.
Like...
I will...
I don't even have any words.
To describe how I feel.
Learning about this.
To describe how I feel learning about this.
Oh my god, there's like... I can't... I can't commentate.
I can't even commentate on this.
Like what?
Like this is like beyond my pay grade.
The game is still up?
The game still exists?
I thought it got taken down!
What do you mean it's still around?
I've been raising my Peter this entire time!
I'm gonna end this game.
It has gone too far.
I am ready.
I'm ready to buy this mysterious burger.
I'm gonna pay for it.
Hello?
Oh there you go.
Five thousand!
Oh wait, I can... five thousand dollars is not bad.
Okay, I gotta throw this away.
We're not playing V-Land!
We're not playing V-Land, guys!
We're not!
There's no... there's no world where I'm gonna fucking play V-Land!
Oh my god, we need to fucking...
Grab 5k so I can end this.
Wait...
Peter... Peter, give me 5k!
I can't keep going on after learning about V-Land.
We're so close.
We're so close to 5k.
We're almost there.
Wait, I don't need to learn more about women because women aren't real!
We had this conversation chat!
Women were never real!
Not on the internet!
Alright, it's time.
It's time to end this.
Alright, I got the mysterious burger.
I have the money.
This is it.
We're gonna kill Peter.
Peter, I'm coming over.
This is gonna end now.
Where is he?
How do I feed him this?
Peter, eat this burger.
Wait, do I?
Open.
Oh, he'll eat it when he gets there!
Alright.
Okay, we're good.
It's just a waiting game.
And then we'll kill Peter.
Okay, okay.
I'm back.
Welcome back, Snuffy.
Snuffy, I have end game ready.
Oh shit!
We got Griffin's son, number two.
Number one, I guess.
Chris has been here for like ten minutes now, Snuffy.
What is he for?
Chris has been here for...
He's the one that's been turning on the speaker on and off!
I thought that was you!
I thought you were...
Dude, pizza?
Is this end game?
No, no, no, no.
Look, look, look.
I got the mysterious green burger.
This is it.
Oh, the mysterious green burger?
The nasty patty?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The nasty patty.
Have you seen like modern SpongeBob now?
Modern Spon...
SpongeBob is still going on.
It's so fucking...
Yeah.
I'm like scared.
I would rather watch like one of those like horrendous...
Have you ever seen like that one adult swim show like Mr. Pickles?
I would rather watch that than like modern SpongeBob.
I was like, what the fuck is this shit?
It was like the only thing like on at 3 in the morning and I used to like click on it and I would be like...
You watch Mr. Pickles.
You unironically watch Mr. Pickles.
And I would start playing and then I would just be like jaw agape the whole time.
I would be like 13 and just being like, what?
It's so fucked up.
It's so gross.
There's so much money in our house.
Wow.
Wait, Peter ate the green burger.
But he's still like...
Wait, what happened?
He ate it.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
What happened?
Oh, wait, what?
Wait, did he glow?
Okay.
No.
No, he just like pooped out of cash.
That's it.
What?
It said ending.
Where's the ending?
I got scammed.
I paid $5,000 for this.
$5,000?
Wait, what?
We have 66 feathers.
What does that even mean?
Oh, I bought a store.
Apparently, there's like a chicken coop and then you like buy stuff at the chicken coop.
Aww.
Why is he still alive?
Oh, is this right next to our house?
Wait, there's some...
Cave.
No, that's a cave.
Chicken coop upgrade.
Where's the chicken coop?
Scares.
Wait, where is it?
Oh, there it is.
There is no ending?
Okay.
It's a forever... Peter is like a... it's a commitment.
Scares.
Make Ernie punch 0.2 times faster.
Make Ernie punch... make Ernie punch... everything just makes him punch faster.
Like...
It just says make him punch.
I'm stuck.
There's a cave over here.
I see I found the cave.
What's inside?
Too bad it's blocked.
Get rid of the vines and you need to fill up the gasoline meter.
To fill up the meter, you have to purchase gasoline tanks.
Once you fill up the meter, you use a match to light up the vines.
Now just sit back.
Once the cave is open, grab... Oh my god.
What is this game?
What did you get?
I'm stuck.
I can't stop the game.
I can't even...
Snuffy, I can't even get out.
Wait, what?
Wait, what's happening?
Is this the ending?
Did we... did we beat the game?
Oh my god.
Wait, what's going... what the fuck?
What the...
He dragged from the Garfield Cup!
Oh, he's dead.
I think I forgot to take...
He got the theory!
It's the Garfield Cup!
Oh!
Oh my god!
It's the fucking Gar... I was kicked from the experience!
It was the Gar...
He gave him the Garfield Cup!
Here comes full circle chat.
Oh my god.
I can't believe it.
You wanna... okay.
You wanna try a different one?
Let's try a different one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're good.
Let's try another Roblox game.
Oh my goodness.
Okay.
I can't believe it.
Classic Garfield Cup was real.
It was actually real.
Okay, okay.
Let's see.
What... what kind of game are you feeling now?
That was a good, like...
Get the... get the blood pumping, right?
Yeah, that was a great one.
I can't believe we killed Peter.
There's... you can have a hundred players in a fucking Peter lobby?
Oh my god.
How do you stop, like, a hundred people from not feeding him the uranium burger?
Like, how do you stop?
I feel like I'll just go straight to wanting to, like, ruin people's games with the uranium burger.
You just go into, like, public lobbies and buy the uranium burger.
I'll fuck Bob, but...
So you said you've already been to, like, the hospital room?
I've done the hospital RP, I've done Dora's, and I've done Warrior Cat's roleplay.
But I'm down to go back to the Warrior Cat's roleplay.
You want to go back to the Warrior Cat?
Have you ever... have you ever turned... like, what I like to do is I like to ask my friends to turn their VTuber self into a Warrior Cat.
Into a Warrior Cat?
Oh, not like... not my... not my VTuber self, but I've done it as a kid multiple times.
Oh, you got it.
Okay, this one's a good one.
Did you do this one?
This one's my favorite one.
Which one?
Is it official?
Because they have official ones now.
They have an official one?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know if this is official.
It is!
My Warrior Cat's RP!
Create your own in the official game based on Warriors.
Yeah, this is!
This is official!
This is the one?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, nice, nice, nice.
It's really good.
Alright.
This is when we boot it up.
Wait, how many times have you played the official?
I've only played it once.
I've only done it one time.
How many times have you played?
Yeah, I've done this one time.
I don't know, it seems like you were pretty experienced just now.
There's bunches of them, that's why.
I played a couple of them, but this one I've only played one time.
Oh.
How do you know it's good if you only played it once?
Because that was just that phenomenon.
Alright.
Apparently I actually have to install Roblox for the- this is how elaborate it is.
You didn't even have them for the other- No, I didn't!
I didn't have to!
I actually have to install Roblox for the Warrior Cat's Roleplay.
Alright.
Warrior Cat.
Okay, let's see.
Uh, join friends.
Alright.
Wait, what server are you in?
Oh.
That's you, I see you, you're the cat!
Yeah!
I'm a cat!
You're made for this!
Oh my god, the icon is like, two cats in love.
Two cats in love.
Alright, settings.
What the fuck is this?
Show display name next to roleplay name.
Show- use roleplay name in chatbox if chat has roleplay.
Oh.
This will be a great play.
This is a great place for you to spend some Robux, I'm sure.
Okay.
Let's see.
Character editor, editing.
Oh my god, there's so many.
There's so many, like, what the fuck is this?
There's so many settings!
There's a warm filter, cool blue lights, dropped item, head turning, warning.
These settings will cause lag.
Wind line- okay, I'm gonna show this, guys.
This is actually crazy.
Look at the effective settings.
Wind line shake effects on mobile!
Who the fuck is roleplaying on mobile?
This is a full PC game.
Look at all these fucking settings for my Roblox RP.
Okay, now I'm gonna hide it because I don't know what it's gonna show.
Play.
It's pretty safe so far.
I think the main thing is that your username might show every so often.
Okay.
Oh my god, it's character creation time.
Alright, welcome to the character creation.
This is where you can customize your cats with colors and accessories.
You can change your cat's color using the left panel.
You can use the paintbrush to color individuals?
You can use the slider to change the age.
I'm gonna be a kitten.
I'm gonna be a...
You mean a kit?
I'm gonna be a kit.
Yeah, a little kit.
I'm gonna be a doki kit.
Have you ever read Royale Cats?
Oh, 100%.
Until, like, it got way too convoluted.
I stopped when, like, you know, the three kits that had powers and stuff?
Chosen three?
Yeah, the chosen three.
And then one of them was a fake one.
And then they found out she's fake.
And then she ran into the cave because she got so fucking emo about it.
And then she fake died.
Oh my god.
You've just done most of it then.
At least most of the good stuff.
And then I stopped because I was like, what the fuck is going on?
So fucked up after that.
And then, like, I was so tired because Crowfeather was fucking every fucking cat that showed up.
So...
It started getting so wacky.
Yeah, and then, like, cats started, like, fucking every other cat.
And then I lost track of which cat was fucking which cat.
And then I...
So I was so fucking confused at that point.
And then I stopped.
I just thought, you know, it just got too weird.
It just got too weird.
Crowfeather, like, banged, like, four different cats.
And I was just like, bro, what the fuck is going on?
Crowfeather is so fucked up.
Bro, he's like any cat that looks into his way and he's like, I'm in love.
I'm in love now.
And I'm just like, bro, fuck off.
I'm so starved.
And then, like, I'm like, what does this cat have that's, like, special?
He's like a little brat.
He's like a little bitch.
There's so many cats in this world.
What the fuck does Crowfetter has that like two medicine cats were like I'm in love.
I didn't see two medicine cats.
That's like pulling in like the hottest girls at school like the medicine cats there.
Yeah, because like the medicine cats are like it's like forbidden love because in war- okay for those who don't know It's like a clan thing so like there's like a cat that's like the doctor and like they're like super religious because the doctor- like they don't- they don't fuck.
It's like super forbidden for the medicine cat.
Yeah, they're like the- what are those girlies called?
A nun?
They're like cat nuns.
So like they're- like even the the guys who the cat priest too.
They're not allowed to- they're not allowed to like have children or have like like mates or whatever.
So like the thing is there's this one cat that managed to get two different medicine cats to like fall in love with him and bang and I'm like what does he have and then after that He got two new cats to fall in love with him So it's like what the fuck does he just have a big dick like what's going on?
Is his scent like super like attractive?
I don't understand I don't understand Like does he have game?
Like...
How much thought you've put into like how attractive this cat is?
Like I'm like I don't understand!
Like why does this cat keep banging other cats?
So many cats!
And then like I stopped reading it because I was just like this is like I don't- I just really hate Crowfeather.
I really- I read Crowfeather so gross!
Crowfeather, I want to push him down the stairs.
My cat!
I always wonder about warrior cats then I look at my cat.
And like I was going to the bathroom and she came into the bathroom with me and then she just started gnawing on the door stoppers.
He's like, I heard warrior cats.
I enjoy.
She's so smart!
My little killer.
I don't know what...
I can't try on any of these Robux outfits.
I don't know how do I know if they're good or not.
Wait, you bought Robux outfits?
Well, I have Robux, but I haven't gotten an outfit.
But some of these are like, if you want like lovely earpiece, that's 150 Robux.
I'm gonna be... I'm gonna be Crowfeather.
I'm gonna be a black cat.
You're gonna have to turn heads with Crowfeather walking around.
Yeah, I'm gonna turn heads with Crowfeather right now.
This is it.
This is... I hate him, but like if he has game then...
Scames, that's the word!
Okay, I'm gonna be a baby though.
Oh my god, I'm so tiny.
You wanna be... I need to find a mom in...
Mom?
Okay, I'll be... how do I... you said you're a kit?
Yeah, I'm a kit.
I'm a kit.
Okay, I'm gonna load in as my cat.
You're gonna load in as your cat.
Oh, you already have a cat?
Yeah, I got... I mean, I had a quick kitty that I could make.
I don't know if there's any too many options.
I need to check like, oh, earcuffs.
Kitty pets, ThunderClan.
There's nobody in ThunderClan?
Who the fuck even likes WindClan?
I know!
It's like the most forgetful one.
Yeah!
It's like RiverClan, ThunderClan, ShadowClan, and then the other one.
WindClan.
Yeah.
Oh, I need to buy it.
Try to buy the extra ear types so people know I have cred.
I'm gonna buy.
I'm gonna spend.
I'm not being... I'm just like, kitten and the only one person in ThunderClan.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna become the leader.
I don't wanna become the leader.
I'm gonna... I'm gonna buy curled ears.
Curled ears?
I'm gonna buy curled ears.
What does it look like?
I don't even know.
Oh my god, it's so ugly.
It doesn't even tell you.
It's so ugly.
It's okay, guys.
I need people to know I spent money.
Oh my god.
Guys, it's so ugly, guys.
It's so ugly.
They have pansy earpiece.
Left hearty butterfly wing.
Pumpkin flower.
Luxurious body piece.
Wait, it's locked.
Tier 4 luxurious body piece.
Oh my god.
Oh, you should see my cat.
I'm giving them the...
Like, you know, like the Disney animal smirk?
Like the bedroom eyes.
The dreamworks face?
No, no, no, not the dreamworks, but the bedroom eyes.
When Disney draw this bedroom eyes with the little...
The little, like, narrowed eyes.
And you're like, hey.
I'm gonna give them the Disney eyes.
Oh my god.
You're really just making the most fuckable...
Excuse me, I'm a child.
I'm a child.
Vine wraps.
I can... what the hell?
Spangles and splotches.
Okay, wait.
Let's see.
The forehead diamond.
I have a forehead diamond, so I'm special.
A forehead diamond?
Yeah, yeah.
Stripe bandana, stripe collar.
Normal muzzle.
Long muzzle.
Short muzzle.
It's 150 Robux for short muzzle?
What does that even mean?
Leading heart necklace.
Let's see.
Oh my gosh.
There's flowers.
There's spiky flower.
Painted ear leaves.
Oh my gosh.
Okay, wait.
There's so many choices.
Okay, what are the paid ones?
The lovely earpiece.
What the fuck is this?
Like, the ruffled head.
Two hundred and ninety-nine?
Oh, I see.
Okay, it's not so bad.
Cause like, you see how there's like the little like pink icon next to some of these?
I thought you had to buy them individually, but if you buy something that has like, I bought pink flower one and you get all of the pink flower stuff.
Like all of it.
For that much money.
So like, you pay 300 to get like all of those items.
Alright, that's a lot better.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
Alright.
I'm just like, Wait, there's something for a 599 Robux.
I'm buying this.
Guys.
Give me a second.
Oh my god.
It's a fucking restock of Robux.
I should have never booted this.
It's limited balance bundle.
You don't understand.
Oh my god.
Okay, guys.
Guys, look.
Look at this.
This was 599 Robux.
Oh no.
Oh my god.
I'm not...
Guys.
Guys, it's worth it.
I don't know.
Oh my god.
Wait, did we get raided?
I literally just brought my chat back.
I was like going crazy.
I was like, wait, where's my chat?
I thought I deleted it.
Dude, I'm so much for raid.
I'm gonna get the chin tough.
I'm gonna be like, um...
Oh my god.
Bro.
Bro, I'm gonna get all the ladies when I outgrow my kit phase.
When I...
When I pass my kit phase, guys.
I'm gonna get all the ladies.
Just you wait.
Okay.
Let's see.
Oh, wait.
What's this?
Tail streak?
The tail.
The normal tail.
Oh, I wanna have like a plum...
A plum tail.
And then...
What's this?
Cuff.
Right cuff.
Okay, okay.
Sores.
There's vine wraps.
There's so many accessories!
Why is... I'm just buying them all.
There's so many!
This is how they get you.
It's how they get you.
It's totally...
You can make the decision yourself.
You're strong.
No, I'm not.
I wanna be like...
I wanna be Crowfeather.
Oh no!
Okay, I got it.
Most fuckable cat.
I'm done.
Alright.
Let's build a thunderclan.
We'll populate this clan.
We'll populate this clan!
Okay, wait, wait.
Are you the only one in thunderclan?
Is that you?
The HUD.
The bottom HUD buttons can be used to change clans.
This menu lets you edit information about your character such as name and description.
Okay.
You can check out the animation sitting.
Change your clan allegiance.
Go to the other location or see a map.
Alright.
Oh my god, look at me.
I'm baby.
Wait, I wanna change my cat info.
Doki and Kit.
This Kit is going to grow up and be...
a...
a fuckboy.
There we go.
Did I save it?
Oh, I forgot.
Okay.
This Kit is going to grow up and be a...
bad...
a bad boy.
A bad boy.
This is me.
I'm the tiniest Kit out there.
I can't believe no one wants to join thunderclan.
Are you Breedpelt?
That's you.
Oh my god.
You're Breedpelt.
Oh fuck, of course you are.
Hey, hey, hey.
Dude, there's somebody else here.
Dude, look at our thunderclan.
It's already so populated.
We already fucking...
We fucking populated thunderclan.
There's so many fucking... Oh my god.
...crow pelts.
Breedpelt.
There's like five crow pelts here.
Breedpelt, you did it.
You repopulated.
When you were a kid too.
Nevermind.
You're also a kid.
Wait, wait.
Sides up.
It still says a kid.
It still says kid.
It says I should be an apprentice.
Change rule.
Oh, change rule.
Oh, nice.
So you can size down, but you can change your rule too.
Oh my god.
Wait, wait.
How do I size up?
How do you do it?
Just click on the bottom.
There's your cat info.
And you can add your canonical cat name.
And then you can add a description like Super edgy.
Oh my god.
I'm a big cat.
I'm a big kid.
Just so you know, there was something in my mama's milk that made me like this.
Something in your mama's milk?
In the cadmium?
She's got the asbestos.
She lived in the barn.
In the attic.
My cat mom.
My cat mom was definitely taking something.
That's why I grew up big and strong.
This kid is going to grow up and be a bad boy.
That's me.
Wait, what did you say?
I'm a bad boy.
We should visit the other clans.
We can wage war on them.
I love how we're all just black cats.
We've literally created the crow-pelt.
WinClan was the one that had a lot of people.
Too many people.
They had it too good.
I'm going to go in there.
Are they roleplaying right now?
Oh my god.
Very nice cat and very friendly.
I'm so sorry.
A loyal and intelligent feline.
That's their medicine cat!
Wait, how do I talk to these people?
You want to go flirt with their medicine cat?
Hello.
I'm a joke.
I'm the leader.
From thunderclan.
I'm lost.
The leader?
Up front?
I'm lost.
Trying to find my mommy.
Look so random.
Wait.
Now that I'm the leader of thunderclan I gotta change my name canonically From breed pelt to breed...
You're the leader?
I'm having a conversation with...
with...
with Fury Oak.
Wait, what is this?
With the medicine... Oh no.
Am I ruining this...
this poor child's time trying to roleplay?
You gotta be cool.
You can be the deputy.
Or a queen.
Do you want to be the wetest kid?
Bro, the medicine guy is like, I don't know how to help you.
Do you know what they look like?
Wait, I should age size myself down.
I'm so sorry, child.
Stay far away from disgusting, evil cats.
Oh my god.
We have suffered through many losses today.
We mourn the loss of our past leader.
But tomorrow...
What the... this is an actual story going on!
This is an actual story going on!
Stuffy!
The roleplaying is!
The roleplaying is all about...
It's like writing a book.
Oh my god, there's so much immersion!
We gotta be in character.
Wait, this is High Rock, right?
So you gotta be like...
Let me get into my roleplay.
I'm looking at the clan leader.
If you go to innovations, you can do stuff too.
You can do stuff.
Yeah.
You can be like, Let me break into my role.
You know, I actually used to do warrior cat's roleplay on Neopets.
I actually used to do warrior cat's roleplay on Neopets, And my character was Wild Pelt.
I would do OOC, you know?
And then I had pre-built character sheets built out for my cat roleplay.
Oh my god!
No fucking- See, I did the same thing.
I don't know if- I didn't do Warrior Cats roleplay, but I think for a while I did like Bleach, like the anime Bleach.
Wait, on Neopets?
I- Okay, I did it on Gaia Online.
Tomorrow- No, I've never.
I was a Neopets girl.
Anyway, the fucking leader of WinClan was like, tomorrow we shall- I shall get my- Oh, they were- He was doing a clan meeting!
A Crash WinClan's clan meeting!
Fucking WinClan!
How did you even get there?
I visited WinClan!
I don't even know how to leave this one!
How do I leave the Purr for tomorrow?
You go to like the clan and map, and then you click join.
The map?
Wait, you just joined it?
No, I didn't join the clan, I just wanted- I visited their camp.
Go to camp.
Oh, I'm in RiverClan, that's the wrong place.
Don't worry, there's nothing fun happening now because- Oh my god, please start- Because I fucking crashed their clan.
I crashed their clan meeting.
Wait, what about ShadowClan?
What's ShadowClan doing?
Oh, you can drink water.
Is- Is ShadowClan still around?
ShadowClan- Yeah, we've done away with those guys.
Yeah, everybody in ShadowClan's dead.
There's nobody here.
There's nobody in ShadowClan!
This just looks like the end of the world.
This is like ThunderClan reskin.
Bro, everybody in ShadowClan is dead.
A fresh kill pile, we gotta go kill somebody.
You wanna kill somebody?
I gotta go feed the clan.
I remember when I first- Oh my god, there's the leader stand.
When I first joined up the WarriorCats RP server, and then I got some- Some like- What was it?
Queen?
Some queen to feed me, because I was like, wah.
Oh my- Okay, so can we reload and- Oh, I'm gonna go into a different server and just like- Can I get a mother in roleplay?
I need that.
I need a mother figure.
They like picked me up and was like- They picked me up and was like fucking feeding me and also trying to take care of me.
Sold, sold, sold, sold.
Let's go join WinClay.
We need to fucking find a- We need to find a- They camped where the queen is.
Where are the queens?
WinClay definitely has to have like a queen.
I feel- I gotta change breed star then.
That's too much.
What is it?
There's a loner here.
Where are all the other cats?
Where the fuck are the other cats?
Who are all- Only WinClan is alive apparently.
I don't know.
Who even wants WinClan?
Like what the hell even is WinClan?
Like who the fuck is that?
They weren't even relevant in the story at any point.
I know.
All the clans- Wait, what about the kitty pets?
I'm gonna check if the kitty pets are still around.
The kitty pets.
Yeah.
I got ignored by the kitty pets when during my first time.
I'm going to WinClan.
I'm gonna go find a mom.
You're gonna find a mom?!
There's fuck- Wait, how do I go inside?
I don't know.
Where's the door?
Oh, there's the door.
I don't know where, like...
How do I open doors?
How the fuck do anybody do anything as a kittypet?
This is so peaceful.
Something about this feels wrong.
Like, these people are at such peace.
Little cats sleeping away.
And I'm loading and being like, ma'amie.
Ma'amie.
Charm.
Oh wait.
Me when I...
When I... When I...
Oh my god, there's a kittypet right here.
Oh, you found the kittypet?
I found some kittypets, yes.
Hello.
I'm lost.
I'm trying to find my mommy.
Oh my gosh, I loaded right... wait.
I loaded like right in a bunch of them.
No, wait.
A child.
Is that you?
Is this you?
No way.
A child.
Wow.
No way.
You gotta be like EBC for mom.
This person's just saying censored things in fish emojis.
Really?
Hello.
Are you hungry for real?
For real?
No way.
I'm not.
I'm hungry.
I'm getting choked.
Oh my god, they're like, no way.
Stop.
Bro, this kittypet is so mean.
What is he doing?
He told me to starve.
I can't even tell what they're saying.
Horrendous thing.
They told me to starve.
What are the settings?
I don't know.
Animations.
Wait, animations.
I can't believe it.
This kittypet pooped.
I'm just trying to find a mama.
I'm a baby.
Baby.
I'm just a baby.
They're so mean.
I'm just a little kid.
I haven't grown up.
This is why I'm gonna be a bad boy.
It's because of my environment, Snuffy.
I feel like we're like unloved kids at an adoption center.
Yeah.
This is why I become a bad boy.
Nobody.
Nobody loves me.
Yeah.
Oh my god, what the fuck are you doing?
What the fuck are you doing?
Oh, you know.
What happened to my name?
Wait, what happened to my name?
My name was good.
Oh, you got reported.
You got reported.
This is worse than Green Star.
I can't believe it.
You got reported.
Oh my god.
You're ruining this for children.
Wait, this is a kid's...
I'm not associating myself with you.
I don't know her.
I'm running away.
Guys, we just...
You loaded up the game being like, man, I wanna be just like Crow Pelt.
He got so many bitches.
Yeah, but like, I didn't write that down.
I just wrote I'm gonna be a bad boy.
I didn't say anything.
I just said I was thirsty cause I wanted some mom to love me.
I was thirsty for love.
I think you're gonna get your account banned again.
I think your account's gonna get banned.
Oh, I didn't do anything wrong.
Why is this guy red?
I'm red.
I didn't read the description.
I read it.
What do you mean?
I literally...
Oh my god, there's like a bunch of loners.
You felt cold for a second.
Warm for another.
Then cold again.
You needed something to keep you anchor.
What you snarred.
Everyone...
Happy Christmas.
Starve.
Oh my god.
We keep getting told to starve.
This is my house.
Her stomach growled.
Wait, I gotta type this.
Wait, oh wait.
Okay, wait.
How do I fucking...
Dude, I picked up a toy.
I need to talk to everybody.
Doki Pelt looked around the barn.
She was still lost in...
Trying to find her way.
She saw several cats in the barn.
She was still lost in Mannagham.
She saw several cats in front of her.
Her stomach growled.
Has anyone...
seen my mom?
Wait, not Doki Pelt.
Sorry.
Doki Kit.
You're aging yourself up so early.
To verily, Kit.
Why didn't we all make it...
Why didn't everybody chose their cat to be Cropelt, like...
They're all black cats with blue eyes.
Because... it said, I'm sorry.
Because you guys all wanna be special.
I wanna be realistic.
I don't wanna be...
There's so many cats in this house.
We belong to some crazy cat lady.
Bro, this entire story is about being in a c- It's written by four cat ladies.
I mean, literally this is a cat lady literature genre.
Like...
Did anyone talk to me?
No, no, everybody's ignoring me because I'm a cat lady.
I'm a child!
Everyone watches TV in the house.
I hope they have Garfield on TV right now.
Minus one RP, Snuffy!
You're not immersive!
Retta's on the couch as she flips through the channel's haphazard room.
I'm on the couch as she flips through the channel's haphazard room.
We're
in the house!
We're in the house!
There's a TV and everything!
It's not bad RP!
This is- We're literally indoor cats.
I'm indoor cat RP!
There's like a cat tower and everything!
Oh my god, they're gonna pick me up!
Oh my god, they picked me up!
How did they get picked up?
They asked my permission.
Okay.
They asked my permission and I got picked up.
Oh my god, where am I going?
Is he gonna feed me?
Is this my new mom?
Am I too big?
Do I need to be extra small?
I don't...
I'm down five.
They put me down.
I can't move.
I did something to my game.
I wish you held and cradled.
Okay.
How do I move?
Feed me.
Oh.
Yeah!
Did you get picked up?
Yeah, I got picked up.
You gotta be extra tiny.
Oh my gosh, that's great.
I'm extra tiny right now.
I love how you're like curled up so much.
A little Pete's.
Hurt.
I know, I'm so tiny.
Are you ready for it?
Wait, sheave claws?
Oh my god.
Can I do animations?
Can I like sleep?
No, you can't do anything.
Doki continues to...
Doki continues to starve.
Waiting for something.
Some cat...
to give her food.
Doki continues to starve.
I'm like...
I need food guys.
Where am I?
Oh my god, these guys pick me up.
They're gonna pick me up and give me food, I think.
Wait, where are you?
Are you not in my house?
I'm in the barn.
No, I'm in the loner stuff.
The loner?
Where's the kitty belt stuff?
The kitty belt stuff?
Where's the cat belt stuff?
The loner!
What do you eat?
Doki Kit looks up to the cat, to the strange loner that picked her up.
Anything.
I'm so hungry.
See, I'm just trying to find a parental figure who will love me, but I think I'm getting kidnapped.
I'm getting abducted right now!
You're dragging me into the street!
Plus one IV.
I'm so immersive.
I'm hungry.
I'm pulling up my Neopets roleplay right now.
That's medicine!
Do you even flip and turn?
Okay, I'm gonna eat my heart.
How do I go to the...
loners?
I'm eating grass right now, Snuffy.
You eat grass?
I ate my grass.
I did it.
I ate it.
It's good.
They made me eat grass.
Do you eat like, hay?
Like a horsey?
There's like cat mint.
Oh my god, there's so many loners here.
Look, I spent more than one year roleplaying warrior cats on Neopets.
More than one year roleplaying?
Okay, I would do like...
That's all I need to be here.
I would do like...
High school roleplay, Neopets roleplay, magical fantasy roleplay.
And then I would have like character sheets of like templates of all these Neopets roleplay.
There's like a roleplay board in Neopets.
That's what I did on Gaia Online.
They would have like roleplay guilds and forums that you could join.
Yeah, and then there's like one where it was like superheroes school roleplay.
I had so many.
Superheroes school.
Yeah, and then I remember one of them, one of my templates was like a guy that knew like telepathy or some shit.
I was like telekinesis.
Oh yeah, telekinesis.
Oh my god.
I was on the roleplay leaderboard.
There's some good stuff then.
If you're into that, then I have many a world to take you.
Do you want to try a different Roblox world?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Doki Kid signing out.
Doki Kid leaving.
At least I got fed after all this time.
I got fed and I'm okay now.
Get fed, leaves.
Actual wildcat RP.
That really works.
I got fed, I leave now.
Goodbye.
That's it.
I'm leaving.
That's all that matters.
Let's see, let's see.
What's another good roleplay one?
Um...
Oh my god.
Where do I go?
There's one that like it's not as funny and I genuinely, but I genuinely have like a super good time with it.
Um, I don't know if I can find it.
Uh...
What is it called?
It's something, it's something fantasy themed.
It's really fun.
It's like those games where you...
like have to survive.
Like as a character.
Like an animal and like other animals can eat you and shit.
It's basically the roleplay but like for serious though.
Like that's the mechanic.
Wait, what is it?
What is it called?
You don't know?
Oh man.
Something with an E maybe.
Let me see if I can find it.
The one that says the weather survival game is like really good.
Oh, natural disaster?
That's super fun.
That one's just a fun one.
Weather, weather, that weather...
Oh, it's natural survivor?
What's it about?
Um, it's like...
We can play that one.
It's super, it's super fast and easy.
It's like, oh my god.
Probably one of the oldest classic Roblox games right there.
Natural disaster survival.
I can link you to if you don't see it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll just click on your link.
This one is super fun.
So instead of a curse game, this is a classic.
Survival.
Okay.
I'm waiting for this to pop up so I can join you.
Open.
Open my Roblox game client.
I hope the kids are okay.
I don't think kids...
This is all about how much the kids are okay.
This is like Chester Kids on where if they know where to go during a natural...
What the hell?
Now we're back into regular Roblox territory and it's gone.
You're best to survive the natural disaster.
If you die, you can spectate others.
Are you in here?
Yeah, I think I'm in here.
Wait.
Was it you?
Maybe my room...
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I think my room got full.
I'll just join again and see if I got into yours.
I don't know where I am.
There's this cool guy.
Oh my God.
Look at him.
Damn it.
Okay, wait.
Close the game.
I think we'll have to load up together somehow.
There's a giant fucking chick called BP is cool.
Okay.
I'm going to load into it.
Are you in my room?
No, I think yours is full.
This game is really popular.
Oh, really?
Okay.
Wait.
How can I join with you, though?
I don't...
See, this is the fun part of Roblox.
I don't really...
Okay.
Wait.
I'm going to...
Okay.
On the count of three, let's like, put it up together.
Like, one, two...
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
I'm ready.
One, two, three.
Okay.
Boom.
Let's see.
Yeah.
Let's see if we can load it together.
Okay.
Yeah.
Maybe like, we should mute ourselves and then...
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Maybe that's easier.
All right.
Did you load it?
I'm loading it.
Yeah.
I'm ready.
Okay.
I don't...
I don't see you.
Dang it.
Okay.
I see San Francisco.
There were no survivors.
Okay.
I'm going to mute my stream audio so nobody can hear us.
I'm going to...
I'm going to mute mine, too.
I was going to say, I'm not going to mute mine.
I'm going to mute mine.
There's Woody.
Oh, you guys are missing out.
You don't see Woody.
Okay.
I'm...
I'm opening it.
Oh, my god.
Wait.
I need to show my chat Woody.
Look it.
There's Woody.
There's Woody in Roblox.
I don't...
How do you get Woody?
Is this...
There's a fucking spider.
There's a Woody in my Roblox game.
Oh, my god.
This person is a fucking spider.
I've got like...
I've got a spider woman.
I've got a spider demon woman.
You've got a spider demon woman?
What in my room?
What the f- There's an anime boy!
Okay, wait, let me- I'm gonna mute my- I'm gonna mute myself.
So we can actually- Get in the game together!
Alright.
Okay, okay, okay, guys.
I'm gonna mute myself, guys.
We gotta make sure we get in the room together.
Give us a sec, chat.
We did it!
Guys!
It took us so many tries!
But there's f- Lightning McQueen!
This was worth it.
Guys, this was worth it.
We have Lightning McQueen, chat.
We have Lightning McQueen in our lobby.
Ka-chow!
Oh my god!
There he is!
I'm your biggest fan!
Mr. McQueen!
Are they on a roadblock state?
Okay, okay, so here's what- Here's- Here's- Here's natural disasters- Oh, we're in the- We're in the Spanish We're in the Spanish lobby.
It's acid- It's acid rain.
It's acid rain.
Oh no!
Oh no, I'm going in!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, take shelter.
Take shelter.
Lightning McQueen!
This is a re-assumulation of a- of a- of a pandemic happening right now.
Oh my god.
A natural disaster.
Lightning McQueen!
He's gotta- He's gotta get in the garage!
He knows how to play this game.
He's in the garage.
He has the exp- Bro, we're in the Spanish servers.
We're- Spanish?
Yeah, people are speaking- Everyone's speaking Spanish.
Hello, Mr. McQueen.
I'm your biggest fan.
I'm your biggest fan, McQueen.
McQueen.
It's really- It actually is.
Like, what?
I've bypassed the servers so far that I can't hold my That is Oh, yes.
Is that the other house next door?
He said kuchao.
What's kuchao?
Kuchao with a man screaming fire emoji.
That's him!
That's Lightning McQueen!
Is that actually the Spanish way to say it?
Kuchao!
Is that kuchao in Spanish?
...
Wait, it is?
Oh my god.
It is Spanish.
Somebody else repeated it and they were like kuchao?
Oh my god, did we get here?
Did you live?
Yeah, I did.
Here's a hack.
If your health is still injured before the next game starts, you gotta do a hard reset or else you're at an unfair disadvantage and you're missing HP.
Okay.
Blasting Roblox tech right here.
Oh my god.
I can't believe.
I gotta figure out how to get this Lightning McQueen skin.
This is fucking fantastic.
Bro, this is a great skin.
Kuchao!
This is fucking Kuro.
This is a fucking Kuro cosplayer.
What the hell?
We got fucking VTubers in my instance.
I'm following Kuchao.
I trust him.
I trust Spanish Lightning McQueen.
This man fucking spent money on this.
Okay, there's a bit of a cloud front coming in.
I don't know what the disaster could be.
Is it fog?
Yeah, it looks like dense fog.
I'm on top of the ceiling to get a good purveying view of the game.
The situation here.
Back to you Dokie.
I'm with Spanish Lightning McQueen for an interview.
Oh, it's a fucking blizzard.
I'm an ish.
Oh no.
What do we do Mr McQueen?
You gotta run his engine.
Okay, I got it.
Stay warm.
We warm.
Huddle together guys.
Body heat, body heat.
Yeah, body heat, body heat.
Take off all your clothes and huddle up together.
Oh no...
Get inside McQueen for the heat!
We need the radiator!
What do you mean?
You think we're okay, Mr. McQueen?
Ka-chow!
Oh my god, ka-chow!
Oh my god, do you think we'll be okay, guys?
I can't even see my HP.
I can see McQueen's HP.
My HP is so low!
You're half HP!
Oh no, the walls are turning into snow!
Oh no, don't touch the snow!
Oh no!
Oh god!
Look at Smirk's face!
Ka-chow!
He's spelling it differently every time!
Oh, ka-chow!
Ka-chow!
I feel like we're a bunch of Pokemon!
I know!
Oh my god, he's a gamer.
Look at his HP, he's so high!
His HP is so high!
Oh god!
Okay, right, I gotta wipe.
How do you win this game?
You just have to survive!
You just get the highest points and survive as long as you can.
That's how you do it.
Surf Central.
Alright, I'm pretty sure I'm gonna die first before you.
Why didn't we get put into the world?
What the hell?
Even Ka-chow didn't go!
Oh my god, we didn't!
We're just too good.
You know, we're just too good.
We're on a win streak.
Yeah.
He's not happy!
Spanish Lady McQueen is not happy about this, look at him.
Oh god!
He's like, where was my game?
Where was my game?
Oh, there's a weather machine to power up?
Need a lift?
Just 30 robux to get a green balloon?
What the fuck is the green balloon?
Oh my god, I saw Woody with a green balloon.
Oh, that's cheating!
That's cheating!
It's like pay to win.
That's totally pay to win.
That's what I love to hear.
Classic.
No, no, no!
Avoid black crowds?
Wait, does that affect us?
No, no, no, because we're not part of the experiment down there.
Oh my god!
We can watch them like little ants scramble around.
McQueen is getting squished!
He's so popular.
He's getting squished!
Koochow!
What happened to him?
Oh my god!
He's...
Wait, do your emote!
How do you do your emote?
Period?
Oh, period, yes.
Period.
And then... here.
That's my emote.
Koochow!
He's both shivering and warm.
I don't know what emotion this conveys.
Does someone just call him dad?
He really likes this girl.
He's like driving onto her.
Oh no!
McQueen!
Stop!
Your career, McQueen!
McQueen, you can't be seen like this!
You have a wife!
You have a wife and your best friend!
This is a Porsche!
Oh my god.
Why?
How could you do this in front of all of us?
Literally, you're our hero!
I think Spanish McQueen has like different standards.
Dude, we still won.
That counted as a win for us.
Yeah, we're just gamers.
Did he just post an emote of an amoeba?
What the fuck is that emote?
What is that emote?
Level 4 weather?
Level 4?
There's like one person down there.
What the fuck is that word?
Classic.
Are you gonna get on the rocket?
There's a rocket?
Wait, is this the only person playing the game?
We did it.
Powered by...
There's four natural disasters.
FIVE natural disasters?
Good job.
Wait, wait, wait...
I think we have to go up.
We need to leave the planet.
I think that's the result.
I've never seen somebody pay that much to have five natural disasters.
That's like... we're gonna die!
How did you get in the rocket?
Oh no!
Did they knock down the platform to cross into it?
You gotta climb the...
No, they knocked down the platform to get into the thing.
They did?
Those monsters!
Kill them.
Are we dead?
Enable the rocket.
Volcanic eruption.
Fire.
Thunderstorm.
Oh my god!
Thunderstorm!
Guys!
Put her down!
Oh my god!
Is that okay?
I can't tell.
Oh, I'm so scared.
There's fire!
Are you in the rocket?
It's a tower!
It's a flash flood!
That tower is getting destroyed by lava!
Flood!
Oh!
I'm on the rocket!
I'm dead.
Bro, no one's surviving that.
I was so fucked up.
Bro, no one's fucking surviving that.
Holy shit.
I like that you can just pay money to instantly kill people.
Yeah!
Just put them through the worst experience of their life.
So level five.
Nobody lived.
Nobody fucking lived.
Thank you.
Thank you, cool2x, for like, literally ending our lives.
For like, pay to end.
Pay to end.
Forget pay to win.
That was a fun game, though.
Pay to end them all, yeah.
This game is really addicting.
It's good fun.
It's just art.
And it's just funny map and, you know, just silly survival.
Oh no, I think Lightning McQueen left.
No, no, he's at the bottom floor, contemplating life.
He's fighting with a dog.
Yeah, he's fighting with a dog right here.
With mentally unwell.
Mentally unwell?
Oh, okay, but having an ass in my name is a bad moment.
Lightning is running away from the dog.
Ciao.
He's running away from his problems.
He's running away.
Just like the first movie, guys.
There were no survivors.
Damn, really?
No survivors?
I wonder why.
I'm fucked up.
I like the volcano right next to the planet, too.
Alright, Snuffy.
Give us another server.
Another server?
Alright, alright, alright.
Let's find a new game.
That one's a good one.
A classic one.
That one was good, yeah.
It's one of the oldest games, like, on Roblox.
Like, I think that thing is probably more than 10 years old.
Wait, really?
I don't know if there's a way to, like, look when it got posted or something, but yeah, that thing is...
That is a relic.
Created March 28th, 2000.
That's crazy.
2008.
Holy... the person... this stick master, Luke, has made so much money.
Oh, yeah.
That is... that was a big one.
You know, the biggest brain?
Oh my god.
You make your own Roblox world, and then make your...
Make your own Roblox world.
And then...
And ironically, have that idea.
Put cosmetics in there so people will have to spend Robux.
You could hire somebody, like, like a game dev in Roblox to make a game for you, and then you can just, like, get rich from microtransactions.
Oh, yeah.
We're gonna farm children.
That's so ethically right.
The target section, the target children's toy section is just riddled with, like, off-brand Roblox games.
That, like, Roblox creators got, like, money from their game, and then they just want to make that same game as, like, a standalone and just keep getting money from it.
Like, the big one is called, like, Pet Simulator or something right now.
Pet Sim... oh, wait, I've seen that before!
Yeah!
Yep.
It's fucking crazy.
There's so much drama regarding it, too.
It's insane.
Um, okay, so I think another good one...
Hmm... what are you feeling?
We can do another roleplay.
We can do kind of a never-before-seen experience.
Let's try the never-before-seen experience.
Let's, like, try all different experiences here.
Yeah, yeah.
Get the full Roblox...
Roblox style.
Okay.
Let me, let me, let me peruse what I've got saved here so far.
I'm gonna change my face.
Oh my god.
This might be an interesting one.
I've never been to this one, but it is a it is a official sponsor one.
Oh!
What's it called?
Oh, wait, we shouldn't say it, so then we could actually... I linked you, yeah.
Yeah, I was gonna say we shouldn't say it.
You can let me know if this is, like, something you'd wanna, you'd wanna, like, do that.
Oh, wait!
Yes!
Yeah?
Okay, okay.
I'm opening, I'm opening it.
Oh my gosh.
Yes.
I've never done this one.
So I'll be new to it as well.
Oh my god.
It's a fucking tycoon.
It's one of those games.
Tycoon games?
Oh my god.
It's a tycoon game.
It's so cute!
Would you like a quick walkthrough?
Sure.
Oh my god.
Wait, I'm gonna join you first.
Let me know when you're in the server.
I'm in, I'm in.
Okay, I'm gonna...
Are you sure you wanna leave the experience?
Yes, sadly.
Sadly, I have to.
One of my other favorite, like, official sponsors is in, like, one of the Roleplay Town worlds.
Is, like, a canonical, like, Home Depot.
Like, a real sponsor for Home Depot.
What?
Home Depot has a fucking Roblox server?
Yeah, they have, like, in one of the Roleplay Towns, Yeah, they have, like, in one of the Roleplay Towns, they have, like, an official, like, building where you can load in and, like, have, like, sponsored...
Home Depot content!
Oh my god!
Also, you have to rejoin the server, cause I think they...
You got sniped.
I don't know, this one might...
be a single player game.
It's a single player?
No!
It could be, it could be.
Some of them are, some of them are.
I don't know.
Nooo!
How can... How else will you join?
Okay, I loaded into another one.
How else will you join my tycoon?
Oh, I think it is.
This server does not...
This experience does not support private servers.
Oh, yeah.
Alright, guys, I'll show you what it looks like.
And then we're gonna find another server.
Chat.
I'll show you what we joined.
I'm pretty sure you saw it from Snuffy's side.
But, like... No, I didn't saw it.
But, like...
No, I didn't saw it.
I didn't saw it.
Oh, okay.
Guys, look.
Look, it's the Hello Kitty experience.
Look.
There's Tsunomoro!
Hi, it's a pleasure.
Welcome, Hello Kitty!
Oh my god!
Look at this!
There's gotcha... Of course, there's fucking gotcha.
There's gotcha.
Tsunomoro!
Where's Tsunomoro?
I don't wanna do all of this.
I just wanna talk to Tsunomoro.
Alright, I'm done.
I've had my experience.
It's like that Hello Kitty...
What's that Hello Kitty game that South Park advertised?
Hello Kitty Adventures?
Is that it?
Oh, oh!
Hello Kitty Island Adventures?
Yes!
It's basically like the free version of Hello Kitty Island Adventures.
It is!
It's actually... It's still a free game.
I have it on my iPhone.
If you have like a iPod... Apple device, it's free on the Apple Arcade.
Oh, whoa!
Not sponsored, by the way, but if Hello Kitty Island Adventure would like to sponsor me...
I'm right here!
Absolutely!
It's very neat.
I'm right here!
I've never played this one.
I linked you a new one.
I've never played it, but it looks appetizing.
It looks very entertaining.
I'm gonna join off of you.
Give me a sec.
I'm gonna leave.
I can't believe Hello Kitty Island Adventure didn't win Game of the Year.
There you go.
It's so fucking robbed.
I know!
I was so sad.
That should have been best mobile game!
What the fuck is this?
Let's try to find foods hiding in the house.
This is us.
I'm not even in your server.
What the fuck?
Where are we?
What the fuck is this?
Okay.
What are we trying to do?
I think it said you have to hide or something.
Or find food.
I don't...
Wooo!
I don't see like an enemy anywhere.
Speedfest.
Yeah, who's the enemy?
Wooo!
Oh my god, they're so tiny!
How are they so tiny?
Wooo!
I fell down.
There's a chef?
But where's the chef?
A chef?
Yeah, apparently there's a chef somewhere.
I can't get out.
I'm scared.
I'm stuck.
I'm gonna like hide under... I'm gonna be like a food that you dropped and that you haven't like seen under the fridge for 10 years.
Oh, that's true.
Me too.
I'm under the chair.
There's no way they'll find me.
I'm going to the fridge.
Oh, apparently he's gonna spawn or something.
Oh yeah, so it's like prop hunt.
Oh, I'm not big enough to go under the fridge.
Wait, I can be a pizza!
Wait, how do you change?
How do you change?
I don't know, but...
Wait, I can be pizza!
I found a pizza!
I'm here now.
I'm pizza.
Wait.
You're pizza?
I'm pizza.
I found a pizza.
Oh, bread?
These are really good graphics for fucking Roblox, not gonna lie.
There's a strawberry!
Oh my god, I'm bread.
Oh my god, bread is so cute.
Get over here.
I'm gonna be under... there's no way people are gonna find me.
Guys, if we're all in the fucking same place, the chef's gonna know we're not...
I belong here.
I belong here too.
Wait, wait.
Let me get on top.
Let me stack up.
This is a cursed sandwich.
Okay, wait.
Lie down.
Okay.
Okay, wait.
Let me move up.
There's no way they'll know.
We're pizza.
Wait, what is that guy named Urinary Trash?
There we go.
It's perfect!
They'll never know!
Guys, if there's 20 apples under here, it's gonna look weird.
If there's 20 apples down here.
Maybe it'll buy us time.
We'll reach for all the apples and we're in the very far back.
We're hiding.
Oh my god, there's a croissant.
Where the fuck's the chef?
Like, what is...
Why is there not a chef?
What am I...
What's the game plan here?
Are we just food?
Did he die?
Is this it?
Hide and seek.
He is too sm...
What does that mean?
Where's the chef?
How are we supposed to get found if there's nothing to find?
Maybe it's just a round.
Is there like a timer?
Somewhere?
I feel like we've been walking around for a while.
We need to go fast.
Give me over... Oh my gosh, I'm so fucking slow.
My legs can't fucking handle this dumpy.
Weeeew.
Oh, I found the pizza under the couch.
Yeah, yeah, that was me.
I am so fucking slow.
Where's the chef?
Who are we hiding from?
I'm just gonna...
There's like so...
so many things here.
It's just... there's a me.
Oh, there's a whole other room.
Maybe he's in another room.
Are we trying to find the fucking chef?
Is that what's happening?
I'm gonna find him myself and get cooked for you at the least.
Yeah, at this point I'll find the chef.
Who's Crumpet?
Where's your face?
Crumpet?
Oh my god.
There's a baguette?
What is this?
I'm in the bathtub.
Coming soon.
How'd you guys get up there in the bathtub?
Oh, wait.
Is it just us finding other hidden items?
Is this the game?
That's the game.
It's just finding the food.
That's just finding the food.
But it's adorable.
I kinda love it.
Mmmmm.
No,
we clicked it.
It just says I'm too small.
I'm too small.
How did you even get up there?
Wait, what's this?
There's a fucking croissant!
I'm gonna be a croissant.
What is this guy?
He's literally like an ant.
I'm croissant man now.
There's like a tiny pea somewhere too.
I think that is the game.
You just fucking...
You're just finding all the items.
What croissant?
This guy's like a singular blueberry.
And he's so fucking tiny.
Oh my god, yeah, Crumpet.
Is it the Crumpet guy?
Yeah, he's so fucking tiny.
It was just a name.
Oh my god, there's a giant melon up here.
Oh wait, I'm like weighing this down.
It's like an elevator system.
This is worse Waldo, but food.
Guys.
Guys, I need... There's a tomato?
Oh my god, there's several tomatoes, but I wanna be the giant melon.
Guys, I need a giant melon.
I'm addicted to this.
I'm enchanting.
I can do this.
I'm helping this book.
I... No, I'm trying to that me and my...
me and this tomato gang are trying to walk up the fucking vacuum.
Guys!
I tried to lift him up on this elevator and I thought he was gonna climb to new heights, but all he did was just like jump off.
Oh my god, how did this tomato do it?
Let me climb.
Alright.
Wait, no!
I'm too fucking long!
I can't do this as a croissant!
I'm gonna do it as an orange.
Guys, I need to be the giant watermelon.
We're all trying to fucking...
food, like, and they're just sitting on each other.
And I'm like, is this the equivalent of roleplay?
Like, food roleplay?
Is this food roleplay?
Carol, your dough is so fuzziness!
Oh, I hear ya.
How did that other tomato do it?
Oh, there's a banana!
I see a banana up here.
I'm playing getting over it, but as fruits.
This is a hockey arena!
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Guys, how... I can't stop spinning.
Guys, how do we get up here, guys?
Guys.
Nooooo!
No!
Oh!
I knocked somebody off.
Get out, get out, get out.
I need to get up there and be a melon.
Come on.
This is it.
It looks so much better to be a circular fruit.
AHHHH!
I give up.
I can't...
I can't turn into a melon.
I've given up, Snuffy.
How do you find the melons?
It's like, literally up there.
It's up top there.
Oh my god!
All the way up here?
It's all the way up there.
Oh, you gotta get up through the Dyson vacuum.
I couldn't get up there.
I did, but then...
I got this.
We have to build a fucking ladder together to get up there.
I'm a piece of pizza.
I'm gonna be a vital... I'll be a vital...
We need a ramp.
We need a make a ramp, dragons!
Make a ramp!
Why the fuck did you jump?
Why?
Did you die?
I got shot and died!
Build a ladder!
I need that melon!
Excuse me.
Build a ladder, so...
That's the end game!
To be a melon!
We need something...
I was congested!
Somebody lie down!
Oh shit!
It's just a...
There's an egg.
We're all trying to fucking...
Do you see the tomato?
We're all trying to fucking climb with single file, guys!
Single file!
What a fucking long ass line!
Are we in the fucking UK in the queue right now?
We're at Disneyland.
There's no fast pass here.
We gotta get a fast pass.
I gotta get my app out.
I feel like we're in...
There's no fast pass.
Look at it.
Oh my god, there's a traffic jam.
Of all these fruits.
Guys!
Get up!
I need my melon!
The fucking tomato is too...
Get up!
I don't understand.
I can't fit.
Alright, here you go.
A cookie!
Oh my god, a cookie?
Guys, I don't think the tomatoes...
We need something flat and then you lie down and then you stack up amongst each other.
Become a pizza.
Yeah, yeah, all pizzas!
All pizzas and breads!
Yeah, yeah, all pizza and bread!
Change now!
Oh, I found a mango.
I got knocked into a fucking mango.
Oh my god, look!
Look at them!
They stacked up!
We've actually coordinated it.
Yeah, but I think one guy killed the other.
This guy is like a calzone.
He's a whole pie.
Oh my god, this is it!
Oh!
What?
Wait!
Wait, this is it!
Guys, collide into each other and then push me up!
Guys, we collide into each other and then we ragdoll into it.
Pump, pump, collide right now!
This is the strat!
Force myself to ragdoll up there!
Look at the people trying to make a ladder up top, Snuffy.
Do you see that?
It's actually so useful though.
Their brain is huge.
Here I come.
I'm gonna go test it out for myself.
Just taking a nice walk.
You can't get collided up there.
Oh my god, they've made like a whole...
Okay, don't walk up there.
Don't jump.
Don't jump at all.
Okay.
Nevermind.
Ignore my strat of the colliding.
It doesn't work anymore.
No!
We just need one person to be the member!
And then...
This is like that one meme from the Jimmy Neutron where it's like, the pizza is aggressive.
Just flying everywhere.
Oh my god, I just saw a pizza fall.
Oh my god, did you see that fucking apple stacking up against each other?
Hello?
I'm sorry, I didn't...
Look at the stack.
Look at this.
I can't move.
Are you stuck?
Wait, you're stuck.
Please help.
Mr. Tomato.
Swap characters.
No.
No, please.
Guys, please.
Let me fucking be a melon!
Please!
I'm going back up.
I'm back down.
Okay, I got stuck, but I'm good.
I'm coming back.
Alright.
We're single file.
Guys, stop!
Guys, let me get up!
What do they call these things?
Like immovable force?
Stop!
Bro, we can't progress!
I wanna join!
I wanna join them!
Look at them!
Wait, some of them fucking fell.
What happened?
Oh!
Oh, wrong direction!
Where did I go?
What the fuck?
Where the fuck did I go?
You need to be bigger and better.
Assert my dominance over the ladder.
I hear you.
I'm just getting pushed around like a nobody.
I got like pushed out of bounds.
Oh my god, there's a tree.
I'm here.
Maybe this is... it'll launch me.
Guys, I think I'm gonna give up, guys.
I don't think we're getting to the melon.
Let me through.
Let me through, I'm important.
I'm an orange.
Oh my god, there's an onigiri on the table.
How cute!
Guys...
I haven't seen anybody with that one.
I haven't been up here in so long.
I'm a tissue next to the onigiri.
Oh my god, we made it.
We made it, Yozo!
You and I!
We did it!
Did you get up there?
You're a melon?
No, not really.
We're trying to figure out how to get up top.
I'm gonna try and push.
Oh my god!
Oh my god, the lemon!
Oh, he kicked out the other apple!
The other apple got kicked out.
I'm ragged.
Okay, I shouldn't have ragged off.
Wait, someone got to the melon!
Oh my god, they did it!
They did it, they're a melon!
Click it!
He's literally standing there, just haunting you.
Click the melon!
I wanna see what it looks like!
Did he click it?
I got fucking squashed.
That's not a melon, that's a pumpkin.
Where the fuck is the melon?
Did he not even click it?
He wants you to have the satisfaction yourself of being the first melon on the map.
No!
Get me out of this game!
Just click the melon!
Just click it!
I just wanna know what it is.
I just wanna know what it looks like!
I'm so distressed!
He clicked!
Look at him!
He's so big!
He did it!
Look at him!
It was worth it.
Look at this giant melon.
Worth is giving me like a sense of disassociation as I get shoved to the floor.
And I'm just like, who am I?
Let's like, kick the melon.
Kill the melon.
We're all just like...
He's a pumpkin!
Huge melons!
Oh my god!
We killed the melon!
We actually killed the melon!
Good job guys!
Good job!
We did it!
Let's find another game, Snuffy.
Alright, Snuffy, find me your best game ever.
This is LG.
The best game ever?
Oh my goodness.
The best server.
Okay, okay, okay.
No pressure.
That's a lot of pressure.
No pressure or anything.
No pressure or anything, Snuffy.
Oh goodness.
Oh goodness, goodness.
Okay, okay.
Okay, okay, hold on.
I need to cook for a second.
You need to cook?
Wait.
Did I start the game for real?
Did I start the game?
Oh my god!
Wait, what?
Found hiders?
Oh, I finished the game.
Wait, what?
There was really a game the whole time?
It was trying to find the food.
That's it.
I literally restarted the server.
You were like the server owner?
What?
I'm in a different server now, I think.
I think I'm in a different server.
Yeah.
This was the game.
You gotta find all the food.
That was it.
Whee!
I found the melon and I won the game.
Dang.
I thought that was just all about teamwork.
It was literally finding all the food and then that's it.
And then you could end the game.
I found four and then the game was good enough.
I found one that's like Roblox Omegle.
Is that what it was called?
Omegle?
Oh, I found...
Is this a tomato?
Oh my god.
Or is it?
I'm me now.
Okay, we should not play Roblox Omega just for the sake of our safety.
We should not play it.
Yeah, it's got like a heart in the game.
That's dangerous.
Roblox Omega.
I don't think I feel safe playing Roblox Omega.
Just saying.
My only favorite is Nicki Minaj's Gag City.
That's not a very good one.
What?
What even is that?
It's Nicki Minaj's Gag City.
That doesn't...
Oh my god.
Okay, okay, okay.
The ultimate... This is a tough one.
There's a lot of different options here.
What does Chat think is their most favorite Roblox game?
Yeah, yeah, Chat.
What is like the ultimate game?
I've got a lot of niche games.
They're all good, but I would never say any of those are the best.
The best Roblox games.
Someone says Starscape.
What's Starscape?
I have not heard of that one.
So clearly that's a lie.
There's a lot of Starscape.
Starscape?
Yeah.
Star and Escape.
Never heard of this.
The Mimic?
Isn't that the...
Isn't that like...
Wait, isn't that...
That's famous, right?
Isn't that famous Roblox game?
The Mimic?
I don't know.
Sounds familiar.
It does sound familiar.
Good girl sorority.
People say...
What is the Mimic?
Wild Horse Island.
Wait, someone says Mimic.
Try the Mimic.
Alright.
Should we do it?
I can...
Let's see it.
Let me take a look.
It is highly rated.
It seems very popular.
Alright, let's try it.
I think it's a horror game.
How scary can Roblox be?
Of course, this is a pretty spooky game.
How scary can Roblox horror be?
Snuffy.
Come on.
Okay.
Right.
This looks pretty high def.
No.
Whoa.
How scary can this be?
Am I in the...
Where are you?
I'm in the lobby.
I think I see you.
See me?
I'm just going to take my skin away.
You did too.
You look like a regular woman now.
Guys!
Guys look at Snuffy.
Look at how you don't even have a shirt.
You're fucking naked.
What the fuck?
You have pants on.
I can't even tell.
You got like a Garfield.
Garfield!
I was gonna say Darfield!
Doki Garfield!
Oh yeah, my Garfield face!
There's saves!
So over here there's invite friends?
Isn't it this one?
Oh that's like invite real friends.
Gamer lobbies!
Oh yeah?
Might put us into another different instance.
No, wait, what?
Okay, I can invite you.
Let me hide the game.
Yeah, me too.
I don't know what happened, but I did...
Oh, it says I joined you.
Did you get my invite?
Did I?
Look at your actual Roblox notifications or something.
Wait, I have a Roblox notification?
On the website.
On the website maybe?
Oh, I see it!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, join.
Open.
I can't notification.
What are you talking about?
Okay.
Play.
Am I in?
I don't know.
I think I'm back in the lobby.
Oh, me too, me too.
Wait, how the fuck do we start?
Guys, how do we start this game?
How do we start?
We're back in the lobby!
Let's see.
Where do you start?
Play?
Just play?
Oh, there's lobbies if you play.
Oh, just play.
I'm so stupid.
Okay, do we... Chapter 1!
Chapter 1!
Chelsea, wait.
Create lobby.
There's like four fucking books.
Is this Japan?
Oh my god.
Normal multiplayer?
Oh, there you go.
I joined you.
That's me.
Hey, I just started before you started.
There was no like private lobby.
Okay.
A butterfly.
A beautiful butterfly.
How scary can a Roblox lobby be?
Whoa, I joined Fart.
Flashing lights and jump scares.
Uh oh.
Guys, get...
Oh my god, it's dark.
There's jump scares, guys.
La...
Hello.
Quinta Aztecs?
Quinta?
La Quinta Aztecs?
Do we just go inside?
Are we at a school?
Whoa, this is first person.
I feel like I'm drunk.
I've got like a wobbly camera.
Whoa.
How do we...
Where are you?
I'm right behind you.
You see me?
Yeah, I see you.
But like, where do we go?
We are drunk.
What the fuck is this?
I'm like wobbly like...
That was a crazy fucking party, man.
Oh my god, that was fucking crazy.
Let's go back to school.
Let's go back to...
Let's go on school property.
Oh my god, we're gonna break in.
Let's break in a school.
Mr. Henderson's never gonna expect this.
He took his beer out of his car.
Oh my god.
Bro, bro, we gotta go.
Mr. Henderson's never gonna expect this.
He's gonna go to his class.
And yet, bro, still, still...
Oh man, he's gonna love this.
Bro, he's gonna freak out if we rearrange all the chairs, bro.
Rearrange the chairs?
What are they gonna look like?
Just like...
They're gonna look so disorderly.
Yeah, yeah.
We're gonna be like, this isn't my chair.
Oh my god, bro, we gotta like move the desk like just one centimeter like up or something.
And then people are gonna be like, whoa, that's weird.
This doesn't feel right.
Oh my god, there's stamina.
There's stamina.
The door seems not to...
Can't prank our senior prank, man.
Senior prank?
We're doing our fucking senior prank right now, bro.
Oh, this is an invisible wall.
Where the fuck's the key, man?
I think this is the door over... over here.
Is that the door, bro?
Oh yeah.
Bro, bro, is this it?
Oh, bro!
We're gonna... he's not gonna expect this!
Principal Wally's gonna get so mad, bro.
Oh my god.
This kid doesn't have a backpack he needs?
Oh my god, bro, Principal Wally's not gonna expect this.
Why are the toilets just like out of the open?
No way, bro.
Is this how boys live their life?
Is there just like toilets with no doors?
Yeah, I mean, when they pee with the urinals, you don't need doors.
That doesn't even look like a urinal.
That's like a straight up toy toy.
Look, it's... look, there's budget cuts.
This is not a very good school.
Bro, this is a big boys' locker.
Oh my god, you look like the monster.
I think it's me as best as particles.
Your fucking head looks like the fucking monster.
Bro, bro, bro!
Bro!
Bro, I got to the gym, bro!
Oh my god, we're gonna spray paint this place.
I need to get to the other side.
Wait, why is there grass in the gym?
Yeah, why is there... what the fuck?
What's wrong with this gym?
Also, why...
Did I forgot to bring my glasses or something?
Like, why...
He adds 10 m higher.
Why is it blurry in front of me?
I got that depth of field eye around me.
Yeah, bro, I forgot to bring my glasses, man.
This is embarrassing.
A key is needed.
Yeah, find the key, bro.
Bro, I don't like the sound of my footsteps here.
Mine are not as hell, dude, I got pink boots.
Bro, I think there's mold.
I think budget cuts hit hard, man.
Yeah, this is looking... I mean, I kind of like this nature look to it, maybe.
You know?
That's kind of...
No, I found the pool!
Oh, you get the key?
No, but I found the pool, man!
That's ominous.
Don't fucking drown.
Do you know how to swim?
Oh, I do.
But I failed swimming class.
I failed my swimming lessons like three times in a row.
Because I couldn't do the frog.
The frog?!
Was it the frog and the butterfly?
I don't know.
Is the frog and the butterfly the same thing?
But I failed it like three times in a row.
And then my parents gave up.
Oh, you're swimming there?
Like, okay, I guess you'll drown.
They didn't want to... They didn't want to keep like, Oh my god, this kid plays Valorant!
Bro.
I like this cat.
Oh my god, that's Crowfeather!
That's Crowfeather.
What does it say?
Cherry blossoms bloom upon the arrival of the something new...
I know that character.
That's woman.
The arrival of the woman time.
Something women.
Cherry blossoms bloom.
Average high school ex- It smells in here.
No wonder this is a horror game.
There's a Sova player.
Oh my god, there's like trash bags.
Alright, we gotta go back.
Why do they have a computer room right next to the pool?
Bro, this guy's a freak, man.
Where the fuck is the key?
There's another door over here.
In this shed?
Oh, is there anything in the shed?
Surely nothing bad would happen in a shed.
Oh.
Oh, there's the key.
From the key now I can open the gym door.
Does it not go in my- Oh, it just stays there for- Jesus, every time I look at your face it's- Same about you!
You look so fucking smug!
Like, every time I look at your face, it's like, there's this giant fucking cat person beside me.
Oh.
Apparently we have to find the cherry blossom key.
This is not the right one?
Oh, the tree?
This is a gym, so it should be.
Alright, here we go.
We gotta go to the gym now.
Can we die in this game?
I assume we can.
I- I think we can?
Probably?
This looks like we would be at risk of like, death, yeah?
Yeah.
I think- Should be how.
This is how we die.
Oh god.
My feet scared me.
On the other side.
Don't worry.
The witch can't show up now!
We're still in the beginning.
Oh, we have infinite lives, so it doesn't matter.
It's here.
How do you know?
Cause I- Oh, there's the cherry blossom key!
A tree.
Oh, it's so pretty.
Oh, maybe we start the monster at the cherry blossom.
It started cold drinks.
Alright, let's go.
I'll offer her.
Oh, that's her!
How does Sakura tree grow in the middle of nowhere?
That's freaky.
How did it- Now this is me at 3am.
This is you at 3am.
What the fuck are you doing?
Get that string cheese from me!
From the fridge!
What the fuck are you doing?
Alright, open the door.
Okay.
She likes to mimic them.
Be cautious.
Don't let yourself be deceived.
Turn back now before it's too late.
Leon?
Who the fuck is Leon?
Leon, help!
What are you doing?
This isn't Resident Evil 4.
Wait, what is- she likes to mimic them?
Do not let yourself be- I hate this.
I hate hearing people that's- Oh my god, what the fuck?
That was a blow dryer.
That scared the shit out of me.
Okay, we- Maybe we should have like a code to like reassure if this is like you and me.
Bro!
Bro, they have Gucci bags!
Oh, is this what Gucci is?
Yeah, that's Gucci!
Oh my god.
In Sanrio?
They have Gucci in Sanrio.
Is this what Gucci is?
I'm getting everything- Woah!
Woah!
Did you see that?
Oh, I just like static in my ears.
I thought my like- my hearing aid just malfunctioned.
That was terrible.
What the fuck?
What did you see?
Did you see something?
Yeah, I saw something.
I think I made fun of this man's Gucci bag and he got mad.
That's real.
That's a real- real school experience.
I don't like that.
Oh, Doki behind us!
Oh, she mad.
She angry.
Nobody's perfect.
That's why pencils have erasers.
Oh my god.
She's gone.
You showed her your key and she left.
Oh, she's gone.
I showed you my key.
Please respond.
I'm gonna insert this somewhere.
Where was a locked door?
This one?
Wait, so do you actually have hearing aids?
No.
No, I'm good.
I've got good hearing.
I'm good hearing.
Okay, I'm gonna say, what the fuck did you do?
No, it just sounded like static.
Oh, there's a hole in me.
What's this?
Hey, if you're reading this, I don't know much.
Alright,
let's go in there.
I picked up a couple keys.
They gotta be a little bit more like... descriptive.
I picked up key number two.
Oh...
How the fuck did we get here?
Loading chain... Whoa!
Okay, I can really use these glasses.
I need these glasses, man.
Why is there a fucking pool with trees under here?
Oh, yeah, well... I feel like...
I feel like I'm gonna get... Wait, what the fuck is that?
Oh god, I got goosebumps.
What the fuck is that?
Do you see that?
I...
I... It's a... It's the woman!
Is that the woman?
It's the woman.
What are you doing here?
It's not real, it's not real!
Women are REAL!
What are you doing here?!
Name three non-protect- What happened?
Are you okay?
I don't think she liked that, dude.
I called her out on her fucking gamer blog.
Alright, opening that door!
Thank god we got this permakini.
Are we in Japan now?
No, we're in... no, this is not Japan.
This is...
This looks like one of those silly games.
This is not Japan!
These are not Japanese characters, unless they're kanji.
Oh no, we're in Japan!
That's not kanji.
Okay, yeah.
Oh my god, they took us to Japan!
There's two bookstores next to each other?
I don't know if my mom was okay with this, dude.
I didn't sign a release.
Oh my god, did you sign the permission form from your mom?
I forged it.
You forged your signature?
Bro!
That's not cool.
There's three bookstores back to back.
This is not a very smart business decision.
It is a school trip.
Maybe we're in a library section.
Oh hey, there's another...
Okay, that was so cheap.
That was such a cheap jump.
That was fucking... That was like a 2009... Like I just opened a YouTube video and... Bro, we got like FNAF, man.
There was a car driving down the street.
The fuck?
Oh my god.
That was so cheap, man.
Oh yeah, that's not... Yeah, fuck you.
Fuck you, man.
This is not FNAF, man.
Oh my god.
Alright, next door.
Next door.
Apparently we die in this next part.
Oh yeah?
I have the key to the hidden door.
Is this like run for your life kind of moment?
Am I finally gonna use my stamina?
Wait, I hear people.
I think we're gonna die, Snuffy.
I think... I think we're gonna die, Snuffy.
Just stay to the right.
You don't leave.
That's the maze trap, right?
Stay to the right.
Yeah, maze trap.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
I don't like this.
I don't hear her anymore yet.
I don't like this, Snuffy.
I don't feel so good.
I think she's around the corner.
It's a big maze.
What the...
Snuffy, maybe Roblox games can be scary.
Oh yeah?
Yeah, you're feeling the stress?
Uh oh.
I just...
Oh my god.
I just... I just see you fucking just fall.
You just... You just... You just...
She just fucking touches you and then you fucking just fell.
It was literally like a tall woman standing emoji.
Just like she just stood there and...
I saw a woman and died.
Oh my god.
You...
Okay, one more time.
One more time.
Let me see if I can get through this.
Let's see.
Okay, let's do this.
I don't think that was right.
I think that was a dead end.
I think so too.
Alright.
We can do this together as a team.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wait, what do you think?
What do you... Oh, wait.
What's this?
Here.
It has to be here.
There's like stuff here.
It's a dead man.
There's a key.
Yeah, I got the key.
Key two.
Okay, key two.
I got key three.
No, it's called... What is key three?
Oh, key three.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, but where's the door?
I didn't see a door.
I didn't see...
Wait, how do we hide from her?
Like, what's the mechanism?
I don't know.
Well, okay, she has to go to one of us and then whoever lives...
Run past her.
This is a trap.
Oh my god, I'm so scared.
Oh, here we go.
We have to look for the doors.
Okay, let's go.
Okay, okay.
Alright.
Door.
Where the door at?
I wonder if it's the same area always.
Oh, the last one.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So it's like, I know this game like the back of my hand.
Oh.
Bro, what the fuck?
There's so many games.
Why...
Wait, where did you go?
Where did you go?
I got scared.
I'm scared too.
I'm dead.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't know...
I don't know where you are.
I'm dead.
I'm coming.
Where are you?
Where are you, Snuffy?
I'm dead.
Uh-oh.
Oh, no.
Where am I?
I'm in several dead ends.
We split up.
What happened to teamwork?
I'm coming.
I'm not coming.
I'm not coming anymore.
Oh my god oh my god oh my god ok you can run you can't run from her you can you can you can you can!
I'm back in the beginning!
I'm back in the beginning I'm back in the beginning!
No no no.
Ran right out!
I just ran out.
You found it though!
You found it?!
Yeah yeah yeah yeah.
Where is it?!
If you go over can I just die a comb to you?!
I think so.
So... Is it to the right or to the left?
It was to the left.
It's to the... Oh!
You did it!
Oh, nice!
Just one of us has to find it.
We did it!
Yay!
I contributed.
Look, I found the key, you found the door.
Yeah, yeah.
She chased me.
That was fucking scary.
She literally... The funniest thing is like, she doesn't do anything.
She just like stands, like standing like...
You have like a Discord, like a...
stabilizer thing or something.
So when you start screaming, it was just static because it was so loud.
Let me check my Discord settings.
Oh my God.
It was just like...
It was just like, what the fuck?
Sorry!
Oh my God.
Oh my God, wait.
You start playing music.
Oh, I have echo cancellation.
Oh yeah, noise suppression.
Automatic game control.
All this shit.
Oh my God, no.
It is so funny.
I'm so fucking sorry.
Oh my God.
My Discord audio is probably so terrible.
Discord shakes fresh and early.
Dang it.
Okay.
There she is.
You first, m'lady.
What?
I just... I did the last one.
You go ahead.
Okay, fine, fine.
I'm gonna go to the left.
There's no way.
Oh my God.
Okay.
I didn't give her eye contact.
See?
She didn't hurt me because I didn't look.
It was just text jump scare.
Yeah, it was just text.
Okay, where do we go?
Talk to the farmer.
Where would the farmer be?
Where's the farmer's daughter?
Whoa.
Oh, we're gonna walk and dead this?
I have a bag.
I have an inventory, but there ain't no inventory.
Well, I haven't picked up anything but keys, dude.
We're gonna walk and dead this farmer.
Walk and dead this farmer?
Yeah, let's eat his legs.
Oh, I found it.
We're gonna... Wait, where are you?
I haven't seen you around before.
Oh, there's the farmer.
Hello.
We're not from here.
It says click to continue.
Oh, well, please be careful around here.
My brother recently went into the city and he hasn't been back since.
I don't know how much longer I'll be able to stay here.
She's probably already watching us as I speak.
If you've seen a lady playing the Biwa, it's already too late.
We did!
I did see that lady.
We saw that lady together.
Can I...
Yeah.
How about I live here?
And bring her here with you?
I guess we go straight, right?
I guess so.
Why are we being haunted?
Because we picked up a key?
Explore the cave, search for the door.
Again?
That's because like...
Bro, I just wanted to do my senior prank, man.
Senior prank?
This is a different type of senior prank.
Now we travel to Japan.
Accidentally showed up into the cursed lands of the Japanese farmhouses.
Oh, I don't like this.
I think these are the weeping angels.
Is that like a Doctor Who thing?
Yeah, I think that's the...
Like you have to have eye contact with them or they're gonna start fucking coming over to us.
I don't know.
Are you a Doctor Who fan?
I watched Doc...
Oh, they are!
They are!
They are the weeping angels!
I'm fucking doing it!
What was that?
Oh my god, another dead person.
Is this the brother?
No, it's a woman.
Another dead woman.
I knew it was weeping angel.
There was no other explanation why they were stones.
Oh, there's more of them.
Oh my god, there's more of them.
Oh, oh.
Look at them!
I don't think they...
I don't think they stop moving if you look at them though.
Oh, oh.
Oh.
They're everywhere.
Oh, they're everywhere.
In your...
In your mic!
Oh, are you?
Oh my god, I'm sorry...
I think so.
Oh.
I'm so...
Yes, let's...
Yes, you just stand there.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Truth!
Oh god.
Oh god, my stamina.
Wait, am I going backwards?
Oh god.
I don't know, I'm going forwards.
Woah, woah, woah, woah, woah, woah, woah, woah, woah, woah.
We're trying to...
I don't know where I am.
I don't remember which way I was going.
Oh, don't worry.
One of us has to make it.
If I die, you're gonna have to figure it out though.
Did I do it?
I think it was this way.
I think I'm going the wrong way.
I'm gonna go this way.
Oh, there's the crazy lady!
Oh, every time I look at her, I get goosebumps!
I'm in the house, Nuffy!
The original one or the new one?
I don't know!
New house?
New house!
I don't even... I'm in... I'm in the...
The crumbly...
New house!
Looks like that is the only place to go.
I can go left.
Don't worry, Nuffy.
I'm gonna beat this game for us.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I didn't!
Oh, I thought I died.
Oh, thank god!
We're in the hotel?!
From Japan to a hotel?!
We're getting a tour of the city, a beautiful garden, and now we get a full expense paid trip to a hotel.
Oh my god!
I hate this game.
Wait, what's this?
What's... who's...
Chat with...
Chat with hamburger...
Who the fuck is hamburger?!
Sheesh!
Bro, she has a Club Penguin shirt.
This is all her doing, man.
Who is she?
Oh, you go.
I don't know!
What is she doing?
Japanese myth I have heard about.
I don't recall much about it, but I do know she can bring you anywhere she pleases.
Eventually, those targeted by her fall into madness.
Are you into madness?
You're like a penguin.
Clapping on the floor.
She's like a Club Penguin fan.
Hamburger cheese.
Is this like a real person or is this just like...
I feel so.
Maybe it's like a Make-A-Wish.
Her Make-A-Wish is to... I mean...
Okay, is it fucked up?
Because like she's in a wheelchair and I was like, maybe her Make-A-Wish is to be in a Roblox game.
Like, is that... is that fucked up for me to say?
Like...
I... I...
It's... I don't know!
I'm just wondering!
Like, why is there like hamburger...
Why is there a freaking hamburger cheese?
I mean, I think that like maybe it's somebody in the lobby or something.
It just like picks a player that was like in the same lobby.
But she's in the wheelchair!
Where are you?
Oh my god, Doki, wait.
I... I can't stay here.
My presence is...
My presence is being hunted.
Wait, what?
Is that you over there?
Ohhhh!
She's on me!
She's on me now!
Did you die?
No, no, she just kinda stopped coming for me.
Oh my god, dude.
I hear her.
Bro she's, she's fucking...
Fucking playing that fucking guitar right now behind me.
She's literally strumming!
She's strumming on that guitar!
Menacingly.
No, no, nooooooo!
AHHHHHHHHHH!!!!
Thank you for the elevator music.
Where are you?
Where did you go?
I don't know what to do.
She's like impossible to avoid.
Oh She's actually only capable of moving in a singular direction.
Bro, where the fuck are you?
I'm about to win us a game.
I hate this bro.
Whoever suggested this fucking game.
Fuck you man.
You didn't come with me to the next floor.
I did.
I was already in the next floor.
I got I got there before you got there.
Oh, I thought you died.
I thought that's why you screamed.
What are there's a look at this maze.
Did you see this map?
Oh my god, there's a map?
Take a look.
I hate this game.
Okay, so simply okay so Bro, I fucking hate this these cheap jump scares.
Take a left.
Take a right.
Take a take a straight.
How do you know where to go?
Okay, okay.
I look there's a map right here.
You just gotta memorize it.
Okay, there's a map.
Okay, okay you're gonna fucking figure this out for me because I don't know.
Take a left.
Take another left.
Take a right.
All right, I'm at it.
I'm I'm walking.
I don't know why Okay, oh I see you i'm right behind you you're right behind me Yeah There's a monster right in front of me.
So we gotta fucking figure out how to do this together.
Oh, there you are Okay, there's a there's the girl like right in front of us Okay, okay, let's split up one of us has to figure out.
Okay, i'll go right Let's split up gang Okay skip it truly one of us can find it Yeah, yeah, yeah She'll be dividing our attention.
So one of us will die.
One of us will succeed.
Oh, that's me.
That's me.
That's me Goodbye
I'm just oh there is a map what the fuck It's pretty big Okay front guys memorize this map right now for me Okay front forward left forward left forward Right Okay Oh, that was awful.
That was really awful.
That was so bad.
Oh my god.
That's you.
Okay.
Let's figure this out together Did you look at the map?
Oh, yeah, let me okay, okay refresher.
Okay.
Okay, let's look at the refresher Okay, left f l f l r f l f l f l f l l Wait, what?
Okay, all right guys type in like flrs type in flrs guys
First direction is Yeah, yeah, yeah r r Guys, I don't know.
I think we already fucked it up.
I think we already fucked it up guys I feel like Guys, oh no and then f here f here, right f I trust you and then what?
F right l Okay And then and then f right F yeah, we f we skipped it ff.
No, or was it?
Oh, it was an r Was i'm going r?
Yeah, it was an r.
One of us has to f This always works in the movies Yeah, and then I'll go f And then I'm gonna go l This is And then I don't know if you go f Okay, okay, I'll go I'll go r And then l I'm going f All right, that is a That is a dead this is exactly where I died.
I think I think this is where I died last time I think this is where I died last time Okay, I'm going f Okay, I definitely went the wrong way I She's on me she's on me She's on me Oh my god it's the guitar strummer She's on the ceiling Oh my god you got the fucking The ceiling climber I got the guitar She's got the ceiling climber I got the batar There's two of them?
Oh no Oh no where do we It's over.
It's so over.
I literally hear you running from her.
I'm so lost.
I'm so lost, guys.
Wait, you did it!
Oh my god, we did it!
I knew splitting up was the right idea.
We distracted them.
We divided their attention.
We're in my now.
Divide and conquer.
Just like my favorite war politician said.
End of chapter one.
We did it.
I think this is a good time to call it.
We beat the game, guys!
Guys, we beat the game!
Oh my god!
We're gamers!
Where's the key?
Back to the lobby.
Let's go.
Get me out of here.
Roblox core games, man.
They need something else.
Oh my god.
We beat the game!
I never trust the recommendations on these.
Maybe Jump Scare City.
Oh my god.
Beat the game.
The Mimic.
Another easy win.
Oh my god.
GG's.
Next time I'm taking us to fucking Kitten Simulator.
Fuck this game, man.
I was like, it's a Roblox game.
They're not scary.
Bro, what did I play?
It's good to play a game because I just moved into a house for the first time.
So I'm glad I can scream.
Yeah.
Sorry about the echo.
I'm proud that this room is probably really bad for echo.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
This is like your first day streaming back to from Apple TV.
After your move.
Yeah.
And we played Roblox.
I'm so excited.
Big Roblox stream.
Yeah.
The Roblox stream.
Christening the new house with a big Roblox stream.
That was so fun though.
I had a great time.
Oh yeah.
Me too.
If you ever want to play again, please let me know.
I have a million of games.
Oh my god.
No.
We should totally play Content Warning.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
That's...
I'm so excited.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
We should totally do it.
That would be so fun.
You want next week?
Yeah.
Next week we got 4K.
We should totally farm it before the game dies.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
I'm totally blind to it.
So I'll save.
I'll save my innocence for...
Yeah.
Me too.
The only thing I know is that clip I sent.
I'm sure we will discover more cursed objects.
That was fantastic.
Thank you so much.
This was so much fun.
It was.
That was really fun.
Thanks for giving me the Roblox tour.
Oh, I'm so excited.
I was afraid to bring you to some of the darker ones because I was just like, how deep is this like hole going to go?
Like, how should I introduce somebody who's not seen a lot of games?
I think you're ready.
I think you're ready to see how far this Roblox goes.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
VLAN?
I'll figure out.
I'll get like the, the like a secret internet, like save of VLANs.
Yeah.
No!
Thank you again, Snuffy.
Thanks for the collab.
Thank you, Jolie.
I'm going to go talk to my...
I'm going to go chat now, but thank you, GGs.
Content warning next week, guys.
Next week.
Hell yeah.
All right.
Bye bye.
See you later.
Thank you guys.
Thank you.
Bye.
Oh my God.
That was really fun.
That was actually...
I had a great... this was my first time actually like collabing with Snuffy.
We've been wanting to do a collab for like a while now.
Like I said before, at first we wanted to do the Warrior Cats RPG.
Yeah.
And then we have like, oh my God, she gone.
She gone.
But I'm really happy to be able to talk to her.
Like the first hour was like, literally like podcast time.
Oh my gosh.
Well, how do I... well, give me a sec.
Neb, thank you for the aqua soup.
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much!
Okay, let me fix this real fast.
Let me...
Let me fix the collab room real fast, chat.
Okay.
Leave.
I wanna leave.
How do I leave?
Is this it?
Oh my gosh, I'm so baby when it comes to this.
I think this is good.
But yeah!
I hope you guys really enjoyed...
Really enjoyed like...
Snuffing on the channel.
It was nice talking to her for like the first hour.
Just having a little podcast before we even start the game.
And then the scuff of us setting up like...
The collab room and everything.
But I definitely had a great, great, great, great, great time.
Thank you everybody for watching everybody!
I'm going to...
Do some behind the scenes work.
Gonna prep for my karaoke that's on Friday.
So I'll see you guys next time everybody.
I hope you guys had a fun time.
As always everyone, stay hydrated, posture check.
Get up and move around to get that blood flowing.
And if you stay up for me, head to bed.
Because you deserve it!
I'll see you guys next time everybody.
Bye guys!
Bye!