Hello everybody.
Oh, wait, I'm locked in by the way, no.
Ahahahahaha!
Okay... Let me see...
Sorry, I was late because I was playing Marvel Rivals before I could stream Marvel Rivals.
Um...
Alright, now... Okay!
So...
I... Yeah...
We're back.
And... We are not doing any curse of Ra...
or any curses or anything.
Oh, wait, sorry.
I had my mic on my recording settings.
Give me a sec.
I forgot about that.
Okay, now I should sound... there you go.
I just sound better now.
Oh, I'm like loud too.
Oops, sorry.
Give me a sec.
I have everything on my... oh, wait, no, I'm fine.
I have everything on my recording settings.
So, now it's fine.
Okay, so...
So, alright, so I'm sort of climbing a little bit.
I think, I think.
So, there's no curses.
There's no curses right now.
Because if you fucking curse me, I will continue to cancel streams and just replace it with Marvel Rivals.
If we don't make it to top 500, I will replace all my streams with Marvel Rivals.
Until we get top 500.
So, you better hope that I fucking get top 500 today.
You better fucking hope that.
Or we will never play God of War.
I will fucking hold God of War hostage until I get top 500.
You think I fucking care?
I care about numbers.
I care about being a top 500 gamer right now, alright?
I...
So, don't you fucking act cocky here.
Don't you be a little fucking bitch and curse me guys.
Because we're gonna be here forever.
If we do not make it to top 500 today.
Alright.
So, yes.
We now have... we have now optimized our... our queue now.
So, we have Wanted and SK playing with me.
And SK and Wanted are... well, to be fair, they're both... well, at least, like, I'll actually have DPS players this time.
Because for some fucking reason, every other player in this entire Marvel Rivals lobby are getting too many DPS players.
But I have the opposite of that problem.
I have too many support players in my team.
So, to fix that problem, now I have two DPS players.
I'd rather have too many DPS players than...
Then... oh, okay.
Now that I said that...
Alright.
Alright, now I have four DPS players.
Now...
Alright.
I... you know what?
No, I deserve that.
I actually...
I... I fucking deserve that.
You know what?
No, that's fine.
Carl, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
The cloud nose goes on after it hits the eight... six hour... the eight hour mark.
Wait, when was the last time I put the cloud nose on?
I don't even remember.
Carl, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
The cloud nose goes on when we hit a breaking point.
We've not yet hit our breaking point.
We're still okay.
No, it's still okay.
We have... we have yet to hit our breaking point.
Also Jarrah, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Alright, here we go.
Maybe we'll get to see plat one again.
Wouldn't that be fucking crazy?
What the fuck?
Oh my god.
What?
What the fuck is going on here?
What the fuck?
I don't even... what the fuck is going on?
We lived?
I mean, okay.
Yay, we lived!
Now this is my house now.
See, look.
It's not too bad.
Guys, that wasn't too bad.
It looked pretty rough in the loading screen, not gonna lie.
In the starting screen it looked rough, but like, we made it work.
We made it work.
I do hope I end top five.
Like, I could end top 500 though.
Oh.
Alright, that was not my fault.
I could not see him.
Well, I think he's gonna fucking eat me.
Oh shit!
Sorry, I didn't realize.
Sorry, I didn't realize SK was getting beat up behind me.
No, no BC for now.
I wanna chill a little bit before I get into BC territory.
I wanna chill.
No, that's the worst part.
The worst part is that for Qs, DPS...
Oh shit, again!
DPS gets more... Oh, what the fuck?
I thought he would go the other way, not gonna lie.
Jesus Christ.
Oh my god, okay.
I'm ready to dance.
It's dancing time.
It's still dancing time.
What was I gonna say?
Oh yeah, DPS gets more... I don't even know what it's called.
LP?
What is it called for Marvel rivals?
SR?
Oh my god, Captain America.
I'm dancing.
I dance so hard.
Points?
Oh yeah, DPS gets more points.
I don't know.
Overwatch is SR.
Apex is LP.
What the fuck is Marvel rivals thing called?
I need to get some gamer subs.
I'm not okay.
Gotta hit a wall.
You can tell I'm not okay right now.
Alright, I'm going this way.
Where's our tank?
Oh, there he is.
He's gonna put 19 inches of venom.
Not on me though.
Oh my god!
It's fine, we're fine.
Where the fuck does Spider-Man go?
Oh, I'm scared.
Please, guys.
Your team's capture progress, guys.
Oh no, not the Assemble.
It's fine, we're safe here.
Oh, I don't feel safe anymore.
I need to reload.
Oh no, I almost got it!
I almost got him!
I was so close.
Poppy, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Good luck on the rank.
Today's my birthday.
I wanted to wish you luck and share money.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, dear Kofi.
Oh, time to enter the portal.
Dance!
I almost ran and danced, girl!
I don't know if you guys noticed this, but I almost dropped into the hole.
How did we...?
Guys, we can't leave.
We can't leave the...
No!
Oh, thank god.
Oh no.
There's so many people that need heals.
I got PTSD over Hella.
Because I feel like...
I feel like Hella's always targeting me.
Oh god.
Got another portal.
Guys!
No!
Guys,
where's our portal?
Where the fuck is our portal?
Dr. Strange, make a... Oh, he's dead.
He's dead.
I actually won because of the portal.
Because of the portal.
Portal!
No!
Oh, Strange can't do much no more?
Nice.
That's what I like to hear.
After this, I'm gonna make some gamer subs.
I need to lock in.
I need to fucking lock in.
I don't even know who to... Okay, I'll give it to one dude.
I always give it to...
I give it to whoever I'm playing with.
So they can't complain about lack of heals on their stream.
That's the only... That's the only reason.
Alright, here we go.
It's optimal.
Are you real?
King is like, okay.
Okay, come on.
Oh, he's so low.
Come on.
He's dead.
What the fuck?
Oh my god, I didn't even notice him.
I was like wondering who fucking is beating me at the fuck up in the back.
I need to like get my awareness needs to be a bit better.
I legit was so confused.
I was like, I'm getting beat up.
Who could it be?
Oh, you mean the giant fucking incredible Hulk in the back?
Hulk is one of the sneakiest characters out there.
I don't know if you guys know that.
I'm gonna say it.
I know like...
Oh my god, what is he doing?
He's so low.
Oh!
Jump down here if you don't... Sorry.
I jumped down.
I'm stalling.
I stalled for so long.
Please guys, no.
Don't say that guys.
We need to end this fast.
Guys, don't say that.
Guys, please.
Please.
I can't say that.
We'll be fine.
I believe.
Okay.
Oh, I'm locking in.
There's like a Psylocke right behind us.
She's really annoying.
She's being a little bitch right now.
What the fuck?
Pizza roll.
Are you okay?
Nice.
Okay, this is way too close for comfort though.
This is way too close for comfort.
The games are getting like harder because people are learning how to play.
So like, people are being like more coordinated.
And they... Ohhhhkay.
Oh shit.
Double I.
No.
Me too.
Dad's with me.
I'm also ready.
I'm ready.
Oh shit.
One fear.
No.
Nice.
I always get solo ulted by Psy.
I think it's because like...
I mean, that's literally how you gotta play Psy.
You just gotta solo ult the fucking support.
But by God, it makes me so mad.
Because I can't do anything about... How do you hit that?
How do you hit an ice hunter?
What, you gotta have like fucking eyes that can see 500 frames per second?
Is that how?
Like, how?
I literally have to like... My eyes have to be like 500 frames per second.
By the way, guys.
I think you'll be proud to find out.
I'm not one trick anymore.
I can play Cloak and Dagger.
Now I can play both Cloak and Dagger, guys.
I finally realized how to play Cloak, guys.
I fucking figured it out, chat.
I figured it out.
She's suppressing a 3-trick.
And then like... And then my Mantis is not that of a troll pick anymore.
Now... Now...
I can like sort of use my ability.
So like, you know, if Luna gets picked, that's fine.
It's not the end of the world this time.
For once, it's not the end of the world.
I'm not... I won't be that mad.
Oh my god, I'm sorry.
How did I not kill her?
Oh, she was one!
How is she still alive?
I think... Oh.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Oh, shit.
Oh!
Oh, shit!
Guys, we gotta... Hey, guys.
Oh my god, that's so fucked up!
I hate Groot.
I fucking hate... Oh my god, I... I...
I'm full of you.
Oh my god, I hate Groot.
I'm gonna burn all trees after this.
I'm taking a while.
I'm just gonna window shop.
Oh my god!
Okay.
What?!
Okay,
I actually did not expect that.
I didn't think she would actually see me.
Holy... That's crazy!
That was such a crazy peek from her.
I hear a Psylocke, though.
I hear her fucking footsteps.
I hate trees.
I fucking hate trees.
Okay, we're fine.
We're fine.
We're okay.
Fuck trees.
We're so okay.
Oh, come on!
Give me this win!
Please!
No!
Pizza roll!
Oh my god.
Oh, pizza roll.
You gave me a little heart attack there.
Because we cannot re-contest this if we lose.
Oh, they have Hella ult, but I don't think I have...
Oh!
Speaking of Hella ult...
What?!
I can't defend all of that.
I can't defend all that.
What do I do?
I'm just...
I'm just a little...
Fuck me!
I just have one ult!
I just have one fucking ult!
If this person, if Penny Parker, shows up on my stream...
We ban them.
For taking my elo.
That's right.
If you show your face in my stream...
You're getting banned!
For taking my fucking elo!
That's what you fucking get!
No one takes my elo and fucking lives in my chat!
No one!
Takes my elo!
Where are you Penny?
Where the fuck are you?
I'm gonna go get...
Oh shit, nevermind.
I was gonna say, I'm gonna get some Anuka honey.
No, don't say that!
I was climbing!
Chat!
I was actually climbing!
Guys!
Don't say that!
I was actually...
Going up!
Wait, wait, wait.
We were actually fucking going up!
I saw my elo rise!
I stream and then I get cursed.
Oh my god.
It's the life.
It really is.
It's the streamer life.
No we don't, we don't need the opposite.
We don't need the opposite of that, guys.
Please.
I was almost back to plat one.
Guys, okay.
I'm gonna lock in for this game.
No talking for me.
Because I'm resting my voice right now.
Okay guys.
This game, we're resting our voice.
Alright.
I believe.
Alright, lock in.
Alright guys, it's time to lock in.
Doki is locking in.
I'm putting it on.
Doki is locking in!
It's happening!
Okay, that guy fucking is an idiot.
How the fuck did he die like one second?
Okay, lock in.
I'm moving so much, I'm sorry.
Oh
my god, I'm so unlucky.
I'm so unlucky.
I had to peek because I wanted heals.
Jesus Christ.
This Hanzo or Hawkeye is really good.
Oh my god, he's so good!
He's actually crazy!
We have zero kills.
Guys.
Guys, I think I started this stream and I got jinxed.
I think...
I think I started this stream and then the curse became...
I thought I got...
I legitimately thought there was no curse because we were winning all our games but then I think the curse only works if I...
if I stream.
I think that's it.
Legitimately, I think I figured it out.
It only works when I'm streaming.
Oh no, please.
Don't root this.
I'm so scared.
Okay, we're fine.
We're so healthy.
Oh.
I hear footsteps and I'm scared.
I'm scared.
I hear footsteps and I don't want to die.
Oh, come on.
Oh, it's the goat feet!
It's just goat feet.
I was like, what's that footstep?
Alright.
We're all gonna dance.
Cause we love to dance.
Woo!
Okay.
Oh my god.
Oh.
No, no.
Oh my god, I...
No.
No!
He peeked me!
I didn't think he would look at me.
I thought he was fucking blind.
I'm scared.
Guys!
Guys, burn the trees!
Fuck on trees!
Okay, nice.
Nice.
Okay, they have two fights left.
I need ult, though.
Please.
I hear him now.
I think it's bad that Groot is in this game, cause now it makes me really fucking hate trees.
Like...
I...
Oh,
thank god.
I was gonna die.
Okay.
I had to.
Nice, we got Loki, though.
That's good.
We had to.
Okay, that's good.
That's good that Loki forced my support ult, cause he died for it.
Oh, thank god.
I will become the one slayer.
Because of Marvel Rivals, I'll fucking...
I'll become the one slayer.
I now understand the one slayer.
You know, I sang his song, so how bad can I be was like super catchy, but now...
Now I understand his message.
Now I actually understand his message.
Please, no.
Every tree, every tree I see, I'm gonna bring a Doki Amber Doge to it, and I hope he pees on that tree.
I hope all the nourishment he gets is just from my dog.
If it rains, I'm gonna fucking put like a tarp around a tree, my designated tree, so he'll never get water.
And then every morning and night, I'll bring my dog over to that tree, and that's all it's gonna drink.
That's all.
I'll pick a tree, and then I'll be like, I'll name you Groot.
And then maybe I'll buy another dog so I can target two trees.
That's true.
Damn, Doki, that's...
Bro, Doki, that's really fucking crazy.
It's time.
Maybe I'll live.
Oh my god.
Pizza roll, please.
Pizza roll, you're scaring me, pizza.
Get the tree, get the tree!
That's all I care about.
Get the fucking tree.
Nice.
If we run out of oxygen, that's the risk I'm willing to take.
You can fucking credit me if we suddenly run out of oxygen.
I'm willing to take all credit for it.
So I can finally sell what I've always wanted to sell.
Bottled air.
I can finally be like my Oshie.
Jesus Christ.
Goodbye.
Wait, guys, I wanna know.
Does my ult outheal in the moral?
Skating.
Does it outheal in the moral?
Cause I know it does not outheal a fucking Magneto ult.
I don't know, try.
Guys, I can't just try it.
I can't just try it.
Yeah, fuck that Pacific clone.
Oh, she's one!
Alright, we're five.
You fucker!
We will damage boost.
We will damage all of this.
There's no way.
You actual fucker.
I will do a dance-off with you.
You think, you think you're a better dancer than me?
I've been dancing for definitely more than 20 hours.
Hey, I know that guy!
Not really.
He's in my queue though.
I'm gonna use the bathroom.
I can't believe I got 99.
I- oh my god, I'm- AAAAAH!
Okay, I shouldn't.
I need to- I need to calm down.
Doki, you got it.
Yeah, calm down, Doki.
Oh my god.
Fucking...
Wow.
I can't wait to have Mr. Ballwasher as my tank.
At least we know he practices good hygiene.
Am I winning?
For once in my life, in Marvel Rivals, I am.
I know it's a crazy concept, guys.
It's fucking crazy.
Oh my god, we have two- Is it my birthday?
We have two tanks?
Oh my god.
Oh my god, happy birthday!
Happy birthday!
Oh my god.
I don't think I've seen two tanks in a long time.
Oh.
Okay, is Google mapping right now?
Is Google mapping?
Oh, I'm fucking just behind their Jeff and their Hela.
I froze somebody.
Don't worry.
I'll come in soon.
I should come in before like we- Oh my god.
Oh my god!
The portal literally just closed!
Oh.
Oh!
You guys, um...
It's like I wasn't- You know, they didn't know.
Oh my god, did it again!
That did not happen again!
Oh my god!
I'm just- Dude, fuck me, I guess.
Oh my god.
I'm not aware of my surroundings there.
No, I take full blame for that.
I take full blame for that.
I was not aware of my surroundings on that specific map.
Like...
Oh my god.
And then the Jeff to eat me at the end.
That's so fucked.
That's actually so fucked.
Alright, now I'm aware of my surroundings.
It's not gonna happen again, I swear.
Okay.
Um, okay.
I don't even know if we should engage with this.
Like...
Jesus Christ.
I'm-
Jesus.
You're just- You'll just live forever, I guess.
Until you don't?
Oh!
Oh, I time!
Yippee!
Alright, okay.
Alright.
Uh, that's a lot of ults.
Oh, that is- That was a lot of ults there.
Yeah, I- Yeah.
Hahaha.
I will admit that the first fight I trolled, but like I picked it back up.
It's not fully my fault anymore.
I just think our Venom is having a rough time.
I have to heal- Okay.
I can portal.
I'm portaling in for now, dude.
All I'm saying is, Japheth's gonna fucking eat us.
Oh!
Oh my god!
Bro, Japheth just- Japheth was just there!
And then Japh- Hahaha!
Oh my god, he fucking jumped down!
And then- And then Japheth was right there!
I think- I just think it- Oh my-
Not only will I kill our trees, burn all the trees, but I'll find every shark out there in the ocean.
Why do we need sharks?
I think like, they make Japh- Hoping to increase awareness of sharks, and how they're cute.
But, it was the opposite effect.
Cause now, in my head, I'm thinking, Jaws was right, and we should've kept going.
Wait- Hahaha!
Now, in my head, I wish we kept going with Jaws, and the message.
I added- They added more reasons for my hate.
I didn't hate sharks before, but now I do.
I used to be like, those weak fuckers, who were like, Guys, please, sharks are good people.
Every year, only one- Only five people die from shark wounds, every year, which is very low compared to like, vending machines.
And now I'm thinking, I don't care about any stats.
But like, I know what's going on in Marvel Rivals.
Hahaha!
Oh my god!
Oh my god, please.
Oh, I stayed on point for as long as I could!
Winnable!
Guys, I don't think that was winnable, guys.
I don't- I don't think that was winnable.
Oh shit, what?
Wait, on stream labs?
Oh hey, that's not me.
It's fine.
I'm- I'm so fine.
I'm- I'm okay.
I am okay.
I'm okay.
It's not 99 anymore.
That's all that matters.
Look guys, I think- I think it's doable.
We just- You know, we get the bad losses out of the way.
And then- Do we get the same- Okay, we did it.
Oh my god, we got- We didn't avoid him!
Why did we avoid the fuck- Oh.
We did not avoid.
We forgot to- We didn't avoid this guy.
I think it's dumb that you can't avoid here.
I wanna avoid here.
On here.
I want- I want to be able to avoid right here.
You can't avoid- You have to wait until you're at the- The game- You have to wait until you're at the game end screen.
No.
Don't say that.
Four hours.
That's the max, I think.
Well.
I predict it'll take me four hours.
I- Why can't, like, the enemy team have, like, fucking four plus support players?
Why is it always me?
I predict four hours.
I just need to get- The moment I get to plat one, it's gonna be smooth sailing.
Right there.
Right here.
Right now.
The moment- The moment- Plat one.
Things will be okay.
I won't fall off.
Round two.
I'm not gonna fall off this time.
In the back, when they TP.
They're gonna TP, aren't they?
Oh, they're not TPing.
Oh my god.
They have a Hanzo.
I'm scared.
A good Hanzo with this healer is actually so scary, though.
Okay, it's fine.
I'm thinking right now.
I'm using my brain.
I'm staying on high- Oh, shit.
No, I should go to my team.
I'm focusing so hard.
I'm not gonna do the fancy jump.
I'm just gonna use the stairs for once in my life.
I'm not gonna use the shortcut.
Oh, there they are.
I'm trying!
Guys,
I think we should touch.
No!
I got it!
What the fuck?!
I can't get that to the portal!
That portal was fucking crazy!
I got kidnapped by my own fucking ally!
That portal was such a- I was like, where am I?
Where did I go?
Like, where did I go?
Oh my god.
That was so unlucky.
That's actually- That's actually what a crazy portal that griefed me.
That portal actually griefed the shit out of me.
No.
No, I felt it too.
I felt it in my heart.
I knew that was gonna happen too.
I was like, I feel like I'm about to get eyed.
Yeah, no, I'm definitely avoiding him.
When I- If I have the time- It gives me the fucking time to avoid.
Oh my god.
Bro!
You're so fast!
I don't know what to do.
I don't know.
Like...
I don't fucking know.
It's okay, it's not me, guys.
At least we know one's name.
It's not me.
Jesus Christ, our Venom feeds so much.
That's the biggest issue.
I think our Venom is just a feeder.
Oh, who did he take?
I'm ready to put on a show.
Yippee!
Yay!
Kill him.
If you don't kill him, I will fucking cry.
Please!
Oh my god.
He's getting closer.
Don't worry, he can't see my face yet.
He's dead.
I'll live.
Oh my god!
I'm sorry.
I don't know how the fuck you live.
He's one.
I don't know who I'm saying that to, because I'm not in the voice chat.
But guys, he's one.
Please, I swear to god.
I thought that was just for him.
Venom.
Venom, please.
Oh my god, okay.
You know what?
We take this.
What the fuck is he doing there?
Oh my god, please.
Oh, I have to use this.
Please.
No!
No, I also hate all spiders too.
I hate a lot of things.
I used to never hate a lot of things, but after playing Marvel Rivals, I started to hate.
I'm the hater now.
I don't know, fuck it.
Seeing, if I, every time I see a Peter Parker, by the way, I'm definitely afraid of bugs, but like, if I, I would fucking go outside and squish a spider.
For every time a Peter Parker annoys me.
Run.
Run, you're such a bitch.
Alright, I'm going outside and squishing a spider.
Alright.
No!
I'm at my hater arc now.
This is my hater arc.
Are we
fucked up?
Nope.
I get zero heals?
Who?
Who is it?
What do you mean you get zero heals?
All I did was heal.
Who was it?
There's no way.
All I do is fucking clap.
No, it's not the Venom that's complaining.
It's the Doctor Strange.
I'm like, that cannot be true.
All I do is fucking clap.
I haven't existed in any other way.
All I do is go, clap, clap.
Okay, not that.
I don't want to waste my cooldown yet.
Alright.
I feel like we do need a Doctor Strange, though.
Oh, we got him.
Welp, we're tied.
Welp, nevermind.
We're not tied anymore.
We're not even anymore.
Oh my god, please.
Please.
I will fucking- oh my god!
Alright.
That's awkward.
Good luck, my man.
Hope you hit that one shot.
Just gotta hit one shot.
Sleepy, hope you hit that one shot.
If you hit that one shot, Sleepy.
Oh, you're almost there.
What is this?
Just one shot!
Wait, SK's on Spider-Man?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yeah, like...
I don't know.
That's not me.
That was not a me issue.
It's the stream curse.
It's the curse of Ra.
I was winning almost all my games off stream.
It's literally the curse of Ra.
All my off stream games, I was winning.
I started the stream so close.
So close.
Nice, he fucked up.
Come on.
Jesus Christ, thank God.
I don't know if we'll win this.
Our team fucking sucks.
Our Venom fucking sucks.
I don't think Venom is the play.
He feeds so much.
It's our Venom.
I'm sorry.
Goodbye, guys.
This is where you all die.
Oh, Penny, why did you...
Oh, Penny!
Wrong way!
Wrong way, Penny!
Okay, that's fine.
Oh, we cannot help you.
Sorry, SK.
Guys, if we lose faster and not cap the point we can queue into our other game and optimize our queue times.
Instead of you know playing through hell.
We need to optimize the queue hours.
We're stalling the inedible.
Oh my God.
Who the fuck is shooting me?
There's no reason for me to ult here.
Oh my God, I'm ulting.
There's no reason, but I'll still do it.
Yay!
Let me stand in front of all of them.
Okay, I stopped him.
Hey, guys!
I stopped him!
Goodbye.
Goodbye, Penny.
Guys, no.
Don't cap, guys.
No, don't do this to me.
Guys, please.
You don't need to cap, guys.
Who the fuck said that?
This guy?
The sleepy guy?
They literally said pocket me?
What about me?
Oh my God, please.
Alright.
Oh no, we're gonna cap.
Oh no.
Oh.
No, we're gonna cap.
No!
Okay.
I knew we could do it, team.
Guys, I knew we could do it.
Oh my God.
What a team.
God, I wish I can fucking...
Oh, I wish I could just step on you.
Oh, I didn't fucking see you.
You got spread out on the fucking pavement.
It's fine, I'm...
I'll just say that Marvel Watch has definitely...
has definitely fucked me up.
I tried.
You had 20 people on you.
What do you want from us?
All we do is heal you!
Please live.
They're gonna use the Spider-Man ult after this!
Or that, too.
Ashley, fuck you.
Ashley!
Okay, you gotta admit...
No!
I did something so fucking cool.
I...
Oh my God.
I did something so fucking cool just for it to be negated by a stupid magician.
I'm okay.
I love...
I love this game.
I love Marvel Rivals.
It's my...
It's my favorite game of the year.
This is honestly game of the year for me.
Oh my God, I can't.
I have to wait.
Where is he?
I have to wait for 20 things!
Okay, there we go.
Yes.
Alright.
We're fine.
Oh, you're right.
You're right.
I'm definitely dead inside now.
Alright, give me a sec.
Let me do a magic trick, too.
I'll be like Dr. Strange, guys.
Wait, where is it?
Alright.
I gotta make sure I also grab...
Okay, I'll do a magic trick as well.
This is so cool.
Alright, where is it?
I like how day two, my optimism is gone.
My joy and optimism is now gone.
It only took one day.
It took one day.
If you watch like...
If you watch like yesterday's stream versus today's stream, you can tell it's a different...
You can tell I'm a different person now compared to yesterday.
It only takes one bad day.
That's all it took.
Her smile, her optimism gone forever.
One really, really fucking bad day.
I'm back in my Overwatch days.
My Overwatch fucking game mindset.
Oh my god, it's him.
It's him, please.
If you don't punish this fucker, I swear to god.
I swear to god.
If he gets to do all that for free, I swear to fucking god, I'm gonna be so...
Oh my god!
It's not fair!
The Venom actually has a buddy to do all that with!
He gets a Black Panther to dive with him!
He's being enabled!
It's okay.
It's just another day.
Another day on the grind.
Just another day on the grind.
I'm like worried about like...
Jesus.
Okay, it's fine.
It's fine.
Everything is fine.
As long as I don't get dived, it's fine.
We live.
Let's just live.
You know what?
I just... Oh my god!
Alright.
You're all okay though, right?
Are you guys all okay?
Cause I'm not.
I'm not okay.
I was not though.
Yeah, that was a Jeff.
I don't understand.
I avoided him thinking like, oh my god.
He was so fucking... He was trolling there.
But like, now he has a... Now he's not?
Why couldn't he do this for me?
Why couldn't he play like that on my team?
Wait, they hit nobody?
Oh my god!
No!
Guys, you're right.
I only took him two games to lock in.
Okay, this Black Panther is really fucking good though.
He's so annoying.
Nah, I hate Panthers too.
Oh my god, please don't die.
Please don't die.
That's all I ask for you.
I'm ready to put on a show!
I'm ready too!
Dance off.
Yippee!
Dance off!
Alright, it's fine.
Guys, I can feel a Jeff ult coming in.
Oh, I feel it.
I'm ready for it.
Nom, nom, nom, nom!
I have to put this on a tank because like, our tanks take way too much fucking damage.
Om nom, nom, nom, nom!
Oh, thank god!
Fuck you!
Don't
die!
No!
I'm sorry!
I wish you were here!
I'm sorry for laughing!
Now I don't have the heals!
I'm sorry!
Because I was like, he got nom, nom, nom, and then Venom was like, she has no support partner now.
And then everything went downhill.
My turn!
Yippee!
Get over here.
Oh wait, shit.
Oh no!
I was joking!
Don't come back!
But not now!
Nice.
Oh my god, we pulled it back.
He actually got over!
He actually got over here!
Who would've fucking thought?
Yeah, it's whoever ults second, yeah.
I waited a little bit.
I didn't like, instantly Luna ult when I heard hers, because like, if my team's okay, then I don't have to Luna ult.
I just waited until I saw somebody low, and then I Luna ulted.
Because I was like, okay then, then like, we need it then.
Because then I'm like, okay, they're obviously gonna use aggression ults after the Luna ult.
But, if I wait until, if we kill them in time, before they use their aggression ults, then we'll be fine.
Yeah, I'm a filthy support main.
Just like, I just wanted to go through my Overwatch days.
Also, being a DPS player or tank player is way too stressful.
Versus support.
IMO.
So, I think playing DPS is way too stressful.
Woah!
I don't feel so good!
No, because like, DPS, you have to manage your heals too.
Like, you have to play around health packs, but a lot of supports can heal themselves.
So like, or the support duo will insta-heal him back, so like, I don't have to worry about like, you know, lack of healing on myself.
But playing DPS, you always have to like, remember where- Oh my god.
Oh my god.
Oh, he hit the fucking wall.
That's- I'm such a loser.
I'm so bad.
Oh, hello.
He's still contesting us.
Oh!
I do love.
Nope.
Nice.
Not nice.
Oh wait, oh my god!
Holy shit!
He's got that wolf in him.
I just- Okay, you're fine.
It's okay, he's fine.
You're fine too.
Oh my god, you're all so fucking healthy.
Man, there's a guy over there.
Ooh!
Nice.
I feel like a lot of games is a sad- Like, you know.
You know when like, you can't kill anybody as DPS, it's sadder.
It's sadder than like, you know, losing cause you're a support.
Cause when you- When DPS lose, we all know why we lost.
Stairs at DPS.
Or tank.
Stairs at DPS or tank.
We all know.
But like, as a support, you're just like, whoops!
What could I have done?
Like, my team was just bad.
I can blame the team more easily as it- What the fuck!
As a support.
Alright.
Ooh, this is halfway.
Oh, shit!
He went full-on!
He went in a full-on panther mode!
Oh, and then- And then SK... SK went too wild.
Oh!
It dropped into everything!
Okay.
I don't have to use ult.
I gotta hold my ult until their Luna uses ult.
I didn't think he would fucking go back!
Oh, no!
I couldn't ult!
I'm coming back!
Live!
I'm ready!
Get on board and I'll start dancing!
Yeah!
And again!
Yay!
I got my own stage to dance!
Yay, we won!
Oh, my god.
I don't know.
I think also for me, I'm so comfortable playing support that like for me, I'm so comfortable playing support that it's not that stressful versus DPS and tank.
Because, like I said, like, you know, I don't play DPS and tank that often.
Like, I know I play DPS for Apex and stuff, but that's different.
Apex is so different from like actually playing DPS, but when I'm playing DPS or yeah, I know, 9800.
Like, god hates me.
It's just like so stressful.
Because I'm not used to it.
And it tilts me even more because like I play support.
And then when I know I can tell when we have a very bad support player.
So it tilts me even more because I'm like I'm just like
If I was on support right now.
Things would be different.
So, yeah, in my head I always be like I could do a better job than this fucker.
And it makes me want to queue support.
Because I'm like, I need to queue support to be like to show people how good support play like.
So it's just, oh, it's like that shit.
I like a mental warfare in my head every time I try to try to do like DPS your tank.
And then like I hate tank.
I'll never touch tank.
Anyone that's a tank player you actually enjoy pain.
I'm sorry.
Like I feel like I feel like being a tank player, being a tank main is like no fun.
You guys actually enjoy pain.
Like you're an M right there.
Because it's like because it's like as a tank player, you have to rely so much on your teammates to do something.
I mean same with support, but then like as a tank, you have to stare at the enemy while you're like, I hope my DPS does something.
Like
So that's why I feel like I don't know, I don't know when I try to play tank, I'm just like oh my god, I slap and then it just does like one damage and I'm like oh Oh Unless you find a fucking lone support support player by themselves in the wild that's really it.
If you find a support, if you find a- just like how that venom kept fucking trying to fucking dive me every time Wait, what did SK say?
Solo queue tank is a peak experience
Top -notch team to win this one I'm Luna Snow.
Like the moon I shine in darkness Oh
Do it
She wouldn't do it She wouldn't fucking do it I know, she's weak
Oh yeah, especially when you're a solo queue tank.
I think also No, no, no Surefour, no
Stop, he's gonna curse my queues I can feel it.
Surefour, we got you, but like Surefour, we already we got you but like American
Hahahahaha This could've been you, you could've been in this trio queue
Okay, I had to make sure there was no fucking stupid mines Oh Goodbye
What the fuck is going on in there?
And they start fucking fucking hammering What are my tanks doing?
Oh my god What are my tanks doing?
Oh, hey guys I don't know if I wanna be here Magneto, you're gonna Magneto, I'm sorry We're gonna No You're being silly
I just like to I just like just watch the Thor and my tanks just look at each other Like Just like I don't know, I think it's like really silly seeing him just fucking hammering the portal He's like hammering the air I think like we can maybe do something about it Oh,
he got it too Guys, break the tree and save this poor man Oh my god he's timing He's hammering Oh no
Oh no Okay, I might put the orb on on SK just cause she's a flanker The group prism, I'm like guys, can we like please we need somebody to like, I don't know Oh my god, wait, where the fuck, oh I thought the mantis was with me I didn't know she fucking went right I was like where the fuck did the mantis go Alright,
I'm coming back Oh thank god he's dead Hammer man is dead
Okay Wait, wait I thought he died
What the fuck, he hammered He hammered the thing
Please, mantis, look at me Oh, Hella revived him I'm getting like fucking targeted
I didn't even realize he Jesus, whoops
I'm a little scared Where's our tanks I didn't even realize he got like resurrected by Hella cause Hella needs to get a final kill for it Oh my god This is We're gonna loop We're just gonna keep looping Oh my god
Oh my god This Thor is insane Now you guys are gonna be like See, see a good, that's See, a tank can do stuff Yeah, now look at our tank Our tank is not having fun You didn't say that But what about our tanks Our tanks was having the worst day of their lives
Maybe one of the tank is having fun But our tank was definitely not having fun Time to switch things up Including which side you're on Some tanks can't have fun
He is the son of Odin That was a portal I don't think it was a portal issue I was like if we all walked, if we couldn't get past that thing, I don't think even if we get the point, our team was gonna be okay after that I don't think our team was gonna be okay Like,
if we had issues just trying to get to point
Why only play Luna?
Cause Luna's good She's like S tier You always need a Luna Yeah, I need Luna, Mantis Luna, Mantis Cloak and Dagger I heard like if you know how to play Rocket really well, then he's also really good For like healing wise But only if you're really good at like bouncing his shots off Bouncing his shots off things
Yeah, but you have to be able to understand the angles on where things are I can play Mantis now, but like, I feel like Oh, there's a portal Why can't we do that?
What's going on?
Oh my god!
I'm scared
Guys, please Please, you guys are taking way too much damage for me I'm getting scared, guys Guys!
Oh, okay None of us done the simple thing of going on point That's okay That's okay
It's alright I know it's not my fault No, that guy deserved it He was No, he was gaming No, he was gaming No, he deserved it He knew what the fuck he was doing I blame Surefour He came in here, threw a curse on me and then it was downhill
It all went downhill after that Everything was gonna be fine until he threw that fucking curse
So, honestly Things could've been better Things definitely could've been better
That's good, this is where things change, right?
Things will be different now Right?
Right here, right now Things will be different Is Jazzy?
What was wrong with Jazzy?
I have so much hate in me that like, there's no singular hate anymore You guys gotta be very specific
You guys have to be very fucking specific
Oh nice, cool portal Oh, the portal's gone Okay
Alright, no, I'll stay down here
Where's our other DPS?
Oh, there he is That portal?
What's going on?
Oh, what's going on?
Things will be fine We got one of them
Oh, you're fine, you're fine, doctor Woah!
You were not fine Oh my god, you're so not fine Oh my god I actually got greeted by the fucking staircase
It just, it was just, it just had to be He walked in there I think this is one of the worst maps Honestly This is, this is one of the worst maps This is actually one of the worst I hate all these stupid staircases
Like, it's just so inefficient
It's so dumb It's actually so fucking dumb
What's going on?
What's going on guys?
Hey guys, are you all okay?
What's going on?
Oh my god Oh my god, bro Okay, you guys had to back up there
Oh, I can't see you Oh, I see you now I can't see you anymore again I got you
Oh my god, nice I froze somebody There's a portal?
Oh, that's our portal It's like, where the fuck Oh Oh, goodbye Unless
That was a very shitty ult from him It's fine Oh, he's one
It's fine Everything is fine We're all alive and healthy Oh, except for that guy But like, we didn't care about that guy anyway, right?
He didn't matter in the grand scheme of things Nobody even remembers his name
Oh, she's gonna start dancing
It's fine
Oh my god, not another one Guys Please Ping me so I can heal
No Live
It's okay, we're just giving them a little space
But like That was
actually an insane portal But he didn't kill me He forgot about me That's right, fucker Should've killed the fucking support That's Ashe's Oh my god, people are getting too good at this game, guys I need to get top 500 before people learn everything I don't have enough time to fucking learn all these tech This guy already learned the fucking Doctor Strange tech
This is why I'm trying to speedrun it on stream, so I don't have to worry about everybody learning like 200,000 things
I've never seen that portal tech though but it's actually so fucking smart Don't hear that, Tyler I will, I will just not now
There has to be like a lot of tech that I don't know from Luna Has it not been?
It's fine, it's fine I got you
100 like
You're fine, you're so healthy Oh, your shield's gone No!
I heard the crack I heard the crack and I knew it was over I heard that and I'm like, goodbye, Covey Goodbye, Covey I vaulted for the last fight which is good
Okay, not yet though Alright, now I vault There we go Kill him, kill him Oh, okay, don't worry That's fine, you can use this to kill him though We're stuck here now We're stuck in this stupid fucking map
Guys, it's not toxic relationship, he's better This is a healthy relationship Guys There's nothing toxic about it He's different My revivals is different He's third person and there's no role queue and voice chat's broken and and yesterday I lost like 15 games 15 games
And...
and there's no regen.
So he's different.
And there's six of us.
But like...
Like guys, you don't understand.
It's not toxic.
I'm having... I'm having so much fun... right now.
Guys, this is... this is so fun.
I'm safe.
Oh my god, please!
Google Maps faster!
That's fine.
I'm healing here.
What's going on on my screen right now?
I can't tell.
There's a lot of things going on on my screen.
That's fine.
We're keeping... keep each other safe.
Keep yourself safe.
What the fuck is going down here in this corner?
Whoa!
I said that... I wrote to Surefour.
I was like... I was like haha, noob down.
And he said, keep yourself safe.
I wonder what he means by that.
That flank was crazy though.
I don't think it was a flank.
I think they just came back from spawn.
That's crazy.
So, that's when you know he plays League.
He says that in League, because if you say anything bad in League of Legends, you get like instantly banned.
Which makes sense, you know?
Because like, League has like the... League has like the most intense reporting system.
Oh my god, that was such a good eye.
That was such a good web.
People keep asking me to... Oh my god!
He died so fucking fast.
Can he?
Ah, I didn't reload my hands!
I'm sorry!
My hands are very limited!
It's fine, we're fine.
I don't... I don't want to watch Arcane, because like, I'm too scared that's going to make me want to play League.
I feel like... I don't think I need that in my life.
Because like, everybody who watched Arcane kept getting... went back to League.
Or like, started League, playing League because of Arcane.
And I'm just thinking, I don't want to play League.
I really, really don't want to play League!
I'm worried it's going to like... I'll be like, oh my god, maybe League... maybe League's not that bad.
Maybe it won't be that bad.
But that's how they get you.
That's how they fucking get you.
They know.
Toki knows.
If we shoot her, she'll die.
Oh my god, nevermind.
Well, I mean, technically she did not die.
Oh, maybe I die.
Unless...
I'm okay.
Yeah, because League is coming back now.
People are playing League again.
Because Arcane's doing really well.
Season 2 Arcane was apparently really, really, really good.
And I'm like, oh.
Oh, I walked into her!
I was like, she'll go forward, right?
But she went backwards.
That's fucked.
She actually went backwards.
I'm coming back.
No!
Oh, no!
I'm okay.
That's how they get you.
Guys, you need to be faster in your Google Maps, man.
That could have been a fight right there.
We could have had a fight right there.
Where am I?
Oh, she's one!
Okay, nice.
That was an insane ice shot though.
Holy fuck!
That ice shot was fucking crazy.
Yay!
Oh my god, please.
Please get me in a plat one.
Please.
We just need one more win and I'll be plat one.
And then we need four wins and I'll be diamond three!
Oh, wait!
No, I was amped!
Yay!
Oh my god, okay.
Okay, we need 40 and then 55, 67, 89.
Okay, we need three wins.
I need three wins.
Three wins and then I'll be top 500.
Top 500, please pray for me.
We're back!
We're back in three wins hell!
We just need... Guys, please pray for me, guys.
Please, put your hands in the air, give me your energy and pray for me.
We're back to three wins!
It's time.
We're gonna break the cycle.
The cycle ends with me!
This is it!
We're gonna be here for it!
Alright, if we do... If we have one win left, I'm gonna get in a call with him and I'm gonna try so fucking hard.
I'm gonna start comming in the moment we're at one win.
Oh my god, break the cycle!
Break the curse!
This curse only lasted one game!
It's gonna be different!
It's fine.
I'm fine.
I'm fine, everybody.
I love Marvel Rivals.
I just wanted you guys to know.
In other games, I never had like an instance where I won it.
Even in Overwatch, you know.
You know, the thing is, Overwatch didn't have like animals where I'm like, oh I guess hamsters.
But like, you know, with Hammond and Winston, you know, you know, I'm fucking... I don't like it when Winston like dives at me as a support.
I wouldn't be go out to be like, you know what, good thing they shot a Harambe.
I wouldn't say that.
I was like, oh my god, how could they do that?
But like, for some reason, in Marvel Rivals, I'm like, I wouldn't go outside and like fucking... I want to go outside and fucking burn a tree down.
There's just something about this game that makes me like... No, it hasn't done this to me for in Overwatch.
I never felt this fucking hate in me before.
I never felt this hate before.
There's just something about Marvel Rivals that's different.
I think, you know... Oh, I know why.
No, I know why now.
You know why?
Because, you know, when Winston fucking jumps at you, he doesn't say, I am Groot.
I am Groot.
When you hear that for like, you know, the fucking 50th time while he's fucking on your ass.
Like, it starts getting to you.
Like, Winston doesn't go, I am Winston.
I am Winston.
Because like, you know, you hear different things.
But for this game, you just hear one line.
You know, and then like... And then like, you know, Roadhog, yeah, you're gonna say like, oh yeah, but what about Roadhog?
Oh my god, I'm fucking gonna stay down here.
Oh no, it's fucking Groot.
Oh, fuck you.
If you say I am Groot to me one more time, you say, say I am Groot.
Also like, Roadhog.
In Roadhog, you know, you could be like, well, Roadhog's like Spider-Man, you know, like, you know, not, okay, no, actually, yeah, but like, the thing is, or like Doomfist, like, I don't know, like, you say like, Spider-Man is like, is like Doomfist, but like,
but like, you know, after like, Doomfist punches you, he doesn't fucking do 320, 320 somersaults in the air, and then fucking have 800 DP, like, not a thousand, not even a thousand, 30,000, 30,000 DPI, 50 million cents, and then you see him in the air fucking,
and we're like, rawr!
And I'm just, like, I even hate fucking him.
Like, he's not, he's not even as bad as Genji too.
Like, Genji was fucking bad.
Like, Genji wasn't as bad as this.
Like, like, Genji was not as bad as this too.
Oh my god.
You know what, I think we can win this.
I think we can win this.
I'm sorry, I chose the tank.
All right, but then, like, the thing is, like, like, yeah, so like, Doomfist, when he runs away after he tries to kill you, it's like, it's like, you can see him.
You can at least see him.
When Spiderman does it, he does, like, nine degrees angle flips, and then, like, flips, and he chooses all the angles that's possible in the fucking world to run away.
Okay.
I don't think she's okay.
Like, what the fuck happened to that Luna Snow?
It's fine, we're fine.
I wish I could do what you do.
Nice.
It's just very tilting, watching a Spiderman, trying to think he's him.
He's a public menace.
Now I know how the newspaper guy felt.
He was right.
I want pictures of Spiderman right now.
Someone give me pictures of Spiderman.
He was fucking right.
JJonas was right.
That's a wild statement.
Out of everything I said, that's the wildest statement?
He's a menace to society.
How do we know he's even a vigilante?
What if he- what if it was all planned?
What if it was all, like, orchestrated, you know?
He paved- he paved them.
He paved them.
I'm gonna win this.
He paid them to make himself look good.
I bet, like- oh my god, he fucking died.
Alright, you guys ready to dance?
That's right.
I waited for that tip.
Okay, maybe Okay, now you should be fine.
He's fake.
I can tell.
You don't know that.
You don't know Spiderman has no money.
Maybe he's some rich boy.
Yeah, I bet that's fake news made up by Spiderman.
Who's Peter Parker?
Who is he?
What's his full name and address so I can send it over to that newspaper company?
Give me his full name and address right now, where he lives, and then direct it to J.
Jonas Jameson.
And then mix- and then- and then so I can call the cops.
Fucking call the cops on Spiderman, on Peter Parker.
I'll throw my thing down and get there.
I'll get your arm, okay?
Ducky, no!
No, Ducky!
Give me Spiderman right now!
Ducky, don't be a snitch!
And that's why I hate Spiderman.
What's wrong with you?
If you play support and you have to deal with this fucker, you know what- Bro, all the fucking support players that have to deal with Spiderman would agree with me.
You guys are- you guys are just get to play frontline.
You guys are not the backline players.
You don't understand.
I'm gonna start a petition with all the other support players.
To fucking get him doxxed by Spiderman.
He is a public menace.
We have to doxx him for the safety of the community.
There we go.
Support players, support group.
I think you started to sound like Eggman.
Oh shit, sorry, I was- sorry, I was thinking about how much I'm gonna fucking squish a spider after that.
He's not even in my game, but I still hate him.
He doesn't have to be in my game for me to hate.
The mere thought of him just makes me go fucking feral.
The average support player.
What the fu- oh my god, I chose the wrong side.
Where did he fucking come from?
Oh, I bet- I bet it's because I said I was gonna fucking doxx stupid Iron Man, stupid Tony Stark.
Protecting a criminal.
Of course he'll protect a fucking criminal.
We all know he's a fucking criminal too.
We all- we all-
Get him a fucking cancel Iron Man.
Yeah, I bet you Iron Man evades taxes.
That's right, get down, tax evader.
Are you okay?
My arrivals has changed me, guys.
That's right, Iron Man.
Pay your fucking taxes, Tony Stark.
Oh shit, I didn't hear that!
Okay, I may- I trolled a little bit, I didn't hear- no wonder everybody went like right- left side instead of right.
I was so confused.
I was like, why did people go- went that way?
Yeah, they're only one push against us.
Oh, they're so excited when they see this.
I'd like to die for this.
I can't anymore, actually.
Oh.
Oh,
he's one!
Oh, he's one!
Left side, right side.
Oh, just because I want someone to pay their taxes.
Insane.
Alright, I'll make sure- I'll make sure, like, some of these guys are alive.
Maximum AT!
Okay!
You know what?
Real firepower, let's go!
You'll live.
Where did you go?
You'll still live.
Oh, I thought he would go-
What?!
Yeah, you're fine.
Oh my, it's fine, it's fine.
Rocket Raccoon lives.
But Mag's like hard pushed.
He's one.
Mag is like super low.
Alright, we're fine.
Our man saved the universe?
Freakiness.
How do you know that he actually saved the universe?
Guys, huh?
How do you actually know?
That's fucking right.
Get on the cart, guys!
You guys said it, but did you guys see it?
Did you guys actually see him save the universe?
He's guilty by association!
He's protecting a criminal!
Yeah, but that could be propaganda!
He's a billionaire.
He can afford it.
Yeah, were you there?
It could've been like, filmed by a movie studio.
Just like how they faked the moon landing.
They could've faked it, like how they faked the moon landing.
Just like how Tony Stark's dad faked the moon landing.
Oh, fuck!
Please kill her before she kills me!
Oh, nice, nice.
I'm coming back!
Stark, you stop playing this game.
I'm pretty sure Howard Stark faked the moon landing.
And Tony Stark faked saving the universe with the same movie studio.
And that's just a theory, a dokey theory.
Check out my column in the next newspaper on the mogul... what was it called?
The newspaper company that fucking Jay Jameson ran?
The Daily Bugle?
Yeah, check out my column in the Daily Bugle next week.
Of course!
Of course, Jay Jameson, my oshi and my hero.
I always read his newspaper every day.
He knows what he's saying.
I love his podcast too.
His podcast is really good as well, guys.
Check it out every morning.
Especially when he tells me about how...
About how the 5G waves are turning our spiders gay.
Jay Jameson's podcast gets wild sometimes.
Toki, please stop.
I'm not real anymore.
This is what Marvel Rivals has turned me into.
That's Jameson.
That's Jay Jameson.
I watch his podcast every morning.
We're fine.
Okay, I should really lock in.
I have not been locking in the last two games.
Is it noticeable?
Oh my god!
Okay, there was no way I could save that.
That was a lost cause.
That was definitely a lost cause there.
Hey guys, we're sort of stuck.
The supports are stuck down here.
Alright, nice.
Oh no, he's gruting.
He's fucking gruting again.
It's fine.
That's fine.
It's not that fine, but it's fine.
I'm gonna get arrowed right now to the fucking face.
I wish I was getting arrowed to the knee instead.
At least I can survive a knee.
Oh my god!
I watched a man die in front of me.
Everything is fine.
Oh no, Jeff is here.
I just noticed.
I noticed the bubbles.
Not the bubbles.
Jeff is here.
Oh my god, I didn't hit?
No!
Goodbye.
Fucking three of us?
I knew it.
The moment I felt.
This is targeted.
Fuck, go in.
Go in.
I can... No!
I could've ulted!
I think I'm just...
I'm just gonna ult.
If I hear Jeff, I'm fucking ulting.
They should bring me back.
They should...
Jaw should be a thing again.
Fuck me.
I'm healing.
I'm keeping you guys alive!
Jaws was right too.
Nice.
Holy shit!
The freeze hook?
Oh, now that's hate.
I still can't believe the very first thing they did with the models being datamined...
is to make hate animations about Jeff.
Which I fully support.
Hate triumphs.
Triumphs lust.
Hate is just stronger.
What can I say?
Who's next?
Honestly, he should be.
What the fuck happened?
Oh, nobody wants to shoot that?
That's fine.
We don't have to.
There's none of them using any ults that require me to ult as well.
Alright.
We got rid of their ult.
They literally used the I.
I'm gonna use it when he goes yum yum yum.
I'm using it when he goes yum yum yum.
I'm gonna do it.
Oh, okay.
Oh, that's fine.
The Hanzo just kills all of us.
We're way too split for my ult though.
That's the thing.
I can't use my ult!
Everybody was so split!
What?!
No!
I pressed Q!
I actually pressed- It went off!
What?!
It went off on my screen!
Oh my god.
That's fucking crazy.
That actually was so crazy.
It actually went off on my screen too.
Yeah, I might have to ult here.
God, I hate you.
I hate you.
Don't worry!
Oh, you're fine.
You are fine.
Okay, nevermind.
Go!
Go in there and kill him!
Alright, that's fine.
We're fine.
We're so healthy.
It's just me.
It actually was just me.
What's wrong with you?
What's fucking- What is wrong with you?!
I have a mantis!
There were three people together!
What is wrong with you?!
That's so fucked up.
That's actually so fucked up.
That's actually- Oh my god.
Now you know why I hate sharks!
My hate is justified.
My hate is so justified.
We can win.
I have ult.
They have ult too.
No!
Get me out of this fucking world!
Okay, I'm coming back.
I'm coming back.
I'm ready to fucking dance!
Oh, he's gonna eat you, but I'm free.
I'm sorry, bro.
I'm still here, though.
We live for as long as we can.
I live for as long as I can, so does our mantis.
Oh my god, the Jeff.
At least I wasn't in the Jeff ult, guys.
Guys, I wasn't in the Jeff ult.
At least I wasn't in it!
That's all that matters.
I wasn't part of it.
Don't be mean to Jeff.
Oh, I might get banned.
I hope Jeff has a very good day.
It's okay if they count half those points because of Jeff ults.
You can't do that on stream.
I don't want to actually get banned.
I'm not mad.
I swear.
Toxic positivity, guys.
Oh, what's she doing here?
She's just gonna walk out like that?
Crazy.
There's like... there's like a fucking hella right there.
Oh my god.
We gotta focus up.
No.
It's fine, it's fine.
We're fine.
Nice!
Kill him!
He's a washed surgeon anyway.
He can't even fucking perform surgery anymore.
He lost his worth in society.
Get him out of here.
Get the shark too.
Make him extinct.
Oh, he lives.
That Doki.
Damn Doki.
Nice.
That is low Doki, please.
Alright, and now... and now we wait.
Wait.
Specifically to Jeff's feces.
Just to Jeff's feces though.
Did you hear that?
Oh shit.
There was a... did you hear that?
Like, was it Lee?
That's planning on... or Deadlocked?
That's planning on adding like...
No, it wasn't Deadlocked.
What was it?
There was a game that's planning on adding like team chat or slash voice chat.
I forgot which game it was.
There was like a big game that's planning on adding it.
Was it Fortnite?
Oh, was it Fortnite?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Fortnite's planning on adding chat.
That's gonna go so well.
With all the children.
That's gonna... that's gonna go so well.
No, Lee should never add voice chat.
No.
I will ult if I hear...
Oh,
he put... did it to you?
That's right.
Goodbye.
Oh!
No!
Yes!
I'm sorry.
That's fine.
No, just both our teams, you know?
It's just both our teams.
I'm just gonna wait here.
I did Mantis ult too.
I passed the quick time event, guys.
I successfully quick timed event.
I got one up there.
That is not a fucking liar.
He's getting healed by Jeff.
Like, Jeff!
Jeff!
Bye.
Monkey?
Did he just say monkey one?
Who the fuck is monkey?
Who... who is monkey?
Who's... who's monkey?
Venom?
Oh, Bucky.
I thought he said monkey.
I was like... I was like, which one's the monkey?
Okay, it was... it was Bucky.
It felt like he was saying... oh my god.
Like he was saying of an M.
They're two WPOs.
They're wide.
Oh my god.
You fucking jump so fat.
I'll get one up.
I can bubble you out of escape.
Oh, nevermind.
I think you're fine.
I had to do this so I can get myself healed.
No, no!
Yay.
There you go.
They're frozen.
She's traumatized.
I am.
I'm like, who the fuck is monkey?
Bucky!
The PTSD response every time.
I can't.
I want all Jeffs to not have a good day.
But again, I'm scared of typing that in chat because I don't know how... I don't know what the report system is like in the Marvel Rivals.
Apparently, someone that SK reported yesterday, that was in our game yesterday, got banned.
So I'm like, whoa, what did he... I don't remember what he said.
I don't...
So I'm a little worried.
The system works, guys.
Yeah, you get notified if somebody gets banned from a report you do.
I don't want to get banned.
I mean, I care.
Okay.
But I do care.
Oh my god, that's fast.
Okay, now I can hear the Bucky.
I can hear the Bucky now.
But when he says that, it sounds like monkey!
I'm not crazy!
How much?
Now he's back, now he's back.
He's in range.
Oh, he's so low.
Nice.
Nice, nice, nice.
I'm just gonna push it in and fuck it.
I wonder if it's like Overwatch PTSD too when he says that.
You're like, monkey, monkey, monkey, monkey!
Instead of like, Bucky.
He just went full Overwatch there.
Oh, my god, he just pushed it like that.
Yay!
Yeah, he's actually calming.
Is that crazy?
People communicating in this game as if you... as if like, you know...
You know, as if it's a team game.
What is that?
In a team game!
You have to use... you have to communicate.
I say as I don't even join the voice chat of the people in my stack.
Bro, you can't critique me for not...
Mondin's not even in the team voice, guys.
He's not even in the team voice, guys.
So like, it's not my fault.
It's not just my fault, chat.
By not calming, it's not just my fault.
LOL
I do not make it...
Look!
SK is calming for us.
As a stack, we unite as one.
SK is our... is our like, resident speaker.
She's our... she's our resident speaker.
She speaks for all of us.
What the fuck this is, mate?
Oh shit.
That's fucked.
I had to hold really close because it pushed...
It didn't push that far.
Thank you,
God.
Where am I getting shot from?
Oh no, oh no.
Yay, I get used!
Makes me happy.
Jesus Christ.
This is... this is why...
This gameplay... this gameplay is exactly why...
This fucking gameplay from the Groot is exactly why my hate is justified.
Makes me want to break some sticks.
Okay, sorry.
Let me go back to PMA.
Let me go back to...
Don't worry, I'm a very positive person, guys.
I don't hate people that much.
Well, not people, you're right.
No, I don't hate people.
I hate other things.
Wait, is this a game?
Is this a rank up game?
Oh my God.
Okay, alright, I'm ready.
I'm ready to be in call.
What if like...
Would it be funny if we lose?
That would be so funny.
Is it auto top 500 when you get to diamond?
Is it?
We'll find out.
I'm checking the leaderboard.
I think you have to 1 or 2 after diamond.
Okay, guys, we're not getting voice yet.
Is she in here?
I have to win 1 after diamond.
Let's see who's in there.
Oh, I have the one that gets with the Mantis.
She was a really good support.
Alright, I'm gonna get some napkins real quick to blow my nose.
I'll be right back.
Mantis shoes.
Alright, I'm back.
Okay, how is this looking like?
That's right.
That's alright.
Captain America.
Wait, that's Cap- Wait, what?
Captain America is this guy.
Is he Viking Captain America?
That's not Captain America.
That's not- What Captain America is that?
Captain Gladiator?
Yeah, what's the context of that skin?
Where is he from?
What country is he from?
There's no gladiators in America.
What the fuck?
I jumped here because- Oh!
Oh!
Woah!
I saw Black Panther!
Captain Norway?
Is he Captain Norway?
No, he's a gladiator, so he should be Captain Rome.
Okay, we're focusing.
We're focusing.
Okay, that's a lot of damage.
Oh, I thought that would hit him.
I thought he was going to go to the left side.
Come on, tanks!
We have- Technically, I feel like we have two off tanks, if you think about it.
Get the tree!
Get the- Oh my god, we could've killed the tree.
Oh, this is bad.
This is so bad.
Nevermind, we can- We make it work.
Don't worry, she'll be fine.
What the fuck?
Where are we?
What's going on?
No, no, no!
Oh, nice, nice.
No!
Are you serious?
I was 99!
Oh my god, we would not have lived.
None of us would have lived that.
I don't think you can ban heroes yet.
I think it has to be like a full diamond lobby.
I think you can only do it in a full diamond lobby.
I'm trying to figure out who would've fucking healed.
Our two tanks are like super...
Nice.
Get in!
Okay, I guess we both get- Alright, let's at least- Oh, he's sleeping.
He's a little eepy.
It's fine.
Alright.
It's totally fine.
He's getting fucking kidnapped, but I think he's healthy.
Get the tree!
That's fucking right!
That's right!
I'm gonna fucking break your kneecaps.
No more jumping for you.
Just like in I, Tanya.
Oh shit.
What a reference.
That's just such an insane thing to say.
I've said a lot of things, but you can't- You can't say that was the most insane thing I've said today.
What kind of this?
Jesus Christ.
Yeah, none of you guys are living.
You can heal them, but I'm fucking walking away.
That is very confident.
Oh, I'm sorry.
We closed the door on you.
So good luck.
Oh, he didn't live.
Oh, is that SK?
Oh, she didn't live.
Unfortunate SK.
When the door closed, it was over.
The door- Oh, we closed the door again.
As soon as that door closed, it was over for her.
I knew.
I heard a portal.
You got a portal?
The fuck does that mean?
Oh, that's right!
Oh, that's not right.
Oh, that's okay.
I can dance on the other side.
Let me walk the other way.
You're gonna make a wall?
Oh, that's fucking right!
Oh, I wish I could crouch spam.
This is the only thing I wish this game had.
Crouch spamming.
Get iced again.
Ice, ice, baby.
Everything's fine.
Alright, I'm fucking- I'm sorry.
You're just gonna have to die.
What?
Oh, shit!
We got, like, trem- We got Wakanda'd!
Heroes don't kneel.
I think we're not the heroes right now.
Are we doing a bad thing, sending this over?
Like, doesn't this mean we're destroying the planet when we're sending this over?
Yeah, guys, I don't think we're heroes anymore.
Oh, no, he doesn't see me, though.
He doesn't see me.
Oh, but he sees me!
He was actually so low, too.
I'm sad.
Oh my god, he was so low.
No, I have to reload my hands!
Guys, I can't!
My mousepad, I can't!
That's fine, let's all just dance together.
Oh my god!
Are we?
We're- Oh, no.
Oh, we pushed pretty far!
We pushed pretty far!
That's fine.
That's fine!
We pushed so far!
There's hope!
I am- Okay, I'm so locked in.
I'm so fucking locked in.
How dare you say that?
I am the most locked in person here.
That's not true.
I think SK's just a lot locked in, and me, not gonna lie.
But, like, I'm so fucking locked in, guys.
This is it.
We can win this, I believe.
I'm currently plat 1.
If we win this, we're diamond 3.
And then we have to win an extra game.
It's not an instant top 500.
Oh my god, but we're actually climbing.
I thought these only happen in my dreams.
I thought these only happen when I'm dreaming.
Wait, how do I get up there?
Oh, shit.
Woo!
We're gonna play up here?
That's interesting.
Oh, they just opened this door.
Where?
Are they gonna portal?
I fucking knew it.
Oh my god.
Oh, woah, woah, woah, woah, woah, woah!
Woah!
Okay.
Okay, I did not expect to see him there.
Alright, that was unexpected.
The flank there.
I know, that's- I know.
It's cause he does like- he does like this.
That's- oh, I didn't.
I thought I, like, did like a whole goodbye.
Goodbye there.
I knew he was- What, already?
Already?
What?!
No, I was 10%!
Okay, that wasn't my fault.
That was definitely not my fault.
Bro, he- Oh, shit, bro, they're treating us off.
What do we do?
We're building walls.
Where's- where's a hero that can fucking make fires?
Where's-
Oh, we're using this.
Oh, we- okay, nice.
Oh, we used two support ults!
No!
The mantis also used it!
That's unlucky.
The mantis also used her support ult and I didn't know.
That's fine, we still have three ults.
We have three ults.
Okay, that's not fine, though.
We lost- Here we go.
Let's run back.
Oh, if only we had one of those.
Okay, maybe?
Oh, nice!
Nice.
Okay, not nice, we just got one pick off that.
What?
We only got one- we got one kill off of that.
That's unlucky.
It's okay, we can full hold this.
We can full hold this.
That's fine.
Five minute full hold?
Probably could've been worse.
Like, it can't be that bad.
Again?
Okay, we gotta heal each other.
We gotta heal each other.
As long as we got each other, we should be fine.
Okay!
To be fair, the mantis' eye- oh my god, one of our tanks has like 14 deaths.
That's crazy.
How do you have 14 deaths?
You're so buff!
I'm just gonna put on the other tank.
I can't- Our tank is like, not having it.
I can!
Press Q!
Press Q and it wouldn't let me!
I got pinged so hard.
Oh, no!
No!
I got pinged so hard!
Guys, it's so funny that I lost this game.
It's so- it's so fucking funny!
Oh my god.
No!
It's okay.
It's about building character.
Yeah, but the thing is, they're not talking about me.
They don't know who the fuck I am.
That's the best part.
They're only talking about- Wait, is this the same team?
No, we have different people.
We're fighting the same team.
We're fighting- we're literally fighting the fucking same team.
Like the moon, I shine in darkness.
That's crazy.
That's crazy that we're- we're fighting the same team.
We only need one.
We don't have any tank players?
Oh my god, we have zero tank players.
Bro!
We got this shit.
I believe in us.
There's no- we don't need a tank.
This is- it's alright.
Guys, we just need three wins.
We just- guys, we just need three wins, guys.
Guys, we don't need two anymore.
We just need three wins.
What was that?
That's fine.
Exactly.
If we just kill everything, we don't need tanks.
You're right.
Oh my god, you're so right.
We actually have zero- that's crazy that we have no
- Good luck.
Oh hey, okay.
I thought- I thought we all had a plan where we killed a tank.
There's only one- we killed everybody but the fucking tank.
How is that possible?
We didn't even kill the tank that mattered.
Good luck.
I'm like not doing okay.
Like mentally and like my- oh hey, nice.
We got a tank!
Oh my god, we got a tank, guys.
I knew it.
I knew that we had actual tank players.
Oh my god.
We actually had tank players.
This guy was like, you know what?
I actually sort of want to win now.
Wait, what's breakable?
Okay, I can stay up here.
Oh god, my hands.
Okay.
Yay!
We're undefeatable!
That's fucking right.
That's fucking right, just start dancing.
Whoa, nice, I'm back up here.
Oh.
I'm fine.
Whoa.
Mantis, don't make her do this to me.
Mantis, why didn't you let her do this to me?
Why didn't you let her do that?
Why didn't you just watch?
Mantis.
What?
And
he's also asleep.
What?
Okay.
I went in and like...
They were ready.
I don't even think we could go touch.
Fuck you in particular.
Yeah, definitely should not have went, yeah.
Never should have went in the portal.
That...
Going through that portal was a mistake.
That's for sure.
Definitely...
Where I was gonna die.
I didn't know who to...
Who's MVP?
Alright, you get this.
If you do really well, you get a little treat, little girl.
You get the little... Oh my god!
Okay.
I didn't mean it like that.
I didn't...
Okay.
I was just gonna give you a piece of candy.
Now I'm uncomfortable.
Now I need to report to HR.
Sleep, sleep.
Doki got ERP.
The timing for that was crazy though.
Oh my god!
Look at me, look at me!
Mantis, look at me!
Look at me!
As long as you look at me, everything will be okay.
Mantis, nice.
Fine.
Okay, we're fine.
No, no, no, no!
Good luck, everybody!
Oh my god!
I didn't know where these come from!
I didn't...
Where did Wakanda come from?
I don't even know where Wakanda came from.
Save them.
I'm a hero.
I'm a fucking hero.
Okay.
Yeah.
You're alive.
That's all that matters.
You're so healthy.
You're incredibly...
You're very healthy.
You're still so healthy.
I'm not though.
I'm not healthy, I'm not okay.
Please, just dance with me!
Nice.
And then I leave.
So I hope you live.
Please.
Mantis, nice.
Alright.
We're a little fucked, guys.
We have zero support ult.
And...
We have storm ult, guys.
So like...
I think so.
Mmm...
Something's not right.
I'm a little concerned.
I don't think we've been very successful countering storm.
No.
What do I do in that situation?
What do I do?
I'm the only one...
Oh my god.
I just died.
I just...
Oh my god.
I just died.
I know I'll die...
I'd run.
But like...
Where do I go?
It's okay, guys.
Three games.
Three games, guys.
I'm gonna use the bathroom.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Three games.
Oh, thank god that...
I'm gonna make sure I avoid the Luna Snow only person.
I'm gonna make sure...
That Luna Snow only person, I'm avoiding her so...
Oh, wait.
Actually, no.
That's fine.
I...
I can play other characters now.
Guys, I'm not a one trick anymore.
Chat.
Just so you guys know.
Also, Lucas, thank you for 50 gifted shits.
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
Thank you so much.
Guys, I'm not one trick anymore.
I can play other...
I can play Cloak...
and Dagger.
Oh, shit.
We're running three supports?
Three games.
Three fucking games, guys.
This is Marvel Rivals codes.
I used to be only able to play Dagger.
But now...
I can do Cloak and Dagger.
That's right.
That's fucking right.
I finally learned.
And like...
Is my Cloak and Dagger the same level as my Luna Snow?
That's a good question.
I can play them.
I know what their moves do.
I wish there was a way...
I guess like if I...
I guess it's defensive ult is to counter.
Just a lot of these ults do so much.
Nice.
No one can die now.
Oh my god.
I thought I hit him.
I'm gonna heal the right side.
I think they got the left side.
Oh, they definitely got the...
The only issue right now is that...
It's gonna be harder to get support ults because there's three of us.
Oh shit.
Fuck.
It's fine.
We're all so alive and healthy.
I am at 60% from my first support ult.
That's fine.
It's fine.
Oh my god, this is like ghost.
Oh no.
I hope we get roll Q.
This feels just like ghost.
Who is he trying to kill?
Oh my god.
Oh.
That's a little awkward.
That's fine.
We got two support ults for one support ult.
What a great trade.
Worth it.
Roll Q did not kill overwatch.
Roll Q improved overwatch in my opinion.
No.
Roll Q was not what killed overwatch.
Other things killed overwatch, but it was definitely not roll Q.
I don't know.
Do I put on another support?
I'll put on another support.
So I don't have to worry about healing the other support.
I'm like thinking like, obviously everybody is going to be keeping the DPS alive.
So then I'm like, who will keep the other support alive?
You know?
Bye.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Hello!
No goodbye!
Wait, I hit somebody.
Wait.
Oh, I'm trying to keep going.
Oh my god!
Again, I'm sorry!
Oh my god, nice.
I'm scared.
No!
I needed heal!
If I got heals, I would have gotten my ult.
What the fuck?
Is she okay?
It's okay, I'm coming over.
Do not be afraid!
Okay.
I guess I have to use this.
Do be afraid.
Oh my god, do be afraid.
Oh yes, C9!
C9!
Roll Q?
Saved competitive Overwatch?
Just there shouldn't have been roll Q and quick play.
Roll Q should have been choice and quick play.
There should have been like, quick play with roll Q and then like, um...
Cause I know they added no limits, but they should have made roll Q for quick play the arcade mode.
Versus, uh...
Versus the other way around.
That was the best round I've had in five games?
That was GOATS!
You do not say that about GOATS!
That is like nobody dying for like a hundred years.
I wouldn't say that was the best round.
GOATS was fun until it wasn't.
I don't want my games to last 20 years, guys.
Wait, where are we at?
Are we at three games or two games?
I've lost track.
We've been at this for way too long.
I feel like...
I feel like it's been 20 years.
Okay, three games.
Oh yeah, cause we lost the all DPS round.
I missed.
My ice missed.
What is GOATS?
It was basically a type of...
It was basically three supports, three tanks, and nothing died.
That was GOATS.
And then the thing is, nothing was stronger than GOATS.
Because nothing was stronger than GOATS, everybody played GOATS.
Because if you play any other...
If you try to play a DPS character, you're just fucking throwing.
Like...
And basically...
That was what the game was for like months.
Quick and competitive.
Because it was literally the only thing that would let you win.
The only thing better than GOATS is a team that's better at GOATS.
And the reason why it's called GOATS is because the team that invented it was called GOATS.
Their team name...
Their team name was literally GOATS.
And they were the fuckers.
The brilliant fuckers that invented the most fucked up comp possible.
That's why it was called GOATS.
Oh, nice.
Got her.
Okay, guys.
It's fine.
I got you.
You know what?
Let's let the two supports fucking tank this.
Alright, now it's my turn.
I expected us to kill something.
Guys, nothing has died.
Guys...
Nothing has died.
Nothing has died, guys.
Guys, nothing has died.
Welcome to GOATS.
I swear, nothing has died during that entire fight.
Oh my god, nothing died until we died.
Oh, guys, they went GOATS.
Guys, I can't.
That makes sense.
Oh my god, they went GOATS.
Oh my god, they fucking went GOATS.
They fucking went GOATS, guys.
They actually went GOATS.
Oh my god, I mean, they went GOATS.
Oh my god.
Oh no, that makes so much more sense now.
That makes...
That makes a lot of sense.
I was like, wondering why nothing is dying even more.
I love GOATS.
This is the fucking new meta.
Guys, this is also why I wanted to hurry up and get top 500 before shit like this is brought back.
I couldn't...
I couldn't deal with bringing this... with having to play with this.
That's why.
Alright, let's go.
Let's fucking go.
We're attacking now.
We're fucking attacking.
We're fucking attacking now.
Please.
Please, kill anything.
Oh my god.
I can't believe it.
They also went GOATS.
No, I'm not plat 2, I'm plat 1.
I'm actually plat 1.
Look at that.
That's not me, but like, look at my rank leader.
Alright.
Two more games, guys.
I'm gonna avoid.
Oh wait, no, I don't need to avoid.
I don't need to avoid because I can actually play other characters now.
Am I not plat 1?
I think I thought I was plat 1.
No, you're fucking gaslighting me.
I'm plat 1.
Two more games.
Oh my god, thank god.
Okay, two more games, guys.
For those who are like, Doki, but you said three more games like an hour ago.
Guys, two more games.
Yeah, you wanna know why I said three more games an hour ago?
Let me show you my history.
Yeah.
And let me show you my...
I've been looping.
Alright.
Oh, new people.
We're facing similar people.
Please don't do goats.
Please don't do...
Please, I can't.
Please.
Those games.
I can't heal.
I can't deal with that again.
I can't.
Oh my god.
No!
My stack!
My stack is...
My stack wants goats.
Betrayed.
Betrayed by...
Betrayed by my own group.
I got betrayed by my own group.
Oh my god.
You wanna win.
Guys, please.
But I'm not that close.
I'm not even one game...
It's not even my top 500 game.
Guys, if it was my top 500 game, I would've said it.
Guys, can we please go goats?
I'm one off.
Guys, this is my top 500 game.
Guys, can we please go goats?
This is my top 500 game, guys.
So this is the future.
Or one future, anyway.
Oh god.
Oh, he's so low.
Oh, what?
I thought that would hit.
Oh, we lost one of our supports.
Oh, we lost both of our...
It's okay.
I'm also support, guys.
Guys, I don't think it worked.
Guys, I don't...
We lost.
Guys, we lost both of our supports, guys.
It's okay, this will be different.
It's okay, it'll be different.
I'm gonna put it on our DPS, actually.
Because our DPS is a flanker.
Where are we going?
I don't know where we're going.
Where's our other tank?
Oh, that...
Oh.
Hey, guys.
Are we okay?
Guys, are you guys okay?
Guys, are you guys okay over there?
Everything will be fine.
Oh!
It's okay, we don't need DPS.
What was my HP?
Guys, I don't think goats is working.
I don't think this team...
This team can do goats yet.
Three more games, guys.
Three more games.
Guys, I don't think three support works.
Guys.
This team does not know how.
This team does not know how to play goats, guys.
We're not in Grandmaster yet.
Guys.
These guys...
Thank God, too.
But thank God.
Thank God they don't know how to play goats.
Because then we could swap out goats.
Guys, three more games.
Whoopee!
Three more games!
Yeah, they don't understand goats yet.
Thank fucking God.
They don't...
And I'm okay with that.
Where the fuck did our Thor go?
Okay!
Alright.
Jesus Christ.
Are we...
Oh, no.
Am I okay?
No.
Okay, I'm okay.
I'm okay.
Where are we hiding from?
Oh, that guy.
Yeah.
We're stuck in this hellhole loop of three to two more games.
It's always been...
Three more games!
Two more games!
Three more ga...
Three more games!
Two more games!
You're all fine.
You're all okay.
Okay.
Except for you.
Everybody is fine.
Nice.
Three more games!
Two more games!
When will this hell end?
Okay.
Oh, shit.
He walled himself up.
I'm, like, scared to peek because of the...
the Hanzo.
Okay.
Like, I don't know what you want me to do there.
We're safe down here?
I think we all...
We were not safe over there.
We were...
I realized.
No, we were not.
I mean, do, like, two or three more fights, I think?
Jesus Christ, okay.
Okay.
Okay!
Um...
Yeah.
That's a little bit too much damage, guys.
That's a lot of damage.
I don't know what you want me to do.
You're just running.
Oh, my God!
I healed you!
Where?
Okay, that was a fucking...
Okay.
I'll give credit where credit's due.
That was a really good shot.
Please.
The tree's 1 HP.
I'm gonna look into the portal and see what it looks like.
Oh, my God!
That's what it looked like.
That was actually a crazy shot from him.
I...
I'm impressed.
You know what?
He deserved that.
No, he was definitely aiming for me.
He literally...
He let the shot...
No, Hanzo main...
No, Hawkeye.
Sorry.
Hawkeye mains are actually scary as fuck.
Okay, who's carrying, though?
Sorry.
Sorry, Wunder.
If you're a good little ace, you get to have my little present.
Four...
Three...
Two...
One!
Of course, we're still going.
I'm still streaming.
If I'm still streaming, we're still fucking going.
I need to figure out, like, when you play witch healer.
Like, when do you play...
Like, when should I play...
You know...
Or, like, Adam and Luna...
Adam, Jeff, and Mantis, and shit like that.
Like, when would it be a good time to play...
Adam, when would it be a good time to play other support?
I'd like to, like, figure that out.
Later.
Oh my god!
Holy shit!
Yeah.
They all got deleted there.
That was such a good bait!
Did you guys see that?
With the Adam ult into the...
Into the fucking Psylocke ult.
That was actually such a good ult combo.
I don't think it was intentional.
There's no way.
Nice.
Oh no!
She's one!
That's fine, we're fine.
Get him!
Oh, goodbye.
Wait, what the fuck?
I don't need to ult.
Oh, big B.I.Q.
It's time to dance!
Oh!
Wrong way!
I'm a little scared, though.
You and I.
She's one!
Oh, that ice was actually clutch.
Oh my god, that ice was actually clutch.
Oh!
Where did he come from?
Where did he...
The tree grew in front of me!
The tree suddenly grew in front of me!
The tree...
Where did he come from?
Guys, two more wins!
Wait, one more win!
Two more wins!
I don't fucking know.
I don't know if it's exactly Diamond.
I don't know.
I don't know where the top 500 is at.
Where is it even at?
Okay.
Alright.
Oh my god, I hate that guy was on my team last time.
Alright, if I see...
Okay, I need to know where...
Where SK is.
The moment I see where SK is, then I'll know.
The fuck is SK on here?
Guys, I don't see SK on here.
Wait.
Oh no, it's on Diamond 2 now.
Guys, it's...
I think it's two more games.
We're at...
Wait.
Wait, okay.
There's no top 500 on here.
Oh no.
Oh, don't tell me.
No, it's not.
Guys, it's not.
Oh,
it's not two more games.
It could be.
It could...
It could be any amount.
It could be...
Oh no, it's Diamond.
There's a very limited spot.
Oh no.
I don't know.
Oh my god.
Top 500 is far?
Don't say that.
What number are you?
It's 80 points?
What?
Okay, it's three more.
It's...
It's three more.
Guys.
Welcome to hell.
It's three more.
No, it is.
Because you gain 30 points.
You can gain 30 points per win.
So, like, it's three more.
Because I'm at 90 points.
And if I win, then it'll be 20...
It'll be 20 something.
And if I win again, it'll be 60.
And if I win again, it'll be top 500.
That's how math works.
Guys.
Three more.
We're back to three.
Every time we win, we're back to three.
Just three more.
This is it.
We're always three more.
This is actually feel...
It's the fucking...
It's the answer to life.
It's just always three more.
As bad as things get, I tried to stay calm.
This is my fucking highlight.
So, I might be rusty.
30 seconds before you attack.
Get ready.
Fear thyself.
I'm not this.
I believe in you.
Oh my god, we're actually doing goats.
We're actually doing goats.
Oh my god, we...
There's gonna be hero bans, right?
The moment we hit diamond lobbies...
DPS boost.
The moment we hit diamond lobbies, we're gonna have like full hero bans, right?
No one's gonna ban Luna.
Who's gonna fucking ban Luna?
What kind of freak's gonna do that?
There's no way.
There's so many...
At best...
At best, they're gonna try to ban Hella first.
That's why I believe.
Oh no, we're going higher.
No, we're going higher.
If I can heal this guy.
Woah!
Fine.
Everything...
It's not fine.
I don't feel fine anymore.
No, he's back as hell!
That's fine, we got 30%.
Guys, no.
It's three left.
Yes.
It's...
We're eternally at three left.
It's just always three left.
It's going high.
We're fine, right?
Let's heal again.
It's fine.
My turn!
Wait, where's everybody?
It's still my turn!
Oh, we lost one.
That's not good.
Oh, and then I got...
That's not...
Also not good.
Oh, that's not good.
He's gonna get respawned, guys.
I'm worried about that.
He's here.
I'm good.
Jesus Christ!
Our healer takes so much damage!
It's fine.
We're fine.
I'm just peeking the stairs.
Oh my god!
I'm on one.
Oh!
Big viking!
Tries to pound!
Small woman!
Save me!
Alright, we're fine.
Oh my god, the viking's back!
It's fine.
We killed the viking.
It's just like...
It's just like American Horror Story.
You know, the witch scene?
Oh my god, things look dire, but it worked.
It worked.
Things looked really dire, but it's working.
Oh, you guys never heard...
Watch American Horror Story?
Or is that scene?
Okay, so like...
Spoiler alert!
But like, American Horror Story is like every season, it's a new story.
And then the thing is, it's like really fucked...
One of the story is like really fucked up.
So like, these girls discover they're witches by having like powers manifest.
And then like, one of these girls' powers was that if you try to bang her, you die.
And she found out because like, her boyfriend was like, let's do it.
And then she's like, okay.
Like, you know.
And then, you know.
And then he fucking dies.
That's basically it.
And I was like, that's a fucked up power.
That's actually a fucked up power.
And then the other witches have like real fucking power.
And everything.
Like, some of them are like power of nature or like resurrection power.
This fucker's power is that she can't fuck because any guy she tries to bang fucking dies.
So it's like...
It's like...
Bro, that sucks, you know?
Like, compared to everybody else and her fucking...
Jesus Christ, QM.
What is this?
What the...
Huh?
What?
Woah!
Guys!
Guys, that's a lot of fucking damage.
Yeah, it's limited...
Yes, it's limited to men.
Because it's her...
It's her virginity that causes it.
The power is stored in the virginity.
Wait, don't... What happened to her?
Oh!
He DC'd!
I was gonna say, why is this so much harder?
I just realized.
I didn't even notice he was fucking gone.
That makes a lot more sense now.
That's fucked.
We should at least just get a bot.
We actually have a DC.
Like...
When did he DC?
I was like, we have one tank.
I didn't even realize.
Oh, that's actually fucked too.
I think at that point we have to run a DPS.
Oh no.
Oh no!
Our only tank!
Alright, nice.
We should get like, stat bonus.
Like, you basically get XP.
Ult charge twice as fast.
If you have a lever.
Guys, I don't think we should push up.
Guys, yes.
I'm so low.
Oh my god, we lived.
Oh my god, he's back!
Welcome back bro, we're winning.
Oh no, don't say that.
No!
Welcome back bro, we're winning.
Fucking dies.
Oh hey.
There we go.
Don't worry, I saved your life.
No need to thank me.
There we go.
Oh, okay, that's fine.
We did it!
We actually won a 5v6.
That's crazy.
We're just that good.
Oh my god, we're in diamond now.
We're in diamond.
But we still need three.
We still need two more games.
Yes!
We're 99.92% better.
Than all of you.
We're out of the plat mines.
Oh my god.
Actual two more games.
Two more games.
It's two more games.
People never ban Luna.
They always ban a DPS.
What kind of freak will ban Luna?
You have one ban and you pick Luna.
There's no way.
I believe society would not do that to me.
Oh my god, I'm literally right here.
I'm so close.
I hope all of these people lose.
There's only a hundred spots left.
Yes, you can.
Yes, of course.
You can always drop back down.
There's no way.
We're in actual diamond lobbies.
How does hero ban work?
Wait.
How does hero ban work then?
Yes, see?
See?
Everyone picks Hella.
Yes!
I'm free.
Oh wait, you ban two?
Yeah, fuck off.
Yeah, that's right.
Alright.
No
one cares about banning Luna.
Sorry, Esky, but it's...
It's a risk we gotta take.
Let's go.
Wait, are we going goats again?
Oh my god.
Okay.
We can make this work again.
We have Storm.
I mean, we're in diamond.
It should be fine.
Everybody's really good in this ELO.
We're in diamond lobbies now.
That's fine.
We're in diamond.
It's fine.
We've made it.
We've made it, guys.
Two more games.
Two more games!
And then we're top 500 for a day.
We get to be...
Top 500 for a fucking day.
Holy shit.
What the fuck?
How?
Jesus.
How much damage are y'all taking?
Who is it?
Oh my god, everybody's taking so much damage.
Jesus Christ.
Oh my god.
I have ult, but like...
I don't even know this.
Okay, now it's definitely worth it.
Like...
Now it's...
Oh my god.
I don't...
I don't know.
Guys.
Guys, I don't know if their support is working right now.
Okay, yeah.
Yeah, when I'm ace right now...
Yeah, I think we need a little bit more DPS.
Jesus Christ, these games.
Oh my god.
Guys.
Guys, I need help.
I need help.
They're all there.
Okay, guys.
We get like...
One kill.
That'd be pretty neat.
That'd be pretty neat, guys.
Neato.
I don't even know...
I think it's just a team diff.
Oh my god.
That Punisher is fucking crazy.
He has 15 kills.
Hmm.
Yeah, that's a...
Yeah, this is...
That's a little awkward, guys.
That's a little awkward.
Don't worry.
This game will be different, right guys?
Right?
This game's gonna be different now.
Guys, three more games now.
Guys.
Three more games.
We're stuck in a loop of two and then three.
When will it stop?
Oh my god, he also...
I hate this because like...
I keep going back to the portal.
So it's like...
What?
Why?
Going back in.
Get me back in.
I don't want to be back in.
I don't want to be there anymore.
I survived.
But at what cost?
I watched all my friends die.
What?
Oh, we don't get it again because everybody is so alive.
Guys, give me a sec.
You're all taking an exceptionally amount...
Large amount of damage, everybody.
That is very, very hard to heal, everybody.
Oh my god, is that...
Oh my god, we got killed.
Oh my god.
Oh, no!
No!
I didn't see the fucking Doctor Strange!
Jesus Christ.
Poor guy.
I don't know if we lived this.
But I will try my best...
To just start swimming.
Just start dancing.
Hey guys, we should touch the point.
Yay!
Three more games.
Three more...
Three more games!
I'm stuck in hell.
I'm actually...
I'm stuck in fucking hell.
Three more fucking games!
I'll grab a snack.
I haven't had lunch.
I...
Tokyo tonight?
Yes.
I'll be right back.
Back.
I got myself...
A tangerine.
I haven't had one...
Actually, no, JK.
I haven't had one on stream in a while.
But I've been eating tangerines off stream.
Um...
Because I went on...
Whole Foods.
I'm never buying from Whole Foods again, by the way.
Um...
Whole Foods is a fucking scam.
Fuck.
Tokyo, I'm never gonna get sponsored by Whole Foods again.
No.
I saw they had tangerines.
So I was like, yeah.
I didn't realize...
You know, they're supposed to be more healthy.
But like...
Oh, there's...
Oh, there's somebody.
There's somebody that's not Diamond.
No hero bands.
Thank God.
But like...
Basically, like...
I didn't realize Whole Foods...
Was like, you know...
I know it's like mostly like...
Expensive.
More expensive.
Because...
But I didn't realize it was just...
Organic.
And gluten-free.
Because I was like...
I want something not gluten-free.
But like...
Their entire pasta aisle...
Was like gluten-free pasta.
I was like...
I don't fucking want gluten-free pasta.
I want regular pasta.
Yeah.
So like...
Made me angry.
I got angry.
I wanted regular pasta.
Yeah, so I'm never buying from Whole Foods again.
I wasted so much money.
Because I was already there.
I was already there.
Oh my god.
And then I bought like...
I bought like a...
Tag...
What is it called?
The pasta.
It starts...
I don't know how to pronounce it.
I know how...
I know how to...
Spell it.
The tag...
Something.
I don't know.
I gotta focus.
Fuck.
Gotta keep people alive.
I tried to keep people alive.
But it was not possible.
It was not possible.
Well, we'll talk about this later.
I don't know what he expected.
I...
All I did was left click.
They take so much damage.
I might put it on tank instead.
Because these are like flanking tanks.
Yeah, our tanks are like both...
I'm gonna go fucking in and just start fucking brawling.
They're both like...
What's it called?
Tanks that wanna fucking fight.
Can't heal this myself.
Can we touch?
Oh.
Woah.
Woah, that's...
Woah, that's unlucky.
Woah.
Woah, I might be dead too.
Guys.
Guys, there's a tank right here.
There's two tankies right here.
There's...
There's two tanks right here.
Oh my god, he's still there!
The tag...
Tag...
Gelate...
Noodles.
I was like...
Oh, I love those!
But they tasted terrible because they were the gluten-free version.
I'm sorry if you guys like gluten-free noodles, but I was not feeling it.
I was not fucking feeling it.
I was so sad.
It tasted so fucking weird.
Oh no.
I'm gonna be a mindless foreigner.
I don't know...
AGAIN?!
Just need to know.
It knows.
You got the most healing out of everybody.
Oh my god.
Nice.
Okay, it's fine.
Oh, I'm 90%.
96.
I finally learned how to hide in the corner when I hear hello.
No longer am I gonna fucking...
Fucking...
I shall no longer look at things like that anymore.
I finally learned.
Oh my god.
Use this because you're all so low.
I'm a little worried here.
Oh shit.
JK.
Why am I fucking worried?
Oh my god.
He could've again-ed us.
Nice.
I finally learned.
Okay, I'm still trying to peel the stupid tangerine.
But yeah.
I'm not...
I'm not gonna buy from Whole Foods again after that.
I was so unhappy about my pasta.
Because I was so excited because I was like...
I've never...
I haven't had the Tagliatelle latte noodles in a long time.
And then I'm gonna...
I'm gonna...
I can't wait.
Oh my god.
I can't wait to make some new pasta today.
And then I was so disappointed.
I just...
This is so weird.
I've never had gluten-free noodles before.
I'm honest.
I've never had gluten-free noodles.
So...
So I was just like...
I was just like, you know...
I wanna try something new.
And then I said like, whip eggs.
By the way, what does gluten...
What is gluten-free anyway?
Also like...
What the fuck is gluten-free?
I don't even know what that means.
No wheat or...
Wait, no wheat or flour?
Oh my god!
Oh shit.
That's basically pasta!
No wonder it tastes like dog shit.
Holy shit.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to eat gluten-free stuff.
But it did not taste good.
Okay.
Oh my god.
If I knew that meant no wheat or flour...
I would not have fucking ate that shit.
I would not have bought that.
I was just like...
Hmm...
It's expensive.
Maybe it's good.
Little do I know.
It was literally one of the worst pastas I've ever had.
Nice.
We did it.
Yay!
No, three more games, guys.
Three more games.
Oh my god!
Okay.
I got scared.
I saw the portal and I saw fear.
I had fear in my eyes.
Nice.
Oh my god.
Two more games!
Guys!
Guys, two more games, everybody!
Guys, two more games.
We're so close.
Two more games!
Okay.
Three, six...
Yeah, two more games.
Fully two more...
It's actually...
Actual real.
No, it's two games.
There's still a hundred spots left.
There's still a hundred spots left in top 500.
So it's still two more games.
That's so interesting though.
The banning thing.
The ban system is incredibly interesting.
Okay, we're playing three supports.
Okay, we have no tank plays.
Okay.
Oh no.
Hello?
I won't say hello.
Oh, Hawkeye?
That's fine.
Oh.
What do we do now?
I don't fucking know.
Magneto?
What if we just ban Dr. Strange?
Black Panther?
Who the fuck plays Black Panther?
Ha ha ha!
Okay.
Yeah, Sylark got picked.
We don't have a tank player.
Guys, this is bad.
We don't...
We don't have...
We don't have a tank player.
Oh, and of course it's on this dogshit fucking map.
Fucking course.
Guys, three more games.
No tank player.
It never ends.
It never fucking ends.
Four...
Three...
Two...
One!
Don't forget, securing the mission area is your top priority.
Hell is my realm.
But sooner will not be the only one.
They won't know.
They won't...
How does this TP shit look like?
I always feel like it takes so long.
Even like for people who know what the fuck they're doing.
Oh, we got a kill.
Look at that.
Good for him.
Oh, we got two kills.
Good for them.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, I live.
Fucking idiots.
That's fucking right.
I live.
Oh, you gotta move?
So they're basically walking to the area?
Oh, that's interesting.
I didn't know that.
So they actually have to walk to the area they want to TP in?
Bro, that's fucked.
I don't know why it takes so long.
They're literally fucking traveling over.
Trying to figure out when to use this ult here.
Oh, okay.
That's fine.
Oh no, he's on the mushroom.
We have no support ults now, so what happens, happens.
Okay, um, yeah.
There was nothing I could do there.
Sorry, buddy.
Sorry.
Reload.
You have to turn around.
You have to turn around again.
No!
Okay, that's actually funny.
I did not know you had to walk.
You have to walk to the place.
It's like, it's literally Google mapping.
You're fucking pulling a Google map, being like, where the fuck do I go?
Oh my god.
Where the fuck?
Wanted on Widowmaker?
This is the first time I've seen a Natasha.
I don't think I've ever seen one this entire in rank.
This is actually...
Oh my god!
Wait!
I didn't realize we TP'd into them!
I was so surprised.
I never realized we actually went into them.
Alright.
I'm gonna go to SK because she's been carrying.
Whoever's a good ace gets to have this little gift.
Just gonna have to get regular healing now, Hella.
Gotta deal with regular good old healers.
Oh!
That's fine.
That is totally fine.
Because we're dancing.
Yeah!
You wanna keep dancing, everybody?
You wanna keep dancing?
Oh!
Stop dancing!
The dancing has stopped!
We went too far.
We danced too hard, guys.
Guys, we should've stopped dancing.
We definitely should've stopped dancing.
That's fine.
Oh my god.
I'm just gonna do this.
Because you're all grouped up anyway.
Fine.
Alright, nice.
Okay, not nice.
Oh, that is definitely not nice.
I'm fucking...
I'm gonna skate away.
It's time to skate away.
Wait, who's over there?
Why did you live that long?
Alright, we gotta go!
I'm fucking...
Let's go!
No!
I couldn't touch it!
We couldn't touch it!
Oh, that's fucked.
Three more games, guys.
Three more games.
Bro!
Oh my god.
It truly is hell.
Damn.
Damn, that's fucked.
That's so fucked.
See, this is why we need roll heal.
You see, this is exactly why we need roll Q, guys.
A nice deep freeze.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, that's bad.
Three more...
Three more games.
Bro, this Gatsby guy.
All he does is complain.
Bro, he...
He doesn't even have top kills for the king.
For Hella.
Their...
Their ace is a Hella.
Where's our fucking Hella ace?
Oh my god.
Oh my god!
It's like a Bastion!
That felt like looking at a fucking Bastion right there.
Oh, he got...
What?!
That's literally like a Bastion turret.
I'm opening a portal.
Hella, please!
To be fair, our strange build.
I don't think...
We had zero tank players.
We got three more games.
God, that's fucking...
I'm in purgatory.
I'm actually stuck in purgatory.
I'm fucking...
I'm stuck in this purgatory of three to two more games.
I've...
I've only had one occasion.
I only had...
Whoa.
Okay.
Bro needs to touch me.
Alright.
Dude, I'm stuck in this hell.
Oh, whoa.
Just...
Whoa.
Oh, fuck.
We got Gatsby on our team too.
Bro!
We got Gatsby!
We have three people there!
Hella, babes!
Guys.
Guys, we gotta start avoiding people.
Lmao.
I thought they avoided him!
I legitimately thought they avoided him!
Guys, I think we have four more games.
Oh, they ban Hella too.
Nice.
See, I told you.
They always ban DPS.
I like how the guy picked Hawkeye.
I was like, yeah, you know what?
Yeah, fuck Hawkeye.
Oh, even they were like, yeah, fuck Hawkeye.
Oh my god, this is...
My fucking hellhole.
My fucking...
Hellhole.
My personal hell.
That's three to two games.
Three to two games.
I can never escape.
I chose this.
I told you.
Everybody's like, wow, escape!
Woah, what?
Nobody's asking.
Woah, Jokey bro.
Okay, to be fair, some people did.
But like...
But like, you know.
There's me.
I'm pretty cool too.
I'm pretty cool.
Unless you're on the enemy team.
You're banned if you steal my ELO.
If you're on enemy team and you fucking go like, woah, Jokey!
And I lose to you.
Don't make me find your name.
Alright.
I'm going in.
Guys, I'm like...
Oh my god, this actually fucking confuses me sometimes.
Nice.
Jesus Christ.
Everybody's taking so much damage.
Oh, it's because we have like a fucking squirrel girl one trick.
Which is basically like a Junkrat one trick.
So much damage.
And I'm scared.
I'm fine.
I feel so safe.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Except for that guy.
Oh no, he's getting...
Reload.
No!
I
bought a...
It's okay, we got a point at least.
We actually got fucked over by the jump.
Wait, I still have a point.
Let's go.
Oh my god.
I jumped off.
Dance alone on my stage.
Becoming a solo act.
I didn't wanna be Beyonc.
Wait, but I held the point though.
You know what?
I held the point though.
Where is...
Goodbye.
You...
It was just...
You just can't live that at that point.
Okay.
Oh my god.
Woah.
I think that guy just got solo ulted.
Woah!
I think I just saw him get solo ulted.
Oh, I thought I got him.
I think I have squirrel ult now.
I'm gonna reload my hands.
I'm sorry.
You're alive.
You're alive for a little bit longer.
God, okay.
You're alive a little...
Oh my god, please.
Why does no one wanna dance with me?
Oh, he got shielded?
Oh my god.
That would've hit if he didn't get shielded.
That's actually so fucked.
Guys.
Four more games.
Guys, this is not looking good.
We gotta start avoiding other DPS players.
This is not looking good.
We gotta start avoiding DPS players now.
We've made it.
Guys, we finally made it.
Diamond is the elo where there's too many DPS players.
Plat is the hell where there's too many support players.
I don't even know who's like doing well in our team.
Like, who should get this?
Three more games.
Literally.
Literally three more games.
Three more fucking games.
Four games actually.
Four more games.
This is where we die.
This is where I die.
Wait, Gatsby swapped to squirrel.
It's over.
He's mindbroken.
He's done.
He's fucking done done.
Yay, I'm again!
Is it again?
Oh shit!
Okay, that was crazy.
Oh, I froze somebody.
I even stood in front of...
I even went to stand in front of her.
I even stood in front of her.
Guys, I'm coming back, please.
We are undefeated!
Guys, again?
I'm just going to play on the support for now.
I'm going to play on wanted.
Just one.
Oh my god, he's so low!
Oh, who is it?
Who is it though?
That's him.
There was no saving that.
Oh, I saw people dead.
I don't think it's yay anymore.
Guys, it's not yay anymore.
Guys, the yays is over.
It's no more yays.
No more yays!
I'm at diamond!
I'm diamond three!
But, three more wins, diamond three.
I swear, I'll be chasing this top 500 high for like the next...
I swear, I'm going to do another stream.
Oh my god, I swear to god.
And I get to touch grandmaster before I get to top 500.
I swear to god.
I'm always like this close.
It's okay, it's fine.
It's fine.
I don't know where the squirrels are, but I assume everything is fine.
I'm dodging as many things as possible.
Oh my god, did he get it?
Did he get it?
I don't know if he did.
If you want heals, you gotta come down here.
Oh my god, he's so low!
Oh, no!
No!
Oh my god.
Okay, nice.
Holy shit.
Oh my god.
We're all trying so hard.
If I can't go, my god.
Bro, shut the fuck up, Gatsby.
Touch some fucking grass.
Gatsby, touch some grass.
He's just Gatsby.
Lock the fuck in.
How the fuck do you remember that?
Like, how do you remember the exactwhat's wrong with you?
What's wrong with you?
How do you remember the exact...
Actually, are you okay?
Like, exact number of damage...
What happened there?
Again!
Yeah, I'm capping for us.
Don't worry.
You don't have to worry about me, I guess.
They just want to think about how I'm doing.
I like ban system.
I'm glad they added a ban.
But then that means those who learn Hawkeye and the people that learn Hawkeye and Hela, there's no It's actually, like, sucks to be them, I guess.
Oh myguys, guys, there's like 20 people behind us.
Because I think, like, Hawkeye is insta-bad.
That's what I'm saying.
Why waste it on a support?
I can one-trick all I want.
That's the best part.
They're enabling me.
Oh.
Okay, goodbye.
Alright, yeah, there's no saving that.
I'm getting away from you guys.
I don't wanna get hit.
This is a really tight game, though.
Alright, we push.
Alright, we don't push that side.
We go to the right side.
Oh my god, Ihonestly, what's the game plan there?
Alright, they said winnable.
We have DPS.
We better kill the Psylocke, because we know what's gonna happen.
We should really kill the Psylocke.
Oh, got it.
Yeah.
I knew the momentyou know, the moment I used that ult, I was like, oh shit, wait, that was sick.
Guys, I need you guys to stop grouping together so you won't die.
Wouldn't that be cool?
Are you alive?
You are.
Okay.
He lives.
Oh my god, he does not live no more.
Oh, that'sthat's a lot of damage.
It's just you and I support, and also you, I guess.
Guys, we have to kill that.
We
Oh my god.
Okay.
Before we kill, we gotta avoid it.
Okay, whookay, who's avoiding him?
Four more games.
Guys.
Hey, we broke the fourthree game thing.
Okay.
I swear to god, they better have avoided him.
I swear to god, wethat was suchso fast.
If I see fuckingoh, he's not there.
Okay, I was gonna say, if I see Gatsby there again, I swear to fucking god.
Oh my god.
Four more games.
Oh, thank god.
Thank fucking god.
We get to finally have him on the other side.
I'm so happy.
Oh shit, someone issomeone's notDiamond!
Who could it be?
Water real quick, guys.
I'll be right back.
Alright, here we go.
Alright, two supports.
We haveoh my god, I've never seen two tanks before.
I feel like it's been 20 years since I saw two tanks.
It's actually crazy.
They actually exist in this world.
They're actually real.
Who the fuck would've thought?
They actually exist?
Two separate tanks?
Is it crazy, like, today I bumped into zero Luna mains?
What the fuck happened last night?
Guys, I don't know about this.
Oh.
I have to reload.
Oh my god.
What the fuck happened?
We got two fucking kills.
Oh my god, what happened?
It's fine, that's fine.
I'm gonna put in one of the tanks for now.
Because we have two, like, flankerslike, two tanks that arewe have the Captain America that's more so, like, he's going in.
Yeah.
See, there he is.
He's going fucking in.
He's going in, in.
Jesus Christ, he's going so in.
He's still going in.
He's stilloh, oh, oh, oh, oh, dancing in the circle!
Alright, that's fine.
Oh my god, the stupid tree!
It's fine.
Oh my god, she'sshe's her!
She's him!
Oh my god.
Okay, that's fine.
I'm on the Panther now.
Their group!
Yeah, I think me putting it on the Captain America was a good idea.
Because he has not yet died, which is crazy.
I honestly did not expect him to live that long.
And now he might die.
Because, like, the Penny Parker is the one that's tanking everything, so me healing Penny is healing Capuh, Captain America.
So it's beneficial.
What if I stay behind there?
He can never hit me.
There's no way he gets in here.
Woo!
My god, you're so silly!
I can't believe he ran.
Is he still alive?
He's still alive?!
Look at all that!
My god, he actually lived?!
Oh my god, I'm gonna get my nethernether ult again at this rate.
Please, guys.
One kill!
There we go, it's not that difficult to get one kill, guys!
Oh, okay, Iokay, youoh, okay, I'll go DPoh, okay, I'll go attack, I'll go heal.
So, who's gonna be who?
I like how we couldn'twe couldn't figure out who wants to be healed and who wants to be attacked.
Wait, what?!
I was like, yeahI can'tyou heal?
I heal?
Oh, we both heal, okay.
It's very difficult to figure it out.
I couldn't tell.
We're just too busy dancing.
We're just dancing.
Oh, we just kept dancing.
And then I'm just gonna... oh, he's... oh, ho, ho, ho.
That was me last time.
Nice.
Goodbye, Captain America.
Hello, Captain America.
Oh, goodbye forever, Captain America?
Oh my god, please.
He's so... he's half, he's half.
Okay, nice.
We'll play here.
Oh no, Benny, no!
Please!
Why are we still here?
Please get over here.
I'm here to dance!
Get the trio!
No!
He couldn't dance!
Poor guy.
He couldn't dance.
Whiskey, please look at me.
Whiskey, please.
Please, I'm like right here.
Thank you.
Oh my god.
No!
Oh, he can fly.
Could he sing too?
Oh, I'm sorry.
There's too much.
Oh
my god, please!
This fight is never ending!
I have ult, but I wait.
Okay, we got Groot.
We have both support ults.
Oh my god, and he came in through a portal!
Guys, four more games.
We need two!
I am two!
Yes!
Oh, not yes!
Not yes anymore!
Not yes!
Oh,
did SK also ulted?
Oh my god, I didn't realize she ulted too.
I didn't realize.
Bro, what the fuck is wrong with this guy?
Bro, thank god he doesn't know VTuber exists.
Thank fucking god, bro.
Fuck that guy.
That actually kept ulting of SK?
I thought that was the enemy Luna.
I didn't realize it was SK that ulted.
Man, he's a fucking weirdo.
Bro, he really needs to touch grass.
He really needs to- Bro, what the fuck is wrong with you, bro?
Actually?
Bro, what's wrong with him?
Bro, I don't know.
What does he do?
Bro, is he okay?
I don't think he knows- He has social contacts.
I don't think- I don't- I don't think- I don't think he knows that he was like condescending with that.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Let him live in- Never meet your heroes.
You don't know if we're shit-talking you if you bump into us in rank.
That's right.
If you were in my lobby...
You know damn well...
I was not a good person to you.
True.
Never meet your heroes.
Exactly.
I should talk every- Exactly.
I should talk every random.
That's right.
Oh, thank you.
I got the little peek-a-pews.
Oh my god.
Again!
You should know better.
Whenever I said a nice thing about randoms.
You should know by now.
Again!
I'm scared.
Don't look at me.
Okay.
Nice.
If we win this, we're back to three- We're back to the three game phase.
I like to do that as my shortcut.
Cause I know you can do the stairs, but this is faster.
But it's also like...
Not efficient.
Oh,
this is bad.
Where's my cover?
Guys, this is bad.
This is bad.
We were all gonna die anyway.
Three to four.
I hope it's just three to four.
Bro, we had five ults, bro.
It's fucking crazy.
My...
Everything should be fine.
Wait, did it not work?
Jesus Christ!
Stand in a line!
Stand in a fucking line!
Line!
Oh, when I fucking jumped off.
He actually jumped off!
Oh,
it's bad.
I didn't want to use my ult, but...
It's bad.
I'm putting on the other tank, so it'll be easier to heal.
Yeah,
I'll use mine after then.
Okay.
I have to use this.
It's okay, guys!
It's okay!
Stand underneath this!
Don't stand underneath this!
Nevermind!
Do not stand underneath the bridge!
I realized the error.
Do not stand underneath the bridge, guys.
When you see an LL.
Oh, you're so low.
Can we get anybody?
Oh no, this is bad.
Oh, this is bad.
I cannot... I won't be able to get all... in this fight, so...
No way!
Guys, I don't... Yeah, I was gonna say, bro.
Yeah, that portal is not gonna hit.
Oh my god, Dr. Strange, please!
Live for us!
Live!
Oh, he lived.
Wait, why?
Oh, because she was close to ult.
I'm gonna put on the other tank.
It's just...
Our tank is taking too much damage.
Oh my god, I have to use it.
I have to use this, so...
So we can all live a little longer.
Oh my god.
I'm trying to see you.
Oh no, he's brooding.
Oh no, he's brooding!
But the touch is soon.
No!
I'm standing on a point, guys!
Someone else stand on it before I die!
No!
Oh my god.
Oh my god, I actually did 48k healing, too!
For the last...
Oh, look at me!
Oh my god!
Oh my god.
I kept...
Okay.
Oh my god.
Bro, that's actually paid!
How much healing?
Okay, I'll show you guys.
And my accuracy is higher, too.
And my accuracy...
That's so painful.
Oh my god.
I did so much heals.
No, just four more games, guys!
Is it four?
3, 6, 7, 8, 9.
Yeah, it's four games.
Get me out of this hellhole.
Get me out.
Let me out.
They did more damage?
They had the opportunity to do more damage.
With the space that they had.
The space I had?
I had to just heal.
The tanks were just not okay.
They were...
They were not okay.
As in like, they were not healthy at all.
Every time I looked at them, they would be like, no HP.
And they'd just be like...
They'd just be like...
I'm Diamond 3 currently.
I'll pin it, too.
Okay.
Currently...
Currently at Diamond 3.
Top 500.
500 is high D3.
Okay.
Yeah, I had no time to not heal.
I just had to heal non-stop.
I had to heal non-stop until like, you know...
Until something happens.
Holy shit.
Fucking hell.
Oh my god.
No.
We had some good games.
This is the...
This is the curse Gatsby.
We had Gatsby.
Gatsby.
And avoided Gatsby.
And then he's not on DPS.
That's the worst part.
Gatsby...
Gatsby was on our team.
Took DPS.
Gatsby was on the enemy team.
He finally decided to play support.
He finally decided to fucking fail.
He actually was like, you know what?
I'm gonna fail this time and play support.
Instead of DPS.
Yeah.
We asked him to give us DPS.
And he's like, no.
So I think it's like wanted.
Or...
Wanted or SK.
I had to go support.
So yeah.
Oh.
Alright.
GG's.
Thanks for the game.
Okay.
Fucking...
We can do this.
We can...
We...
We could do this.
Oh my homie.
That's why he's fucking dead.
In his...
That's why he's dead.
Alright.
Four more games.
How are you always stuck in the fourth three?
Four to three.
It's always four to three.
How?
How are we stuck in this hellhole?
This is the worst purgatory.
I got to experience what it was like when it was...
I swear.
If I like...
Oh my god.
If I have to...
I'm okay.
I'm so okay.
Oh shit.
It's KarQ.
Ready.
Oh my god.
Wait.
Oh, he's gold.
Can you Q?
Can you...
Oh, bye.
Oh.
Goodbye KarQ.
Wait, is he not?
Oh, bring berries.
That's yellow.
That's gold one.
Guys, that's just yellow plat, guys.
Yeah, that's just yellow plat.
It's like...
It's basically platinum, but there's a visual bug, guys.
It's just a visual bug, chat.
I've seen him around in Overwatch days.
Never...
He was...
He's east though.
So...
So I never really got him...
Got him much.
Yeah, he's a fucking eastie.
So...
I never bump...
I rarely bump into east coast players.
Unless like...
Unless like I VPN.
Sometimes I VPN the east coast because at one time...
At one time, east coast lobbies were better.
And I would swap to...
Swap to east coast for Overwatch.
He's an eastie.
West coast, best coast, always.
Game Awards is tomorrow?
Wait, is it?
What time is it?
What time is the Game Awards?
Game Awards is just...
Yeah, you're damn right you are.
It's a full diamond.
I'm Luna Snow.
Like the moon, I shine in darkness.
Oh, that's a cool icon.
Where is Rudy?
Hawkeye?
Do we have a strange player?
Yeah, Hawkeye.
Oh, I can play strings.
I'm not the best at it.
Hella?
Hella or Hawkeye?
Hawkeye.
Let's go 50-50.
Whatever.
Alright.
Perfect.
Nice.
Do you guys want to ban Strange?
Or do we want to play?
We can... I say we ban him.
We ban Strange?
That's how you can do it.
Yeah, fuck Strange.
No portals today.
No fucking portals today.
Alright.
No Psylocke for you guys.
Sorry, SK.
You gotta learn a new character.
Portals cancelling.
Cancel now.
We're in a timeline where...
Where Doctor Strange never became Doctor Strange.
He's still a successful plastic surgeon.
What are we gonna do?
Fucking ban Luna?
They're never gonna ban Luna, guys.
I can literally be enabled to be a one-trick.
They're never gonna ban her.
They don't want to waste a slot on a support.
Oh.
Star Lord.
Oh, sorry.
Heart Surgeon.
Oh my god, hey!
It's Spider-Man!
I almost got it correct.
I get like 50% of my Marvel lore correct.
Because I'm a DC girl.
I'm a DC girl so I only get like 50% of my Marvel lore correct.
I just know it was a surgeon of some kind.
I took a 50-50 guess because I know he like fucked up his hands from a car crash.
Because I never watch the movies.
Jesus Christ!
Guys, Thor is doing bad things right now.
Oh,
goodbye Fabi.
I thought that was the enemy right there.
Okay, I need to put this on the Venom.
Wait, how did we lose our guy?
Oh.
Okay, goodbye again.
He's so tired.
Oh no, guys.
I think I might derank.
Guys.
No.
No, I just...
Not like this.
Oh my god.
I missed it.
Oh, I missed it.
I missed the freeze.
That's okay.
Just beat up Thor, please!
Kill the gun!
I thought we could hit in four hours.
I was fucking foolish.
I was a fool.
For believing in...
Guys.
If we don't do it in six hours...
We're Marvel rivaling again.
There is a possibility...
That we're just gonna keep Marvel rivaling.
It's getting closer to God of War, guys.
It's getting closer.
Oh,
what?
I ulted.
Guys, I think...
I don't know, guys.
Yeah.
The announcement...
I'm playing more Marvel right now.
Guys,
why?
Why didn't you just went in?
Guys, you're in Diamond!
Please, please.
Watch out!
Oh, no!
No, I got fucking caught!
No!
I need farming going!
Oh, my God.
He's so dumb.
Why did he not go in?
Oh, my God.
Bro!
No!
I don't know.
You're not fucking going in.
I think the issue was that we were all on...
They were on high ground, but both supports were on low ground.
That was a problem.
Oh, my God.
Guys, all I'm saying...
If you curse me more...
Streams will continue to become Marvel Rivals.
Oh,
no.
I can't derink.
No!
I'm going to add my own BGM at this point.
He broke the fucking...
Oh, my God.
I used three ults there.
It's fine.
We're fine.
Where do you hear this clown music, Dookie?
What do you mean?
Don't you guys hear the music too?
Don't you guys hear that music?
Do you not hear it playing?
Please.
I don't want to...
I don't want it to be spawning time!
No!
Alright.
That's fine.
That's my least favourite time of the year.
It's okay.
It's not okay.
It's fine.
We're so bad.
That's right!
You and I!
Come on, get him!
That's fine.
We're fine.
My sanity is gone, but look at this cool number I've got.
I'm diamond three!
That's where all the high elo players are.
Dookie, that's not...
We should top 500.
We're stronger together!
Guys, we need to...
No, I had to look behind because I got...
They were like, we need healing.
So I was like, you do?
Let me look behind me.
No,
he was one!
Wait, where's my res?
Where's my res?
Where was it?
Where did it come from?
Where did it go?
Oh, you're right.
Okay, I have an idea what to play.
I think it'd be fabulous to have an all-superhero band.
Having an all-fabby band was a good idea.
I know what music to play after this game.
It doesn't matter win or loss.
I've been stuck at four to two games for so long.
I know exactly what to play.
I think like, honestly, I think if we have a tank player, it'd be easier.
I legit...
If we have a tank player, it would be a little easier.
I think.
Alright.
Here we go.
That's fine.
I'll have to heal as one of them.
Guys.
You guys are taking a lot of damage and I'm scared.
You guys are taking way too much damage and I'm a little scared.
Okay.
No!
Fucking course that kills me!
Fucking course!
Oh my god.
Get the point.
Get the fucking point.
Who's still on it?
Who's a freak that's still on it?
You don't.
Okay.
Please.
I can't.
No!
I couldn't hit in time!
I got hit.
Oh.
Poor Magneto.
Oh my god, Mercy res.
Okay.
I don't know if this will work.
But...
Guys.
No.
No!
He booped me off the health pack!
I almost got to the health pack too!
I actually almost got there!
That's so fucked.
That's actually so fucked.
Okay.
I think, like, we gotta reset.
Why are we going in one by one?
Stop!
We have one last fight.
And I don't think I can...
No!
Alright.
Oh my god.
I do hate...
It's time to bring out the circus.
Alright, this is the song I...
This is the one.
Alright.
Wait, let me see if I...
Okay, this is the one I was thinking of.
Alright.
Oh my god.
This hurts.
Alright, is it this one?
Or is it?
Oh my god, where is it?
I need to find it.
Okay, wait, wait.
What's...
Okay, so you know how, like...
Okay, wait.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
I need to find it.
I need to find the...
I need to find the exact soundtrack.
No, that's creepy!
No!
What is it called?
Is it this?
Oh.
Wait, I think it's this.
Wait, okay.
Okay, okay.
Entrance.
Alright, I don't know if it sounds...
If it's like...
A little different or not.
Oh my god, nobody is like...
In yet.
Okay, this sounds sadder now.
This is a sad version...
Of...
It's slowed and...
This is a sad version of it.
Put it on the nose!
Draver, put it on...
Bum, bum, bum, bum, buuum...
Fly back in the circus we go!
We're back in the circus!
Yipeee!
We're in the circus now!
How the fuck?
How did they all die?
Oh nice, he rooted.
Go Groot him!
Go Groot, Groot!
Guys, he Grooted too hard, guys.
It's fine.
I'm gonna put on the other tank, so we can have both tanks up.
So they'll never die.
A little pause...
Please look at me.
You're not gonna win that 1v1, you're bad.
Know your place.
Know your fucking place.
Be a good son.
Don't
worry, I'm here.
I didn't put on repeat.
We're in the game, I can't put it on repeat right now.
You're not important, Psylocke!
You couldn't even win a 1v1, you think I'm gonna let you just get healed over our fucking tanks?
Oh, you got killed, okay.
Okay, maybe it's okay.
Oh no.
Oh no, I'm in.
What's he gonna do?
Shoot me from here?
Okay.
It's fine.
Wait, did he?
That's fine.
See?
It's easy.
Look at that.
I picked wisely.
God, I'm so fucking good at Luna.
Oh my god, I'm so good.
They get healed, I win.
That's right, Groot.
Start Grooting!
Groot all over them!
And then I won't burn all your family down.
Okay.
But not like that, Groot.
Okay, Groot.
Okay.
I didn't realize there's an invisible wall there.
So that like, you can't, you have to jump to get past it.
Wait, are they also Groot?
Well, that's fucked.
How can you just start Grooting?
Oh, he's gonna Groot.
I froze somebody, I don't know who.
Oh no, he has no shield.
Alright, it's fine.
It's fine.
Please.
Oh god, I'm dancing.
I'm gonna dance!
I'm gonna dance so you all live!
No!
Oh thank god, okay.
Okay, it's Hella vs.
Hella.
Who wins?
Nice, we won.
Alright.
Alright, let me put this on repeat.
And then we can all enjoy it.
Wait, what's the word called when you make a song sad?
Make a song sad?
Like, you know how like, there's happy things, happy songs?
And, uh, minor!
Oh yeah, circus music and minor key.
Okay, let me see if I can find that.
Circus music and minor key.
Creepiest- is it this?
What does this sound like?
That's how I feel.
What?
I just said it's a madness.
Do you like the London seafood?
What year is it where you come from?
Four.
Bum bum bum.
Three.
Two.
One.
This is where we live forever.
Anxiety.
Bum bum bum.
How I feel when I play this game sometimes.
Oh my god, this is how I feel playing this game.
It's getting more intense.
How did I- I don't even- I was not focused in that game.
Oh, now you can see what hap- yeah, yep.
You'll live!
You're gonna live!
They're gonna fucking kill us after this.
They're- they're still gonna kill us.
They're definitely gonna kill us after this.
Oh my god.
Oh, he's coming in.
He's grooting.
Oh god, okay.
He's grooting!
Dr. Strange, you're fucking crazy!
Oh my god.
We're still putting a show!
That's what I'm trying to do!
Where are you guys?
Where the fuck are you guys?
I think I'm Groot.
Oh my god, where the fuck did you guys go?
Holy shit.
All I'm saying is that they were not there.
Me and Groot, we're homies.
We're tight like that.
He's grooting.
Nice.
Got you, Hawkeye!
Look at that, that's the first time I called him Hawkeye instead of Hanzo.
He's grooting.
Okay, this is fine.
No, not the car!
Okay.
I got you!
He is Groot.
Oh, that's awkward.
That's so awkward, guys.
That's so fucking awkward.
That's okay.
We're gonna make good use of both our support ults, right?
He doesn't know I'm right here.
That's a little awkward.
It's Groot.
Oh, he has the eye.
Oh, we're fine, we're fine, we're fine, we're fine, we're fine, we're fine, we're fine, we're fine, we're fine, we're fine, we're fine.
We're not fine, we're not fine, we're not fine, we're not fine, we're not fine.
We're not fine.
We are...
I'm here, though.
I die on point.
There's too many...
There's too many Groots.
There's too... there's too many Groots.
What do we do with all these Groots?
We're keeping you up.
Stop!
Let me heal!
I can't see you guys!
Am I not dancing?
Oh, I am.
I'm dancing.
I stopped dancing.
I didn't realize.
Okay, we're fine.
You're taking so much damage.
I'm feeling so stressed out now, for real.
Remember when I say support doesn't make me stressed?
This is the most damage I've ever seen them take.
I swear, they are... they are taking so much damage.
Like, what the fuck?
Jesus Christ.
It's just... it's just...
Oh, no!
No!
We're all gonna make me live!
Nothing died!
I have 47k healing!
Holy fuck!
Oh, my God!
There's no way!
Bro!
What do you want me to do?
I... all my heals are going to her tanks!
Oh, my God!
What?
I have 47k... oh, guys.
Guys, I have 47k healing, guys.
Guys, I don't think the DPS really want to swap, guys.
No zero... that's just a stupid excuse.
That's a fucking cop-out answer.
Dude, we cannot do this.
Hold on.
Alright, this is bad.
Uh, we're down a burst, so be careful.
What's wrong with purple?
I like purple.
Just rooting.
I'm right.
Up top, up top.
Zap.
Zap up there.
I'm getting so much free space!
Jesus.
I'm getting so much free space for that.
For no reason.
No!
What?
I pressed Q!
It had Q in there!
It showed on my screen!
That's their off-angles.
I'm like 1v3'ing on high with stream.
Portal behind me.
Oh, my God.
That's... oh, my... that tilted me.
That actually tilted me.
That tilted me.
Holy shit.
Cause that was a Q on my end, too.
I got pinged so hard.
Okay.
Nice.
Yay!
Oh, my God.
That's a lot to push, though.
This is a lot.
Oh, my God.
There's so much to push, though.
Oh!
Oh, my God.
Alright.
Three minutes to push that far.
This is gonna be a little bit difficult.
It's gonna be a little difficult.
Just a little bit difficult.
Can we get... we have 52k healing.
If we had two tanks, I definitely could've got 70k healing.
I think.
I think if we had two tanks.
It was definitely possible.
Woo!
I'd be so sad if we hit grandmaster before we hit top 500.
Like, we're always chasing that top 500 dream.
And it's always two to three games.
Like...
The two to three games.
It's always two to three games.
I'm brewing.
Groot, Groot, Groot!
He's still Grooting!
Jesus Christ, I don't know what to do, guys.
You guys take too much damage for me to do anything.
Guys, you guys take way too much damage, guys!
I am Groot.
Oh my god!
Yes!
Okay!
Like, what?
Like, how?
I think we need a second tank, guys.
Guys, I think we need a second tank, guys.
I know, guys.
It might be five more games, guys, because DPS Ego is today.
You guys wanna come down here?
Oh...
You guys wanna come down?
Okay, I cannot heal.
My ult is not like infinite heals, guys.
It's...
It's like...
There's a finite in there.
It's a...
There's a finite and not an infinite.
No, we haven't got a kill and attack, guys.
It's a little concerning.
I'm gonna TP S.
Okay.
Alright!
This is the last ditch effort!
Do you think it'll be okay?
Do you think they'll be okay?
Do you think...
Guys!
Oh my god!
Do you think SK knows a tank player that's...
Wait, what's my heal?
What's my heals at?
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck.
That's so painful.
Oh my god!
I'm at 60k heals!
Holy shit!
I'm at 60...
Oh my god.
That's crazy.
I'm at 60k heals.
How did I get there, you might wonder.
Oh my god.
This always happens.
Alright, let's see.
That hurts.
This is the Gatsby curse right here.
It all started with Gatsby when they didn't avoid him.
This is the Gatsby curse.
It started here.
And then it never...
It never recovered.
The Gatsby curse was real here.
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck.
Do you know any tank players?
Online?
Lmao.
Oh, not a single one.
Oh!
Now we're just missing a tank player.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
It's okay, we'll be fine.
It's okay.
This is what happens when you curse us like this.
Guys.
This is what...
You wanted this.
Tomorrow we're cancelling the voice part of the stream.
It's Marvel Rivals and announcement.
It's over.
Lmao.
You wanted this.
It's Marvel Rivals and announcement.
Lmao.
You gave me the Curse of Ra.
You live with your mistakes.
You're living with your mistakes today.
Lmao.
Is it?
Wait, yes.
But you...
You are fucking sheep to sure for.
You're fucking...
You saw him be like, Curse of Ra.
You're like, hehe.
Curse of Ra.
You contributed.
You fucking contributed to the problem.
It's...
You know what you were doing.
Lmao.
Curse of Caspi.
Alright, here we go.
Here we go.
Okay.
This is fine.
I think I was...
I'm playing fine.
It's just RNG as always.
It's always RNG.
RNG.
The RNG-sus is not on our side today.
Run.
Woah, I am so fast.
I got the bubble.
I got the bubble, but there was no reason for me to have the bubble.
I didn't need to be that fast.
Woah, that scared the shit out of me.
I think I'm gonna put on the tank though.
Get off.
Be secure.
No.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Get off.
Please.
Oh my god!
Oh, they got it.
They got it yet again.
Where's Captain America?
You get this.
You're just gonna go in and feed.
I know it.
Oh no!
Oh!
I...
I can't...
I can't heal through that.
I cannot heal through that.
There's no way.
They have to be doing...
That was crazy.
That was the craziest play they could have done.
Someone please shoot this.
Shoot the fucking thing.
No!
No, it was the moon dragon.
Not the moon dragon.
It was the fucking...
The moon knight.
Curse of the fucking whatever.
I don't fucking know what it's called.
He ulted with the Gibraltar.
Oh, not fucking Gibraltar.
Groot ult.
With the Gibraltar ult.
No, it's past three games.
We're...
We're at those demon hours now.
Shoot this!
You're in...
Oh my god, please.
Why is nobody shooting this?
Okay, I guess I'll shoot it.
That's fine.
Guys.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, I think we might...
I can't believe we're gonna have to swap.
We're gonna have to...
We're gonna have to do...
Marvel rivals and announcement.
What is this hell that I fucking got myself caught into?
We're always three games.
Three games and then everything goes downhill.
Three games and then we all suck.
Oh yeah.
The Curse of Ra works at a specific time.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, just one.
This curse to be broken.
I'm gonna give it to our Groot.
I have to give it to her tank.
They take way too much damage.
I would give it to DPS but...
Our tanks just...
Our tanks are fucking sponges.
They're actual sponge.
They're doing it again.
No, no, not again!
I need to just...
I just need to like not...
I just need to like not even ult when I see that combo.
I just go GG's.
And just die.
It was like reflex for me too.
I'm sorry, Dr. Strange.
You're not gonna live.
Oh my god, it was literally like...
Oh no, no, no, no, no.
Groot, Groot, please.
You're not okay, Groot.
Oh, we broke it.
Oh my god.
I'm watching you soar.
Fly, you beautiful angel.
Fly, you beautiful...
Okay.
Nice.
Okay, he has ult.
Oh, when he...
Oh my god, this is why...
This is why I won't get ult.
Because now people are doing ult combos now.
They're figuring out ult combos, guys.
Fucking ult combos.
They're figuring it out.
Guys.
Ult combos, guys.
I'm meta.
Like, I knew it was...
But you're still alive.
You're still alive.
So we're gonna...
We're gonna figure this out together.
Yeah.
If I live...
Oh my god, he's gonna eat.
Oh my god, he ate.
Oh, he captured it though.
No, Jeff!
Okay, I got him though.
Beat him, beat him up!
Oh, he's fucking dead.
Oh, I'm dead!
What?
Hey guys.
That'd be cool.
Let's...
Oh, we're not gonna...
Oh my god.
We're back in the circus.
We're actually back in the circus.
How?
How did we get back?
We left.
We left and now we're back.
How?
We're back.
We're back in the circus.
Oh my god.
I can't.
I fucking can't.
Oh my god.
If I get back to diamond, we're stopping there.
We're stopping there.
Oh my god.
I can't believe it.
Wait.
No, it's...
No, we'll find a better song.
Guys.
We're gonna find...
No, we're not doing...
We're gonna find a better sound...
song at it.
Okay.
Don't worry.
I found a good song.
Here we go.
No, wait.
That's copyrighted.
Copyright free.
Wait, that's so scary.
That's a scary...
Oh, wait.
Is this?
No.
I'm trying to...
No!
Okay.
Alright, guys.
When you get in the circus, you don't get to play Luna anymore.
You can't play Luna anymore when you're in the circus.
When you're in the circus.
Sad music.
We're just gonna go straight on.
She can have Luna.
I'll play Mantis.
It's okay, guys.
Give me a sec.
I know you want the clown nose, but I have to make a small edit.
I have to make a small edit of how I feel in the inside.
Oh, no.
I can't.
I can't make my small edit yet.
Bum bum.
Play whatever you feel like playing.
I am a guardian against evil.
30 seconds before you attack.
Get ready.
Whoa.
What year is it where you come from?
Not years anywhere.
All that matters is now.
Right.
Gotta be present.
The battle starts in 5...
4...
3...
2...
1!
You're mine!
I'm not Luna.
I need to remember that.
Feelin' power!
That's fine.
You feelin' power!
Go!
Feel so strong!
No.
No!
Goodbye.
Get one back.
Oh my god, we capped it though.
We capped it.
Oh my god.
You got this.
You're gonna feel so strong.
But what if...
What if I don't wanna feel spider-tapped?
What if I don't wanna feel like spi- Oh my god.
The muse- The old stuff.
Feelin'- Feel strong.
Feel so fucking strong.
Goodbye.
Feel strong!
The moon- If anything happens to you, it's your- You're bad.
Where are they?
Go!
Beat him up!
Fucking you're so strong!
Okay, there you go.
Huge.
I told you I'm not one trick anymore.
I'm not a one trick no more, guys.
I told you.
I told you I can do it!
I can do it!
I can play other characters!
Be empowered!
Be inspired!
Go do your thing!
Keep being strong!
Alright.
Go, do your thing again!
Keep doing your thing!
You also!
Alright, that's fine.
Woah!
That's not fine.
Hey, we can all heal this now.
Goodbye, all of you.
Be empowered!
That's right!
I'm not a Luna main!
I'm not a Luna one trick!
I can play other characters!
The music is getting a bit upbeat.
Okay.
Let me adjust.
Look, if we...
We need to do this.
If we wanna...
Okay.
Save as.
Alright, I'll put on my clown nose.
Next game.
I'll put it on next game.
I told you I can play other characters now.
I told you.
I told you I know how to play other healers now.
It only took me one day.
It only took me one fucking day.
Are we close?
I'm back in the circus.
What do you think?
I had optimism.
I felt like I was a god.
I get to ban other characters.
And then we're back here.
In the pits.
Be inspired.
Woah.
Be inspired again.
You too.
Woah.
Feel strong again?
You know you want to.
Go do your thing.
You too.
Keep punching.
It's so funny.
Just keep punching.
You too.
Do your thing.
Oh shit.
Okay, I messed that up though.
I definitely messed that up.
That's fine.
Doctor Strange, do your thing.
I made you strong.
Strong.
This her projectile is so fucking weird though, not gonna lie.
That's fine.
You gotta feel strong too.
Oh no.
No!
You can eat me?
No.
No, I didn't know.
I didn't know you can eat.
I thought it was just like Luna.
That's so fucked.
You can eat.
Now I know.
I never realized.
I never realized you can get bored when you ult as Mantis.
Feel strong.
That's fine.
Feel so strong.
You wanna punch somebody?
Go in there.
Punch for your heart's desires.
He has eye.
He has gonna eye after this.
Get out.
That's fine.
You know what?
Maybe I should just play Mantis.
Fuck this.
You know what?
I'm gonna start playing other characters.
I'm scared now.
I'm scared.
There
it is!
Let's go!
I feel so inspired!
Dude!
Alright.
They still have...
Guys, I fucked up.
No!
I can't!
Every fucking time!
I'll never leave this fucking map.
I'll never leave.
He'll always get me.
He'll always find a way.
I like reflex try to heal them by shooting.
It's like buy reflex too.
Cause I feel like I'm playing Luna.
And I've been playing Luna for a while now.
I feel inspired.
There you go.
Oh shit!
No!
I almost killed him!
Oh my god!
That's fine.
So much Luna.
But I'm learning how to play.
I'm learning how to play Mantis.
Be inspired.
You be inspired too.
I can't heal you over there.
But you're gonna be so inspired.
Go punch!
Go fucking punch!
You go punch too!
Oh he's dead.
Go do your thing!
Go!
That's fucking right.
You made me so angry.
Oh that's fucking right!
That's fucking right!
If I can go up to you.
I'm kidding.
That's fucking right.
Hope you remember who I am.
Go do your thing.
Oh my god.
I'm so sorry.
I did it.
I'm so-
My game crashed!
No!
Alright, that's how we recall it.
My game actually crashed!
I've never had a- Oh my god and we won too!
We're gonna win!
I don't think I can get back in time.
I don't think so.
I think the game ended.
That's so cruel!
That's actually so cruel!
Can I get back in?
Reconnect!
Oh my god!
Life's not fair!
I'm coming back team!
Holy shit!
I died and everything went to hell!
Could be inspired.
Oh my god.
That was actually fucked.
That was so fucked.
I can't believe that actually happened though.
Oh my god I can't- Oh shit!
That's right.
Be inspired.
I'm gonna fucking make sure you keep punching.
Keep punching!
Just keep punching!
No, I'm gonna keep punching too!
No, no, no get away from me!
Oh he ate his own teammate!
That's so fucked!
Oh my god!
Where is he?
I can't believe he did the eye and I crashed!
I can't believe his Jeff ate him!
Oh my god the Jeff fucking ate his eye!
Oh my god.
Okay.
Alright.
It's fine.
We were fine.
Everything was okay.
Everything was okay at the end.
Everything was okay in the end.
We're fine.
Oh my god.
That could have been bad.
But it wasn't.
And that's all that matters.
No guys, we didn't fully crash.
It's still possible to at least get back to Diamond.
But before I do...
Wait, am I still in the group?
Oh I'm not.
Wait.
I'm not.
I crashed and got kicked out of the group.
Lol.
I'm a two... No, I can play cloak and that.
Wait, okay.
Before... That's good.
That gives me time.
That gives me time to set up.
Okay, give me a sec.
Alright.
That gives me time, chat.
That gives me time to do what I wanted to do.
Alright.
Oh, it's not centered.
Sorry.
Now it's a sad clown nose.
There we go.
Now we're the sad clown.
We're a sad clown.
We're gonna queue one up.
We're sad clowning.
Oh my god.
At least I'll have...
At least I'll have like...
My ping again.
It's fine.
I can mantis now.
Oh wait.
Also...
To fit the theme.
We gotta fit the theme.
Let's see.
Wait.
I can't do it.
This is...
Sad clown.
No, SK!
SK!
We got kicked out of the group and we didn't realize...
We didn't realize we're out of the group.
It's like trolls.
I lost my...
I lost my happy...
My happy...
Cause my...
My grandma died when I played Marvel.
Oh wait, that's fucked up.
No, I shouldn't say that.
I shouldn't say that.
Be inspired.
Sad hog.
Who would help me?
Who?
Who would fucking help me?
Who would help me?
Who would help me in these sad times?
No!
Because Marvel Rivals killed my grandma.
I swear if A2938 is Calvin, I swear to God.
That's a Calvin username.
That's an aimbot Calvin username right there.
Because Marvel Rivals killed my grandma.
What the fuck?
Wait.
What's going on?
Wait, what the fuck?
Wait, what?
What's going on with the ping?
Yeah, everybody's lagging.
Wait, this is everybody.
But we don't have the point!
Yeah, they are.
That's crazy.
Are we getting DDOSed?
We don't even have the point!
This is the clown suit.
This is why.
Oh my God, they're actually DDOSing.
They're DDOSing the servers?
They can't move!
This is not fair.
He can actually move!
This guy actually can move.
Look!
He can actually play the fucking game!
I don't fucking know.
Who's fucking DDOSing?
Oh my God!
I knew it.
I told you.
Spider people, you can't trust them.
I fucking told you guys.
You guys didn't believe me.
J.
Jemison was right.
I watched his podcast.
He was right.
I fucking knew it.
Never trust a spider person.
I fucking told you guys.
I fucking told you guys to never trust a spider person.
Yeah, ping's back to normal.
That's so fucked.
For a rank up?
Maybe J.
J.
has a point.
This might be where we die.
Oh wait, nope.
Unless...
No!
Me!
Oh my God.
I mean...
We're undefeatable.
Oh my God.
Jump, we gotta jump.
Alright, be inspired.
I'm back.
I hear him.
Yeah.
Oh, I needed... I didn't sleep in time.
Oh no, he's gonna get the point back.
And he's gonna DDOS.
I thought it was my internet.
Alright, let's see.
The ping goes up.
Let's see.
Oh, ping is still fine.
Ping is still fine.
So far.
No, no.
Oh, thank God.
I'm sorry.
Oh fuck.
No!
He's gonna play legit.
Yeah, I think so too.
And then he's like, oh, I don't need a DDOS.
And then so he's playing legit now.
But like, they had such a huge ult advantage that like...
It like fucked over our economy.
Alright, do your thing!
Alright, goodbye.
Oh, you're lagged.
Alright.
Try.
For
real.
I don't think we can kill him.
Alright.
Kill him!
How is he still alive?!
Okay.
No!
Holy fucker!
Actual fucker!
Oh my God!
Oh my God, you actually...
He almost got me!
He actually...
Aww, don't talk too much shit, they're gonna do it.
Oh my God.
That's just crazy, I don't know how he was careful.
That's a different level of retarded though.
That was so scary.
That was so fucking scary.
Did I just buy way too much Luna?
Like, I can't.
I feel like I'm terrible on DDOS now.
It's alright, it's alright.
I almost have a...
Aww.
I almost have my ult too.
Alright.
It'll be fine, it'll be fine.
It'll be so fine, I feel so fine.
Yippee!
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo!
Oh, he's swinging his hammer, he's ready.
He feels so inspired.
Okay.
Okay, but you don't understand, we got DDOS.
Oh, whoops.
That's a little awkward.
We're a little stupid there.
Okay.
He's inspired.
Kill him, kill him, kill him, kill him!
Just kill him!
Kill him, kill him, kill him!
He's so low!
Oh, we used both support ults, so that's bad.
That's so bad.
We accidentally used both support ults.
I didn't think he was going to.
Oh,
what?
No!
I should've slept!
I should've slept, I forgot to sleep!
I forgot to sleep!
I need to remember my shift.
I was going to use Jetfall.
Goodbye.
No, he didn't.
He did not.
We got somebody else.
Yeah, I'm going to go up at the bottom.
Alright, hello time!
Whoa!
You can do that!
Oh,
I thought...
Guys, we need you!
Oh, shit!
Dude, Jesus fucking Christ.
Please, we need to kill something.
Please!
Kill something!
Oh my god, they got so much from that!
Bro, we need to just pick targets, bro.
Shooting at different people, that's why we're not...
That's why you guys aren't killing me.
That's it.
It's party time!
No!
Oh my god!
Alright, no!
That sucked.
I don't know if he'll live, but...
No,
I almost had it!
I almost won!
I literally won!
No!
I was dressed so hard to keep Gem up!
I just got it!
And we didn't get DDoSed.
We got DDoSed there.
The DDoS actually griefed us.
Yeah, they DDoSed us.
That's actually crazy.
I almost had more healing than the Luna?
That's fucking... okay.
That's sad.
That's...
That's so sad.
How did I almost get more healing than the Luna?
Alright, I'm gonna request a join.
Wait, has she said anything?
Oh.
Okay.
Alright.
Did you at least win?
I...
No.
I got DDoSed.
Hold on!
Our entire team got DDoSed for them to win.
What are these games?
I'm gonna use the bathroom.
Ports, let's fucking go.
It's three support hours.
We're going back to GOATS.
I believe in GOATS.
Oh, we're back to hell.
Don't want to let me off this well, guys.
Tomorrow...
It will be Marble Rivals.
End announcement.
This is what you wanted.
You cursed me to suffer like this.
How
did I die so fast?
Okay, I need to look.
What did he do?
He didn't...
Okay, okay.
Alright, I'm locked in.
I'm going back in.
I'm going back in, guys.
We're going back in.
There we go.
Locked in now again.
Random bullshit.
I fucking love random bullshit.
Wowee, there it is.
There's that random bullshit right there.
I should have started lowkey misplaying Mantis because I had such insane DPS.
It's fine.
Random bullshit time.
I'm going DPS too.
I want to DPS now too.
It's my turn.
It's my turn to DPS.
Oh, you got healed.
You got healed.
I healed you.
Oh, he... yeah.
Yeah.
It's fine.
We're fine.
Everything is A-okay.
Everything is okay.
Holy shit!
How did he die?
What the...
Okay, guys.
You guys gotta stop dying so fast, guys.
You guys...
Oh, okay.
Sure, we'll watch.
We're gonna watch.
Is she flying?
I'm not using my ult yet because I know...
Okay, maybe I don't need to use my ult yet.
Oh, okay.
I thought he'd live that.
But that's okay, guys.
That's fine.
We all... Oh, he used the I anyway.
So that's great.
That's great to know.
I was saving it up just for that.
Wait, what did they do?
Door, please.
Door, please!
Goodbye.
Hey, we did it!
We did it!
He did get all of us!
That's fine.
He didn't get all of us, so we're fine.
You know what?
I'm feeling a little wild next game.
You know what, guys?
Next game...
I'm gonna play Cloak and Dagger.
That's right.
I'm gonna show you guys I'm not a one trick anymore.
That's fucking right.
I'm fucking gonna do it.
Oh, I'm gonna go fucking wild.
I'm showing my character art.
Is that crazy?
Is that fucking wild?
It's almost like...
Oh my god.
Is that crazy?
If I'm gonna be at the circus, I'm gonna be the whole fucking circus.
I'm watching.
I might as well...
I might as well be the entire fucking circus.
Let's go!
Let's fucking fight!
Okay, he's...
I've been through so much.
I swear...
That's fucking right.
You gotta fucking clown on.
Get fucking clowned on.
Guys, if we can...
If we can...
If we can break this...
Break this streak...
Things will be okay.
I'm playing so well.
Loki, you're playing so well.
It's not you.
Just break the cycle.
Just...
Break the cycle.
You can do it, Loki.
You can fucking do it.
Don't let them control you.
Don't let them do this to you.
I think I got a porta.
I need a porta.
What are you gonna do?
Oh, there they are.
Oh, they fucked up the porta.
They fucked up the porta.
Like, what's that?
Oh, there's the porta.
Oh, they...
Okay, you could've...
I don't know.
Like, looked at me?
Okay,
guys.
It's fine.
No way!
Get away!
Alright.
Goodbye.
Oh, goodbye.
No.
It's okay.
I don't know how...
How...
Where do I go?
Oh, he's so low!
Oh, I thought he was gonna run to the left.
Kill him.
We don't need the Pope anymore.
But like, in the game, in game, in game, guys.
In game, in game.
In game.
I'm not opening that can of worms.
That was an accident.
I meant in game.
In Marble Rivals.
Woah.
But what if I don't want to go against the world?
Are we stopping them, guys?
Are we?
Oh.
I don't know, guys.
Guys, are we stopping them?
I can't tell.
Guys, I...
Bro.
Bro, I don't think that's a good...
Bro, get off the turret.
Oh, I froze her though.
Where am I?
No.
No, not the door.
No, I got stored!
Oh no.
Guys.
Beat me.
We can't stay together.
I got rid of the Ankh.
I'm gonna put down our tank now.
Oh, guys.
Guys, we gotta push up, guys.
Guys, all I'm saying is we really gotta push up.
Guys, there's a lot of free space.
Yes.
We gotta push up, guys.
That's a lot of free space we're giving them, guys.
Guys, if we push up just a little bit, guys.
Alright.
I guess I'm ready to put on the show.
Goodbye.
Guys, we gotta go.
We gotta touch the cart.
Guys.
Guys, please.
Please.
Please, just hit me one time.
Guys.
Oh, thank god he copied Luna.
Okay.
That's fine.
Whoa, gotta stay away from that guy.
Oh no.
No.
No!
Why is it me?
Stop.
Please.
I don't deserve this.
Oh my god.
Legitimately.
I don't deserve it.
I don't deserve the hate crime that Jeff did to me.
Oh my god.
The curse.
The curse hits at a specific time.
That fucking shark.
That motherfucking shark.
Oh, I'm not a one trick.
I'll show you.
I'll fucking show you all.
Okay, we can't.
We actually need Luna though.
We actually...
I can't.
We actually need Luna.
How did it get this bad?
The Gatsby curse.
We should've...
I'm gonna put on our tank.
I think our tank really needs it more.
Like, I legitimately think that...
Yeah.
Our tank...
Cannot sustain.
I would love to, but...
Legitimately, we need it on a tank.
Okay.
I'm so scared of getting...
Hit me once.
Hit me once, please.
Please heal me once.
That's all you need.
Okay.
I'm trying.
Reload.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, they dropped down.
I'm sorry.
Oh my god.
No!
Use all the random bullshit you can find.
Oh no.
Yes!
Oh my god.
I think I...
I think I clutched that.
I legitimately clutched that so hard.
Oh my god.
I clutched it so hard.
Thank god.
I had to work so hard for that.
I had to work so hard.
I need something sadder.
I need sadder music, guys.
I can't.
I'm not sad enough.
I need sadder music.
Yeah, yeah.
Here we go.
This is how I feel inside.
Boom.
Oh my god, I've got fucked over there.
He just walked up.
They can do that?
He just walked up!
Don't worry, I'm here.
I'm here.
I'm coming over.
Oh, they went off point.
Let's go.
HAHAHAHA YAY
They went off point.
This is... I need something.
I need something sadder.
I need something even sadder.
Yay, I need something even sadder.
No, that's happy.
Wait, what the fuck?
That's not sad.
Sad music.
Very emotional.
Oh, that's...
I like that.
I feel it.
It's too quiet?
Don't worry.
It's a sad flute.
It's a very sad flute.
You go there, flute man.
Say my emotions for me, flute man.
Tell the world how I feel.
I feel like...
I'm like staring out.
I'm telling you how Marvel Rivals killed my grandma.
This is a very emotional for me.
I'm just...
I'll show you how it's... I'll show you how I'm not a one trick.
That's right.
It's time.
Okay, I need something more inspirational.
All right, here.
It's time.
No, I'm a three trick now.
Also, if we lose this, I'm swapping to Luna.
Bom bom bom bom.
Guys, it's okay.
Tomorrow, it's sure for... it's just sure for duo tomorrow.
Things will be okay.
Guys, I need you guys to peek me.
You guys can help me.
Bom bom.
Right on.
Bom, bom.
Bom bom.
Bom.
No, no, no.
No!
I couldn't get out!
Fuck!
Oh my god.
It's fine.
You don't need me there.
You don't need me.
Oh, fuck.
Okay, you might need me now.
Bom.
Bom bom badowm badowm.
Badum
Bum bum badum badadum Bum bum Bum Bum bum badum Bum bum Bum bum Bum
Bum bum Bum bum bum Badum
I'm not a one trick!
Bum ba dum bum ba dum...
I told you.
I told you I can play other support.
I fucking told you.
I learned.
I learned other support.
I told you.
I told you I know how to play other supports, guys.
I fucking told you.
Wow, that hurt.
That's fine.
Okay, no, I'm not playing Loki.
I don't like Loki.
I don't like playing Loki anymore.
He's like really situational.
He's doing it his way!
That's right, that's right.
That's fucking right.
This is it.
I'm showing my chat that I'm no longer a one-trick.
That I have variety.
I'm no longer a one-trick.
I can play other characters.
I can do other things now.
I'm a three-trick now.
I can play different support, determine with the situation.
This would be key.
But Luna is like my auto-pick.
She is my... she's my first pick.
I am a three-trick now.
A three-trick pony.
Okay, nice.
I was worried that... alright.
Character development and also she looks great.
Whoa, what do we do?
Okay, the turrets gone guys.
I'm like a little worried with what we're supposed to do here.
I made it so you can fight in there!
That's looking right.
There we go.
There we go!
I told you.
I told you I could fucking do it.
None of you... you guys didn't believe me.
You guys thought I was throwing!
I told you I can... I can play Cloak and Dagger now.
I fucking told you!
If we win this, I'm done for the day.
I'm back to Diamond.
I will be back to Diamond.
For the next game.
And then I call it.
But if no Diamond, I continue my... my circus.
And then tomorrow is another day.
Tomorrow.
All right.
We call for comms.
Okay, wait.
No, that's not what I wanted.
I call escape.
It's time.
Hello?
I'm calling for the comms.
We are gonna win.
The Doki Bird voice, I haven't heard in so long.
I'm calling for the comms.
All right, all right.
Mordred was so sad early when he was playing Mantis, because y'all would ult at the same time every time.
Yeah, yeah, like we both had the same idea!
We had the same idea.
But there was no saving for this team.
There was no saving though at that point.
I think... I think... I think at that time the team was GG's.
It was cooked.
It was Jover.
It's okay.
We got to win this.
So we can both go to sleep.
And then we go again tomorrow.
We go again tomorrow.
I'm down.
Let's go!
I'm streaming at 630.
I'm playing with them.
Oh, I think I'm playing with Brian late night.
If you want to come.
Wait, does he have rank?
No.
He's gonna be really bad.
Okay, I guess we don't go.
We'll probably have a few hours before he gets on.
Okay, okay.
No, I'm playing at 630.
It's like super late.
Because that's my PSC.
Oh, that is super late.
Yeah, probably no time.
But the day after.
That guy did not get off his turret.
I don't know what to do with him.
Oh.
I'm not looking good.
Um.
This is salvageable.
I'll touch.
Okay, I'm out.
Um.
He dead.
You have one tank?
Oh, you do.
And they have two.
That makes more sense.
It's okay, tanks are overrated.
That's true.
Peek me so I can give you an orb.
I got you, you have an orb now.
Thank you.
This guy.
You're so healthy.
You're so healthy right now.
I'm extremely healthy.
You're so healthy, but we lost our other support.
I exercise every day.
You're so healthy still.
Oh.
You're just non-stop getting healed.
I'm just healing the Hella.
You're the best.
Because all she does is feed.
You're so very healthy.
The Hella is still feeding.
See, it's fine.
It's fine.
I got logged.
Where did you shoot me from?
What?
I'm making a comeback.
Okay, I'm coming back.
Hanzo moment.
We are undefeatable!
Uh oh, he never misses.
And they're undefeatable.
How do you beat that?
This Hawkeye is really good.
Oh, that's the guy that I said no to stacking with.
Sorry, guy.
Oh.
At the end of the game, he was like, anyone want to stack?
And then all of us said no.
Oh.
We should stack with him.
I'm making a comeback.
He's just having a lucky first round.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I don't know.
He's killing a lot of people.
That is true.
Oh.
He don't have an orb.
Yeah, lucky first round health pack.
Wait, I thought there was one there.
Oh, crap.
Oh, he's not okay.
Uh oh.
Our team is not okay right now.
Yeah, this is not looking good.
Not looking very inspiring.
I'm almost here with my ultimate ability.
I will inspire.
I'll inspire our team with a motivational speech.
Hang on.
We got this, guys.
Are you inspired?
I don't think that inspires anybody.
Fire, please.
Oh, by the way, you never had an orb, so you might die.
Oh, unless...
Oh my goodness.
You're fine.
You're not fine.
I'm so fine.
Everything's fine.
Everything's awesome and cool when you're part of a team.
They're gonna Magneto, I think.
Yeah, they do.
There it is.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, you got...
He freaking buckied me out of my dash.
Yeah.
Oh.
I'm not feeling inspired anymore.
I don't know.
You need another motivational speech?
I don't think...
I'm not...
Oh.
One last game and going to sleep was too good to be true anyways.
It was...
Oh.
There's much more suffering to be had.
Who gave him again?
Who was it?
Eski, I don't...
I don't think we're gonna win this one.
Nah, nah, nah.
We got this.
I don't think...
I don't see a world in which we lose this.
Really, I see multiple worlds.
I think us...
winning this...
is like...
the 0.1% chance.
I like how he's like...
do you tank?
And then they swap to Adam.
Like...
Oh, there we go.
You're not ready for the SK Luna snow.
Oh my god.
Although I was the only DPS doing anything.
So we'll see how this goes.
Yeah, that's...
Yeah.
I feel like...
Who do we avoid?
I don't even know.
Because Nyan Cat Balling was popping off the last couple rounds.
Maybe...
It's their round.
It's his round.
I think...
I think our team's just overall better.
Maybe better at tanks.
Yeah.
This is what coms did.
We started coms and then we just...
Everything went downhill.
Everything's already been downhill.
Everything went downhill with coms.
Alright, here we go.
Awesome time.
I'm gonna start inspiring.
Inspire!
This portal just brought us somewhere that we can walk.
People are dead.
I don't feel very inspired.
Me neither.
Especially after the play I just watched our Moon Knight make.
Yeah, why did he drop down?
I don't know.
That definitely did not inspire me.
He did not have to drop down there.
Oh dear.
Oh.
Whoa.
It's okay.
Now's our time.
Is it though?
Yeah, we're gonna cab this fight.
I'm feeling it.
Okay, me too.
I am ready to put on a show!
They're putting on a show.
But don't worry, I'm icing up.
Alright.
I'm trying to inspire people too.
I'm putting on a show.
I got headshot.
Oh, he headshot someone else too.
I am ready to put on a show!
Oh, that's cool.
Um.
You know...
I think...
Maybe next game's our game.
Maybe it's next game.
It's gotta be this one.
No, I don't think it's this one.
I don't think it's this one.
I think you're not in the same game as I am.
I think you have someone's bot open.
I think you have someone's bot open right now.
And you're watching that game and you're not playing this lobby.
I don't know who I inspired, but I inspired somebody.
We're undefeatable.
Oh, nice.
Not nice.
I didn't even see the Magneto!
This is...
One of the games of all time.
For sure.
Really?
We've had a lot of them.
And I think all of them were with me.
At least...
Okay, that's probably for sure, though.
I'm on the flank.
Alright, that didn't work.
The moon haunts you.
Wait, our Bucky's going off.
No!
There's a fucking Doctor Strange behind us!
Oh, frick.
This might have been my fault.
No, I don't think.
If we got that point, we were just...
Even if we won.
We were just delaying it.
I was sacrificing...
I was saving us.
From three more minutes of disappointment.
Exactly.
From a longer game.
You saved us.
From more pain.
Honestly.
I am ready to put on a show.
We just won our next two games!
Yeah.
That'd be easy.
I believe.
Just two games.
Right?
Just two.
Yeah.
How much did you lose for that one?
23.
Okay, it could be worse.
It could be worse, you're right.
This one...
It could be worse.
Yeah.
At least they can't ban Psylocke.
That's true.
You know, we just...
I'm feeling good about this one.
Yeah, me too.
All we need to do is get out of plat.
And then...
Get decent hours.
Games should be great.
Yeah.
Oh, but you're not gonna be playing, so...
I think Surefour said he's down.
He's down to play.
But I don't know when he's gonna stop.
Oh.
I don't know when he's gonna stop.
That's the problem.
You can just leave him.
Oh hey, they have the Iron and the Nyan Cat person.
Oh.
You're really different.
Oh, I stole Psylocke from a lesbian.
That's okay.
What a hero pool.
Psylocke and Jeff.
What a fucking hero pool.
Yeah.
I set the Jeff swap.
I didn't think they would play, you know...
Another DPS.
I'm not a fucking gamer.
This will be fine.
This is a rematch of this map again.
Why did they do this to us?
Why can't we have a different map?
Oh no.
Why?
Why did they do this?
It's alright.
This time.
This time it'll be different.
I gave you an orb.
But you might lose it if our tanks are...
Oh.
Nice.
You might lose it if the tanks feel a little bit feedy.
He's Groot.
Okay, Groot.
Gotta chill a little, man.
My dude.
Ouch.
Chill a little, dude.
Gotta chill just a little bit.
Alright, you're losing your orb privileges.
These tanks are doing too much fucking...
Okay, okay.
They're feeding a little too much.
You're gonna be losing your orb privileges now.
Oh my god, they're both support ults.
Oh, the Punisher's so low.
The Punisher's one.
He's Groot.
The Groot's one, too!
The Groot's one!
Eliminated.
Okay,
nice.
I have ult.
I have mine, too.
It will be awesome time next fight.
Nice.
Good fight.
I was using that.
Okay.
I think they have Groot ult.
They haven't used it yet.
Oh, they're Groot.
Oh!
Alright.
Time to dance!
Everyone here is just...
Oh, okay.
I don't even know how you died there.
I went boom, boom.
Where did your HP go?
It was my Judge Dre and Executioner.
Okay.
It's fine.
We held it.
For now.
For now, Judge.
Got you.
Thank you.
That's a good trick, huh?
Oh.
No!
Lesbians!
They're pressing all their buttons.
No!
Oh, frick.
I got hit by a stray.
We had no defense ult.
Jeff, why are you a shark?
Why?
Oh, Jeff.
How many did Jeff get?
Jeff, how many?
Jeff died!
I don't think he got anybody!
Did he even get anyone?
I don't think he did.
Jeff, how do you not get anybody?
Alright, this time for sure.
Alright, I'll give you back your orb.
You have your privilege again.
Yay!
I'm feeling privileged.
I'm fighting Captain America.
Alright, Penny is feeding, so you're getting all the heals right now.
That's perfect.
So you should live.
Um...
You should...
Aw, yay.
Aw.
I had a feeling when I saw zero kills on the feed.
I had a feeling.
I am dancing.
I have forced the undefeatable ult.
Oh no.
Oh.
Oh, where am I?
Oh no.
Again?
Oh, you forced the mantis ult.
Okay.
Okay, I was like, what?
Too many.
Ow.
Jeff, please.
You don't need to be a shark no more.
Please.
You can be a mantis.
It's just like a shark.
It's the shark of the bug world.
This is the shark of the bug world.
He's so low.
Bam.
Oh my god, grid's low too.
Let's go.
Okay, Jeff, you did not have to...
Okay, that's fine, Jeff.
You just ulted in a 6v4.
Did you get anyone?
I don't know.
But the mantis is low.
What did he get?
Jeff did not need to do that.
That's all I'm saying.
I agree.
Alright, I have one...
I have my defensive ult against all their...
against one of their five aggression ults.
So we'll see how it goes.
Easy.
Captain America's frozen.
Captain America's one.
Assemble.
Alright, here we go.
It's the grand finale.
That guy threw a fish at nothing.
Yep, I saw that.
Alright, Captain America's gonna ult here.
Oh, he's not?
Okay.
That's fine.
That's fine if he doesn't want to.
Oh my god.
Nevermind, it's dance time for them.
Captain America's ult!
He's low!
Got you.
Okay, that's one fight left.
I'm not gonna get...
I'm not gonna get my ult in time for it.
Despite the amount of feeding they're doing.
I'm doing it.
Nice.
Oh!
I did not got you, apparently.
We are chillin'.
We are so chillin'.
Okay, I'm just gonna wait here.
Nice!
Alright, we just gotta push all the way there.
It can't be that bad, right?
It can't be that bad!
We can push it all the way there!
Yippee!
No, we actually can't.
Wait, things are looking much better than I initially thought.
Wait, did we lose a game?
Oh, we lost a game on this map.
That's why it feels so bad.
Everything's a blur.
They all blur together.
There's so many games.
We play so many.
You know, we're 15 and 13 right now.
Getting the plat was so easy.
We're 13 and what?
We're 15 and 13.
Oh my god.
That hurts.
We're so close.
Getting the plat took me 6 hours.
And then I'm stuck in this hellhole.
It took me 6 hours in like a day and a half.
And now we're still plat.
Well, at least you hit diamond.
And we're gonna hit it again.
Oh.
It'll be different.
That's lit.
Awesome time.
Super duper lit.
I believe there's an enemy directly above me.
You have orb so you're fine for now.
Yes, yes.
Our sharko died.
That means I can heal you more.
I've eliminated the enemy.
Don't worry, you have unlimited heals.
Our strange is feeding.
You have so much heals.
Oh, okay.
Okay, like I still...
Okay.
I got slapped by a mantis.
Yeah.
The heals are not that strong.
Despite what you want to believe.
Oh.
We're strange.
Oh no, we're strange.
Oh no.
Oh my god.
Oh no, our shark died.
But I baited their ult out.
I baited their dancing.
Oh my god, Namor, why did you sub in the fucking...
That's good, that means I'll get to ult soon.
They used Groot ult too.
That's great.
That's great, that's great, they used everything.
Okay, I have a plan for this fight.
I don't think he plays DPS.
I don't think Namor knows what he's doing.
Uh oh.
Cause like, I literally saw him fucking Namor ult a dance ult that was there already like a minute ago.
He has not gotten anything with his Namor ults.
Only TP.
Nice.
Alright, I'm gonna wait until that's gone.
Okay, we can go back in.
Nice.
Groot was low.
He will not get the again.
Be alive!
Let's go.
Alright, you get your privilege back.
Yay.
Okay, goodbye Namor.
Bye bye Namor.
Oh, bye bye Dr. Strange.
Yeah, everybody's dying so I'm just gonna leave.
Oh, please.
Please!
Lesbian, please!
Don't stand on the rock!
That's all you've been doing!
Wait, wait, Groot's low, Groot's low.
Nice, we got Groot.
We're getting healed by the tanks that's also taking damage.
That's great, that's great.
We're getting healed by Namor.
I was using that, Dr. Strange.
Oh, fuck.
That's fine, you wanted to bait that, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh no, he's gonna get the again.
Again!
That's fine.
That's not fine, don't worry.
Oh, nice.
See, everything is fine.
Guys, guys, please push the cart.
Please, we just need two!
We just need two people!
Okay, we got two people.
We got it.
That's good, they wasted that!
They didn't know!
They didn't know we got the cart!
They're so stupid!
Oh, thank goodness.
They didn't know!
They thought it was over!
That's really good.
They're so stupid.
That's fucking right.
That's why you'll stay in plat and I'll go back to diamond.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh no.
Oh my bad.
I shouldn't have said that.
I might lose because I said that.
No, no, no.
Everything is awesome.
Okay, everything is fine.
There's like a Moon Knight up top.
What the flip is happening?
He's over there still.
I'm gonna go on Moon Knight.
Double KO!
There's a group right in front of us.
Can we just have?
He's one, he's one.
There's the guy.
I got it.
Where's the Moon?
Alright, we're getting closer.
We have like two fights left.
Did I even touch this?
Yes, you can.
They literally just did.
Oh no.
No!
He's so good.
He fucking solo defeated this whore!
I hope he loses all his coins and he deranks the gold.
Fuck that guy.
I'm gonna stalk through your profile.
Make sure you stay in plat.
Oh, oh.
We're gonna Q snipe him.
I'll make sure.
Every day I'm gonna check your career profile.
So you never get to diamond.
God, I'm 93.
I'm 93.
Okay, this is the one for sure.
I'm gonna fucking avoid you too.
Oh, I couldn't.
You're so lucky.
So I could farm you for this.
Surely we can't lose another rank up game.
I don't know.
We got the Nyan Cat balling guy.
Didn't that person struggle again?
He did earlier, but...
I have a good feeling.
Yeah?
I'm a little worried.
I'm feeling good about this.
No, no, no.
I'm a little worried.
No, there's nothing to worry about.
If we lose this one, we can just keep Q'ing.
Yeah, but...
Would it be easier if we avoid him?
Oh, should we avoid him?
I don't know.
Was he carrying last game?
I don't remember.
Yeah, so he was not then if you don't remember.
He was pretty good on Bucky.
He was getting hooks on our group.
Oh, was he?
Was it Bucky?
Yeah, he was the Bucky.
Okay, okay.
Because I know as Punisher, he was struggling a little.
Last map.
But we had him for a few games earlier on Punisher and we won those.
Oh, okay.
I think he's just unlucky.
If you're watching, because I know they're watching you.
If you're watching this, Nyan Cat, I don't take it back.
Marvel Rivals is changing you.
First impressions matter.
And that was not a good first impression.
Don't meet your heroes.
Even if your hero is not the one that you're watching.
There's so much damage.
Wait, I'll give you the orb.
You have the orb.
Thank you.
You're fine.
I'm healing somebody that's getting damage right now.
Which is the tank.
I'm healing them still, so you're fine.
Awesome.
You're still getting the heals because he's still getting damage.
Where's that Iron Man?
That guy's dead as hell.
You're still getting heals.
Thank you.
They're putting on a show.
Oh man, having two tanks must be really nice.
To be able to do that.
Penny Parker's one.
Yeah, got her.
I'm healing.
Oh my god!
How much damage did you take?
Okay.
Okay, I'm putting a show too now.
It's my turn.
Kill him.
Nice.
Nice show.
I'm DPSing.
Excellent performance.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Thank you.
Alright, you're fine.
Oh my god.
You're so healthy.
I'm very healthy.
You know what?
Today before stream, I exercised.
Oh, you're so healthy!
Oh, thank you.
It's the first time in like a year.
You know what I did?
Yeah.
I played Marvel Rivals.
I already have 60 hours on this game.
I was there since closed alpha.
I was...
They added rank and it was over for me.
I was like, eh.
I'm not... I don't feel it.
I'm not feeling it that much.
And then they added rank and now I'm like, oh.
Now you're really addicted.
There it is.
That's what I was looking for.
Right there.
Yeah, baby.
That was the fix I needed.
Wait, is he...
What in the world?
He's putting a show.
Oh, wow.
You still have the orb, so you don't have to worry about dying yet.
You're my goat.
You don't have to worry about dying yet.
I'm still healing.
You don't have to worry about dying.
You still don't have to worry about dying.
I'm all up in there.
Get in there, get in there.
Just keep getting in there.
I'm in there like swimwear.
I literally can see you in front of me, but you're not there.
I'm extremely in there.
Okay, I can't heal anymore.
Nobody's taking...
Nobody's getting damaged.
No problem.
Wait, there.
Oh, porno, porno, porno, porno.
They're teleporting.
What?
They're not taking it.
Oh my god, I'm on the back.
Nice.
We can live.
We're fine.
Let's get the Loki.
I'm DPSing.
Nice.
Yay!
You'll save my ass.
We're making it happen.
We're doing it.
No, no, no, you're jinxing it.
No.
You're gonna jinx it.
Please.
We're so close.
In the top 5, I'm just gonna be Diamond 2.
And then when we get Diamond 2, it's gonna be Diamond 1.
And then when I get to Diamond 2, it's gonna be high Diamond 2.
It doesn't stop.
And I'll be Grandmaster.
And then it'll be...
And then we'll never get there.
It's fine.
Nobody's getting damaged though.
That's fucking right.
Get eyed.
What the heck?
Get fucking eyed.
Are you alive?
Yep.
Oh shit, you're still alive?
Thank you.
I didn't even realize you were still alive.
Oh.
Oh fuck.
Okay, I was not alive.
Oh thank god.
Thank goodness.
Oh my god.
Okay, that was a good push.
Now all we have to do is not let them do that to us.
That's it.
And then...
And then we're free for another day.
We're free for another day.
And then tomorrow, I go again.
It'll be fine.
Ryan will only play for a couple hours, so we can...
We can play after.
Yeah.
Wait, I thought he sleeps early.
Yeah, he does.
He's doing like a...
A Twitch bounty board thing.
Oh.
Wait, the Twitch bounty board is Marvel Rivals?
Yeah, he has a Marvel Rivals one.
I need to get one of those.
Oh, I know Scherfer got it.
Scherfer's getting it for tomorrow too.
Oh.
I don't know if he's personally sponsored or if it's a bounty.
Because you know how he said he has a sponsor for Marvel Rivals tomorrow, but I don't know if that's a bounty or an actual sponsor.
That's probably an actual one.
He's a big guy.
Oh.
Marvel Rivals, why aren't you sponsoring me?
If you're watching.
You could probably get it.
I don't know.
I do know.
Message Bogert.
Wait, really?
Why Bogert?
Because Bogert has the Necros connection.
What does that got?
Necros is like the sweet baby summer child.
Necros has like direct line of communication with the developers.
Oh shit.
I threw one of his games.
On accident.
He's their favorite child.
Marvel Rivals, I'm sorry.
It was an accident.
It was 100% an accident.
Oh my god, where's my other support?
I'm coming back.
Oh.
Oh no.
They might do what we did to them.
No, no, surely not.
They might.
That was a very fast first point push.
They got lucky, don't worry.
You're right, you're right.
Oh my god, please.
These Loki clones are so annoying.
That's not fair.
I wanted to perform too.
Jesus Christ.
How much damage?
I'm serious.
Holy shit, did he just block that?
I just saw him block the fucking ult.
With like his own shield.
He flew to the Magneto ult.
Oh that's huge, that's huge, that's huge.
Oh.
Oh, they're unleashing hell.
Bye.
Oh, he killed two.
Alright, goodbye.
No!
Escape!
I think they're pushing it as fast!
Don't worry.
Don't worry about it.
This kitty has two tanks!
We have this poor guy!
Maybe I pull out the Penny Parker.
Is it time?
We have this poor guy that's trying to fight for us.
Hold on, I got this.
Oh my god.
How many hours do you have on Penny Parker?
At least...
Half of one.
Okay.
Don't worry.
I'm not worrying.
Nyan Cat has...
Has died.
And then I have got Magneto'd.
I am a little worried now.
It's almost spider time.
Already?
Yes.
Okay, I almost have...
Oh, they...
We are Venom.
I will...
I'm here to dance.
It's spider time.
They have other stuff too.
That's great.
Now we got to save...
We have zero alts for...
Three minutes defense.
But...
That's fine.
That's so fun.
It's okay, it's okay.
They don't have any either.
That's true.
Don't they have...
Low kill?
And also dancing?
And also...
Okay, they might have those.
But...
It will be okay.
Alright.
We are so chilling.
Oh dear god.
We are not chilling.
When does it end?
No!
Oh crap.
My bad team.
I'm locked now.
I'm a little concerned.
I'm just...
Do you really think he's locked in?
I think he is.
Do you really think so, SK?
Yes, yes.
This is free.
Really?
Really with one tank?
It's okay, three defense is a good comp.
Okay.
I'll close my eyes and believe in you.
Don't worry, don't worry.
We have this in the palm of our hands.
I believe in you, but...
If it doesn't work...
Besides, if we lose, we can just keep queuing.
Okay.
He's locked in.
Oh wait, that's a fucking NPC.
I was like, is that Spider-Man?
But it was an NPC Spider-Man.
That one confuses me every single time.
Yeah, that's the first time I saw her.
Yep.
Oh.
Oh no.
They already got a pick on us.
How come they get to have two tanks?
They should like delete one of them.
We should just like...
Lock that other tank stop.
Oh.
He died to the same guy.
Oh no.
It's literally the same guy.
Oh, tank might die though.
I have to do this.
So...
They're gonna come back with Luna's Snowball.
We have to kill them right now.
Okay.
Nice.
Let's go.
Okay, but our cloak and dagger are up to two for some fucking reason.
I don't know why.
Oh no.
I don't know why he did that.
Why did you do that?
We were gonna win that point.
What if she dies by the Hanzo arrow again?
I...
I got Hanzo'd.
Hella still doesn't have her ult yet by the way.
She's dead.
She died.
She didn't even get a chance to use it.
No!
Oh.
She died before she could use it.
If we had...
Cloak and dagger ult there.
Oh.
Oh my god!
The fat figures are us!
Oh god.
I'm gonna report them.
Oh, I can't report them.
I have to report them after the game.
We got this.
We're throwing my game.
That's it.
Yeah.
Bro is not locked in.
You get reported if you don't lock in.
Never meet your fucking heroes.
Don't worry.
My Penny Parker is fucking nasty.
Alright, I'll give you the orb.
Actually no, I'll give the orb to our other tank.
So if you tank too much then you...
Then like, he gets the heals.
Cause I have a feeling you might be the one that's gonna take the most damage.
Yeah, yeah.
Careful of the Hawkeye.
Oh my god.
This Punisher is stressing me out.
Oh, nice.
Punisher, please.
Don't let them have too much free space though.
How is he dead again?
That's a very good question.
Magneto's one.
No!
He got me out!
God damn it.
He's throwing so hard.
It's okay.
If we all...
I have my ult.
I can probably...
I can touch.
Wait, Cloak used her ult already?
For what?
Did I touch?
I'm touching.
It's spider time.
Oh shit, it's spider time?
I'm dead.
I got Magneto ulted.
Frick.
We just gotta...
I'm coming back.
I'm coming back though.
We have another fight.
Wait.
What?
Okay.
Alright, here we go.
I'm heading over.
I'm heading over to you.
We used way too many ults.
Yes, yes, we did it!
Oh my god.
We did it!
We're free!
Not there!
They docked it!
Oh my god!
We actually did it!
We're free!
Oh my god!
We're actually free!
For today, guys.
Don't think it's over.
For today.
Do I get the points?
My game crashed just then.
I think you do.
Surely you get the points.
There's no way.
No, there's no way.
Do you want me to tell you if you got the points?
I didn't, did I?
I didn't.
I didn't get the points, right?
Toki, you got the points.
We're good.
Thank god!
We're free!
I'm diamond 3!
Oh my god, I'm actually diamond 3!
Shit!
I need to see it.
Don't, I need to see it.
All 500 is diamond 2 now.
I'm gonna fucking...
I'm gonna...
It's gonna be high diamond 2.
It's tomorrow.
I just need a win.
I just need it so that...
Nothing bad...
Oh my god, I can't even fucking see my lobby anymore.
I didn't restart my PC to be able to see my game.
It's okay.
We did it.
Diamond 3.
Diamond 2 is top 500.
We're always just...
We're always just 1.
Just 1 rank away.
Literally, it won't become diamond 1 tomorrow, surely.
Tomorrow.
Guys.
Guys, if...
Surefour and I...
Because he's playing earlier, guys.
If Surefour and I get it before my announcement stream...
Then we keep the announcement stream chat.
But if we don't...
Get ready for more Marvel rivals.
If we don't...
Oh my god, I can't even...
Wait, how do you know I'm diamond?
You're still in my party.
Oh, and it said diamond?
Yep.
Okay, can you take a screenshot of it for me?
Yeah, I got you.
Can you take a screenshot and I'll post it on Twitter live?
Wait, you didn't get to watch the rank though.
I didn't.
I crashed when I had to watch this fucking thing.
This is the best screenshot I can get.
Hold on, hold on.
You're diamond 3, right?
Yep.
Can you take a picture of your diamond 3?
Just the thing.
And then I'll just post that.
The big one?
Yeah, the big one.
And then I'll live vicariously through your picture of the diamond 3.
I'm gonna use that.
Wait, let me take a better centered one.
That's my diamond 3.
Guys, look.
There you go, that one's good.
I'm gonna post that on Twitter right now.
No top 500 today.
But we made it to diamond 3.
Diamond 2 is top 500.
We're going into more.
Spiraling into insanity.
Okay.
We had a good win streak.
We were like 5 and 2 at the end.
Yeah, but you saw what happened.
Oh, wait.
I didn't realize we went on a 6 loss streak before that.
You saw what happened.
You saw.
Yeah.
GGs, SK.
GGs, have a good night.
You too, go sleep.
I have to go back to work after this.
Oh my god, good luck.
GGs.
Okay, bye bye.
Guys, something I thought would take 4-5 hours is now 8 hour mark.
And I have to go back to work.
But...
Thank you everybody for watching.
We go again tomorrow.
If I get top 500...
Before...
The...
My announcement, you're free.
You're freed.
But if we don't...
It's my revivals and announcement.
Have fun, everybody.
We'll see you tomorrow.
As always, everybody.
Stay hydrated.
Posture check.
Get up and move around and get that blood flowing.
And if you stay up for me, head to bed.
Guys, you deserve it.
Honk honk.
I'll see you guys next time.
Bye.
Honk sadly.
Honk.
Honk honk.