Hello, everybody.
Look at my lo-fi in.
Give me a sec.
Now it's actual late night radio.
Hello, everyone.
I hope the music isn't too loud, though.
Let me... I'll turn down a little bit just in case.
Oh, so this is gonna be...
Hello.
Hello, hello, guys.
So for those who are new here, what is Good Night Dragoons?
Good Night Dragoons is just gonna be like...
i want to do this like i'm gonna try and do this like once
every week um maybe like every saturday or friday um and
it's basically like a chill late night session because i
always see a lot of vtubers that do like morning radio shows
or like morning streams and it'll be like like like you know
like like more like oh hey this is the first thing you
listen to in the morning um i'm not a
As we all know, I'm not a morning person at all.
I'm mostly a night person, a night hour.
So I was like, you know what?
I'll be better than a good morning radio show, a good night
radio show.
Because at least I'll be awake.
So usually I'll just do this before I sleep.
Or like, you know, most likely, I don't know.
Sometimes I might be going to bed after the stream.
Maybe not because I do have a lot of work to do.
I've been procrastinating.
I've been like taking a lot more naps than usual And because
of that, I'm so behind on a lot of things I'm so, I'm so
behind I have like so many things to do behind the scenes at
the moment And I'm like, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh But that's
basically it It's basically just like a late night Like I
guess you can call it like a late night podcast Oh my gosh,
speaking of that, okay, this is a little already off topic,
but like, I don't know if you guys, there's been like a new
trend at the moment where, um, also I guess like the stream
is also good for those who are on the other side of the
world, and you guys don't have to wake up super early for me
anymore.
Um, well, for not, not anymore, but like at least once a
week, you guys have this afternoon slash a little bit of the
morning radio show for you guys on the other side of the
world.
Because, like, I usually rarely stream at these type of
hours.
But I want to do this.
Like, I want to try and be, like, super consistent.
I'm not going to do this every day.
Because I don't have the stamina for that.
And, like, I...
I...
Guys, I need time to do other stuff, too.
So...
So, this is just going to be, like, maybe I'll try to do
this, like, every Saturday.
Every Saturday at the same time, like, 9 p.m.
pst unless there's something that's happening on saturday
i'm gonna try to make this like super consistent on having
this every saturday um and i chose saturday because um i see
it as like you know the weekend type deal for people in na
so like because i know like you know nine it's it's one and
yeah was it it's like midnight for the easties over there
it's midnight for the easties over there so like you have an
excuse to stay up for a little bit longer you stay up for a
little bit longer for the stream and um and uh and it's also
like not too early for those on the other side of the world
and not too because i wanted to be like the perfect balance
well it's not perfect but like a good balance between like
you know uh people in na and people on the other side of the
world And I'm very sorry to the EU goons though People in SA
too I'm really sorry for the EU goons though Because like EU
goons ain't fucking faring so well lately
I'm so sorry for the EU goons I'll try my best You guys
still have your 1230 p.m.
streams though So At least you got that It's always so hard
though I always want to have like At least one stream For
some like for people around the world Always just one stream
for you Like at least Not one but like at least one stream
Where Where people can catch my streams You know like just
at least one of them So I try my best to balance As much as
I can Medi Thank you for the super chat Thank you thank you
doki's very own late night talk show the next jimmy foul
thank you for the super chat thank you thank you jesus thank
you the super chat thank you thank you oh my god as someone
in na who's maintained aircraft on the mid-shift this is
great for me i'm so glad you're making this a thing thank
you the super chat thank you thank you oh my god jesus you
have your own very own plane oh yes i forgot doki airlines
you reincarnated into a plane thank you jesus uh crow doki
go to bed thank you I actually okay I think it's just
because I've been like working a lot lately but um I've
actually uh I've been like taking a lot of lap naps lately
so um the past like I think the past like three plus days
I've been like napping more um I think it's because like
I've been working a lot lately so my energy level has been
like a lot lower than usual um and like oh my gosh I during
that collab uh with juna brie and kai uh my brain was so
fried because i just woke up from a nap and i don't know why
i do this i always be like i was like okay dokey uh dokey
what this nap won't you up too badly every time i don't oh
my god every time i don't i need to learn to not nap before
stream because like my brain was like trying to wake up
before like before the stream and then like they were all
like talking a lot in the in the call and I was just like
yeah I felt so awkward before this stream because I was
still waking up so my brain was just like oh because like
they all know each other I didn't I didn't really I was like
the new person in the group um so I was just like oh gosh I
feel awkward oh my gosh my brain to like interact with
people my interest introvert self is like slowly waking up i
felt less clever during the collab i felt like oh my gosh i
was really watching the collab and i was like oh my god if i
was more awake i would have said this instead i would have
been i've been like oh i would have like role played more if
i was more awake i would have been like you know we were
making the jokes about the elderly i would like said why
don't you visit me in the retirement I would have said shit
like that.
I was like, oh my god, Doki, if you were more awake, you
would have been so much more clever in this collab.
You would have said more funny thing.
I was like, Doki, why are you just being reactive?
You would have been so clever if you were more awake, Doki.
Lord Kurosus, thank you for the Akasupa.
Thank you, thank you.
I learned that taking naps are worth this.
middle school i've been exhausted ever since thank you for
the akasupa thank you thank you i let my clippers down what
would they clip from me now i'm glad you guys still like to
collab i always want to try it like i always like want to
like improve myself in content creation so uh i was just
like oh my god i could have said this i could have said that
but yes i do rewatch my vods just to like Be like okay, what
can not like not like critique my my commentary skills.
I'm not gonna critique my commentary, but it's just like
technical wise I rewatch my VODs for technical wise and also
like sometimes I'm like whoa, I'm actually really funny
And then I re like I rewatch my VODs.
I was like wow I'm actually really funny I don't be like I
can't believe I came up with that But like I don't know like
today I will watch the collab I was like oh my god I could
have been funnier.
Oh my god today.
I was like today I actually was like oh my god if I said
that it would have been so fucking funny Why didn't I say
that?
Because like you know how it's like I was a demon and we're
joking about the bachelor party I could have been like wow
who ordered a number Boucher Wow, I could have said that I
was like I was like, oh my God, I set up the perfect joke
about the bachelor party, and I didn't go full circle.
A wig, Doki, would have went full circle.
I had the perfect setup, Doki.
You had the perfect setup.
You could have went with it.
Because I kept, like, what else, a demon?
I kept like, you know, doing that attack where, you know,
doing that attack where you're like, it's like you're
basically like the bachelor party type deal.
I was like, I can't believe it.
I set up the perfect joke for this and I didn't.
There was no payoff.
I threw.
I fucking threw.
It would have been such a, it would have been so good.
um anyway yeah my brain actually my my brain was like not
awake it like started like slowly booted up the comedy
sector of my brain was not fucking on at that time i need to
remind myself to not take naps i i not like okay to not take
naps before a stream because i swear to i feel like i feel
like i'm just like not i realize i'm not as funny if i
taking that before the stream
i was like i was like oh my god i'm definitely funnier if i
just don't take a nap before the stream
and i definitely i need to remind myself not to do it i need
to remind myself not to nap before streams because uh my
brain just doesn't have enough time to boot up uh boot up
and be active and actually like and actually like create
content because I'm like still so like Ligarthic and stuff
like that um anyway also oh yeah uh I I got distracted a
little bit but um I was also inspired i was also like uh
inspired by it's the newest trend right now it's like a
newest trend in content creating where uh content creators
are uh are making these like new channels new channels where
they edit the their vods in a way they make compilation and
they edit the in a way where it's like uh videos you put
before you start like videos you put before you sleep type
deal like white noise have you guys seen that lately i've
been like okay wait there's this channel i've been like play
it showed up on my recommended uh recently and it's been
like uh so oh my gosh let me see if i can find it it's been
showing up in my recommended i've been like watching it
regularly like whenever i before like when i'm like heading
to bed i just put it on my phone and um just play in the
background uh just to like help me sleep because it's like
white noise um i'm trying to figure out remember like what
channel it was it was like showing up in my recommended a
lot yeah sleep channels so um it's basically like a lot of
like content creators now recently are making channels
dedicated to like uh giving me like editing the vods in a
way And they basically, like, mute and lower all the loud
sounds on those videos.
And then, uh, they, they, like, mute and, like, lower the
sounds and remove all the screams and everything.
And so, like, you can put in, it's, like, the same video.
It's almost the same video.
Just, like, you can put it in a background and you want to,
like, wake up to it, like, stuff like that.
Um, I'm trying to, like, remember which channel it was that
kept playing, um, I kept getting recommended of, uh, that's
basically your old vibe.
Uh, also, Dala, uh, Dala, thank you for the magenta soup.
Thank you.
Finish watching your stream tips video.
Here's the tuition I can spare.
Just wondering though, should there be a personal Twitch to
watch others and a work Twitch to stream as?
Thank you for the content.
Uh, no, because why?
Why?
There's no point in having separate Twitch channels unless
you want to be like incognito.
I don't have separate Twitch channels.
Um, I usually just use one.
So, uh, so honestly, like, there's no need to, unless you
want to be, like, secret about who you watch.
But even then, you just get, like, BTTV.
I think that's, that is, yeah, if you get BTTV, you can, um,
you can, there's, like, anonymous mode where it logs you out
of the Twitch chat.
It logs you out of the Twitch chat, so, like, they can't,
people can't track who you're watching.
Uh, but obviously it's only available on, it's only
available on, like, PC uh, it's not there's it doesn't exist
on mobile.
So like I usually never watch streams on my phone anymore
Because like I've noticed I've noticed people have been like
stalking who I watch
And then people would like at me in the chat and would be
like whoa dokey's here So so I just I just watch on PC
because I just watch on my PC because I have the I have the
plugin that like puts me in anonymous mode So people can't
like look in the chat list to find me
Yeah, yeah Just like, I was like, oh, well, that's awkward
Sean, thank you for the super chat, thank you, thank you
That sounds like a scam to brainwash viewers I'm not
thinking of the super chat, thank you, thank you I'm trying
to like remember that channel Okay, okay, I'm gonna gonna
like i'm gonna be like png for like one second give me a sec
guys this is important like now i'm dedicated i need to know
i need to know what because like i always like i put that
channel in the background i can't remember it on the top of
my head now now it's like in my now i'm like you know like
those moments where you're like oh my god what is it that's
me right now that's me what do you Okay, there you are.
Oh, okay.
Was it Cat-Catty-Caris?
Catty-Caris?
I think that's... Is that his name?
Was that the... He has a sleep channel, right?
Catty-Caris sleep.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Catty sleeps.
Yeah.
This guy's video...
This guy's, like, videos has been, like, in my
recommended...
For so long.
And it really helps.
I don't know what the fuck...
Okay, not gonna lie.
okay not gonna lie I'll say this I I have no idea what his
videos are like every time I put I just put it on the
background for actual white noise I have no idea what his
content is I literally forget what his content is I just put
it on because it was just really good white noise I just put
there's a background oh something fell what fell okay not
important um i i put in the background and then he's like
and i'm like
so i just this is like i got a lot there's also like did you
know did you know gaming also has one too did you know
gaming sleep uh i think it's yeah what was it sleep okay did
you uh video game facts to sleep too yeah this one i also
have i also do this one too um uh miko thank you for the
super chat thank you thank you hi dogi just came from your
holiday stream sad i wasn't even gonna catch you live but so
happy to know you sam your oshis are my oshis too so the
mona's too cute thank you for the super chat thank you thank
you that's fucking right you never forget your first never
forget i i talked i i uh told the story before but for those
who uh don't know about my history with samuel stuff um so
like uh also i hope that is the music okay at an okay volume
chat is the is the music at an okay volume by the way um but
yes anyway uh as i was saying when i was like growing up Um,
it wasn't just, I never had, like, a favorite Sanrio
character until, until I, until I saw Sinemoro.
Uh, wait, there's music?
Okay, I'll turn it up a little bit.
I'll turn it up a little bit.
Alright, so I've never had a, I've never had a favorite
Sanrio character until Sinemoro came into, uh, came into the
picture.
Um, and the thing is, uh, um, before then it was there used
to be I don't know if it's still around I don't know if it's
still around um but there was this other it was a Korean I
think it was Korean store um it was like good night bear I
think that's what is that what he's called good night bear
no it's that's not him it's that blue bear blue bear is it
Korean oh it's literally blue bear oh my god
Bear.
Okay.
So, um, so basically, uh, there was this, there was these
stores going around.
I don't know if they're still, I don't think they're popular
anymore.
I honestly don't think they're popular anymore, um, in NA.
I knew they were like, they were super fucking popular back
then when I was growing up.
But I think the company was called like Morning Glory.
And, um, I used to, like my mom used to buy me a lot of
like, like the mascot characters from the like from the
store and I used to be like obsessed with Morning Glory.
There was this other one I saw somebody like I retweeted it
too there was like the Korean bunny I'm trying to remember
the Korean bunny like like he's like not I'm not talking
about Mollong I'm talking about the OG Korean bunny does I
remember I retweeted the someone to an artwork of it like a
parody the oh no not Molan that's like that's like current
Korean bunny but there was like the OG is it mashie oh yes
yes it's mashie motto okay I was fucking obsessed with uh
mashie mashie motto and a blue bear that's the that was the
original original Korean bunny.
Now everybody knows about Mulan, but Mashimaro was the OG.
The OG Korean bunny.
Marty, thank you for the Akasupa.
Thank you, thank you.
Sincere person who sleeps 17 out of 24 hours, I need advice
on how to sleep quickly when my brain doesn't want to stop.
Thank you.
Okay, thank you, thank you.
Straight up, put white noise.
This is how I fall asleep.
I just put white noise of any youtube video um usually the
best ones are like podcasts or like someone you know there
it's just non-stop yapping so i'll just like um just play
like any youtube video or like twitch streams or anything
you can do music as well music doesn't work as well for me
when i sleep so i just put like uh podcasts or like
commentary videos or i used to sleep to apex streams back
then um now i just put on like random long videos like it
has to be super long too like maybe like 20 plus minutes i
choose a video between 20 plus to an hour so like uh you
know if i wake up the video will still be going um and uh
and it really helps a lot with falling asleep and like i
can't really like and also like when you're putting these
videos they're talking a lot too They're talking a lot so
like your brain doesn't think about like, you know, anything
else in your thoughts You're just thinking about like you're
just your brain is just focused on the white noise that's
playing around That's playing on your phone and and honestly
like I have no idea what any of the videos talk about Like I
have zero memory of any of the videos that play when I go to
sleep I it just like my brain just deletes all of that
information
but that's basically how it helps me go to sleep too um uh
but yeah anyway as i was saying the old uh before sanrio uh
i my mom would buy me a lot of this like from the morning
glory company like the stores there used to be so many of
the stores uh where i used to live and uh and i would have
like i don't think they're like as popular anymore i think
they got replaced by a lot like similar stores but it's not
morning glory anymore but i always have like a lot of
stationary a lot of like pencil oh you know like those lead
pencils where oh my gosh okay it's okay it's like i don't
know people still use these but as a kid um instead of lead
pencils it's like they're like little capsules wait i'm
gonna get a picture i can show the picture on screen um oh i
wish i know what it was called but they're like little
capsules and then you after you finish using them you plug
it out and then you put it on the top and then and then like
you know and then another capsule will come out the guy does
anyone remember those they used to be so popular for
children yeah they used to yeah they used to be like
incredibly popular for kids i don't think people use them
anymore because they realized it was so what's the word it
was very environmentally unfriendly.
It was incredibly wasteful.
I'm pretty sure.
Because, like, you know, after you finish using them, you
can't do anything anymore.
So, I'm pretty sure.
Also a choking hazard.
You're right.
It was most definitely a choking hazard.
But kids loved it.
um um but i honestly i don't know what it was called i just
remember i would there was like i used to use those because
like that's what my mom bought for me uh before i went
before i started using lead pencil um they were pretty fun
though uh more balls thank you for the super chat thank you
thank you i drew the artwork of you of you mashimoto version
i didn't know you would know this cute of course yeah yeah
of course Uh, KR bunny.
And also, thank you so much for the retweet.
Thank you, the super chat.
Thank you.
Of course, it's the OG Korean bunny.
Yeah, it's like a little dart Lego.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm pretty sure, like, because it was definitely, like, a
chokinheiser and also not very good for the environment,
that it definitely quickly died out.
Like, it's definitely, people realize, like, oh that is not
very safe for kids we should uh we should stop we should
stop making them stacking pencils okay let me see yes yes
that's what they are and then i would okay wait blue bear is
that the blue bear version no where the fuck is that blue
bear okay blue bear blue bear stationary okay let's see oh
my gosh oh i'm like looking at all the oh my i had like so
many of these things oh i had this before wait no that's
bootleg never mind did not have this before i wait did i
okay i had this but it was the not bootleg version like
that's a pants i thank you for the money gifted chips thank
you thank you oh my gosh my mom would like I remember my mom
would buy um would buy these types of uh would buy like
these types of stationary for me because it was like you
know a fucking bargain like all-in-one special you know like
that type of deal um but also like uh the non the the
non-bootleg version
just so you know um oh my gosh i'm looking at the morning
glory oh my gosh i love how like the morning glory store
just puts in a moro now just it's just sanrio products now
no you used to have your own burning glory why are you
selling other people's brands you used to be an empire
childhood or my childhood's getting absorbed by all the
other monopolies
oh my god all my childhood they're getting absorbed by all
the other monopolies oh back in my day fox i don't know if
you guys know this but back in my day Fox channel like The
Fox channel Used to be its own network I know It's so crazy
I know it's insane You mean Disney didn't own Like 80% of
the media
No fucking way Prop Thank you for the super chat Thank you
thank you Good night dokey bird Sleep tight and plenty And
keep on smiling for next day next day and next and so on t
thank you for the super chat thank you thank you i would not
be surprised if disney just absorbs like 10 more of the
media around us what else is next okay abc is also disney um
fox is now disney hbo i don't know i don't know i don't know
if disney can actually buy hbo who owns hbo anyway who owns
hbo let's see who owns Who owns HBO?
HBO, Casey Blois, who are you?
Oh yeah, Warner.
Honestly, with the rate Warner Brothers is going.
All right.
Somebody quote me on this in 10 years.
I bet you in 10 years, Disney is going to buy Warner
Brothers.
I bet you guys this is what's going to happen.
In 10 years, Disney is going to buy Warner Brothers.
own Warner Brothers because I fucking who I don't care I
don't care if this guy watches me because like oh and if he
does I say that's an honor that the Warner Brothers CEO
watches this stupid dumb VTuber
um but like I fucking hate the Warner Brothers CEO he's like
the worst CEO that we've ever had for Warner Brothers and
with the rate he's going like all he fucking cares about is
like meaning the like finance like meaning the fucking
financial line and I bet you I bet you I would not be
surprised if Disney offers um that guy like a lot of fucking
money he'd take it a hundred percent he does anything for
tax breaks I bet you he would fucking take he would take the
money anyway please don't copy strike me on any games I play
from
please please i really i really like the batman games please
let me continue playing the batman games i would really
appreciate it please you'll get nothing from copyright
striking me like i get like like it'll be like pennies don't
tell oh my gosh by the way i got hit by limited ads I got
hit by limited ads on my collab.
I must have swore.
Did I swear in the beginning?
Someone pull up my collab stream right now and tell me how
long did it take to hear the first swear word.
I submitted an appeal already.
But like somebody pull up the stream right now and tell me
how long it took for me to swear.
I need to find the sweet spot.
I need to figure out what is the sweet spot of like the
amount of time I can like basically like So you know it's
like oh um you cannot swear in the first like x amount of
minutes And then I need to figure out I need to tie myself I
need to wait until like 10 to 15 minutes until I swear First
10 minutes okay guys maybe I play the intro for 10 minutes
right I just I just play the intro for it was at three
minutes and 50 bro we didn't even last one like less we
didn't even last two minutes oh my god we didn't even last
two minutes before we went into swear mode that's so fucked
up man that's so fucked up um peter thank you for the super
chat thank you thank you uh corner current warner rosio is
speed running bankruptcy thank you the super chat thank you
thank you thank you gladstone thank you for the super chat
thank you thank you just gotta learn to say freak instead of
the other f word okay i swear to god if i get like limited
for the stream guys guys did i swear i don't remember did i
swear in the first 10 minutes today for this stream right
now did i swear in the first 10
no yes but it's already after 10 minutes I can it's already
like it's already like uh what oh my gosh how long I've been
streaming it's already been like 30 38 minutes has it right
oh my gosh I fucking don't stop yapping it's already been
like 38 minutes and like that time flies by so fast um but
yeah I learned that I don't it must be a new rule because I
was I would never get hit in the and I like swore so much I
used to never get hit by the limited ad shit in the past so
they must have recently changed the algorithm or something I
just hate that I hate it because obviously I don't get the
ad revenue I don't get the ad revenue for like the first
couple of hours because they hit me with the limited ads and
because of that and like people usually watch the vibe you
know like after the stream ends People would watch the VOD
instantly.
So it's like, no!
YouTube!
Yeah, the most important hours!
No!
Um, but it was there before.
No, that's the thing.
Um, on my previous channel, I rarely have ever get hit with
limited ads.
It only happens.
when uh i usually only get striked by like music stuff and
it was i would never get striked for this is like it's been
the first time it's been the first time i've been like
getting striked for profanity uh which has been very
surprising d2h thank you for the akasupa thank you thank you
honestly i could figure out what to say it was bouncing
between a genuine question or a dn joke but i can't do that
to my kami oshi just answer Thank you for the Akasuka.
Thank you.
Depends on, like, which Metro series?
I might try Metro at a later time.
I think, like, I stopped because, like, I think I...
I don't know why I stopped.
I think it's because, like, there was too long...
It was too long of a break in between.
So, like, I just stopped playing it.
I think I'm going to try and find a Metro game.
I might start on a Metro game that was considered because I
don't think I actually I don't think I like enjoyed the one
I played I don't even remember the which one I played on
stream I actually I actually don't remember I don't think I
enjoyed that one um as much as I would have liked it I I
mean as much as I I don't think I enjoyed it as much as I
would have liked so I feel like I should try a fine I should
try and start one that I that was considered like um like
universal appeal a lot of a lot of people are asking me
because talked about Fallout um it's really good I highly
recommend checking out the fall I feel Fallout show I feel
like we're in a generation where like gamers are now making
the shows for like video game adaptations um and I feel like
we're at a point where we have people who actually play
video games making good adaptations of a video like of like
um like of video games and um okay the halo series okay we
don't mention the halo series because the halo series was
literally made by a group of creators who don't even who
don't even like play video games they literally don't care
about halo the writers never played halo the only exception
the only i think like last of us because the create i think
the creators of last of us the creators of last of us
actually played the game but they told the actors to not
play the game but the the creators and the writers and the
producers they know the story of last of us and they
actually play the game but they told the actors they're like
no do not play the game we want you to act without any of
the knowledge of what's going on in the video game um and um
but they were still pretty faithful to the last of us game
um um but yet i think like the halo the people in halo they
did not know what the fuck was going on twisted meta okay
twisted meta like there's no not gonna lie i don't i don't
think the video game has much lore like it was the game was
just about like people in cars like each other up in cars so
like i i feel like the game itself didn't really have a lot
of lore to build off of so i was so surprised that
i was i was so surprised that the show actually like did
something
what do you mean as what what's the lore what's the lore I
feel like okay like like I meant like more like I've only
played one twisted metal game but also I was like super
fucking young um and I feel like I feel like the people like
okay if you look at the other games the really A lot of the
game, a lot of them had like, a lot of people like know
about the lore of these games.
Like Fallout has an extensive lore.
Last of Us has an extensive lore and story.
But like, Twisted Metal.
All I remember about Twisted Metal was that clown and then
Cars.
And then they made a whole entire story based off of like...
a car i was like okay
um um but yeah anyway uh i highly recommend like i feel like
the meme about like oh video game video game adaptations is
like almost non-existent anymore um because there's been
more there's been more like home runs than there is duds in
general and i honestly feel like i honestly feel time where
people actually know how to make good video game adaptations
um because they're running out of sequels to do there people
are tired of fucking superhero films and uh people are tired
of superhero films and people are tired of sequels video
game adaptations it's their next niche we're at an era video
game adaptations now.
Honestly, it's true.
It's true.
It's not about superheroes anymore.
It's all about video game adaptations now.
We're at the new stage.
A new era.
What's that word called?
You know, like the next peak of the next peak of cinema?
Fuck, what's that word called?
I forgot what it called.
My English is deteriorating.
The next mainstream thing it's the next mainstream act and
we're getting warhammer 2 the next era we have the next meta
yes it's the next meta no more superhero meta we're in the
video game meta now i think it's also because we have the
graphics we have this we have the ability to do cgi now of
like actual video game cgi so i mean okay here like all
right the good ones there was fallout there's last of us um
the witcher until like they fired half the writing crew the
writers um yeah until they fired some of the writing crew
and also henry cabez um arcane um what else there's so many
sonic was pretty good too sonic mario um the witcher was
good until it wasn't all right guys the Witcher was good
until it wasn't.
You can't blame them, Cyberpunk.
There's been so many actual decent ones.
Okay, Detective Pikachu was pretty fun, yes.
Detective Pikachu was pretty fun.
Only because of Ryan Reynolds.
If it wasn't for Ryan Reynolds, I think the movie would have
been pretty shit.
Not gonna lie.
Ryan Reynolds is the only reason why...
and Pikachu was as good as it is because if you take Ryan
Reynolds out the other actors were so bad no offense to the
other actors but they were not as memorable or as good um
deadpaw thank you for the uh super chat thank you thank you
we're currently in a dune era but next year uh video games
will rise like the what thank you for the super chat thank
you thank you Who's that?
I'm scared of saying their name because I don't know who
they are.
Oh, it's from Dune.
Okay, I was like, I'm scared.
I don't want to get baited to say something.
Yeah, I haven't seen Dune, by the way, guys.
I haven't seen Dune.
I was just worried.
I'm getting baited.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Leah, thank you for the super chat.
Lay home my dough.
Thank you, leho.
Thank you, super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Um, I haven't watched Dune yet.
The only thing I know about Dune is that the...
The only thing I know about Dune is the...
Is the movie theater cup holder for Dune.
Have you guys seen it?
Have you guys seen that?
Oh, is it a popcorn bucket?
Have you guys seen it?
Don't worry, guys.
I can show this on stream.
I think.
Because it's a popcorn bucket!
Guys, look at this.
This is the only thing I know about.
The fucking...
It's a popcorn bucket.
You stick your hand in it.
Your hand.
You stick your hand.
The only appendage that should go in there to grab the
popcorn.
and then eat the popcorn oh yeah that's the only thing i
know about dune it's just this that's my literally my only
only knowledge um but um but yeah that's like everything i
know anyway as i was saying i feel like uh it's gonna be
interesting what uh what the new what was it the warhammer
movie is gonna be because it's gonna start it's gonna me
like oh is it gonna continue the trend of actual decent
video game adaptations um but oh also also also i was gonna
say yeah but yeah check out you gotta you guys gotta check
out fallout i think if you really like the games if you
really like the games if you really like the lore um if you
just like fallout in general even if you don't like fallout
i think it's like really interesting to watch it's actually
really decent i'm only on the first two episodes the first
episode was so good that had to click next like i was like i
want to watch the next one but you guys can get tell me all
the spoilers because i already read all i already guys i
already read the wiki
because i i got into the rabbit hole of you know how like
when you when you click one article and then you click on
the next article and then you click on the next article so
like i was like
that's so interesting because like I love the lore behind
Fallout because I thought it was like it's just very
interesting to read and like if you guys don't know the lore
of like the vaults each vault um each vault has like a
different experiment going on so I was curious I was like oh
what is this vault's like science experiment so they'll like
do like a social experiment with each vault like with each
vault and the vault is where like they put all the people in
there and stuff like that and then i was like oh okay i want
to know what the vault what their the social experiment is
or like the science experiment is going on in that vault
like in the vault we're looking at and then so i got into a
whole fucking rabbit hole of of of the show so i sort of
know how it i i sort of know how the show ends but like i'm
on episode two um There's like, so like, if you guys don't
know about the vault lore, there's one vault where it's just
filled with clones named Gary.
And all they say is Gary.
And, and, um, there's another vault.
There's a, oh, I know you guys are curious about this vault.
You must be like, what's in vault 69?
It's, they basically in vault 69 is one guy.
all women that's what's involved 69 real this is actually
real lord by the way i'm not making the up like that's
actually what's involved 69 um they knew of course they know
every fucking gamer is a 10 year old inside okay no not 10
year old that's the wrong age puberty 14 okay every every
gamer game developer is a 14 14-year-old It has a
14-year-old inside.
Sorry.
I had to think about What age do people hit puberty?
I was like 10 is not the right age.
10 to 14 is much better
The the inner 14-year-old But yes, and then I think this
those were the most like ridiculous ones for me.
I think there was one where I'm trying to remember there was
like another vault where I'm trying to remember there was
like one vault where it was like one guy and then it's all
puppets so they want to see like how insane like will they
be able to function as a human being with no socialization
except for the puppets and obviously the answer is no yeah
no they that person was not okay Um, the puppet man.
Yeah, the puppet man.
So, um...
Wait, did Penny Arcade actually write that one?
Wait, Penny Arcade?
Oh my god, that's a name I...
I fucking... That's a name I haven't heard in so long.
Are they still?
Like, is it still alive?
How... Holy shit!
The creators of Penny Arcade is almost in his...
50s that's oh my god i think a lot of people feel so old
right now oh my god he's in his fuck he's almost in his 50s
they're 46 and 48 they were like the og gamer comics oh no
you're better off a vehicle than him most of this was Guys,
okay, we'll see other...
Oh, guys, cyanide and happiness.
Bro, I'm so sad.
Cyanide and happiness.
They still make really good content, but because they're,
like, super old now, people don't watch cyanide and
happiness anymore.
I still, like, I still, like, watch it ever so often.
Like, there'd be, like, gaps in between before I, like,
watch cyanide and happiness again.
Um, and, uh, the creators of cyanide and happiness, he's
sturdy.
Okay, not as old.
Not as old, though.
Not as old.
36.
That's pretty good.
36 to 39.
That's decent.
That's pretty good.
It makes you feel less old now.
Bro.
I used to love cyanide.
I actually owned...
I owned several of hard copy books of cyanide and happiness.
I have like...
I actually...
I kickstarted a bunch of their games.
game like board games as well because like i honestly i just
love their content and uh don't say 30 look 36 is pretty
decent not as bad as 48 i can't believe penny arcade like
the creators are like 48 oh my god oh they're like the ogs
too oh my god okay um oh my god this is this is like blast
from the past but does anyone remember that fucking cartoon
network comic of oh my god does anyone remember because it
was like okay these were the comics that people used to read
back then it was um it was penny arcade i think grim tales i
think that was it was like cartoon network but what if
they're like super edgy uh and it was like super fucking
edgy so it was like people would read um um uh penny arcade
grim tales uh cyanide and happiness uh and snafu yeah snafu
comics and uh what else there was like Oh my god, Fusion
Fall.
I remember Fusion Fall.
I never got a chance to play Fusion Fall.
I don't know why.
I think I was just too stupid on the internet to know how to
play Fusion Fall.
Mega Tokyo.
Bro, Mega Tokyo.
Guess it was a scam.
Do they still exist?
Oh, they do.
Okay.
Wait, not Mega Tokyo.
What was it?
Not Mega Tokyo.
The Tokyo Pop?
No, not Mega Tokyo.
What was it?
Is it Tokyo?
It was like some...
Well, not...
Was it...
The publication.
Was it not?
It was not...
I'm not talking about Mega Tokyo.
It was like a book publication.
The comic books.
Before, who were like...
I'm not talking about Mega Tokyo.
I'm talking about like...
Is it Tokyo Pop?
Oh, yeah.
I don't know if they're better now.
But like, I heard Tokyo Pop used to have like...
really bad like illustrator contracts.
I think, I don't know, they're better now.
But like, I remember there was like, like several, like
there's publisher.
Yeah, the publisher.
I remember back then, the publisher had like really bad like
contracts and everything for like artists and translators
back then.
Like people were, people were making, not twit longers, but
like a tweeter, twit, sorry, not twit.
Twitter.
Twitter was not a thing yet.
So people were making like the DeviantArt and Tumblr
equivalent of twitline guys about Tokyo Pop.
Yeah.
And then, um, and then, yeah, the angry bloggers.
They live, they were, there was like live journals, Tumblr
posts and DeviantArt journal blog posts about Tokyo Pop
because apparently they paid really little um in terms of
translations and it wasn't like super accurate but the thing
is they had so many license and I think at one point they
went bankrupt so like it took off like majority of the
English um the English translations of uh tokyo pop manga's
so like majority of like because like they own they had a
they almost had a monopoly for like manga and i think they
went bankrupt and at one point and they they had to like uh
they had to like take down majority of like you know they
went bankrupt so they had to basically a lot of manga was
like taken out because of it and i and apparently they're
still around So they must have got better They must have got
better I remember people were like Whoa Yeah They almost
killed the whole scene Because they literally had the
monopoly They had the monopoly Of manga For like the NA side
Because like it was the only way to read like NA manga Like
English manga And then it like They almost went bankrupt
oh my gosh and then there was there was there was uh uh does
anyone remember the okay there was this like thing back then
where it was like i wish they could bring it back man the oc
contest oh my god so i used to love endling uh endling stuff
um ever after oh my god i love reading his comics he like he
stopped because i guess he got a real job
silence think of this uh five give the shows thank you thank
you um but back then there was like original character
tournaments and it was so fucking cool because um um because
like uh there was this thing where uh people would make up
these like tournaments and stuff and then there was lore
around it there was like a whole lore and everything around
it and then it was like people would like um enter with like
original characters and stuff and then there would be like
battles yeah oc battles so like they'll draw comics
animations stuff like that for like oc battles and the most
famous one was um the ever after tournament with endling
hosting it and oh with the Climber.
I used to love the Climber.
Like, I was so obsessed with the Climber.
The Climber was my K-pop stat.
The Climber was my BTS.
All the women loved the Climber.
Was it Climber?
He must not wait, maybe I'm thinking of it wrong.
What was his actual name?
Is his name actually climber?
I might be remembering it wrong too.
Endling tournament.
Ever ever after tournament.
Okay, was it ever after?
Okay, endling.
Oh my god, it's so long.
What did he climb?
I was, no, you don't understand.
It was Oh my god, it's so old that like, oh my god.
Was it, what was his, oh my god, okay, end zone.
Okay, it was called the end zone.
Okay, who was, who were competitors?
Was he actually called Climb?
Yes, he was!
He was called the Climbor!
Okay, I was getting paranoid and was like, am I forgetting
it wrong?
Because all the animation was made in Flash.
Okay, but that shit, I love the lore.
I'm so sad.
The guy, the creator of, the creator of Climbor, He fucking
disappeared because he got a real job too.
So, god damn it.
Why do they all keep getting real jobs?
But that shit was so good.
Oh my gosh.
I was like obsessed with like the lore behind this, the
climber.
And like the ad, okay, like you might think watch rewatching
because i rewatched animations recently because it's on
flash like it was on flash but somebody saved the animation
um uh saved the animations and stuff uh on youtube and i was
rewatching it and i was like oh the voice acting was not as
good as i remembered it i had i had those rose tinted
glasses on it was not as it was not as like pretty as i
remember The fight scenes, though.
The fight scenes were still pretty fucking good.
I have to admit.
Like, the fight scenes were actually pretty fucking insane,
though.
Even if, like, um...
Even if, like, the voice acting wasn't as good.
I think back then, because a lot of them were also, like,
Newgrounds creators.
I would say, like, Newgrounds creators are incredibly good
at fight scenes and fight choreographies.
uh mouse thank you for the or mouse thank you for the super
chat thank you thank you hey dokey any game recommendations
to play when you're bored but won't get you too worked up
thank you for the super chat thank you thank you that is so
difficult i haven't been like actually playing any um um
games off stream um because i feel like we're in like low
key a gaming rut not gonna lie um because like a lot of
people like recommend like a lot of like what are those
those crafting games with like crafting and stuff like that
or i would just say like oh my gosh i i honestly feel like
for me i feel like we're in the low-key gaming rut for me
because like a lot of the games i like are not meta anymore
there's but like honestly if you don't want to get too
worked up and want to pass the time just play some open
world survival games yeah that's what i'm open world
survival crafting games those are like the easiest um games
that are like the most chill type deal uh i would say like i
haven't tried it out yet but a lot of people have been
playing planet crafter recently a lot of people say like
planet crafter has been pretty good um but yeah oh my gosh i
oh my god and there was what's his name carl oh my god bro i
used to love those creator so much carl and the climber they
were my bts man they so i would draw fan art of them all in
my sketchbook all the time it was pretty shitty fan art um
so um but like i used to be so fucking obsessed with carl
and the climber from from like the and like from the what
was it the law of talos the law of talos tournament and also
the the end zone oh my gosh if you guys i highly recommend
checking out at least i'm pretty sure the the comment the
creator still oh my god he's alive oh my i'm gonna follow
that he was my hero that guy was my hero
instead he was my fucking hero i used to love that i would
like read all i would like read like the lore and like
absorb his lore the lore of the climber oh my god his
animations was like fucking sick what's the twitter guys oh
my god bro the last time he posted was in 2012 guys of
course i was he's still oh my god photo bucket bro fucking
photo bucket man okay guys what what is the twitter i need
to stalk him i need i need to stalk this man
um all right check his likes what oh no don't say it please
don't ruin you know when you say don't meet your heroes
don't ruin this for me
Please, I hope his likes are would not be deal-breakers.
Do not ruin this creator for me.
Maude, what's his Twitter?
I need to know!
Please, I need to follow him.
I need to follow all my favorite creators that were my role
models.
Oh my gosh, I should not say role models because now I'm
scared about what his likes are.
Now I'm scared.
I can't say role model because what if I shouldn't role
model him?
Like, no, no, don't ruin this.
Like, I love this shit, bro.
Don't fucking ruin this for me.
Um, but yes.
Also, like, oh, there was another creator, really.
Oh my gosh It was like Oh my god I used to admire so many
artists Uh Back then too So It's like crazy Going back
memory lane And like how How much Uh Uh How much like Um
What's the word How much they've like grown as an artist And
stuff I don't want to expose my show Ha ha ha there was
there was this other artist that i used to like i really
like their art of but like i'm worried that like i'm i'm
like honestly worried about what what they are now because
oh my god okay because i know what happened to one of the
creators and like what pathway they went to so i'm so
embarrassed but there was this artist that was known okay
it's gonna be okay it's so fucked oh my god like when i read
like like as i got older and then as i as i got older and
then like i realized like you know they got older too and
then okay i won't name any I won't name names, but back then
on Demon Art, um, this was for Pokemon Mystery Dungeon.
Um, yes, okay, okay, some people are like, know where it's
gonna go.
So, like, there used to be, like, really popular things
with, like, Animal Crossing and Mystery Dungeon, and, like,
Pokemon, Pokemon, and Pokemon Mystery Dungeon, and stuff
like that.
And there would be, like, roleplay groups.
So, like, people would draw comics and stuff with, like,
OCs.
So, one was the Pokemon Mystery Dungeon Roleplay Group.
And let's just say, um, the main creator of the roleplay
group definitely went a different direction afterwards.
And I remember, it used to be so cute.
It used to be, like, so cute.
And the lore was so interesting but then money talks
no it's not pokemon anymore let's just let's just say um
money definitely talks and um it's definitely uh It was not
about cute Pokemon Mr. Dungeon missions anymore.
And I just remembered, because I used to follow this artist.
Because I really liked their art.
Because it was so cute.
And the story was so interesting.
And then it went a different direction.
I won't say the name.
But for anyone that ever followed the DeviantArt.
Pokemon Mystery Dungeon role-play groups like the most
famous one would know exactly who I'm talking about like
they They they would know because they were like one of the
they were the most famous Pokemon Mystery Dungeon like
artists back then and and it went a different direction half
a couple of years later I I can't name it like it's like
they still do they still make content so I can't say
anything it's just you know when people get older I guess
they figured you know they got bills to play and everything
I understand they get they have bills to pay there's a
market for it but like oh my god little me was not ready for
that little me little me just liked cute art and i was just
like oh
um asad thank you for the akasupa thank you thank you oh my
god it was your first supa too thank you so much uh hey doki
i've been enjoying your content for a while now so i like i
feel like the super chat is so long overdue thanks and keep
sean thank you thank you for the akasupa thank you thank you
i really really do appreciate it uh but yes uh you know what
they say don't meet your heroes that's why i'm so afraid i'm
so afraid like someone was like don't check this person's
legs and now i'm scared now i'm like now i'm scared because
like i've had that moment before where i met where like i
used to admire i mean they had really good art
they got older
um delta thank you for the super chat thank you thank you
and i'm scared because usually usually you know when people
get older i don't know i'm scared
just i don't know what they're doing it now i don't i don't
know i don't know if i would I'm worried my childhood.
I don't want my childhood to be...
I don't want my childhood to be gone again.
Um...
Oh my gosh.
Also, like...
Similar with, like, Newground Animators.
There's, like...
There's, like, some Newground Animators that I've, like,
super admired and, like, was, like, really into their arts
and animation.
And I was like, what are they up to these days?
And then porn straight up
I was like I checked their Twitter I was like Oh that's a
dick
I was like I was like Whoa Alright That takes me back Got a
picture like you know yeah um i only got someone literally
every new ground andra new back in like 2012 porn all of
them every single one thank you for the super though he was
he was super chat i was like oh okay okay thank you thank
you for the super chat thank you thank you it's either like
that direction or they're or they're you know or they're
making making like or they went viral for like a video game
or tv show it's one or the other it's it's one or the other
either a show either a cartoon show or you know drawing
point thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you i
meant check his likes to see if he was still active didn't
mean the other way oh Oh, thank God, okay.
I like Yankee.
Like, I misinterpret that and it started a whole thing.
It started a whole fucking tangent on its own.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Um...
But yeah, It was a blast from a past.
Haunta, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Everyone was too young back then.
But then they realized this dark side of money.
For me, I am just stuck with...
Monkey Martin!
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
yeah also the more i talk about this the more i realized i
was way too young to be like reading or watching any of
these things by the way i should have never been allowed on
the internet the thing is i didn't even start on the
internet really young i wasn't allowed to be on the internet
um for a long time until like i was i wasn't allowed to be
on the internet until like Like I'd even have, like I wasn't
even allowed to have like a Facebook account when like
people were, people, everybody made Facebook accounts.
And like one of my friends had to make a Facebook account
for me because I had no idea about Facebook.
And then all I did, I think when I was finally allowed to be
on the internet, all I did was play Neopets.
I, I, all I did, I literally, I was just like, yay.
Neil Pence instead.
Is that doing anything else?
Um.
Uh, but yeah.
That was like usually.
And then like later on.
When I found out.
What the internet was really like.
Uh.
When I found out what the internet was really like.
I sort of like.
I went all in.
So like.
I like explored the internet.
a lot so like like fucking figure like fucking read about
like like you know like all about the OC tournament and and
the new ground stuff read a lot of like internet comics
fanfiction fanfiction.net before they okay I did something a
little illegal I definitely should not have been reading
some of the fanfics that was i definitely should not have
been reading the lemon
one and then and then also also you know i i found out about
like new grounds and like artwork and stuff like that and
the what let's say lemon and limes lemon and limes uh no but
thank you for the super chat thank you thank you it's up
dokey hope your night's been going well i think it's been
going pretty well thank you for the super chat thank you
thank you welcome to the internet
if you know you know i was an internet connoisseur
oh my god and then the live journal role play groups okay
back then i should not i you know how they're like you gotta
be 18 and over to read this read read this i was 18 for a
very long time
i was 18 for a while so there was like this um there was
like this this uh there was this uh there was this famous
live journal role play groups where uh who wasn't reading
lemons when we really shouldn't happen thank you for the
super chat next to thank you thank you okay so um and you
know you know there was like there were these famous live
journal for those who don't know what live journal is it was
like a lot of like old people would you i'm sorry a lot of
the older generations would use it i was definitely was not
i should not have been allowed on live journal I was way too
young for LiveJournal.
I should not have been on that.
But I've been 15.
I've been 18 for a very long time.
I mean, it was like pre-Tumblr.
It was basically pre-Tumblr.
And there was like a lot of like anime communities on there.
I would use LiveJournal to like take the icons for like
anime shows.
Like some of my favorite anime shows.
Oh my God.
I was part of the Glee Live Journal community.
I, okay, I would admit I would take some of the animated
icons from the Oran High School Host Club Live Journal
community and the Glee one to put on my MSN icon.
And please don't not Glee.
Anyway.
Anyway, as I was saying, um there was like this live journal
role play community where like people will role play as like
different characters from different uh from different
fandoms so like it was like a fucking mixed mash of like
it'll be like the team fortress 2 sniper meeting i don't
know meeting hikaru from oran high school host club and it
would be like the most insane role play session ever Like
there would be like so much lore in it and then it was all
public So then I would like read the roleplay sessions of
like random fucking Characters talking to each other and I
don't bro.
I don't remember what it was it was just like it was it was
either like super hinged or Like or Or just be like super
casual like okay guys not everything it was a lemon not
everything was lemons sometimes it was just general
interactions like what if the team fortress 2 sniper met up
with this random anime character there was like this really
popular one with a persona character like she was the the
one that was like wearing um the detective one not the
persona for not wait what persona are we on in now like it
was before persona not four it was before so in a four okay
that detective character from persona four it was so famous
like they actually were like they became famous in the live
journal community and like the detective character from
persona four and like this person was like i don't remember
who the fuck was she like was what were they coupled with
but like i followed that person's live journal post a lot
because they i follow that person's live journal post so
much they were a really good writer they were a really good
writer and like i was like so immersed i was so immersed in
the lore like this lore and then oh my god i remember like
at one point this they met pinky pie from my little pony
there was a there was a role play session with pinky pie
from I wish I remembered I wish I remembered like um I
remembered like what it was called like it was so popular um
it was so funny it was just so funny um it was actual lore
because like at one point there was a murder mystery with a
bunch of random anime characters and cartoon anime cartoon
and game characters it got to a murder mystery at one point
that they were trying to figure out a murder with a bunch of
anime characters slash cartoon characters slash game
characters and i was so obsessed with what the fuck was
going on and it was all role play
um but thank you for the akasufa thank you thank you
appreciation super chat to feed the over Find links for
every single topic that Toki has been yapping about.
Thank you for the Akasupa.
Thank you.
I love crossovers.
Who was the...
I don't fucking know.
I barely remembered what it was about.
I just remembered, like, the general...
Generalness of it all.
Oh, my God.
Um...
But, yeah.
Anyway, that was, like, my...
My internet history.
That was...
That was literally my internet history.
growing up.
It was a wild internet history.
I should have never, I should have not been on those sites
with how young I was.
I should have 100% not been on any of those sites for sure.
I need you guys to know when I started out my internet
history, I was like playing Neopets, right?
I even had to, I was so naive.
I didn't lie about my age when I started out Neopets.
to the point where like my my parents had to fax the neopets
headquarters proof that I had parental permission to access
the um the more restricted areas of neopets and you guys are
like the restricted areas of neopets what are those it was
basically the forms like um the neobords because like I
didn't lie about my age so I wasn't allowed to talk to
anybody online or like use the neo mail or anything so they
had to like they're like oh if you're under age and you want
to access the neo boards you have to fax um you have to fax
in your parents parental permission like a permission slip
so you can like access the neo boards and talk to the adults
so
I had to get that happened because I wanted to like I would
be like I want to talk to strangers on the internet I was
like mom I want to talk to the straight okay I didn't tell
her she didn't they didn't know they didn't know that it
ended up being I talked to random strangers on the internet
but like because like it was just they're like just like
access to things so they didn't realize at that time it
basically led to me Knowing more about the internet because
you know, I started talking to fucking adults on the
internet
I definitely should not have been Because like a lot because
like you guys didn't know back then neopets was like um Was
mostly for adults and for college students like and I was
definitely neither of them So so there was a lot of like It
was like, I remembered, I talked about the story before, but
like, there was a help section, there was a help section,
and, um, and, like, in the Neo Boards, and I was, like,
really scared, because I was like, oh my god, I'm gonna, um,
I don't know, I think I was like, oh my gosh, I'm gonna, I'm
gonna go to middle school for the first time, and I'm really
scared, and I was like, I don't know, what is middle school
gonna be like, I'm so scared, and then some some adult was
like the help section is for like was for is for neopets
related issues but don't worry 6th grade is not that
difficult this is not the right board to talk about this
This is where like neopets related help issues like but
reporting bugs or like needing help regarding neopet issues
I like my dumb ass was like, please help.
I'm really scared about sixth grade.
What am I should I expect?
No, it was just one person there were several people and
they're like oh do not worry about male school It's high
school you have to worry about
oh my god oh it was so it was so embarrassing thinking back
to it oh they're like no trauma dumping child mom this is
new pets man and then i told the story in the roblox stream
but like i also there was like role play role play board on
neopets and because i wasn't a high schooler it's funny
because i i swear to god i'm pretty sure majority of the
people that were in the high school role play has never been
the high school before because i was just some middle school
role playing as a high school student like in those high
school boards we're like i'm like i was like oh i'm in like
10th i'm a sophomore and and i because they're like
imagining what high school could be for us just just faking
it so like there'll be like roleplay boards where you're
pretending you're high school students and then there's like
multiple versions of it it's like high school but like what
if we're like we all have powers so like mutants like x-men
high school roleplay or like or like um magical school high
school roleplay role play or a superhero high school role
play.
And then I would have like word documents, like word
documents I made on Microsoft Word of like character sheets
of like all these different like high schoolers, plus
warrior cats by the way.
I would have high schoolers and warrior cats with like
established character sheets and um powers and i'll be like
and then i would have like my intro pre-written um my intro
pre-written and everything so i could just copy and paste it
as a as it like to start the story of my character and it
would be like i wish i still have it so i could like cringe
at it i really It was, oh my god, I really do wish I still,
I still have it.
Oh, it's so fucking cringe, thinking back.
Oh my god.
I did that in Gaia Online.
The thing is, I was way too young for Gaia Online.
So like, Neal Pets was like the baby version of that.
The cringe is overwhelming.
I was way too young to use Gaia Online.
So like, there was a baby.
baby version for me for me this is giving me emotional
damage that wasn't prepared for oh and now i'm illiterate i
feel like i think i hit my peak um i definitely hit my peak
in terms of intelligence and writing um during that stage
and neopets and then everything else was downhill from there
like i i wrote a lot for neopets roleplay and then as i got
older i realized i i definitely got more and more stupid and
illiterate the older i got
oh my god holy i've been yapping for so long already i was
already an hour and 30 minutes?
Oh my god.
What did I miss?
You missed cringe dokey internet history.
It was pretty fucking cringe back then.
But who else wasn't like cringe?
But everybody was cringe back then.
Everybody was like super cringe back then.
Because we didn't know better.
I definitely should not have been talking to adults for
sure.
But like at the age I was.
I'm so we did not know what was safe for kids
People back then did not realize that it was sort of a bad
idea that we had like little dot a little dokey at talking
to fucking college students
Oh, I'm just thinking like I don't know why did they talk to
me
oh my god um um but yeah but it's from neopets because of
the boards on the neopet boards it led to me discovering
deviant art and then from deviant art it led to me
discovering like other stuff on the internet like from
deviant art to fanfiction.net to tumblr and to live the
moment the moment my parents faxed that parental permission
slip it was over for me it was so over i sped run my
internet cloud like i'm not into a cloud i sped run my
internet like uh intake i learned things on the internet at
an exponential rate because of that all because My parents
faxed in that parental permission slip and it went downhill
in the pipeline Neopets to new grounds that was not the way
it should go but But it did it fucking did oh my god oh my
god I also had like uh Wait let me see if I can uh find it I
also had like uh uh i like i started like liking videos on
to like as for like uh was it not intel what's the word for
like i guess like topics and stuff in the future so if i
find something funny and interesting oh my god did you guys
see the that fucking furby video of like to a couple this
couple made a Furby Adam not like a Furby robot.
Did you guys see that?
That shit was so fucking With the like Boston robots they
fucking took the Boston robots Dog robot and then turned it
into a freak of nature You guys haven't okay Okay, I'm gonna
fucking show you Show you this
look at this look at this abomination
no not that music okay the full video was so like it was
like this is like basically a super cut of that video i i
think the messed up part was when they were they wore the
fucking mask
oh my god when they wore the fucking mask and everything I
think that was the worst part we say progress if Furby was
released in 2030 instead of 1998 the legs broke what
technology that's what it was chat you wouldn't understand
we're progressing forward not backwards guys um anyway oh my
gosh oh that's it's been super fucking fun i i've been i'm
really enjoying i'm definitely really enjoying these
nighttime gaps i hope you guys have been enjoying it too
i've been enjoying just listening me talk about uh random
things tonight and i hope that i hope that i didn't ruin
your sleep by sending that video
i hope i hope i haven't been ruining your sleep because i
ended up sending the pervy video we're gonna be like okay we
were we were heading the right direction dokey now we're 50
steps behind now i'm never gonna sleep i'm sorry but like
okay i just want to say like one of my favorite videos okay
i'm pretty okay no i'm definitely gonna get copyright strike
if i played it on stream so i i i'm already getting like
limited ads i don't want more but oh my god wait i'm show
you guys what was it called.
This is like one of my favorite songs uh that I'm going to
show you guys okay.
I'm not gonna say it out loud uh uh this is one of my
favorite songs and I need to show you guys this uh where is
it okay I'm not I'm trying not to say it out loud to spoil
it this one.
I'm gonna pause my lo-fi thing real fast and I'm gonna mute
this.
I'll listen to it now.
Guys, this is one of my favorite.
Please play.
Too late.
I'm doomed in this midnight here.
Oh, and George, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
I love this.
This is one of my favorites.
Honestly, if I, instead of ending the, instead of ending the
night with, um, instead of ending the night with Furby, I'm
gonna end the night with Crash Bandicoot.
I'll sing along to it too for you guys People are gonna be
so confused We're not watching the video I got so obsessed
with this song That would like I kept like Whying
I would like It just like hit me I'll be like Wow Wow Wow
Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow
Wow Sweets thanks for the morning dokey.
I'm off to work.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Oh wow wow wow
wow wow wow wow I remember when I first watched this video I
just kept wowing like I would just be like wow
I was like so obsessed.
I don't know why I oh my gosh.
I think I'm I'm so special.
I think I think there's there's something wrong with me.
I would quote this too.
I would quote this video a lot.
You're like but Doki what is there to quote exactly?
I was I was definitely very special.
I don't know why I was quoting this video but I was quoting
this.
video for some reason.
Whoa.
Anyway.
Anyway, guys.
I'm going to call it here.
I hope you guys have a good night, everybody.
I hope you guys sleep well.
And good morning to everybody on the other side of the
world.
As always, everyone, stay hydrated.
Posture check.
Get up and move around to get that blood flowing.
And if you stay up for me, head to bed.
Because you deserve it.
I'll see you guys next time, everybody.
Bye, guys.
Bye.