Hello everybody!
Hello, hello!
They couldn't hear you because I had Discord muted by the
way, now they can.
Hello guys.
So first off, at first I was waiting for Gumi.
You didn't download the game!
I said at first, you didn't let me finish the sentence!
It's okay.
It's it.
Anyway, at first, I was waiting for Gumi before I got really
interrupted.
Anyway, and then, and then I realized I didn't install the
game.
I thought, I thought she would take a little longer so I can
use that as an excuse for a bit longer but i told you 10
minutes and i joined at 10 minutes no no no no you okay no
no wait you did i misremembered i thought you said 15
minutes so i thought it doesn't matter i apparently needed
20 minutes to install 44 gigabytes by the way holy why is
this game 44 gigabytes why is this game so huge we literally
talked about how it's 15 hours long yeah it's yeah but like
there's aren't that like aren't that long that isn't like 44
gigabytes it's a fucking long it's a huge game but anyway it
took me 20 minutes to install install and it takes two we
were talked earlier on we were talking about um how we don't
want this child because in Gumi's words in Gumi's words she
thinks are kids ugly.
I never said that!
Then why did you want this child?
What the hell?
I don't want you.
You said the child's ugly!
Dude, the child with one cereal and cereal is $8.
You didn't even know it was $8 until I told you it was $8.
You were able to buy the cereal and looking at the price.
This is why we're getting a divorce.
You don't look at prices.
No, it's just I don't buy cereal.
I don't.
You don't look at prices.
I look at prices.
I just don't eat cereal.
Yeah.
Then why did you buy cereal for a child?
Oh, but if she wants it because I'm a good parent but if
she, I don't want her.
Okay.
All of us say a good parent wouldn't say I don't want her.
that's that is bro.
Are you really I'd say you're a good parent after that.
Yeah, you're winning this case.
You're winning this case.
You can have her.
Hey, you can have her.
I mean, no, no, wait, wait, wait.
No, you're trying to purposely be a bad mom so the court
wouldn't give you the child.
That's fucked up.
That you wanted the child, not me.
Wait.
Who's playing husband?
Who's playing wife?
I'm playing a husband.
Okay.
Who's going to be playing the husband if you look at us?
I'm pretty sure you don't have a big dick.
I'm sending you a photo of mine too.
Hey guys, do you guys wanna see the picture?
Discord, upload a file.
Guys, do you guys wanna see the picture?
I'm gonna send her.
All right, I'm sending you this.
I'm sending you this.
I think that's a chat, but...
Wait, I am not...
I think mine is biggie!
Mine is bigger, but yours is fat!
Yours is attached!
Mine is part of the body.
It is not part of the body!
That's a rat!
Guys, this is part of the body.
This is my...
It's a fucking rat!
Don't say that about him!
He gets sensitive.
I know you're working through it, but...
I'll get sensitive.
Don't say that.
He's gonna... He's gonna retract.
He's gonna shrivel up.
He's gonna shrivel up now.
You hurt his feelings.
You're gonna hurt his feelings.
Good.
Mine is bigger than if it shrivels up.
Yours isn't real.
It's not biologic.
Biological.
Hey, if I glue it on, if I glue it on somehow, it's gonna be
real.
It's not biological.
It's made of plastic.
Okay, for those of you guys who really want to know...
I made of plastic.
Okay, Gumi, why don't you explain what photo you sent me?
I sent her dick and chew.
Can you say that again?
I said...
Can you elaborate?
I v.
Gumiho sent Doki Bird Dikachu.
He elaborate what that is.
It is a Pikachu with a huge strap on.
Okay.
By the way, guys, this is one of her favorite pictures that
she has in her folder she seven years and that that helps my
that does not defend you that literally helps my case she
has this photo for set i've seen this photo so many times
because she loves this photo so much we've been friends for
more than eight years now and i have i've seen dickachu for
a while now it's so good it's such a good first It's so good
Alright Okay Apparently my sound guy was like You gotta turn
Gumi down a little bit Sound guy Sound guy Okay Okay How
about Nico treatment How about now?
Alright Anyway guys This is gonna be like The true
friendship test Between Gumi and I Because we've been
friends for more than 8 Gumi you know you're not gonna be
You're gonna be screaming that in like go me if i turn you
up right now because you talk like that you're gonna be
screaming in the next like 10 minutes like yeah all right so
by the way later on apparently that's me i was not ready you
son of a bitch that's me it's a cut scene you don't have to
be ready i love cut scenes and you don't
I was like, don't search dick-a-chew in Google.
Yes, if there's a dick in front of dick-a-chew, don't search
it.
Well, you're British?
That is you.
That is so you.
You're British, too!
No, I'm not.
I can't do any accents!
Oh, fuck, you're right.
Oh, fuck you're right.
Oh, my God, our child is...
Is she okay?
What?
What is she doing?
Why is she watching?
dude that was me that was me in fourth grade did i tell you
the story in fourth grade when i was a kid yeah um i got a
bad report card so my family uh told me i wasn't allowed to
be in a room with any working electronics so i was locked in
a dark room basically and i played with what the lights were
allowed to be on but like i played like get out get out that
Anyways, I played with Clay the entire summer and I think
that's what like broke me month Wait, that was your breaking
point?
Yeah, no, I used to be like the stereotypical like quiet
girl in school.
But then, um...
There's no way you were like that.
Playing with Clay, I'm talking to Clay all summer.
Did they have a name?
Does he have a name?
No, I made like different Clay monsters.
Oh!
Pokemon.
They were my OC's, if you will.
You know your original characters do not steal.
You know we love you.
Mm-hmm.
Your mom doesn't love you, apparently.
That means that...
Okay.
Your dad actually doesn't want you.
Neither of us wants you.
We're trying to say we're sending you away to Harry Styles.
The Harry Styles?
We're fucking...
Harry Styles What do you mean?
Okay, yeah, but where is Harry Styles as a location?
Yeah, yeah, of course.
No, we're sending her to Harry Styles!
The person!
Oh shit, you know Harry Styles?
Yeah, I don't like that.
I call him Harry, actually.
Actually, I call him Harhar.
Wait, what the fuck is that bird thing on her poster?
Bro, she's so spoiled.
What bird thing?
Dragon?
Yeah, no.
Bro, this girl is so spoiled.
This girl has a room that's like twice as big as my room.
Oh, fuck!
She lives in a fucking barn?
I would...
Whoa!
No, it's just...
That's not a barn.
It's like...
It's like when like...
Like suburban areas have like those... Oh, no, this is a
farm.
Never mind.
It's a different body.
This is a farm.
That I saw the milk.
and stay Dr. Hakeem, you have to help me now.
What the fuck, Dr. Hakeem?
Together.
But where did she get her British?
Oh, her mom.
Okay, I was going to say, where did the little girl get his
British accent?
That shows I take better care of her because she took after
my accent.
Yeah, because someone has to work and make money for this
family.
I'm a doctor!
I'm literally a doctor!
You don't know, we don't know that.
For real?
You could be pretending, you could just say you're a doctor
and then like just go out to the bar some shit that seems
like a gloomy thing or two honey i have to go to work now
it's 9 p.m yeah it was an emergency call yeah the horses
need help i'm a horse doctor by the way you said you were a
chicken doctor yesterday girl i call me mr worldwide i'd be
all over the world and fixing everything.
That's us.
Does that mean we can't die now that we're dolls?
Maybe.
Yo, the little girl is pretty impressive.
How the fuck did she make a doll with like puppets?
With like crochet and wood.
Did she like carve that herself?
This looks handmade.
Yeah.
Oh, she's pretty talented.
That's our child.
Dude, our place is a mess.
No wonder I'm divorcing you.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It was my fault that the barn's not clean enough.
You literally say you work in the farm and at the barn.
No, no, no, no.
I say I work.
I didn't say I clean the barn.
What the?
Can't keep your workplace clean.
Dude, this guy makes me uncomfortable.
The book of love.
Dude, he has a butt chin.
Oh my god, he does.
Oh, it's not his lip.
Oh my god, you did jump.
Killing myself in game.
Oh shit, we can't die!
We can't die!
Exactly.
Oh my god.
Mr. Um, he's creepy.
I would never want to talk to this guy.
Hey, this could be our, uh, third husband.
Yeah.
We're, uh, divorcing third.
This everyone is Omen from Valorant, obviously.
Wait a minute.
Third.
I promise your daughter to fix your marriage.
How the fuck do you promise our daughter anything?
Why would you- girl wait wait a minute excuse me sir but why
are you talking to our daughter what all right this is me
I'm left okay X is we're using controller right well let's
find a way all right we gotta when you said you're left I'm
left.
So I guess it's just like I'm left.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think so.
Yeah.
All right.
We gotta turn on this lever.
Oh my god.
Be a deer.
Be a deer and help me turn on this lever.
Well, you know you're talking to me about that.
Goomy.
How do I punch?
Turn on this lever.
Whoa.
Ew.
They're alive.
What is going on here?
I have no clue.
But whatever's going on, we can't lower that staircase
without those fuses.
But those fuses?
They just...
They just ran away!
I mean, did you see them on their little fuse legs?
Worry about that later.
Let's just bring them back.
Wait, we had to bring them back?
Then what's the point of, like...
Okay, do we work?
Oh, wait.
Oh, no, it's just two.
We already got two of them.
That's the easiest puzzles ever.
Yep.
Last one.
Yeah, but do we have to do it together?
Yeah, we don't even have to do this together.
Only one of us has to do this.
Okay, A, okay, A, B.
Where the fuck?
Oh, it teaches us to control us.
It's like Mega Man.
You know what?
I don't even need to do this.
You can do this yourself.
I'll just wait here.
I don't like the sound of that.
Girl, I literally need you.
Look at this shit.
Oh shit.
Okay.
I didn't know at first I was like it was like one guy Come
on you're strong enough for that you don't need me
Come on what happened to all the horses?
Girl, I'm not carrying them.
What happened to all the horses?
Yeah, but don't you have to like, you know, like What the
fuck is that sound?
Do you hear that?
What is that?
I think it was the door.
No, there was something.
There was a little grumble sound.
Is it one of your horses?
This is why they're divorced.
Look, that's why we're trying to get divorced right now.
Wait, toggle sprint.
Oh, okay.
We got to press that.
Oh.
Wait.
How do we get there?
Oh!
There's a wood.
There's a wood over here.
There's a wood over there.
Alright.
Look at that, see?
Look at this teamwork.
And then we jump.
Wait, oh shit, I'm dead.
Wait, what?
Oh, okay, this is why you're the doctor.
And I'm the farm boy.
Yeah.
This is why you do all the thinking for us here.
I'm the- Oh.
Sorry.
I'm like the...
Oh, what the fuck, X?
Yeah, I'm like the...
I'm like the...
The arm here.
I'm the muscle.
You're like the arm here?
I'm the muscle!
Wait, how did you get there?
Oh, this way.
I'm the muscle!
What do you do?
Let's check it out.
That's why... Oh, okay, I did it!
You're welcome, sir.
Sweetie Hey, I think we have to do something back here.
What do you mean?
Not for long I mean our daughter's trying to fix our
relationship right now.
What you don't want our daughter to fix our relationship?
Hey, man, I'll throw the shit off the cliff.
Do it.
Do it pussy.
You won't do it.
Yeah, that's fucking right Oh, fuck
What the fuck is that?
Do you see that shit?
What?
Wait, what?
See what?
It's looking at us.
What is?
On top of the bucket, look!
Where is she?
Where?
On the bucket!
Look!
Where?
I think you're going crazy.
Just ignore the glowing eye.
I think...
Yeah, we just ignore the glowing eye.
My bad.
Oh, my head's too big.
Give me a sec.
Sorry.
star all my brain give me a sec apparently my head is too
big okay what do you mean joke what do you mean joke huh
okay there's a reason why i'm the doctor yeah are you trying
to say people who work in the barn are stupid is that what
you're trying to say no i'm just saying i'm than you and my
brain's bigger.
I don't know.
Look at the head size.
Well, what kind of brain can be stored in that tiny head of
yours?
Girl, sometimes I'll be hearing you shake your head and it
sounds like a baby rattle.
No.
Dude, get this guy away from our kid.
Yeah, get out of the way.
I need to go and talk to my daughter.
Your daughter?
Oh, you talk like you own her.
Oh, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
We don't own people anymore.
Whoa, it's 2024.
Hey, explain Powell World.
Explain Powell World.
That they're not people.
Oh, except for those people.
Except for- Why do I recognize your voice?
What the fuck?
No, we, uh, we've never met.
Sorry.
Looks a bit like a vacuum cleaner.
Oh yeah.
Because it is your vacuum cleaner.
Is that a vacuum cleaner?
Vacuum?
It's not my job.
Dude, imagine putting some vacuum.
You know, the guy could suck up all kinds of crap in your
stomach.
Oh, ha, no, that's, uh...
That's you!
You've ruined my bowels with all that crap.
That's your purpose, though.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh!
Ew!
Oh, God!
Is that dirt?
You call that just Well, I mean, you know, some of it
It's... So that's why it broke down It was your fault It's a
vacuum cleaner Fix me Thank you Instead, you put me away for
life in here Oh Look at what you fucking did Oh, shit!
We got consumed Mmm Mmmmm Eww Oh, God.
I hate throw up.
That's a lie.
You have two emotes dedicated to it.
I should have never made that bet with you.
We got bored.
Ew.
Oh, God.
Please just take us to the math part.
That is our strong point.
We're collabing right now.
Yeah.
I don't like that he's like humping the air kind of like
he's on that.
Look at him.
Wait, did he like flex his hips at us?
Yeah, he did.
I think we're getting closer because of our hate of this
guy.
Yeah, I think he is fixing our marriage.
Yeah, look, it is fixable.
I didn't know we'd end up in a place where all vacuum
cleaners alive.
Well, now we are.
Maybe we're stuck here forever.
Forever no way.
We're getting a divorce.
I know we're getting a divorce
What if we both just like go separate ways like do we really
have to yeah We just walk away from each other?
Yeah, like what if we just decide to stay dolls forever?
Yeah, yeah, what if we just decide that what the fuck what
the fuck is that music?
That's bad, bad water.
Hey, have you ever thought about jumping?
There's a fucking eyeball!
Have you ever thought about jumping?
Alright, I'll race you to the finish line!
I'm up.
Hey, I'm already gone.
What the fuck?
How do we do this?
It's not this way.
It's not that way.
It's the other way.
Oh, wait, you have to move it.
No, you have to move it.
to move it okay hey yes oh you bitch you fucking bitch this
is exactly why we're getting a divorce this is exactly why
we're getting a divorce i hope we try to stay dolls forever
i i hope we stay dolls forever and get eaten by a cat
That's taking right- I said it!
I fucking said it!
What are you gonna do about it?
How you can't do jack shit?
You're a doll!
I hope- what the fuck?
I hope you get shit off by a bird.
Whoa!
Hey, I'll wait for you.
Wait, why does it have a thinking over there too?
Oh, nice.
Okay, I have to do this.
What does that do?
I don't know.
Oh, right.
The current has reversed.
Oh, it reversed.
So you have to do the thing on the other side.
Okay, no.
Like, on the other side, you pick it up.
And then, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then you put it up.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, see, you're going to let me tell you what to do.
Man moment.
See, I don't miss the hole.
Because I'm not a man.
It was one time!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh shit, what the fuck is this?
Get in.
You bitch!
My head slipped!
Whoa, hey, look!
Oh, I'm gonna punch you.
Hey, oh, good.
Don't worry, I'll help you.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
No!
Wait, what the fuck is this?
Do it.
Just press the button!
There you go.
See?
Look at that.
I sack him.
Go to the next one, you bitch!
Oh, whoops.
Sorry.
Husband moment.
Go to the next one!
I'm trying!
Duncan!
I am!
I did the thing!
I'm going to be working with you.
all right but give me go this is why i'm first how long is
this freaking vacuum i don't know it's pretty long whoa wait
am i gonna make it i think i made it i made it see look i
didn't miss the hole i didn't miss the hole this time yeah
this is why we only have one kid
Hey!
Thank God.
Thank God we only traumatized one child.
It's alright.
Only one kid will have to pay for therapy.
I'm not paying for it.
She's gonna pay for it herself.
What the fuck?
Okay, I'm dead.
What happened to you?
I don't know.
Someone was trying to jump and I thought she was doing the
right thing.
Oh wow you couldn't even make that jump I made it man You
know you had to you got to grip onto the side to make it
That's not making a jump If you barely made it it's not
making a jump What the fuck why did you fucking
Okay no no no I fucked up I fucked up I fucked up I didn't
realize Homi Homi I can't grip on this You need a...
Alright, now, now pull...
Yes, okay, now keep...
Now keep spinning it.
There you go.
Good.
Does that mean I can leave you now?
What the fuck?
Well, I'm not the one with the third husband.
Hey, no need to be jealous of Omen, man.
Oh, I actually jumped off it.
You know, what they say about marriage to death do us part
what what did that mean you know i think you know why we're
getting a divorce
Do you do this?
Get in there!
You get in there!
Wow!
Look at me!
You fucking bitch!
I'm not even doing anything!
That's just you!
Swap it!
Oh, there it is!
I saw it!
It swaps!
There you go!
God!
How do you go non-verbal?
You have to go non- Oh no, we have to do this too.
Okay.
Goomy, remember all the good times we've had?
Go.
Goomy, remember all the...
You missed that job!
How do we tie him up?
It's because I don't trust you that I'm double jumping.
What do we do here?
Oh, what the... get on the Roombas.
There we go.
Okay, let's go.
We're such good friends.
Friends.
We have to stay friends after the voice for our child.
I only do that to X I like.
All right.
Wait, where's the other end of this though?
Wait, but where do we, do I just like go here?
No.
It doesn't make sense.
Where does the end of that vacuum go?
Oh, I get sucked in in here.
But you could have said something.
Hey, listen.
Every day's a school day.
You learn more and more every day.
You could have said something.
Alright, here you go.
What's this?
I turned out the light.
I don't know what it does.
Why did you turn it back on?
Wait, you don't trust my judge.
We're trying to save electricity here.
Girl, I'm trying to take every cent of your money.
Whoa!
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
I thought we signed a prenup.
Wait, you didn't sign the prenup?
I wrote down Kaza's name instead.
That's fucked up.
That is fucked up.
That is actually illegal.
Wait, did you just admit that you committed fraud on my
stream?
No, hey, no.
Hey, I think one of us had to press the...
You know what to do.
Agumi, you know what to do.
Come on.
You don't trust me?
Okay, that's on you.
That's actually...
I didn't trust you.
Go, go.
Okay, I'm going.
There, see?
Oh, you don't trust me.
Wow.
I'm going to do this.
What?
I'm sending over a platform, man.
How is that a platform?
It's this!
This was a platform!
Oh!
Oh, okay, I see it now.
I'm a little special.
But you like that.
You fucking whore.
Hey.
Oh, get on that.
No, you get on it.
You get on it.
You're pissing me off.
Okay.
I'll do it this time.
Sorry, I didn't know where to go.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't know where to go.
You didn't tell me where to go.
I need someone to tell me what to do.
You didn't aim it high enough.
Maybe you should do this.
Yay.
but clearly i'm not good at aiming you should know with the
in the bathroom i should have known you should have known in
the bathroom what are you doing oh you go up yeah i'm kind
of smart or something what do we do from here oh oh i go
inside wait where are you where did you go where are you oh
like this yeah all right i'm doing it the whole i'm doing it
i'm doing it well you have to aim too what do you mean i
have to aim i'm sending it to you i'm doing it i'm doing it
i think i'm doing it am i doing it i don't think i'm doing
oh am i i'm doing it i'm I can aim!
Oh, I'm making it a little bit dirty.
You're gonna have to clean that up later.
What the fuck?
I'm the perfect husband.
Oh, then we push.
Oh, talk about dead weight.
Yeah.
That's you, right?
What?
I don't even have a death counter.
Uh-oh.
Is that first boss fight?
It's ugly!
You bought that vacuum!
I didn't think it had fucking googly eyes!
No, I glued that on because I thought it looked cute.
Oh my gosh, she just liked me for real.
I can fix you!
That's why you married me!
Oh, I'm an engineer.
Oh!
You're an engineer, doctor?
Yeah.
me yeah we're supposed to take my life
damn that's harsh man you're a you're replaceable that's why
she's trying to replace me with a better husband What?
I'll show you who's the best sucker.
How the fuck do we defeat him?
I thought we had to throw it back or some shit.
Yeah, it's right here.
What do you mean?
I'm literally doing my job.
Girl, what is that?
What?
What do you mean?
That's a hit.
That's a fucking hit.
Ow.
Okay.
Look, if you can't do this, you can't platform.
Girl, did you get hit earlier?
No.
Are you aimed then?
If you're so good.
I'm sucking it.
It's too late.
I'm sucking it too.
Look, see?
Look!
I hit him!
This is the fucking easiest platform game ever.
What the fuck?
Just run!
You can't fucking throw forever!
See?
Oh shit.
I think you can go forever.
No, no, it's fine.
It's fine.
No, you can't.
See, look.
You got tired.
Alright, I'll be at the bottom.
Okay, I'll let you do the work at the top.
Okay, really?
Ow, I got hit.
I fucked up.
Look, I'm sucking!
There you go, there you go, it's coming in, it's coming in!
That's so easy.
Bro, we can't...
How are we supposed to get a speedrun if they're fucking
making us do all this other shit?
I'm pretty sure there's gotta be an exploit or something,
right?
There has to be.
This is the slowest boss battle ever.
Alright
Okay, I can't suck anymore.
I can't suck anymore.
It's the limit.
It's my limit.
Oh Shit I'm okay I'm okay.
Oh, I don't know.
Why didn't you care about me getting hurt?
And the fuck that you're into my run
Suck it!
I'm sucking!
Yeah.
Yeah, I kind of did all that damage.
I don't know what we're talking about.
Hey, I'm back.
Oh, man.
Look, your husband was gone, but you didn't care.
Oh, wow!
Wow!
You didn't even notice?
She's already moved on so fast!
Time to finish this!
How do we finish this?
Can we just...
Oh no!
Her eyeballs!
Oh, that is so fucked up!
Do you think this is too much?
Kind of.
But he tried to kill us.
Oh my god!
Bro!
What is wrong with you?
Ah!
with you oh he's gonna eat his eye
that's up that's up oh my god imagine dying like that well
this was your idea no we both did it i was peer pressure
what why did she make them look like us because you're never
home well why didn't you tell me about them i'm never home
i'm the one that knew about it suppose so well come on let's
find her where are we that's up yeah you were never home use
this place get away from me hey loser i'm getting closer i'm
getting closer i'm getting closer of reality how hey your
husband drowned yeah no new yeah you need my help you can't
you i have to be here unfortunately dude why the fuck is she
still in here playing on her own rose you have no other toys
you can look at her that's crazy this is their only toy I'm
gonna get over there now.
What?
What the fuck is that?
Who was it?
I know the way.
What the hell is that?
I'll take you there if you- Is that a hammer?
Yeah, it is!
My tool friends!
We used to be important and taken care of.
But that human locked us up in her toolbox and left.
Yeah, that human.
Our daughter?
No, you!
You!
oh i heard that heartless woman got a new job in town and
doesn't have time for our hobbies anymore who cares about
hobbies do you know how painful it is to die from rust yeah
you heartless woman what the i don't like its eyes you just
don't like eyes in general only if you can get us to rose
over there okay it's a deal pick me up oh go to that big
door over there i don't even think i want to touch him.
I wonder if you can, like, poke his eyes out.
Okay.
What is... What's going on there?
Where did it go?
What?
How is he on my back?
Whoa!
Oh, you're like that guy from Guiding to the Galaxy?
Yeah, I have the whistle power.
Yeah.
Oh, nice.
I bet you can't whistle.
That's me.
I did that.
That was me.
Do you like my whistle?
Stop!
What are you doing?
Why are you having this?
I can't do anything.
Stop!
Go ahead.
get away get away of course i'm the one that aims what are
you supposed to do oh like this
okay maybe like wait what are you doing i think you have to
jump down Go on to the other side.
No, go on the other side.
Go on the other side.
You said jump down.
Oh.
Okay.
I figured it out.
Gumi.
Okay.
So you do that.
Oh, keep doing that.
Gumi.
I figured it out.
I know how to solve this puzzle.
And that's how you do it.
You're welcome.
This is why I'm the brains.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Your savior is here now.
Ready now?
What the fuck?
You're five.
But how do I get across?
Can I just swing from this?
Oh, can you throw your nail here?
Oh, okay.
What the fuck?
Okay.
You suck at this game.
What do you mean?
You suck at the game, too!
Why didn't you make them jump already?
Why do you need so much prep time?
Why do you need so much prep time, huh?
It's called momentum!
If you were an engineer, you would know that!
But I'm not.
You're the one that settled with a farm boy.
Throw the buggy nail.
Where?
Oh, there.
Sorry, I'm done.
Dude, do I have to wait for it to load a bit?
One?
I don't know.
I think I have to wait for the wheel to complete.
The wheel?
No.
Yeah, it has a small wheel on it.
Oh!
Here, have a second nail.
Can I get that second nail?
I got two nails!
Okay.
Nice.
Look, see, we're working together like a good couple.
Why is this?
Why do we do this here?
Oh, wait, maybe...
Oh, wait, what?
Oh, you have to hammer that.
Oh, it's my turn.
No, no, you have to come back here.
No, you have to come here.
Okay.
Throw in the hole.
Okay, so what I think is that I have to throw it into a hole
after you do that.
See, that's what you do.
So when you hammer...
Yeah, so when you hammer it, I got...
I'm throwing it into the hole.
You're lucky I was here to help you.
I think I'm lucky to have you here.
You're so lucky.
You son of a bitch!
You have to come down here!
How was I supposed to know you didn't make it?
Look at the other screen!
You're trying to...
Why would I look at the other screen?
This is your business.
Like...
Nice.
Thank you.
Whoa.
God.
I hate him.
Yeah, leave us alone!
We're trying to fix our marriage!
And it's going really well.
Right?
Um...
Oh, that's kind of cute.
And you will find the challenge you see.
Do we have to do the challenge?
We're not completionists.
I don't know.
Oh!
I think we have to.
Well, I guess we're gonna have to.
Alright, you want to give it a try?
We haven't got time for this.
Oh, are you afraid of losing?
Me?
No way.
Bring it on.
Oh, I'm gonna bring it.
This isn't a competition, Gumi.
Score it by staying up wait no wait a minute go ahead ready
up no wait a minute go ahead ready up oh no i don't know i
mean we don't have to no no no you know yeah ready up i'm
ready look i'm shaking my hips on the screen no come on can
we we've been we've been such good friends
Where am i gonna go
Oh, no, hey, you're pretty bad
this you're not even gaining points either you're pretty bad
this is not gonna lie neither one of us is getting any
points because you're not staying up it don't have to ow i
think i went from fault like how do i gain points i don't
understand you you getting played with did you not read the
rules that's not I can't stay up for life yeah because I'm a
god gamer it's not fair the game is actually rigged like
this game is actually rigged this is not fair this is like a
not fair.
This game is so rigged.
This is fucked up.
This is so fucked up.
Oh, you got a point!
How?
How did I get a point?
There should be like a cool down.
What the fuck?
How did I even get this boy?
I don't know.
Please.
Thank you.
Give me another point.
I hate this.
I got one.
Oh, I got another.
No!
This is fucked up.
This is like so geared up towards the hammer there's no way
there's no fucking way oh what do you say can you throw your
nail somewhere i don't think so oh oh no here i can yeah
there you go you're welcome okay here you go it's time for
you to do your job hey why but to my other nail Did you not
grab it back?
No, I don't think I get it back.
I think I have to, like, take it and then, like, do it
really fast.
Yeah, I have to do that.
Oh, wait.
You don't even need me.
Yeah, I don't.
You have to do over there.
Uh.
Oh, here, here, here.
Oh, wait, what?
No.
What do I do?
Stay here?
Oh, okay.
Don't worry.
I figured it out.
You're welcome.
And then...
Oops.
Oh, I got two nails!
Oh.
Alright.
And then...
She left it way back where she pulled it out of the platform
early.
I think you're supposed to have three nails.
I'm supposed to have three nails?
Yeah, I think you're supposed to have...
three nails.
No, no, no, no.
I have two nails.
No, no, no.
I have two nails now.
Oh, you have it now?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, okay.
And then I do it here.
Yeah, I'm good.
Um.
Oh, okay.
I thought I was gonna be stuck forever.
I thought I actually soft-locked myself.
Oh, what's this?
Oh, we got to go here.
Oh, it's a game for us.
What the heck is that?
Yeah, what is that?
Flip the switch?
What do I do here?
Shoot at...
Use your hammers on a target to score.
Oh!
Wait, where's the target, though?
This is not fair.
Like...
You just have to hammer, I have to aim.
I think you're gonna be sick!
Oh god!
Yeah!
FBS bitch!
That's what you like.
Okay, I had to run towards that bitch.
It's like playing towards your hammer only.
I have to aim with a controller.
I'm not a controller player.
I have to run.
I have to aim.
What happened to your- I have to aim.
You don't have to aim when they- You don't need to have to
aim with a hammer.
Yeah.
My god.
You have to aim at that.
You have to aim at it.
Okay?
Yeah!
You have to aim!
Cody, don't screw this up.
Are you gonna...
Cody, don't screw this up!
Yeah, yeah, just get to jump.
Yeah.
You're welcome.
Pull it back.
There you go, you're welcome.
Yeah, oh, you're not patient.
You have to be patient.
There you go.
See?
We gotta be patient there.
You trust me?
You didn't say yes or no.
You didn't answer back.
Nice one!
Chissed me off.
Why?
I asked you if you trusted me.
You didn't say anything!
How was I supposed to do?
Oh, what the fuck?
Okay, you have to, like, I have to aim it so that you...
I don't think you can make that, actually.
You have to go through another cycle.
The more I got you.
You trust me?
I didn't realize.
You have to...
Wait, how do you get in here?
hit over there.
Do you have to land up here?
Oh!
Oh, what?
Wait, what?
I have to jump early.
I have to go early.
Oh, okay.
So it wasn't my fault.
Oh, but, okay.
Oh, whoops.
Wait, where are you?
Oh, it's here.
I'm here now.
Oh, there you go.
What the fuck?
How do I...
Oh, I got three nails.
Oh, I fell down.
But how do I get out of here?
Is there anything on your side?
How do I get out of this?
Oh, I can jump?
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I needed the boost.
nice I'm here okay oh this is easy all right and then oh
okay and then I do this jump no you have to do this no you
have to do the other one oh cuz I have to wall jump yeah
okay so like what I figured out is that I have to do and
then yeah and then I do that and then And then I put this
back here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, and then I do that.
And then...
Look at that.
God, I'm so good at this game.
And then...
Bam.
Nice.
I'm so smart.
Damn, she just liked me for real.
Look, we're...
Do we have good teamwork?
I don't know about that.
The book said so!
And you want to trust that book?
Yeah!
Okay, I mean...
I mean, he complimented me, unlike some people.
You get him when you deserve it.
What did I deserve?
Oh, what the fuck?
What the fuck?
That's his friend.
That's his best friend.
It doesn't look like your friend's happy.
Oh.
We have a...
Wow.
Hang in there cool buddies.
We're coming to save you.
Whoa, wait, he's shooting at us.
Oh, we have to run forward.
We have to run forward.
It's parkour.
I'm still alive.
You got this.
Do this for us.
Do this for our child.
You have to be here!
I believe.
I'm here now.
What do we do?
Oh, I have to go here.
I'm on the other side!
What do I do from here?
Oh, I have to do this.
Wait, but what about you?
Will you ever be able to come back?
Is there something you can stick here?
I don't know.
I guess I'll just Do I just wait here for you?
Oh, I think I should have helped you No, yes, you don't need
me
You didn't need me You didn't need me I'm dead I'm coming
back Oh my god, I have to run all the way back Give me a
sec, I'm coming back Give me a sec.
I'm coming over.
Don't worry, honey.
There you go.
You're welcome.
There, see?
I did it.
I'm doing it.
All right.
hammer this.
Oh.
That's my bad.
I pressed the wrong input.
Just don't die like me.
I never died.
You have to put a nail in it, don't you?
Just you have to hammer it first.
You're going to put a nail in it from far.
No, it's fine.
See, you still made it.
You still made it.
Look, you're just making this harder for us.
Run.
What about our speed run?
I'm speed riding.
I'm running.
Put it out.
Push out.
Put it down.
I'm trying.
Now I know why we're getting a divorce.
I know why.
I'm feeling like why.
Now I know why.
Dude, it's Transformer.
Bro, I thought he liked his friends.
Yeah, I think this guy Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa I think this guy
lied Ow, okay I'll put a nail Go, go, go, go, go, go, go I
did everything I can Bro, I don't think this guy Wants him
to be friends with him anymore
Oh, what's he gonna do?
Smash you with the shovel?
Oh, he flipped you off Oh, he flipped you off Oh, we can't
suck the eyes off of...
Whoa!
Wait, why isn't that tool...
Why doesn't that tool have eyes?
He's cutting holes in the floor.
Oh, I don't like that.
Wait.
Where the fuck is the...
Can I just, like...
Ow!
Okay, don't worry, I can do this.
I was caught by surprise.
Wait, do I have to, like...
Oh, he's coming, he's swiping, he's swiping!
Throw your nails!
I'm throwing!
Your fucking thick head blocked my nails!
Okay, here we go.
We're good, we're good, we're good.
Keep hammering, keep hammering!
You did it!
He doesn't have an arm anymore!
Oh!
Oh shit!
Holy...
Oh my god, you're so cute!
Flexible, what the fuck?
I know, I can do this quick.
Because yoga lessons paid off.
Oh.
Oh, he angie.
He angie now.
Oh, what the hell?
Oh, he's very angie.
How do I...
Um...
Don't worry, I dodged it.
Dodged.
I'm gaming.
Oh, oh, he's on you.
I just sat in here.
Oh, shit!
Oh, it's on you.
Oh, no, no, no, it would have passed down to you, though.
I was trying to...
Heather!
Get on!
I need...
We need to close it!
That's why I married you!
I hear you're the one that's supposed to yell the context
clues.
Hover, hover, hover!
Get on!
Dude, you suck!
You didn't tell me the context clues!
That's what marriage is about!
I don't need to know what marriage is about!
You're supposed to tell me the context clues!
Look, him, look, this is not my fault, look, marriage is
like a teamwork, and there was, there is no I in T-Gummy.
There is no, really, there's no I, I have to do quite a bit
of communication here.
There's no I, I don't know, I don't feel like I understood
the context clues in, in, don't Where was my context clues
again?
Don't die, don't die, don't die, don't die!
Hammer, hammer, hammer!
There you go.
Are you happy?
Are you happy now?
I got two.
Oh my god, our floor!
Our floor!
It's okay, it won't cut everything!
Ray?
Um...
See, I told you!
I can't cut everything!
Okay, that's on you.
I swear to God.
Where's my fucking wife?
There you go.
Easy
Nice you see we did it teamwork.
Why do the other tools not have eyes?
Eww oh god
I don't like that at all
You saved us from that bro They're all blind.
You are a true hero.
Yeah, I'm a true hero.
Wait, what about me?
I did all the work!
Did you see that explosion?
Anyway, we still have to get to Rose.
Oh, of course, of course.
We did all the work together.
They have to get to the other side.
Ew.
Step on board.
Really?
Sure.
Come on, it's safe.
Okay.
Yeah, it does not feel safe at all.
Don't worry.
He's very precise.
I don't think that's how physics work.
Oh
no!
She's leaving!
Rose, wait!
Rose, look down!
Gamers, look down!
What the fuck, asshole?
What the fuck?
Bro!
The moment we turn into human form, we burn the book.
For real.
And we never buy books for a child again.
Oh, wait, pause.
Learning was a mistake.
Okay, that's why I'm the engineer.
They turn into dolls, and now she questions the science?
It's true.
Oh, we can skate now.
I'm a skater boy.
Oh, jump.
I fucked up.
How far is this fucking thing?
Woo!
It's like Tony Hawk.
Skater boy.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
How long is this?
There's another one.
There's another one
Oh my god, I'm almost there I almost caught up to you all
right.
Oh my god.
I have to wait for you I always caught up to you.
Don't worry.
Here I am.
Okay, stay right there.
Stay right there
Hello, I'm with you There you go.
You're welcome I turn it on Wait Go..
You?
You wait right here.
Okay, you wait right here.
This one's the shorter path, okay?
You turn not off when I get over there.
Okay.
Okay?
Okay, go over there...
Go over there!
I'm heading over!
Boom!
You're welcome.
Okay, how about you wait...
How about you wait next to the start?
How about you go back?
I'm going!
I'm here I'm here I'm here I fell down I did yay I pressed
it whoa we're so coordinated look at us this is why we're a
couple I died I died I need you back Wait!
Oh wait, thank you.
I don't... Wait, I can just let you do everything and I can
just respawn next to you.
What?
Yeah?
Do you need me for that?
Do you need me?
I think I need you.
Oh, okay, I'm here now.
I'm here.
Wait, we goomy carry, goomy and dokey carry.
Oh, oh, more eyes.
This game has a weird obsession with eyes.
It does.
Thing.
I know who you are.
Nothing escapes my lenses.
Wait, in here?
All right.
Let's see.
Uh, huh.
That's a human.
Is he?
me?
What's going on?
Yeah, what's going on?
Where's she?
Where are you?
You're streaming.
I need a little nappy.
Neem, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me,
me, me, me, me.
Is the rose sat down there with her dolls, and then you two
came alive?
Also, like, it's weird.
That's a little creepy that there's a binoculars up here.
Like, who's looking at us?
The bird watching me?
Oh, unaffected.
She was crying.
Oh my god.
Who heard her?
Can't be us.
We're good parents.
Yeah.
I bought her $8 cereal.
I bought her that true American doll that she always wanted
every day.
She gets a new doll.
What the fuck?
Is that where I'm at?
I'm not even going.
No.
We are having a conversation with a pair of binoculars.
There is no logic in that.
We could be having a nightmare right now.
Well, did you believe that you could be turned into a wooden
doll?
Exactly.
It had to be the tears.
It was a spell I am telling you.
So.
I knew it.
Magic was real.
How do we break it?
You didn't believe in me, Gumi.
My little pony.
Just give me some space.
I need the thing.
Virtual wizard.
I'm still a wizard.
How do we get a kid?
If the spell was cast through her tears, then in order to
break it, in order to break it, that's the laugh you did.
Reverse it through her tears.
Boom.
You are an engineer and you married me.
Yeah.
Sometimes you date and you marry someone because they're
funny am i funny wait i'm funny
what the freak how does she know where exactly our daughter
is at all times i mean whose binoculars are these two that's
that's facing our house
we're outside we're gonna touch grass watch me did you watch
it was pretty cool right what the fuck ew it's too far good
where there is love no distance is too far lock distance
initiative do work bro i'm just gonna punch it yeah Oh, we
got rope powers!
I had an outburst and I had to say it.
All right, let's swing across.
Oh, that's easy.
That tree is huge.
Don't worry about it.
The ropes will take us to rows in an instant.
Sorry, I was looking at the ladybugs.
Yeah, I was looking at the ants.
Okay, we don't jump that way, by the way.
We don't jump the left side.
It's the right side.
It's the other side.
It's the side I didn't look at.
Oh, there's a plane!
Look at this!
Right here!
Oh, throw it!
Throw it!
Where do I throw it?
Oh, no, wherever you want!
Okay.
Wee.
Where is it going?
We'll never know.
Um, did you build a tree house for Rose?
No.
Why do you ask?
There are windows.
Oh.
There's windows.
Oh, we're going to build those.
Oh.
Oh, who lives there?
I don't know, tree people, I guess.
They exist?
I mean, if magic exists, tree people exist too, right?
Why are you not waiting up for me?
I'm right behind you.
You told me to throw in a paper airplane!
No, no, no, it took 50 years.
It's a heavy...
Look, it's a heavy airplane, okay?
I'm not as jacked as I was before when you married me.
Okay.
Yeah.
That's because all you do is do your farm work and then eat
them goddamn potato chips Yeah, but we get fresh potato
chips because of meat.
Those are your favorite potato chips I actually don't like
chips.
So you lied.
So you lied to my face.
I don't like chips at all.
You lied
You're welcome.
I grew those Trust me, I need their rice crackers.
I think I was like, lying isn't good for a marriage, you
know?
I was eating senbei.
You're so lucky I only had one cracker left on my table.
That was perfect timing.
What the fuck?
Oh my god, it's a fucking rat.
Dude, I think that's a squirrel.
No, it's a fucking rat.
Squirrels are just tree rats.
this is this a shortcut or no what the fuck what the fuck
where did he get the jar you know what happens when wearing
a jar no no no please elaborate what happens rainbow dash
what is the context with that what is i why is there white
why is there white goop in here glue isn't that glue look
it's like arts and crafts why did you have glue in here It's
like arts and crafts.
Oh my god, she's talking to you.
Dad, I want to tell you something.
It's important.
Have you heard of this book by, um, Dr. Hakim?
He says that it's important to forgive each other.
This is so fucked up.
Imagine, like, you're a daughter.
Talking to your dad about something important.
He's just sitting there ignoring your ass.
Oh, that is.
That's trauma.
It's okay.
She's already gonna get therapy anyway.
This is just gonna be okay.
It's okay.
She's already getting therapy anyway.
It's a two-for-one deal.
Yeah, she might as well.
Oh, the extra trauma doesn't doesn't matter.
What the fuck?
We're getting interrogated.
Are you in with the wasp?
The wasp versus tree rats?
What?
Kill you?
No.
wasps we'll see you side you're on pull a switch you got it
chief oh my god what they're gonna kill us oh we're
unkillable that's crazy that they're just watching the shit
yeah you know that that's another issue here
they wanted us die why would we help them after they try to
kill us multiple times let's find out i'll only do it for
money yeah you what just about that was terrible horrendous
i think it's like is this alvin and chick monks there's
three of them there's alvin theodore and the other one that
has to be alvin He looks like an Alvin.
Yeah.
Wait, where did the chairs go?
Does it disappear with us?
Hey, the fucking boss.
Well, I got sucked up in it.
What do you mean?
Why the fuck was he holding his pod?
I was like, oh, did you see he has a machete?
Yeah, it's not like they could have guns.
It must be like a broken knife or some shit.
Oh, it's like, look at that tiny knife.
Look, it's Simon!
Oh my god, Simon, Theodore, and Alvin!
Fucking rats.
And look, Theodore!
I found me photos.
What could they want with those?
What the fuck?
They make shrines out of them.
This is...
Were their Oshis?
Oh.
What's...
What's your Oshimark in this?
Is that my Oshimike?
Vanilla.
course oh yeah glasses tree wait they have a tv dude they
stole our tv bro what the fuck how smart are these tree rats
the wasps have invaded our tree and wiped out most of our
tribe oh that's a pocket knife that he has what we can't
kill those crazy creatures you I did not realize there was
like a actual war going on like this game had something to
do with like war between squirrels and Was what does this
mean?
It's gonna get Call of Duty.
Oh my god.
Oh, of course.
I get the gun
I get the fucking bazooka bitch We sent in an undercover
agent to good operator As planned, the wasps believed the
robot was their real queen.
But instead of wiping out the wasps, our agent was seduced
by its power and switched sides.
Oh my god.
The agent went rogue.
Uh-huh.
The wasps cannot take our nuts.
There's nobody this game takes 15 hours.
Oh, wait, we're like speedrunning this shit.
Yeah, I feel like we're already, like, 30% way through.
How far, how much have we finished in this game, guys?
We got through two bosses already.
The vacuum and within an hour and 30 minutes.
Yeah, yeah, fine, fine.
But we wouldn't even be here if you had it knocked on the
squirrel's door.
We're not even at 10% of the game.
Oh.
You believe that?
I don't trust those squirrels.
I don't believe me.
That was a blessing.
Oh, what?
My underwear is now a sophisticated part of a flying
machine.
I sincerely doubt it can fly.
Of course you do.
You never take anything I do seriously.
Wait.
To get back to my real body so that we can get divorce.
Yeah!
Me too.
Oh.
May?
What now?
I guess it's time to kill someone.
Divorce happened early.
Look at that!
Well, look at that!
They answered our prayers.
Oh, apparently we just completed chapter one.
That was actually chapter one.
Okay, how does this work?
It's not fair.
Why do you get the cool zone?
Where am I?
What the hell?
Are you not here yet?
Oh.
I was testing out my gun.
My thing is like fuel.
Okay, you shoot it at the pile of sticks over there.
Okay, you shoot.
The pile of sticks over there.
See, this is why we're good together.
Here are the context clues.
I'll just watch you fire that shit away.
What do you mean?
Over here.
You give me the clues.
What is this?
Oh, it's the practice.
We don't need practice.
We're good.
We're good at this.
We don't need practice.
I already got it down.
See look There you see Look at that No practice needed Wow
This is impressive I'm getting spooky vibes from this place
Can we please turn back Do I have to go there too?
Wait what?
Yeah I'm pretty sure to go through Yeah Yeah I didn't know
if there was something I had to do over there And I can Put
this down See, look, I did it.
The muscle can think sometimes.
Oh!
I don't think we needed to do that, but okay.
Oh, wait, we do!
We have to launch...
Oh, wait, it's up here.
It's up here.
Yeah, I didn't need to do that.
Yeah, and then you have to blast the target.
We go!
Yay!
Progress!
This is like, this tree must be dying Because it's so empty
in the inside Yeah, I mean, they're at war right now So The
grass The grass Look, I was getting there I was getting
there
I was about to I was about to shoot And you just have to be
patient.
Okay, and then you have to destroy it.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't worry, I got you.
Uh.
Oh, it's over there.
You just have to hit it.
What?
Isn't that?
Yeah, I've been hitting that.
Oh, uh...
Wait, lower it.
Stupid.
Fuck you, man.
I thought about the answer myself with no help whatsoever.
Wait, hey, every day's a school day.
You're learning.
Yeah!
I lowered this.
Wait, it doesn't go through.
Yeah, the sap isn't sticking.
Where's this?
Where are you?
I think you need to weigh this down.
Up here.
Oh!
Good thinking, brains.
I think you have to blow up.
it up on you wait it down a little no i think you have to
blow it up on your end yeah yeah yeah see look at that you
need me you need me okay you need me okay okay i think
you've climbed it and then i turn you not even oh i can grip
it yeah yeah yeah nice okay and then i on it yeah yeah and
then what oh and then we go through the door yeah what the
fuck is this what is this that's an acorn experimenting on
an acorn they really are nuts I don't think that's it no we
have to wait like that you go you jump on And then I, like,
push you up.
Yeah, you jump on one of them.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You can grip this?
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I'm pretty...
Can you grip this?
And then, like, you do a wall jump and stuff.
Can you grip that?
Okay, sorry.
That's too far.
Yeah.
Can you grip this?
Alright.
yeah see god i'm so smart you're dead yeah it didn't stick
you for too long okay don't worry i got this
it didn't let me on the wall okay uh this ain't it
apparently then what is it oh there's more here oh there's
more here oh you You go from here!
Oh!
Okay, blow that up.
Get on there.
Okay, I figured it out.
And then you jump on that.
And now I'm gonna make this heavy.
Okay.
Yeah, and then you jump on that.
And then I'm gonna make this heavy.
Okay, and then I'll do this.
I'm running out of ammo.
I'm running out of ammo It's getting a little too heavy
Um Um Blow up the one below you Blow up that one below you I
can't blow up Blow it up blow it up I can't It doesn't let
me It doesn't let me scoop in Oh my god Okay Don't worry I
got this I figured it out I'll just keep I'll just keep over
loading it.
I'll overload it and then okay, I got an idea.
I got an idea.
Okay, you go back on the other side and then you blow it up.
I can't.
You want me to go all the way home?
Yeah, no, no, go over here.
You can't go from here?
This side of me no, I can't shoot while I'm on this oh,
okay, it's okay.
I will use so much goo that it will have to go down.
There's no way.
There's gonna be so much goo on this.
I'm gonna overload this with the goo Hey, you doing it.
I'm doing it.
There's so much goo going on.
Don't worry Do not worry.
It's extra goo.
Okay, and then Okay, okay now you can blow it All right,
what do I do from here?
Oh, I see oh Oh, okay, okay, okay, okay, I'm on it.
Why is she supposed to shoot it?
I don't know.
This is your side.
Yeah, I'm like, why would I know?
I'm looking.
Hello?
My gun's kind of weak.
What the fuck?
Your gun is so weak.
There you go.
Look at that.
Goo.
Now understand why I'm the goo.
What does that mean?
Holy husbands, no.
Oh.
Hey, I wonder what these buttons do.
What the hell?
Oh my god, they have a torture chamber.
Yeah, they do.
What is this?
What happens?
Nice move.
Oh, shit.
What about this?
Oops.
Wrong button.
Oh, you're an acorn.
How did they turn you into an acorn?
Where did you go?
There you go.
You're welcome.
Wait, what?
Oh, I got you out.
Dude, they have a fucking torture chamber for the walls.
I know.
Get out.
Wait, you can just turn them into any cores forever.
So you eat them.
Oh.
Wait, do we go this way?
This lid doesn't look so stable.
Hang on, those are interesting calculations.
Over here, over here.
Corrosive.
Chain reaction.
Wait, what?
Do I just put this?
What's it do?
Oh!
The latches, they're opening.
I got it.
Oh.
Okay, you gotta wait.
You gotta wait.
I made a circle.
Do you like it?
It's my artwork.
Wait, this one.
You missed that one.
Okay, wait.
Sorry, I'm not good at...
I need more practice, please.
Let me go to that bathroom real quick.
Oh, no.
It's...
Give me a sec.
Whoa!
Looks like something was kept in here.
Oh.
Whatever it was, it's gone now.
Oh, it could be like the queen, the queen wasp.
What do we do for this?
Oh.
It's ready.
It's pulling it over.
Oh, okay.
And then you...
Yeah, I was gonna say you get rid of that and then you get
rid of of that and then you get rid of that not to get rid
of any of these boys you do have to start because it weighs
it down oh see like it weighs the branches down it pulls it
over i see
oh oh oh oh don't get it don't get it's okay oh i'm weighing
them down yeah
is that it no there's Quit scoping.
Easy.
Easiest fucking fight of my life.
Look at that!
There's nothing!
Yeah!
Okay, simmer down, Simon.
Yeah, Simon.
It's not a weapon, it's how we use it.
Why do we do this?
There's some acorns over here.
Do those acorns matter?
Oh, I know, I know, I know.
We light it.
Yeah.
Yeah, and then you blow it up.
I think you go up there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then...
Oh, oh, I get it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I
got it.
You have to blow this and the other one.
Give me a sec.
I'll let you know when to blow it up.
Look, we're working together, Gumi!
Maybe this marriage is salvageable!
Okay, you blow like this up, and then blow this up first,
the first one.
And then the second one.
And then I leave you for another woman.
And then I guess I just go, fuck myself.
Yeah.
Hey, May?
I think there's a bridge here.
Let's knock it down, then.
There is?
Ow.
Here?
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
I figured it out.
Throw it.
Look.
Yeah.
I did it.
See?
I will never leave you.
I told you.
I'll never leave you.
I thought we were getting divorced.
You're literally leaving through divorce.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, you have to shoot that.
You shoot through that?
Yeah.
You asked for the divorce.
No, you did.
No, you asked for it.
I disagreed.
What the fuck just happened to me?
I came like lied.
Yeah, you lied.
I saw that.
Look how fun.
Wait, what's this?
Oh, it's a tug of war.
I got the fastest figures in the West.
Oh.
I'm on the right side.
I'm green.
I feel... Oh.
I'm ready.
I played Mario Party.
What the fuck?
No,
no, no, we're back.
Back to Mario Party.
Like, my fingers are tired today.
Okay.
What?
He's so good at this!
Yeah, I played Mario Party.
Would you play it on that?
You want to go?
No, it's okay.
He's really good with your fingers, apparently.
Yeah.
Yeah, sorry about that.
Oh, shit.
Rose and I used to play with it all the time.
Just another thing, this is great time.
Oh, man.
my legs hurt my feet hurt what the fuck why can they make
this a cutscene right i know why do we have to do they're
like look at how beautiful this is yeah just give us the
cutscene
oh my god i'm getting like i'm getting i'm like going
getting on to all the ops how did i not
Okay, I'm coming back.
Don't worry.
I'm here.
If you were worried, I'm here.
Oh, what?
You weren't here the entire time?
I'm here, don't worry.
You don't have to worry.
Gumi, I'm here, Gumi.
Don't worry.
I'm like right behind you.
Say something.
Oh, someone died.
Okay, that's bullshit.
You fucking activated it.
Where am I?
Oh, my God.
I'm getting lost.
I didn't activate shit.
I'm getting lost because of you.
Oh, my God.
Okay, we're fine.
We're fine.
Maybe I should just keep dying because apparently when I
die, I just respond to wherever you are.
Like...
Oh, this has to be a boss fight.
No, this has to be a mini fight.
Too early for the boss.
That's true.
It looks like a mini fight.
May the acorn be with you, they said.
Alright, let's see.
Oh, we just turn it.
Yeah.
There's nothing wrong with that.
We just turn.
Oh.
Oh, oh, and then the wasp come in while we turn.
Um, okay.
They're all down.
It's up to you.
Is there any more?
They're down.
Keep turning.
I'm still turning.
Oh, shield shield was.
This one looks tougher than the other.
Oh, this is...
Yeah, my sap isn't sticking!
Shoot at his butt!
How?
I'm fucking...
Oh, okay, I'm shooting the butt.
I'm shooting the ass!
Shoot it!
The ass has been stuck!
He's enemy yummy!
It's okay!
I'm pulling!
Shoot the ass!
There, see?
That wasn't so hard.
Okay.
Okay, shoot the ass!
Shoot ass!
Oh!
I got shot again!
I did!
His ass is stuck!
His ass is gone!
Okay, I need you to shoot that!
I need you to shoot this group!
Okay, while you do this, I'm gonna shoot the group here.
Oh shit, oh shit, okay.
Got it.
I dodged.
Dodged.
Ash is shot!
One more!
Nice!
He's distracted!
He's good, he's good, he's good!
We did it!
We got him!
Nice.
Did we get it?
Easy.
So easy.
Easy clap.
Oh, fuck.
We're so good at ass shots.
Backshot, backshot.
Oh!
Wait, there's no men in the wasp in the wasp domain I don't
know Isn't it like ants where it's all women and then No,
because how do they make babies then?
They okay because like it's when the wasp when like for the
ants I know like when the ant queen is like needs babies
They start birthing like male soldiers and in the moment the
Queen Anne is pregnant They like kick them out.
I thought those were bees I thought no, it was for ants too
isn't our wives Oh some wives have like male drones
I thought all bugs were like that like all colony bugs are
like that
Yeah, someone's like they mate with a drone and then the
drone dies.
That's their purpose.
Yeah, they were because like every as they should
Whoa I didn't do it yet born to love not to work
Okay, that's the bees are on to something dude like why
would they eat the food they make holy shit like i'm fine
with that it's like snoo-snoo like that that future rama
episode or death by snoo-snoo-snoo uh-oh dead by snoo-snoo
bro why don't we just like shoot the shoot the big the
honeycomb oh you shot me shoot the baby in birthing area I
did there you go the baby there's more there's more there's
more there's more oh shit I was trying to look at the
cookbook stop shooting me stop getting so close
stop!
I was trying to run past them well all right clearly I
clearly have to fucking back out after right here i am i did
the honeycomb i did the honeycomb oh okay i did the
honeycomb again the honeycomb there's a baby on me they
shoot the baby i can't hear you goofed them i did i goofed
on over the baby okay i shouldn't say that out loud
that's like dumb
Oh my god!
There's so many!
Alright, there you go.
The babies are gooped.
What?
Not by me.
I need to clarify.
Apparently.
They're gooped.
There's so many gooped babies!
That wasn't done by me!
Oh god.
Okay.
god i have the hardest job here i have the hardest job here
man
oh hey you got it i did it i did it yay
what do we do here what's this what puzzle is this okay i
clearly can't do anything about it.
Uh.
Oh, wait, there's a wall here.
Nope.
Never mind.
Oh, there's a bottle and a hole.
I think we have to drop the hole.
Drop the bottle into a hole?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure we drop the bottle into the hole.
No, there's like grass on it, on the side.
There is?
Oh, there is!
Okay.
I'm on the opposite side.
Let me walk over.
I did it?
Oh, I see.
Okay, I'll goop the other one.
Oh, the Bs are happy.
B not happy.
I mean, these Bs are easy.
They're not the...
Oh, wait.
There's Bs on you.
Oh, there's two Bs on us.
Oh, that's a boss.
That's a boss.
I got the other...
I got the small ones.
The boss is on me!
I got the small ones though!
I gooped it!
There's so much goop on it, I kept gooping!
Just keep shooting!
I'm getting fucking poisoned!
I'm dodging!
I shot him again!
Keep shooting!
Never stop!
Where did he go?
Oh shit!
Bro, she's so goofed up.
All right, I'm okay.
I'm okay.
Shoot.
He's full.
We have EDF at home, guys.
We have...
This is Hell Divers.
Oh, I had to put this on here.
Nice.
Alright, and then we gotta jump here.
Because I made this for us.
Okay.
Yeah.
Happy anniversary.
This is my gift.
Oh.
Shion!
Binti picture.
Oh my god.
Nice.
Can you, like, get closer to the camera?
Can you...
What do you mean can I get closer to the camera?
Can you get closer to the camera?
Okay.
And then...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Get closer.
Can you...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Can you turn around?
Yeah, that's good.
Okay, he move up a little bit.
Okay.
Okay, okay, move a little bit more left to the left.
Let me see.
Back up, back up.
Oh, yeah, okay.
Nice.
Okay, there you go.
That's all I wanted.
Oh, man, they're fighting it.
It's like a history lesson.
Oh, there's a timer.
Oh, there's a timer!
Those squirrels have some weird machines.
Is that us?
Look at us.
That's us.
Oh, wait.
Is this a puzzle?
No.
I think this is just for fun, man.
Oh, okay.
Oh, my God.
This is our best photo yet!
Wait, let me see.
What the fuck?
I'm not bad.
What the hell?
No, I'm a great photographer.
I need to go.
I need me to go.
What about my photo?
Okay.
Let me go.
How do you want me to pose?
It's beautiful.
What the hell?
Look at this.
Look at that.
That's pretty good.
I know.
Yeah, hey, that's very good.
That was a really good photo.
Oh, these are like all the photos she must have.
Wait, who took these photos?
Wait a minute.
The squirrels did, man.
Yeah, but there's like a creep shots of us, too.
Oh, that definitely looks like...
Yeah, it's time to go down.
There's a lot of creep shots of us, though.
Ducky?
Yeah.
I think they're breaking out the big guns now.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Oh, it is a hammer!
Oh god.
I died.
Where's the HP?
Okay.
Oh god.
There's so many.
Okay.
She's...
They're full of honey.
Oh god.
Oh.
Oh, I'm dead.
I'm dead.
I'm okay.
You can die now.
What?
But not really, not really, not really.
Oh, God.
It's fine.
We're good.
I'm...
Whoa, there's so many bees.
There's more.
How is there more?
Oh, God.
Are we supposed to, like, do a goof this?
Wait a minute.
I don't think so.
No, I think it.
I think we were.
We were supposed to.
I don't think so.
Oh, okay.
Doki, go for him.
Go for him.
Okay.
Nice.
Look, I don't want to get dehydrated.
Okay, I got the first box.
Okay, there you go.
All right.
I'm pooping.
Where is it?
Where was it?
I don't know!
There you go.
How?
What?
Oh, you stupid son of a bitch.
Oh, I'm coming over, I'm coming over!
Oh, I'm here!
Stop, stop, stop!
Why me?
Okay.
But...
Whoa.
The walls.
I... The walls!
Okay.
It's already gooped!
It's already!
Okay.
Jesus Christ, how many fucking bees are we killing?
In front of me!
Okay, I'm just gonna jump.
You know, we don't even need to goop this.
We can just jump.
By the way, I just noticed.
Well, we need goop this one.
What do you think I'm doing?
What why?
Why did you die?
What do you mean?
How did I die?
Why the fuck did you die?
What did you mean?
What the fuck did you die?
I wonder how.
I think we need to have that way.
Come on.
Are you kids winning this?
We're going by boat.
Help me out.
Help me out?
By boat.
Is this a boat?
All right, come on.
There we go.
Now there's water.
Now it's the water level.
Everybody's favorite.
Everybody loves water levels.
I love the water level music.
Don't we need like ores or something?
We don't need ores, Cody.
We've got an engine.
We do?
What?
uh it's in your hand oh the group oh engineer time what this
is you and your engineer brain the physics he's a nun not
just your wooden face mate oh you have a beautiful wooden
face okay um i think he has a health bar dokey
Do you trust me?
Do you...
Wait, it doesn't even do damage if I hit it.
You have to make sure we don't land in the mines.
Why can't I see that one?
All I'm saying is that you have to make sure we don't land
in the mines.
so I can see the mines at ease.
It's not my fault there.
Oh, this is easy.
It doesn't matter if we hit the side.
It matters for my eyesight.
Oh, that's a lot.
That's a lot of bugs coming in.
In front of us.
Turn to your left.
you left right in front of you where I'm aiming in front of
us that's not my friends girl I don't know why aren't you
looking at my screen look hello hello our game crashed hello
hello oh oh oh oh what do we have to do that again do Do we?
Do we?
Hello?
Can you hear me?
I, I, yeah, I hear you.
Okay, okay.
Oh no, this server died.
I'm not seeing it.
Oh, what?
No, no, do we have to do that again?
No, I think we only have to do the ship part.
Oh, thank God.
Okay, I sent you an invite.
I sent you an invite.
Okay.
Proceed.
Alright.
Don't worry.
This tap, please don't tell me.
Oh my god.
We have to do this again.
Alright, here we go.
Hey, oh, it's our ship's full HP though.
It's like nothing bad ever happened.
In front of you.
My front.
I don't know what you're my front my front screen speak
It's okay.
It's like we never lost HP, so I never did anything wrong
Yeah, look at that.
I'm gaming We lost HP because you keep hitting it you keep
hitting it How was I supposed to know this flimsy I would
would lose HP how oh shit our HP I am look see I'm a good
driver look I would be able to drive is like you didn't yell
at me
Is that why our car is all banged up?
Uh-oh.
Oh, no.
It's okay, what is he gonna do?
Kill us?
We're fine.
See?
You're not gonna do anything to us.
It's like a tornado.
We're fine.
Oh.
Oh, wait.
That's a tornado.
Not...
Oh, I have to drive past it.
Okay.
Don't worry.
Do you trust me?
Anyways, I'm tabbing out.
Wait, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
This is not there.
Oh my God.
Where's the boat?
Go through the eye of the storm.
The eye of the storm.
I don't know where the boat...
I'm on the boat!
How did you...
Where are you?
How did you get there?
Look at the blue dog, idiot!
there!
How do I get there?
I'm drowning!
At the top!
I'm here, guys.
I'm here.
I did it.
Wait, I think it's easier if we go into the storm.
It's easier.
No, because our boat's gonna freaking die.
I think it might be easier.
I think it's gonna be easier if we're in the tornado, Gubby.
You're pissing me off.
I think it's gonna be easier.
Oh, crashing us!
We did lose HP!
We did it in front of you in front of you.
My front, my front, my front.
Look, see, we made it through.
We made it through.
Don't crash into that wall.
I mean, we don't have to have a wall if somebody hits the
target.
Well, I have to be close enough to get the target.
Yeah, we did it.
I, like, ripped onto my controller so fucking tightly.
That my hand hurt.
Bro, you gotta relax, Goomy.
You gotta relax.
Hey, jellyfish.
Poke it.
Let's go.
Poke the jellyfish.
Okay.
I poked it.
You sure did.
For some reason, I thought it was that, like, Nemo DS game
from the early 2000s.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And then you could jump on the jellyfish.
You remember when you jump on jellyfish?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then there was some mini-games in the shark tank.
Dude, I actually own that.
Yeah.
The good ones.
Not before they started, like...
Oh, that's a wall.
Okay.
Not before they... It's, like, cash out.
They used to make actual good...
Actual good movie games.
What does that do?
it up oh oh oh you're doing it's me mo it's finding me bo
it's me mo nemo nemo it's me mo time just keep swimming oh
this is easy this is like platform i even cried while
watching uh finding dory oh you did wait what made you cry i
don't remember why it's been so long return oh it's this way
i wonder If we didn't like that, will we be able to find it?
Will we be able to just go forward?
Maybe speedrunners do that shit.
Oh, hey, look, they drew them!
It's like...
Aw, cute.
It's like caveman squirrels.
Wait, there's big evil squirrels.
Oh, my God.
There it is.
There's a dead squirrel.
Holy shit.
That's a giant, big squirrel.
And then...
Oh, that's us!
I think they think we're good people.
I don't think so.
Look how angry you are.
she looks.
Wait.
Is that us?
Yeah, look, there's us.
That's me.
You can tell from my big geek.
Whoa.
What?
Wait, look.
Someone did not like that.
They love toilet paper.
They do?
Where?
Oh, they do.
They love toilet paper.
Yeah.
And, like, all our other stuff.
I'm stealing from my stuff.
Yeah.
They love to steal.
So why are we helping them again um so we can get home or
something toilet one of these oh can you light it no i think
we can go down though
what the fuck is that can i goop it oh what magic is real
Oh, oh, I couldn't make it!
You have to, like, shoot yourself at it.
Yeah.
Nice.
I can aim.
Wait, I overshot it.
You have to hit that one.
I did.
Yay, because I'm a gamer.
Huh?
Where's the next one, though?
Oh, it's over here.
The next one flies.
Where does this take me?
Oh, I have to go in the hole.
Go in the hole.
See, I didn't miss the hole.
I'm literally right behind you.
I didn't even miss the hole.
Are you not proud of me?
Oh, my God, there's a fish.
The hole is pretty darn big, I'll be honest.
It's the sea turtle.
What the?
That's not a turtle.
It's like the sea turtle.
It's like crash.
Oh!
No, it's like the stingray.
Oh.
It's like the stingray that takes them to school.
Well, well, catfish aren't dangerous.
He's big enough to eat us.
No, aren't catfish?
Don't catfish, like, eat everything?
Yeah, they do.
Their bottom eaters.
And they have taste buds all around their body.
Wait, so, like, they're tasting my feet right now?
Yeah, it is.
This is why we're getting divorced.
What?
I should show it to you.
That was my breaking...
That is my lie.
That was the last straw.
Oh, it's like on its back now.
Wait, did you die?
Oh.
It did a flip.
Oh my god, look, it's showing us all these cool tricks that
he can do.
Wait, look!
There's more!
There is more!
Do I have to jump on them?
No, I think it's just decoration.
I wish this was cool and all, but like, stop making me move
on this.
This could have been a cutscene.
Oh my god, he's dead.
Fuck you, Cody!
Why are you blaming on me?
What did I do?
When I- when we get divorced, you can't blame anything on me
anymore.
You have to blame it on yourself.
Yeah, that's the point of our divorce, man.
Oh, to finally take responsibility.
Oh, my God, I'm calling him.
Oh, jump and fall like this in your real body.
Oh, are you calling me fat?
Oh, so enjoy it while it lasts.
Oh, my God, man.
I let myself go because of you.
Because of me?
Hey, Cody, that looks like a shooting range.
Wait, where?
Oh, a shooting range.
Wait, what?
What are you going to do?
Oh, it's over on the other side.
I'm just big-boned, okay?
This is a dad bod right here.
People love dad bods.
Okay.
Aren't charged.
Wait, what?
Oh!
Oh, I see.
Bro, the aim is so weird, though, for this.
Oh, it's the right stick.
Yeah, no.
I kind of don't like this.
Me too.
Oh, no.
What do you mean there's, like, bullet falloff?
What the fuck?
I don't like this.
Oh my god.
Aiming with this is so hard.
It's so difficult to aim with this.
I think I'm giving up.
Yeah!
FPS!
This is it.
Gamer of the Year.
Gamer of the Year right here.
You're a controller player?
Is that it?
No, it doesn't matter what input I use.
I'm just good at it.
I'm naturally gifted.
I'm gonna put you on the left side now on my screen
doesn't matter I'm just naturally talented yeah explain the
Mario party that's not that doesn't require aim that doesn't
require aim that's why explain the hammer game we have to
cross over there we have to cross over
It's okay we don't die.
Why are you afraid of?
Oh god.
We don't even die.
And where are we supposed to get here?
Oh okay.
How did I get here before you?
I was looking around.
Where are we going?
Only one way out.
Oh, look out.
These are here.
Oh.
Okay.
I figured it out.
So, like, we have to avoid the bees on the wood clasp when
we didn't know.
Yeah.
I think I figured that out a bit earlier, I'll be honest.
You get sort of time where they're...
See where they're gonna be arriving.
Yeah.
Oh.
Bro, this game is for babies.
Look at this.
This is a baby game.
We're so good.
I don't think it's a baby game since they're talking about
divorce.
No, babies need to learn early on.
We can't shelter these babies.
You know, you're right.
Yeah, babies don't need to be sheltered.
Oh, poop time.
Poop time.
There you go.
Nothing spawns behind us, right?
No, we're fine, we're fine, yeah.
They just, they only spawn in front of us because they're
not that good.
smart okay how far are we going going up to the top baby to
the moon oh fuck we're in a coliseum oh okay i think there's
a boss fight here what is this place uh i don't know but
they look pretty angry yeah they do wait that's a beetle oh
my god oh he's so cute.
Oh, are you ready for this?
I'm not sure.
He's so cute.
What is he gonna do to us?
He's so cute, though.
Okay, I'm gooping.
Uh, the goop isn't showing up.
Oh, I'm fucking dead.
This guy one shots.
This guy, this guy one shots.
We oh, I think I think I know.
I think I know I think I know.
We gotta lead him here.
um i think you were supposed to fall the floors first i'm
i'm dead because he has to be right on top okay all right
i'm goofing out here i'm goofing here i'm goofing here i'm
goofing here he's running at you i'm goofing here all right
i'm gonna stand here and then like you make sure to shoot it
the moment he runs at us you make sure to shoot it you make
sure to shoot it the moment he runs Okay, yes, nice.
That's it.
That's all we have to do.
Oh, shit.
He can fly now.
Okay, don't worry.
Nice.
I'm bait.
Okay, it doesn't go up yet.
Oh, he's doing a double jump.
He's doing a triple jump.
Oh, baby, a triple.
I told you he was trapped.
I told you he was.
Okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
I'm bait.
There!
Nice.
Please, please, please, please, please.
All right, here.
Oh, no, you're bait now.
You're bait.
Yeah, it's fine.
We can wait for him to walk.
He's charging.
He wants to charge.
You ready?
Yeah!
We did it!
Nice.
We're gaming.
Oh.
Oh!
I'm just a beetle!
He sounds like Seth Rogan.
I'm a mercenary.
I'm a friend of mine.
What food?
Huh?
Worms?
Slugs?
Larvae?
No!
I'm a vegetarian.
And gluten-free.
Oh!
Oh.
Okay.
Well, uh...
You know the queen?
She has all the nectar.
Huh?
So if you help us take her down, you can have as much as you
can.
Shake my head, not loyal.
Gaslighter, gaslighter.
Oh,
we got a ride now!
Shake my head, not loyal though.
Wait, how do we... Oh, you shoot!
You're the aimer!
You have to shoot!
You have to shoot too!
No, I move!
I move and jump, you shoot!
Where's the shoot?
Yeah, no, whoa.
Okay, I jump.
Let me go.
Just remember to shoot.
You know what's crazy is that you were moving the exact same
way I was moving.
Wait, really?
So I was like, wait, I thought I'm moving.
Someone wasn't reading.
I Someone wasn't reading This does not have to do with
reading It just It's called Reflexes You see I jumped
You could have shot that No I couldn't have You jumped into
the barrels You could have shot that into the barrels.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot.
It's shooting time.
All right, nice.
And then I jump.
Look at me go.
I'm a good driver.
I have a driver's license.
I have a dry shoot.
Yay!
Wait, would it matter?
Would it just fall on us?
Maybe.
Like a bomb?
Let me go.
That's when you know I'm a good driver.
What did you do?
You crushed!
You didn't shoot!
You didn't!
Because I wasn't on that you fucking crushed into that!
Our perfect run!
Nailed it.
Wait, he could have flew all along.
He could have just flown all along for us.
I think he regrets working for us.
What the fuck?
He's on fire!
Yeah, now he can fly.
Oh!
Whoa.
That's fucked up.
It's more Yoshi, we Yoshi'd him.
We'll just grab another Bito later.
Damn, that's crazy.
If Mario can do it and have a billion dollar company, we can
too.
There's a squirrel in there.
There's a squirrel in there, 100%.
They said that in the lore, man.
I goofed it, I goofed it, I goofed it, I goofed it!
I pooped it!
I did the- I did the- What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Where's the- Where are you doing?
Why- Why did you leave?
I don't want to get hurt.
What do you mean I pooped the fucking puddle?
Okay, now we go on it.
Let's see easy How do we where's the oh wait wait the the
metal oh wait no wait where's the Wait, but where's the
where's the funnel now?
Where's the funnel I can't find it Do we do backshots?
I think we do backshots I'm trying to find the funnel Wait,
where did you shoot?
It's wherever the X is.
Back shots, back shots, back shots, back shots, back shots.
It's okay.
There's an X right here.
Oh my god, okay.
Oh, how did I fail?
I don't understand.
Don't worry, I'm coming back.
Okay, okay, I'm gooping.
I'm gooping wherever the X is.
Wait, he's looking at me, I can't.
Oh, the bees are looking at me.
I shot the Kochi.
You shot the Kochi?
There's two X's on the back.
Actual backshot.
I can't.
There's bees blocking.
You guys shoot the bees.
I did.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
I'm going back, back.
I'm going back in the back.
Okay.
He's looking at me, but I got the other X.
Kochi down, Kochi down.
Ass time!
Oh, the airstrike.
Oh my god.
Ow!
What?
How was I supposed to?
I died because I was off screen.
That's fucked up.
That's fucked up, man.
Oh my god.
Okay, we're okay.
Spread out.
You heard her.
Where do they go after the bomb but i could just stand still
and just jump from here i don't have to move okay all right
come come with me come with me come here it's the back shot
time back shot back shot back shot i got the backs i got the
back i got the back i got the back well that sucks okay i
got the back i got it where am i where the fuck where am i i
goes off screen This is fucked up.
This is bullshit.
This is so bullshit We're good.
I can stand still.
Oh, don't stand still by the way.
Don't stand still.
Don't stand still by the way Don't stand still.
You gotta keep moving.
I've learned that you gotta keep moving Look at my health
bar.
I figured yeah, it's okay.
It's good thing that your your Fuki is hiding the health bar
So they know they won't know if you got hit or not I didn't
die by the way guys.
I didn't get hit My full HP.
Oh, you're at half HP.
No, I'm full HP.
I'm full HP.
All right, I'm shooting the back.
Back is shot.
Back has been shot.
Back is goofed.
I have gooped up back successfully.
Back shots, back shots, back shots.
I'm gooping them.
Oh, there's too many bees.
You gotta keep shooting the bees.
I have to reload sometime.
That's a you problem.
shots back shots i'm trying to go but they won't let me
they're protecting the queen we have to split we have to
split you go the other side okay it's looking at me i don't
know what to do oh i got it i got it literally attack i got
it i got it i got the back i got the back i got the back i
got the back i got the back okay i got it i got it i got it
i got it i got it okay okay i'm going back up i'm going back
up i'm doing it i got the back i got the back it's your It's
your turn!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
It's fully backed!
F-shot!
What the fuck?
Where am I?
Wait, where do we- Oh, here!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
It's the-the wire!
I know, I know!
Try.
What?
I didn't see it.
I'm not talking!
You're welcome!
Okay, okay.
The bees, the bees, the bees.
What do we do about the bees?
I need you to shoot the bees.
Ow!
You gotta shoot the bees.
I can't aim at the thing because of the bees.
I am!
Okay, I got it!
I got it, got it, I got it!
I keep aiming the bees!
You gotta keep aiming at the bees!
Oh, I got it, I got it!
I don't got it, I don't got it!
I don't got it!
Oh god, oh god, I need to reload.
I'm getting dehydrated Oh, I got it, got it There you go
There you go Okay, bees, bees, bees Bees, bees Bees, bees
It's good, it's good, last shot, last shot We got it
Where's the squirrel Wait, it was a bee That's not That is a
bee That is a bee
she's a fake wait then how do they get more wasp oh shit but
like how did they make the bee wasp make more wass.
Uh-huh.
Where did the baby- Where did the larvae come from?
Why?
Oh.
Oh my god.
Cool guys, don't look at explosions.
Yeah.
We're so cool.
That's so cool.
You see those TikTok videos where we put a gasoline over a
wasp hive?
No.
So we never seen that tick-tock There's like a protein I've
seen a guy that vacuums was what the fuck?
I saw one where you get like a gas like a bucket of gas like
a gasoline and you put it on top of a wasp nest or whatever
Like the wasp nest will all the wasps in the wasp nest will
just fall into it and die You are one of the noblest
pollinators in nature Yeah, of course bees pollinate crops
that feed not dick rider
RIDAR Dick RIDAR
Oh, so you're on the same team now shoot them all What the
fuck what the fuck?
How do I call it this bee's fucking booty?
dodge all those bullets I got something in my eye bro bro we
just saved your furry ass come on Cody we should kill that
aim yeah that fucking aim though oh okay you're driving I'm
shooting where's the gas oh there's my underwear Ha ha ha ha
ha ha That's cute The fucking machine gun man Code not Oh no
Alvin's angry Alvin's angry Don't worry I can fly
What happens So I go Girl
I didn't know I'm gonna go pee I'm gonna go pee
I didn't know that was gonna happen I didn't It was not
intentional it was not Accident.
I swear.
It was just a little T.
He accident.
You guys believe me, right?
I didn't mean it.
I think, guys, I think I'm doing really well, chat.
I think I'm a great husband.
Don't you guys think so?
do you guys think i'm an absolutely perfect husband like the
reason why we're getting a divorce is not because it was my
fault that's uh i i feel like clearly i tried i tried so
hard to make it work and clearly it wasn't a me issue for
this like
sure see father of the year okay i'm gonna make a pull who's
the reason for it
all i'm saying is that i think i'm perfect husband material
like anyone would want me as the husband i'm a perfect dad
and a perfect husband oh there we go see look no crashes no
crashes oh i can rev I can go fast.
You just gotta make sure you clear the way.
You guys gotta make sure.
Shoot the thing.
Okay, here we go.
We're good.
Pump it!
I'm trying!
There's a cooldown.
I can't just pump whenever you tell me to pump.
Well, you're gonna have to pump it here.
Threat the needle.
Whoa, my god squirrel ladders shoot down the squirrels.
They're not people anyway That's fucked up They shot us
first they shot first They shot first Why am I taking
damage?
Why am I?
Why they're shooting?
Yeah, but if you killed them before this I wouldn't get
shot.
That's why I'm swapping to the mouse and keyboard.
It's worse!
It's worse somehow!
The DPI is so low!
That fucking changes DPI!
I can't build a game!
Don't worry, don't worry.
Because the talented controller input can do this.
That's why you need me.
I'm gifted in any input.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, pick one, pick one, pick
one, pick one, pick one.
I destroyed all three, so...
Okay, I couldn't tell because they were still there.
There's something behind us?
There's fucking these behind us!
We're so fucking slow!
Oh God.
I hope you're shooting them.
There's still planes behind us, by the way!
What?
There's something behind us!
Slowly I'm turning!
That's a you problem!
Oh god, oh god.
Why did you pause?
Are you dirty up?
Are you dirty up the...
Pause.
Why are you doing this?
Is it better now?
still haven't fixed my dpi i have to aim with my arm and set
my wrist it's okay we're out we're out are you gonna fight
the squirrel oh my god it's alvin oh shit oh my god fight
fight what am i supposed to do am i just oh i'm just gonna
make sure this is a fighting game now what the fuck it's
What the fuck?
Oh shit!
What the hell?
What the fuck?
Oh, that squirrel is dead dead.
There is no way.
Whoa, I do love you.
Oh, my God.
Oh, oh, we have to balance this.
Yeah, yeah, we have to be fully balanced.
What are you doing?
Okay, I'll be right side.
I'll be right side.
I should have been left.
You should have gone left.
What do you mean?
Okay, I'll stay.
When we're balanced, I'll be left.
Okay?
When we're balanced.
All right.
Okay.
Mm-mm.
All right.
Okay, we'll get it sometime.
All I'm saying is that I stay on the left side.
I know where my place is.
Okay.
Look at that.
Yeah, Gumi?
Yeah.
I want to go to the left side too.
Why don't we just stay in the center And we don't want to go
anywhere We stay in the center I think that's just easier
for us Wow, wait, look at what happened Wow, maybe We just
have to stay in the center How about you stay in the center
and I steer Maybe that's just better Maybe I'm getting
scared There's just too many cooks in the kitchen too many
cooks we don't want too many cooks in the kitchen you're
scary what am i doing what am i doing i am doing everything
i can to save this marriage yeah okay here you go well they
shouldn't have stolen from us all right nice i think we
should go right i think we should go right i think and then
we should go left we should go left we should go left we
should go left no
the beginning oh thank god we're not the beginning we'll be
fine we'll be fine um
we can make it through right maybe we'll be saying the
center don't worry Maybe, maybe.
Oh, never look at a squirrel the same way again.
What?
Oh, oh, it still works.
It still works.
Left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left,
left.
right right right right right center center center center
apex call outs he's one he's one he's one he has a purple
armor still crack crack crack crack crack crack crack crack
crack crack i'm shielding shielding covering cover me am we
loading where's roses rue where is that oh is there oh shit
i was like where the fuck are we supposed to go okay all
right we're good see nice we did it
that's you sleeping sleeping on the job oh my gosh she's
gonna talk to me she's like mom mom do you remember mr.
baboon remember him mom sleeping this is mom sleeping hours
I'm sleeping
Dude, she's about to run away from home at this point Yeah,
she's gonna fucking inside out it Oh my god We haven't
played with them in a long time Damn Mommy has two jobs,
leave her alone Yeah, you talk to dad Bro, what?
Now she's lying?
You're making shit up.
I just want you to know.
Someone's like, I think we need to call CPS on them.
We're not terrible parents.
We have to make a, we are tired from making so much money
for our kid.
Our kid has to fucking napping.
Doesn't mean you have to call CPS.
Yeah.
Wow!
Look at her room!
Tell us we're not providing!
She has a TV in her own fucking room.
Like, what the fuck?
I'm
flying by the seat of your pants!
Oh, ha ha, you're real comedian.
You know that?
Thank you.
Look, there she is.
Oh, I miss her.
Do you think she's okay?
Oh, she looks fine.
I mean, she's playing like nothing.
Yeah, see, she looks like she's happy.
Yeah, but we should just like me when I have to play in my
room.
I'm myself.
She's not disassociating.
Of course I remember.
Whoa.
Are you really ready to talk to Rose?
Why not?
Yes.
She's our daughter.
Well, can you talk to her without fighting each other?
Of course we can.
Of course we're like one minute is all we need.
I don't think you are ready.
Wait, is he trying to stop us?
I think that he is.
And are we gonna let him?
No!
Yeah!
Finally, we don't have to listen to this guy.
Mm-hmm.
What if we can't make Rose cry?
We have to.
Well, we'll be stuck like this We're gonna make our child
cry.
What the fuck is...
We got a sniper on us.
something out okay we have a creep on us dude they're
breathing so yeah i know
a lot of pillows oh it's like a pillow for it yeah
hank brothers oh the mommy space oh she's like she has mommy
issues don't we all alright let's see how do we do this like
the original Wii games you know oh yeah the tank one wait
how do I oh I figured it out why are you getting closer why
are you getting closer I don't like how close you are
you're in the corner We hit each other I just need that one
hit I just need that one hit I just need that one hit And
we're good Wait where did you Yes Yes I would have had a
save I was thinking earlier I'm a gamer I'm a gamer Wait it
says I'm 2 and you're 1 No it says that I'm 4 and you're 1
Well it said 2 and 1 for me It says 4 one for me this is my
way what the fuck this is my way that's why i get distracted
by that i get a head start now what is this what's the
flashlight for does it really matter why is the car truck
wait there's something here what is this this is an easter
egg It's the brothers!
It's the brothers!
There's an Easter egg from their other game that they made.
It's the... I've never played that game.
Me too.
I never played it either.
But it's like the streamer game.
It's like if you want to play a co-op or something it's
either this or the other one.
Alright, let's play the other one next.
Wait, what's this?
What's the level up?
Oh, it's just like Easter eggs.
Look!
The gate is locked!
Wait, what?
By some kind of force.
Maybe they're connected.
Enter password.
Enter password?
It's got something to do with hacking.
Hacking?
Like this?
Oh, you're on the other side.
Oh, override.
Oh.
But what do we do here?
I'm green.
am red
I think are we stupid are we okay we're figuring it out then
we're figuring it out no no we have to make make this guy
angry right I thought it Oh, what?
What?
Look, I thought they were eyelashes, okay?
I thought they were eyelashes.
Uh-huh.
Whoa!
My name, traitor.
Because I bought you in the Space Museum.
Liar.
Rose had picked me at the Space Museum and commissioned me
for a special mission.
I am the only one who can protect Rose from the dark.
side of the universe we're also assigned to protect rose as
her parents stop lying your mission is to make her cry damn
that's a fucked up mission the bigger the better they can be
happy tears moon baboon people can cry out of happiness
tears from rose to take him out space baboon
the space baboon is cps who caught cps on us who was it oh
my god i'm having a panic attack what should we do it takes
two has the most accurate portrayal of panic attacks have
you seen that meme where people were like we're like be
talking about which movies had the best portrayal which
animated movies had the best portrayal of panic attacks did
you did you see that i've seen people say you know that
movie um the pixar movie with emotions or whatever yeah yeah
inside out yeah yeah i've heard people say anxiety looks
fuckable or what inflation oh my god inflation if you want
to know wait what does anxiety look like from Basically, she
looks like the...
She's like the orange one.
Do you know that you released the new emotions?
It's like anxiety, envy...
Dude, anxiety does not look fuckable!
It's like anxiety, envy, boredom, and I don't remember the
fourth one.
How come you get all the cool gadgets?
Because I'm cooler than you, Cody.
Yeah, how come you get the cool one?
I forgot what the fourth emotion they introduced.
Yeah, let's find a way out of here.
Bro.
by Rose, you crazy space monkey, please.
Well, she was the one who picked him out.
Yeah, and you paid for him.
What do I do?
Oh, what if I...
You would be if someone threatened to hurt Rose.
Yeah, well, we're not hurting Rose.
Wait, how do you get up there?
So she can have her parents back.
Uh, I have moon shoes.
Now let's move on.
Oh, I get... I know, I know.
I don't know.
Wait, give me Where are you?
How did you do that?
I'm trying to get there!
I have moon shoes, man!
How did you do that?
Oh.
Wait, what do I do as a big boy?
Oh!
Wait.
Actually, no.
Where are my context clues?
Oh,
I figured it out!
I go smart.
And then I do this.
Wait, do I do this in?
Mm-hmm.
I did it!
You know, I'm pretty smart.
Wait, don't you... You can let go right now.
Yeah.
I know, I was just watching.
I was watching your screen.
That's fucked up.
We're supposed to be a team.
There's a control room at the very top.
If we can get up there, I think we can make it out of here.
What's this?
Oh.
Oh, there's no battery.
You have to go in there.
Oh, okay.
See, this is why we're a team.
You're in my context, Blues.
Okay, I'm pushing it in.
It's on.
You know, I think sometimes I just stop and I just watch.
Because of how smart I am, right?
I just want to see how your mind works.
Yeah, because it's like, it's like a genius.
Eh.
I'm a genius.
You're just like so impressed with how this mind works.
What the fuck?
What the fuck is this?
Wait, I'm in somewhere else.
Oh no, I'm with you.
Oh, it's another game.
This is another game.
Spacewalk.
Okay.
Oh, we play this.
Land on platform.
Oh, it's like that crab game.
This one's gonna be mine.
Boxes have always been mine.
this is platform.
What the fuck?
This...
It's so slow.
Okay.
Oh, oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Come on.
Give me more.
No!
Oh, he fell!
Yes!
Mine!
Wait, that's fucked up.
That's fucked up.
I can do that too.
I took you guys!
Another boyfriend!
Dude, I didn't realize I could take you until later.
Another Point for joking.
Yeah.
I'm going.
What the fuck was that?
Yeah.
It's called being a winning.
What is this?
I think I started like a supernova.
What the fuck?
Can we like shoot the stars into this?
Um, I didn't mean to go into the...
There's the world.
Oh, there is, yeah.
Alright, purple world.
I'm not sure this is a good idea!
What's this?
Oh my god.
Now that was one hell of a ride.
Can I step on it too?
Oh, we can't- Oh, it's like the monkey ball game.
Monkey ball?
Yeah.
Oh, I- You have to push it.
Wait, how do I push it?
Why don't you try becoming big first?
Big, big time.
Okay, I'm pushing.
Yeah, it is!
It's like that stupid!
The monkey ball!
Bro, I push so fucking slow.
B.
Okay, don't worry.
I push.
I'm pushing.
Oh!
Jesus Christ, I wish I'd go faster.
I'm so slow, though.
Can I actually go faster?
I can't.
Even if you dash?
No.
It won't let me.
I have to push as low as possible.
Alright, here you go.
I'm watching.
I'm watching you.
Now what do you do?
Oh no.
I do.
Do I just stay here?
Oh!
I small.
Oh, you crushed me.
Okay.
That's a little fucked up.
But that's okay.
I knew what I signed up for when I said I do.
Wait, what?
Okay, here.
I'm ready.
Go small.
Alright.
Oh Can I push up?
Oh, maybe Oh Oh, you have to push back up You stay small I
can't keep staying small And I'm excited What?
I'm pushing it in Push it in I know I did
oh at least it teleports us which is nice we don't have to
walk back
all right we got it back shots we got it go to red red
portal red portal because i'm red how are you red i'm red
look look at my shirt look at my shirt and tell me that's
That's not red.
That's red.
You just don't understand.
Do we both need to be here?
Oh, it went all the way up.
Red?
Oh, it's this way.
But you have to jump on the planets.
And then...
Here I'll go.
The planet made me slide off.
That was fucked up.
Don't worry, you'll get there eventually.
I'm here now!
I believe in you, Gumi!
I don't believe Boom I trust Why are you saying these things
What
What What do I do for this?
How do you do for this?
Oh Maybe like Oh get on it You have to get on it And then I
like Wait what Oh wait you're already on there.
Okay.
And then you hit me that way.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I hit you to the front.
Bam!
Slap.
Okay.
Yeah, how do you get me up there?
Give me a minute.
Uh, go to the drawers.
The drawers?
There's the drawers.
To you left?
The drawers?
Oh, I see.
I see.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm in.
Got it.
I fucked up.
You gotta restart.
Yeah, sometimes husbands make mistakes.
You can't be perfect.
Because being perfect is very...
More often than not.
Being perfect makes a relationship very toxic.
You gotta be able to make mistakes to show that you're
human.
Oh!
Hello?
There, I'm good.
I'm in.
Okay, I'm tiny.
Tiny man.
Tiny man!
Oh shit.
Tiny man dropped off.
Tiny man is still walking up.
You see that tiny speck on the left side?
That's me.
Hey, I got this.
Alright, I'm pressing in.
3, 2, 1.
Yeah, he happy now!
I'm the short king.
All right, last portal.
I'm surprised we're not at the school yet.
We're not at the math problem.
I told you, the only thing I remember from watching people
play this game is the one where there is math problems.
No, I know what you're talking about.
Yeah, that's like apparently the only like clippable thing
people clip from that game.
Because like, I don't know, I did not know all of these
other things existed.
That's for sure.
I didn't I don't know all these other things existed in this
fucking game Nice you do we just jump assume we just jump
whoa.
Oh, I jumped a little too forward me too
All right, we can do this
What it's okay.
I believe in you you live for me live on for me I'm about to
die on purpose Yeah, I did it.
Oh my god, look, it's like the Android symbol.
Oh yeah, it is.
I assume like...
Oh, I assume I do this.
And then...
Oh.
Oh, I do small.
I'm small.
Okay.
Big time.
Wait, I have to launch you.
Maybe?
Or do you like... Oh, yeah, I do like you.
Oh, we flip!
Our brain is expanding so much from this game.
Wait.
How do you do something here?
What do I do?
Big?
Big.
Yeah.
Where am I...
Where am I moving?
Oh.
Sorry, I got down there.
wind it back because it's okay and then i it launches me
okay okay i figured it out it was the other way i did it my
god sometimes i wonder how i how my brain works sometimes
how would people know i'm the world's greatest dead It's
okay I don't think they need to know any lies This is why
There's no world's greatest mom Whoa After all I've done for
our house Like what?
Like what?
What have you done?
You need to get closer, you need to get closer, bitch What
have you done?
What have you done for this house?
I work jobs to pay our bills While you sit there and make
potato chips Yeah, but you're eating them Oh, you ate one
no, that was a homemade rice cracker.
That's not what you said last night
Now swing Well, I do oh, I have to put that there All right
Oh, we're like a pendulum We a pendulum a pendulum Yeah Yay!
Wow, okay.
Wait, which way is up?
You're all right, Mae.
Look, I'm up here!
Wee!
Yeah.
This doesn't seem to be working, okay.
I mean, we're alive.
So I think it's good progress.
Oh, here I go.
Small.
BB.
Don't worry, I'm heading over.
I'm very slow.
This is fucked up.
I can't see your screen anymore i'm here we do it we did it
we opened everything that should be all of them right i
think so good teamwork see even the game thinks we have good
teamwork look at that oh it's open i'll go on the other side
which way do i turn this way Zoom is this way Am I turning
the right way?
I am Gumi is carrying this what do you mean you need a fun
dad?
Every relationship always has the fun dad and that's me.
I'm the good cop I wouldn't know
The reason you fell in love with this beautiful man is
because I was just so funny Put your feet away.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Collaboration.
Bla, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Oh, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Oh, you're pissing it, mom.
Okay, okay.
Just don't forget, yeah?
Blah, blah, blah.
Collaboration.
Oh, we collapsed!
We've collapsed for like three hours now!
Oh, wait.
Oh, wait, is that game?
There's a game.
There's no... There's a game!
There's a game!
There's... I've left.
I left too.
You gotta pick where I'm going.
I wait for you here in Game Town.
You fucking bitch.
Oh my god, it's tennis!
See?
I'm so fun!
I let you experience fun things, Gumi.
My hand hurt.
I'm the fun dad!
We get to play!
We get to play games!
I need a nappy!
Coolie!
Fun Dad!
Let's see what this is about.
Hello?
Dodge the lasers.
I have no clue what this challenge is about.
Where's that?
Oh!
Oh, I see.
I see now.
Oh, I know where you're gonna throw the lasers.
Watch this Bam!
Dodged.
Oh, wait.
Oh, now.
Oh, now it starts.
Okay.
Oh, God.
Wait, this is not fun anymore.
This is...
Wait.
Oh, God.
I'm trying no no no no I'm still up I'm still up I'm still
up oh no oh no I'm the fun dad I'm still the fun dad you
can't take this away from me oh no no why are you so good at
this yeah i played a lot of oh my god why are you so good i
didn't get hit once i didn't get hit once you're so good at
this i think i'm better at reaction time but you're better
at the aiming thing holy that was intense Okay, which one?
Oh, wait, there's multiple new ones, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, we got this one.
Let's get to the beach, beach?
Wait, did we go on the wrong one?
I don't think so.
I don't know.
Oh, no, we got the right one.
Okay.
You were so focused.
Oh, I have a door.
A little door.
I can't do anything.
Oh, my God, I'm a pinball!
Get the pinball me!
No no no no Right right right right Yeah here here here here
Yeah yeah here you go Oh I can't move Okay Don't worry I got
this That's why I'm the fun guy I actually have to watch
your screen now What?
What?
Okay, fine I'll be honest I just wanted to see if he would
die What?
I gotta did that on purpose, I'll be honest What the fuck?
We have to do this again!
I just wanted to see you die.
I was praying on your downfall.
That is so messed up.
You fucker.
You fucker!
After all you put me through today, it's well deserved.
What do you mean?
This is a team game!
We don't progress!
You don't do it!
I'm having fun!
fun
Don't worry direct our needle imagine you miss that would be
so messed up if I missed it.
Oh my god Still get blown up
I still fucking died.
That's so fucked up What is this I don't know but you gotta
climb it what the fuck is that what are you doing?
I hip-thrusted, uh, a rocket.
You need to stop hip-thrusting, man.
I can't stop.
I can never stop.
Why don't we have a second child yet?
That's on you.
What the fuck does that do?
I don't know.
What is this lady?
Oh, what the hell?
Oh, there it is.
There it is.
It's over there.
Oh, you need to turn it off.
You need to turn it off!
Oh.
How was I supposed to know that I died?
I died.
You need to turn something on, clearly.
Do I do this?
Yeah.
Then I can do this.
Oh, oh.
I fucking, okay.
I feel you wanted to turn that.
I thought about it.
I could see you.
I could see you're a brainer.
and thinking about it there.
Okay, I'm pressing it in now.
It's in.
I don't know if you noticed.
Hold on, what?
It's in?
Is it in yet?
I've said that before.
Whoa!
We were making our first child.
And that is why we only have one kid.
Wait, which color did you go into?
I went to the one on the left of what we just finished.
Which color is this orange?
Oh, it's orange.
I was looking at your screen and not mine.
Cool.
Don't let anyone tell you otherwise.
All right, heal you.
You can't find me.
Where do I go?
I go up here?
No, you're supposed to go straight forward.
I'm here.
Don't worry.
The husband is here.
Oh, I can hip-thresh this.
Watch this.
Ugh.
I have a lot of pent-up aggression right now.
That's not...
No, I'm 10!
I'm 10!
Don't worry, I'm coming back!
There you go.
You wanna watch this?
Look at me go, I'm a beautiful butterfly.
Bump.
That was- I was watching.
That was that beautiful.
Go big.
Ugh.
There you go.
Ew, the noise he made.
What the fuck do you mean?
He went, I went big.
How do I get over to you?
Uh, go big again, I think.
Alright, I'm checking, I'm big.
Can you jump on?
Jump where?
I can't jump anywhere.
Can I?
Because I lower it.
I don't think I can.
Oh, go tiny, go tiny, real quick!
Yeah?
No.
Wait, you go...
Wait, hold on.
Go on the other side.
Other side?
Okay.
Yeah, and then I jump down.
Oh!
And then you go big.
Go big, yeah.
Uh-huh.
And then I go small.
I go mega small.
Oh my god, we're doing it.
We're using our...
We're putting our two brains together.
To make one full brain.
Um, I would say...
I have about 75%.
What?
What happened to the other percent of that brain then?
You're at a 25%?
Okay, nice.
Yes!
Whoops.
I still died.
You have to wait for me!
I still died Okay, you have to go first Okay, I got it You
have to go first You have to go first You have to go first
No, I wasn't looking
I can't use my eyes I'm blind Go I need my context clues
okay see if we work as a team things will get easier i don't
know if you know that you're pissing me off look we can do
this together like a team i'm already here i'm here too i
let you ladies first first.
Alright, I'm pushing it in.
Alright.
Playing a little music.
Ooh.
Nice.
In we go.
Stop fighting your tearing chat apart.
Wait, didn't we?
Oh.
Whoa, whoa.
What's this?
Oh, look at the boxes, though.
Big time.
Big.
Oh.
I want big.
Oh, wait, you have to get below.
On the other side?
Because, like, look below me.
What do we have to do here?
Wait, there's something- I see it, I see it.
There's, like, stuff here, too.
It's over here.
Oh, do we have to grab all these little things?
Ow!
Okay, I figured it out.
We have to grab all these tiny things.
I'm heading higher.
Higher before anybody else.
Oop, oop, oop.
Can I get big?
How do I get this out?
I can't get big, though.
What do I do from here?
A big time?
Oh, I can!
I'm glad.
Because I can't look at your screen.
I did it!
I got one!
Nice.
I got the second one.
Okay, and then...
Do I need to put this closer?
There you go.
I got one.
and then the next one is yours here that's the last one i
think unless there's more no there's one more oh the last
one's like above here how do we do this oh there's a tiny
one here oh i need you for the last one i'm gonna figure out
what to do for this one because it's inside this
there's like boxes to your left yeah no that I already got
that one oh I'm confused oh I have to stop at the button
that's what the button's for big okay and then big there we
go I already forgot about the button in yeah i didn't see
anything on my side can you put it on the pillow all right
then we have to do this one the final one up here all right
i need you to take me to the other side i'm strength i'm
shrunk now i'm baby baby baby time okay I'm going up.
I'm going up.
Where is it going to take me?
I'll never know.
Oh.
Oh, I almost dropped off.
I got the last one.
I did it.
I'm a hero, Gumi.
I'm a hero.
Obviously, we need to put this one over here.
Are you making them further apart?
Yeah.
Wait, I can help!
Okay, and then...
Here.
And...
I'm gonna put this here.
Do we...
Are we missing one?
No, right?
We got all of them, right?
Maybe we are missing one.
Oh, they said we can...
Oh, I know, I got an idea.
I got an idea.
We slant it.
Like here.
I got an idea.
You think your reaches all the way fuck up?
Wait, I think we can.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then we...
Yeah!
I'm so smart!
Look at my brain!
I told you!
This is exactly why you married me!
Look at that.
I told you.
I told you, Gumi.
I can be smart too.
This is true.
It's so true.
Let's look at that.
This is why I'm a catch.
This is exactly why I'm the catch here.
I'm the one that's 10 out of 10.
I'll press this.
I'll do the one here.
Okay.
I turn everything.
Yeah!
Offenses?
Yeah.
What does he mean?
Hold on, but I'm waiting for you.
Oh, wait, you already?
Oh, you didn't wait for me?
I'm here now.
What do we do here?
Wait for you for what?
I don't know.
Just to make sure I'm here.
Wait, hold on, hold on, hold on.
We gotta swap it.
Oh, yeah, there we go.
And then we swap this.
Wait, how do you swap it?
Oh, from here!
Okay, give me a sec.
Wait.
Wait, I can't swap this.
Oh!
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Come here.
Come here, come here.
Yeah, yeah.
Go, no, no, no.
Go stand on the one to the left.
On me.
No.
Yeah.
I'm thinking.
So you're gonna lock it.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh my god!
We're so smart!
Nice!
I knew I could figure it out.
We did it!
Together!
All right, Dr. Hashim.
I see.
The current isn't making it through.
Can you go tiny and then wall jump up?
Yeah.
I'm doing it.
Boom, boom, boom.
And then I'm plugging it in.
It's in.
Overall happiness.
Happy, neutral, sad.
This guy's a freak.
Why is she monitoring our child?
Like, daily mood change.
She could be going through puberty.
You don't know that.
Puberty makes boys and girls do crazy things.
She could be a tween.
Yeah.
Yeah, still super creepy.
Hey, what does this do?
I agree.
It's super fucking creepy.
The laugh tracker.
Dude, ours would be out of the fucking tracker.
And I'm going to break the chart.
Yeah, okay.
But what about her?
Her worry, huh?
Oh, my God.
She's just like us for real.
He doesn't know what he's talking about.
Yeah, he's not a licensed therapist.
Exactly.
degree how about maybe we can uh beam ourselves back to rose
from here no careful oh where's that taking us oh this is a
gladiator yeah this is a gladiator stadium this is a
gladiator stadium okay how do we do this oh there's like uh
red buttons here That's on you.
I'm trying!
I need you to grab this!
Nice.
See?
I did it.
I did something.
I mean, we just jumped.
We don't have to, like, go anywhere.
The point.
I don't think I don't think you should have said so go me.
I'm just saying Yeah, you're like I don't think we have to
go anywhere.
So I was like, okay, I'm gonna zone out for a second Come
on, I need help I need help get down Ah And if it was me I I
am come out.
Come out.
Come
out.
We did it
So easy a little more difficult this is so easy yes aim at
gumi and not me look at that dodge ow it's okay i have regen
it's on you it's on you it's on you it's on you where's the
buddy's over here buddy's over here buddy's over here on me
on me on me on me on me
get the jump you have to jump you have to oh i i have to
walk up a wall man not jump
It's the same thing.
Come over here.
We've got to get rid of that laser.
I'm doing it.
What am I doing?
You get the laser.
Nice.
We did it.
See, that was so hard.
Wait, if I was tiny, They can't kill me.
Where am I?
I'm dead.
Don't die yet.
I figured out that you should not be tiny.
Don't be tiny.
What the fuck?
Oh my gosh.
Don't worry.
Bro.
How do we do this?
You dodge!
You just dodged the fucking rocket, man!
I don't... Oh my god, isn't it worse?
You're like...
No!
What is it?
I... I can't... It's so hard.
It's so difficult.
I can't dodge.
I'm just... I'm just stupid.
I did!
I dodged!
Okay, you know, you ride the rocket and then you try...
I...
I'm doing my best.
Okay.
I figured it out.
Look, look, look, look, look.
Look.
We did it.
Yay.
Wait, get in the ship.
Get in the ship.
Right here.
Go tiny.
Let's just get in the space.
I'm in.
What do I do?
Oh, no, man.
Oh, my God.
He's removing all limiters.
Don't worry.
Don't die.
Please don't die.
I thought.
How did you die?
I wasn't patient.
Is that what you want me to say?
Doki!
I have so much I have to die.
It's okay.
I'm not dying.
It's okay, I'm not dying this time!
I'm there!
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here!
What's this?
I'm here!
Just keep dodging!
Look, I'm here!
I can't look!
I'm almost there!
Don't die!
You're so good at that, though!
You're so good at that!
It's the whole pop-up party, did you say?
I thought you're really good at it.
I am really good.
That's why I've been lasting so long.
I've gone three times.
I was confused.
He makes broken mics on the back, Doki.
I was so confused.
Doki!
I'm running out of space.
I'm almost there.
Don't worry.
Don't worry, I'm almost there.
Don't worry, Gooby.
I'm almost there, Gooby.
I'm almost there.
You got this, Gooby.
You got this.
No!
Look at the sea on the fucking bucket, you fucking bitch!
Okay.
Oh,
yeah, what about the pinball?
Trust me, yes, trust me, Kumi, keep trusting me.
Oh, I'm the shooter.
I'm the shooter.
Where is he?
You're the one with the fucking GPS, dog?
Oh,
left.
I know.
I'm screen-peaking now.
I thought you don't believe in screen-peaking.
I didn't until this game happened.
Where is he?
Oh, there he is.
Wait, no, you missed.
No, I didn't.
Wait, what?
How did I die?
How did I miss?
Okay.
One last, one last one.
Oh, he's so close this time.
We did it.
We're such a good team.
How do we get back to Rose?
I can't let you harm her.
I'm a best friend.
Let me twist the blinds.
You're an asshole!
Whoa!
I'm not an asshole.
I just know what's good for our daughter.
I'm gonna close my blinds.
The sun's in my eye.
I can ask Rose to play with you again.
But you have to help us get back to her.
I'm back.
Is the monkey dead yet?
No, man.
You won't make her cry.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We promise.
Of course, we will never do that again.
Dude, you're such a ghastlyer.
I like how...
Oh my god, so it's Deadpool Super Chat.
It's like, it's like Harambe off over again.
No!
There she is.
She's over there.
Rose!
Sweetie!
Darling!
Look!
This might look strange, but it's us.
It's mom and dad.
Rose!
We need your help.
Look.
Rose is us.
Oh my god, why is she writing?
Is she writing her?
I'm running away letter?
Oh my god, this is like inside out What the fuck you're
hitting her CPS CPS CPS
Wait, I can't do a British accent.
I'll just say by talking a British accent.
I can't do it Oh, I can move like items Dude, imagine she
fucking thinks she's haunted now.
Dude, that was shit.
Oh my god, we're getting closer to math.
We have the power to affect stuff around her.
She's gonna believe in ghosts now.
Let's destroy something Rose loves to make her proud.
Whoa!
Goomy!
Rose loves her elephants.
It's her best friend.
You're gonna kill the elephant.
We make Rose cry.
Hey, my bad I'll buy her a new one.
I promise You're a name and they I'm okay.
I'm an enabler.
Yeah I would admit I'm an enabler, but you had the idea
Enable but you had the idea first Oh
My nose is itching.
Yeah, that's the dust.
We must remember to clean under her bed.
Ah-ch-ch-ch-ch!
Yeah, noted.
Alright, here we go.
Oh my god, look at all her socks.
Yeah, exactly.
One less would be a good thing.
Wait, there's a game here!
Where?
We have to buy a replacement, right?
No.
Wait, look at this.
Yeah, it's time.
Oh, it's my favorite number.
Eight, eight, eight, eight.
Lately, she's gotten attached to it again.
I don't know why.
Oh.
Wait, was there an Easter egg over on the left then?
No, no, I'll watch.
All right, give me a little car.
Drive the car.
Oh, there is.
There is a little car.
Oh, I think I have to push you.
Yeah, but is there like...
we have to do any of this.
Whoa, it is!
There's a rodeo!
Wait, come back!
Yeah, just...
Oh, I have to take you back.
Hold it!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm coming back.
I'm coming back.
Oh, the game was, like, behind us.
That was the main area.
Alright, I held eight.
Oh, my bad.
Sorry, I sneezed.
What?
There you go.
So you made Did you crash?
I'm stuck here.
I did it every time.
Every time I did it every fucking time.
Don't worry, I'm getting you in right now.
I'm getting you in.
You're in.
What?
I crashed again.
Huh?
Oh my god, I crashed again.
Okay, you're in again.
You're in again.
Okay, we're good.
We're good now.
I'm in.
Okay.
That means we're close.
Yeah, we're closer to the sea.
Okay.
Let's go to the rodeo.
One less would be a good thing.
Wait, I'm getting the car first.
I think the car progressed it, doesn't it?
Yeah.
Yeah, we'll just get a replacement.
Yeah, yeah, it like progressed it.
I think you should...
I'm ready for the rodeo.
I can't get out.
I literally mean it.
What is wrong with your game?
What do you mean?
Why do you keep crashing?
You couldn't get out.
You left the session.
I was able to keep honking it.
You exploded on my screen.
What do you mean?
I literally saw you explode on my screen.
Oh my god.
Here you go.
Let's go do the fucking radio.
The rodeo.
Yay.
Why don't we stop?
Stay on the bull as long as you can.
How do you do that?
I don't know.
Won't happen.
I'm glued to this bull.
Oh, oh, it's just it's it's just a rhythm game So I assume
it gets worse, right?
Look at me go Oh my gosh, so fucking easy
Is that not B?
Why do I keep crashing?
Why?
Did you crash again?
Why does it keep happening?
It won't let us progress.
Okay, let's just not do the rodeo.
Let's not do the rodeo.
Let's just progress the game.
It's the server.
Oh my god!
It won't even let me connect to the server.
Pretty boy Give me a I think this was a good point to stop.
I Gooby I think I think this is a good time.
It's not my PC issue.
It's connection It's a connection It's not it's not even the
PC issue Yeah It's okay.
We could finish it another time.
It's a server issue.
I have a great time, though, Gumi.
I think our marriage has been quite solid so far.
Yeah, no.
That was pretty cool.
It's pretty solid.
Did you had a great time?
I think I had a great time.
Yeah, I had an awesome time.
If you had to rate it out of 10.
oh yeah definitely an eight an eight why isn't it a nine at
least what did i do that doesn't make it a nine like name
one thing remember you standing next to a button while i was
fighting for my life against a moon baboon no i don't
remember that you don't remember that no no i don't i don't
know what you're talking about there
But anyway, that was good fun!
What part of the game are we on now?
What?
Did your chat know how far we are in the game?
How far are we, guys?
How far are we in this game, chat?
You guys know?
Out of how many?
We're at chapter five!
We're 50%.
Hold on.
I see that you have a poll up.
Who's the reason for the divorce?
71% Doki.
No, I know.
No, I don't.
We're at 50%.
Alright, next week we're beating it.
We're beating it next week.
Give me a day.
No, next week.
We'll figure it out.
Okay, but I will say...
Yeah.
I'm not...
Actually...
No, I am here next week.
Alright, yeah.
Next week we'll finish it.
Yeah.
We can do it.
We're like speedrunning this.
It's so easy.
Yeah, it's so easy.
I think if we cut out all the times, we, like, clearly we're
just messing about.
Yeah.
We would have been, we might be, like, like, 70.
We would have been 70% done if we didn't fuck around too
much.
If we, as a team, together, didn't fuck around that much.
I think we would have been, like, 70% done.
Yeah, I think if we both completed the challenge, challenges
as fast as we could.
But we were just messing with them now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We, as a team, were messing around together.
Together.
Mm-hmm.
Anyway, we're gonna call it here, guys.
Thank you all for coming.
I don't know if you're gonna call it here, Gumi.
I think you're gonna keep playing Minecraft.
I'm gonna call it here.
I'll see you next time, Gumi.
I'll message you after this.
Yeah, yeah.
Bye-bye, Goonie.
Bye-bye.
Alright, everybody.
I think I did really well.
I think I'm perfect husband material.
Don't you guys think so?
I honestly, like, I did not realize this game was like, had
so many things in it.
The only thing I knew about this game was like the math
part.
And I didn't realize how much more complicated this game was
beyond math i was like holy shit there's more to this game
than just the math portion there's so much more there's bees
and rats tree rats anyway guys i'm gonna call it here
everybody and take a rest day take tomorrow's a rest day i'm
gonna rest today um i feel very very tired today was a very
very busy week for me so i'm going to you know i actually
was tempted to like actually like I think I'm one I was like
flat thinking about at rescheduling the rescheduling the
steam stream because I was feeling really really tired but I
was like no no the happiest I feel is when I'm streaming and
I'm no I when I stream I will feel so much better so like I
like push forward because every time I was like oh my gosh
I'm so tired I'm so tired and exhausted I was like no Doki
you're happiest when you're streaming and you'll feel so
much better you do the stream and I did I felt so much
better yeah it does help I love streaming um and I always
love streaming for so it does help so i'm glad i did stream
yesterday um but yeah i'm gonna take a rest now i'm sorry i
can't do a little i have we haven't done like a little like
end of stream zastodons in a while or like do like super
chat readings at the end um i'm still trying to like slowly
uh not slowly like fast adjust right now to everything going
on there's so many like behind the scenes stuff that i
always have to do every day um so that's why there hasn't
been much like zastodons at the And yeah, when I finally
stabilize, we will have our, we will bring back a little
chat together at the end of the streams and the super chat
readings at the end of the stream.
But yes, thank you, everybody.
As always, everyone, stay hydrated, posture checked, get up
and move around to get that blood flowing.
And if you stay up for me, head to bed because you deserve
it.
I'll see you guys next time, everybody.
Bye, guys.
Bye.