sorry guys for being late I went outside to get food because
I was hungry and then because I didn't eat dinner last night
I was like so oh my god bomb bomb sorry I got I don't have
ADHD I just got distracted all right jokie bird I swear to
God somebody claimed fucking jokie bird terms of use okay
good Nobody claimed Dokey Bird.
Nobody else claimed Dokey Bird during the beta test.
That's great to know All right.
Oh, no, you guys are not seeing a cool ass intro.
I'm so sorry Sorry, you guys missed out on the cool ass
intro.
It was really fucking cool
You guys missed out on the cool ass intro because I was too
oh my god, is this window capture?
i forgot this is window oh my god i forgot this sorry i'm a
mess right now um i literally just got back from eating uh
and then um i could have went straight to do stream but then
i also um t he i also um other than eating i also went over
to to pet my dog because like he deserves it because he's a
good boy uh so so so and then and i didn't realized that
there was a huge ass patch that was going on so i had to
wait for the patch to finish and everything but i didn't eat
dinner last night and i didn't eat oh my gosh dad is still
here looking at me did you miss me did you
oh you know how like okay i don't know if like your dog does
this um but like whenever like my whenever like i stick my
hand out uh dad like gets two little stubby hands and like
um and like latches onto one hand while i pick him up and
it's so cute like he he has he just latches onto one arm
like like like a koala and then like and i pick him up it's
so fucking cute oh my god and then he started tucking his
head underneath my arms now oh yeah sorry sorry i don't have
ADHD.
I'm just, I think I don't have ADHD.
Um, but yes, that's why I'm really sorry for being late.
Um, I didn't have lunch and I didn't have dinner last night
because I was so tired that I went straight to bed.
I went straight to bed and then, um, and then I just slept
all the way until 3 p.m.
I slept all the way until, no, not even 3 p.m.
I slept all the way till 4 p.m.
and went out to eat at um you know took a shower went out to
eat at a restaurant and oh wait no jk i woke up to make my
waiting room and then i went back to sleep i was like i
gotta make my waiting room and and i made my waiting room
went back to sleep and then i woke up at four took a shower
and then went out to eat because i was so fucking hungry um
since i didn't eat anything and then yeah and then i
finished eating at like 4 50 or whatever and that fucking
like not i like sprint walked over like i i hate i hate what
is it called like because like i know sprint walking is an
actual olympic sport what's it called again that thing where
you where you're like power walked is it power walk because
i know like that's an olympic sport uh yeah i power walked
back home and then dad was like pet me and then i was like
oh okay i'm sorry dragoons but if dad wants pet sees that's
important so so i was petting dad for like a couple of
minutes before i was like okay now i i turn on the pc um but
yes anyway speaking of olympics they just literally just
announced that um esports is going to be an olympic sport
now you know know how okay for those who didn't watch the
collab was zen and amali i was talking about how like they
had uh video games as an olympic sport but they weren't
really like they weren't really esport titles they were like
archery and like archery and soccer and all that in like
it's like it's like we sports but like olympics anyway so
they had that but today they vote the committee finally
voted um they finally voted in uh uh esport titles as a real
as a real olympic um for the real olympics but the funniest
thing is that there's no fps games i thought that was so
funny i i fucking you guys were like coping like no fps
isn't dying i fucking shooters are dead i knew it fps
shooters not just But shooters in general shooting games.
It's dying.
We're not even invited to League Rocket League got into the
Olympics before us.
That's fucked up.
Mobile games are in the Olympic esport games.
Is that fucked up?
Like mobile games are in it.
Shooters are not.
We are the new RTS of the generation.
We are the RTS of this generation.
Anyway, speaking of shooters, I'm going to be playing Marvel
Rivals.
All right.
Do you guys want to know?
Which?
Okay.
These are the games I got in.
League of Legends, Rocket League, Street Fighter, Tekken, I
Racing.
NBA 2K.
How the fuck do you guys know?
You make an Olympic sport out of NBA 2K.
Anyway, and then there's FIFA and mobile games.
So, all I'm saying is that developers, publishers of
shooting games did not give them a big enough check.
Because apparently, majority of these games that got in was
funded by the Saudi government.
That's why I'm surprised Apex didn't get in because Falcon
has an Apex team.
That's literally Imperial House team.
So all I'm saying is that Apex did not pay enough to be in
the Olympics.
They literally had oil money.
We don't have oil money, guys.
the shooter FPS game community does not have oil money
where's our oilers who will represent us yes it's the actual
Olympics they literally voted for the Olympic esport games
no we deserve oil money please big day for soccer moms who
have 500 plus hours on candy crush thank you for the super
chat no name thank you thank you yeah unfortunately we did
not have enough funding to have um we didn't have enough
funding for uh to be in the limping's d dragon thank you the
super chat thank you thank you laughs and fighting games i
told you guys i think like i'm really good at analyzing the
current trends Because I told you guys, I was like, oh yeah,
fighting games.
Fighting games are clearly, like, on the rise right now.
Because, I mean, they're expanding.
They literally announced, like, an expansion for Evo.
So, I had a feeling that fighting games is, like, the newest
gaming trend.
All right, let's see.
All right, so, Marvel Rivals!
Marvel Rivals!
A huge shout-out to the devs for giving me an invite to
Marvel Rivals.
Close beta.
I did an alpha.
alpha test and now I'm here for the closed beta.
So the interesting about it is that there are new characters
now.
Venom's in here now.
Whoa.
I hope the volume's okay.
I don't know if SoundGuy is still at Evo.
Oh, that's so cool.
Wait, I want to watch that again.
That is actually really cool.
Oh, yeah, the devs DM me on Discord to give me some codes.
Let's see.
Using his symbiote.
Oh, It's Eddie.
It's Eddie Brock.
Oh, that's so fucking cool.
I really like the animation.
We can be Boop.
Oh, he can be blue, Eddie.
First appears in Marvel Rivals.
Oh, this is his first appearance.
Side and Clash.
Surrender.
Now I'll be feasting on your brain.
What's the difference between... I guess he's blue.
Oh.
Oh my god, that's so fucking cool.
Wait, I really like... Is he a tank?
What is he?
okay abilities wait i want to know what is he he is what is
that what is two fists oh you guys can't see it uh okay you
can see his head what is two arms oh he's a tank okay that
makes sense because of his hitbox okay he's a tank all right
what does he do unleash his tentacles forward to attack
enemies oh that's his normal primary feast uh oh okay i'll
bring up the game volume a little bit
All right.
What's this?
I didn't get to see this.
What is this?
We're all underground for free movement.
Oh, my God.
What the fuck?
Wait, that's so cool.
That's his cue.
What's his shift?
Oh, he can swing around.
Hey, Dad.
Sorry, he looked up at me and was like, kiss?
And I was like, okay.
All right.
Symbiogenerates bonus health against dad.
damage the greater the bonus help generates oh what oh
that's um that's basically hammond that's hammond orissa
sigma thing where you press it and then you get like health
back uh frenzy arrival what's this oh that's the oh so i
brought up the volume a little bit more sound guide Nepis,
thank you for the five get the ships, thank you, thank you.
Cellular corrosion.
Unleash technicals to slow enemies within reach.
Okay, that slows them down and also damages them.
That also damages them.
And then, oh, oh, that's the Spider-Man shit.
Okay, that, no matter what this in the Spider-Man one is
like, it's so disorienting.
I do not, I don't know how anybody can play this.
we were spider-man we were like fucking everywhere and I was
I was like I wanted to I don't get motion sickness but like
that shit fucking sucked like all right what's this venom
shares a part of symbios with spider-man Peter Parker
activating your symbiotic abilities spider-man Peter penny
Parker can convert this time into explosive spikes oh so
like if we have penny and oh my god okay that's crazy that's
actually crazy all right what's this hero story oh my god
you can lock hero stories all right i just realized i should
check the my settings my settings for this oh no not fucking
no no no no no all right let's see limit fps uh 120 that's
like the max i didn't realize that was the max there's no
way okay show my fps please i realize they reset everything
oh yeah everything has been reset okay i'm gonna set medium
um confirm i forgot everything has been reset uh full screen
uh be synced audio let's see all right audio guy let me know
what i should bring up from
playback voice chat voiceover subtitles yeah we always want
voiceover subtitles uh i don't know i actually don't know if
if this is the default i i don't remember has anyone does
anyone get into the beta is this the default or do i have to
redo my um uh meme settings 100 no it's at 200 okay okay dad
you're going down all right is that default yeah this is the
for okay that's default all right i have to change that then
uh let's see a dot oh my god everything reset everything
reset no i hate it when everything resets itself all right
you play with dot ally on um Is melee?
Did they reset melee as well?
Melee attack?
Yeah, they did.
Everything is reset.
So, guys, nothing.
Alright.
Oh.
Sorry, dad's gone now.
They actually reset everything.
Oh, that sucks.
That really sucks.
Because I know I know that... Alright, bring Mastery to 100.
Okay.
I know that, like, I had, like, specific controls.
So, yeah.
I hate when that happens because ah because i i didn't see
does anyone remember what my sense was did anyone guys can
anyone go through my my first marvel rival streams and tell
me what my sense is please i need to know i need to know
what my sense is somebody check my vibe people are like why
don't you check your own vibe because then You guys can plus
more views on it and I can get more ad.
At least I'm being truthful.
At least I give it to you straight and I don't lie.
1.09.
Nice.
Is it 1.09?
Is it actually?
That's smart.
Okay.
Look, I give it to you straight.
I don't, I didn't lie about it, okay?
All right.
Is it actually 1.09?
Okay, 1.09.
That's great.
Thank you, guys.
And thank you for giving me that plus one view on that
Marvel rival VOD so I can get one more cent in ad revenue.
I really, I really appreciate it.
Thank you for boosting my viewer engagement on the other VOD
as well.
For those who are watching the VOD, hey, can you get, for
those who are watching the VOD, it down below what my sense
is and
for those who are watching that vibe comment below to tell
me what sense I was using on my last vibe um anyway let's
see I think that's everything I think uh I'm gonna double
check yeah I think that's everything I think that's all I
have to reset in alright what are the other ones I know
there was another they added another new hero oh yeah there
you go adam warlock this is the other guy the gold guy the
guy with mommy issues uh the genetically engineered adam
warlock wields mighty quantum magic allowing him to wait is
he a fucking heel slot oh he is wait he is oh my god he is
but he was so strong guardians of the galaxy
gentle touch when the time comes for his allies to unite but
like he killed so many people and guardians of the galaxy I
don't understand cosmic Jade okay so so that's him but with
Jade colors that's the MC version he got better he became a
support player.
It's better.
Alright, what's this?
Launch the quantum energy to deal damage.
Wait.
Is this?
Oh my god, he's mercy!
He is!
He's a huge flood of Marvel rivals!
Die!
I have res!
He has the OG res!
Rez ability.
Everybody die on point.
I have Rez.
No way.
Guys, die on point.
I have Rez.
I have karmic revival.
Guys, I have karmic.
Die on point.
Oh, gee, Brissy.
Run it back.
We're running it back.
Avengers never die.
Monster, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Fun fact, Adam Warlock in the comics is the primary enemy of
Thanos.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
All right, that's his that's his all too, by the way.
That's his all.
United the Souls granting them healing over time and
distributing damage taken across the bond.
Oh, okay.
So like we share the day.
Wait, that's so fucked.
Wait, do they die?
Together?
Oh my, wait, that's so fucked.
Oh, you guys, like, take damage.
You guys, like, share damage as a soul bond.
What's this?
I mean, this is actually a really cool ability.
Target an enemy for a bouncing stream of healing, which also
heals himself upon casting.
Self-targets if no alley is selected.
Uh, oh, okay.
Okay, so healing them will heal me.
I see.
Uh...
what's this and then swiftly launch okay that's just the
attack and then regenerative cocoon and adam can fully move
as a soul and reforge his body oh so he has he has second
life wait that's wait he's pretty broken i think his heel
must not be that strong then he must not have a strong heel
because like all his heels are all his heels are abilities
yeah he all he all he does he can attack there's this damage
his like secondary and primary are damage but his healing
ability are abilities like i mean sorry his healing are just
abilities so basically he's mostly he's like a dps more than
a healer um i feel like and then he can okay What's this?
Enhances the Reaper Power of Starlord.
Granite and Power.
Oh, they will all, if you have Starlord and Mantis, they can
also revive.
His E is strong and has two charges.
Oh, this one?
Okay, it has two charges.
Yeah, but I feel like he's more so of a damaged character
because he only heals from his abilities alone.
So he doesn't heal from anything else.
So there's only two new characters.
I believe, this is why I mean...
Wait, wait, no, not her.
This is Juno.
This is literally Juno.
But like, K-pop.
This is literally her.
Alright.
Let's see.
It's the clap healer.
Yeah, it's clap to heal.
That's her.
Alright, so what did sound guys say?
Turn down sound effects and bring up.
Alright, let's see.
Sound effects.
let's bring you down and then i'll bring you down to 85 and
then i'll bring up the volume a little bit there you go i
brought it up a little bit all right guys time to check it
out time to check out the game it's just me quick match
conquest respond to a flexible location and eliminate as
many oh is this death match i think this is death match this
has to be death match because it's like conquest yeah she
collapsed to heal uh emil bring more effects effects than
just healing monster and thank you super chill thank you
thank you yeah that's very interesting um because like adam
is clearly a very like dps character um versus the healer so
it's very interesting to like see in general all right royal
palace time for death match i'll play adam let's see what
it's as adam all right where is i will bring peace to this
universe all right to maintain a fair game environment voice
chat oh okay you're recorded all right that's cool all right
what's what's everybody else playing for death match is this
death match only one i don't know is it like wait oh oh it's
a team death match okay it's team death match all right and
then okay i can charge that i can charge that oh what the oh
we're straight in okay we're straight in okay
that is so disorienting i'm sorry that is actually so
disorienting It was not ready for that.
Oh my god.
There's so many things
Oh god.
I'm running away.
I'm running away bro.
What the fuck?
They're at 10 kills
Jesus Christ.
Okay guys, I don't know if I want to Whoa, who am I playing
against?
Are they fucking in a stack?
Because what the fuck is going on?
They have to be in a stack or something.
Because what?
Oh, God.
This is bad.
This is what?
This is.
All right, who is?
All right, it's time.
It's time.
I don't remember the abilities.
But it's time.
By the way, I don't remember the abilities at all, guys.
I think I remember, like, the one thing I did not like is I
did not remember the abilities.
Oh, God.
I remember now I have to set these up.
I wrote deleted.
Okay, this should not have been my first game.
I'm so disoriented right now.
I am really sorry Holy shit Alright That was fast That was
so fast Alright we're gonna play call quest at another time
I can't I literally did not have time to learn the game I
did not Bro I didn't have time to learn the game What What
All right, Conquest fucking sucks.
I'm going to do a quick match.
Okay, if you want to learn the game, do not play Conquest.
I did not have time to, like, register anything.
I literally showed up, and then the enemy team got 20 kills
in literally 10 seconds.
I don't know how that was possible.
I don't know.
That was possible.
That was so fast.
I didn't get 10 kills that fast.
Okay, now I can learn the game.
Hmm.
Okay.
Let's see.
F1.
I need to remember.
Okay.
Shift is the soul bond.
E.
Okay.
Shift is soul bond.
E is the avatar life steal.
Okay.
Use the heals and I can get soul bond to people.
Alright, I'm just going to get soul bond to everybody.
I'm going to get soul bond to everybody I see.
Why learn when you can die?
Jesus Christ.
Alright, it's okay.
We're fine now.
We've learned how to play this game now.
Alright.
Everything is fine.
I can finally learn.
Wait, is this a new map?
This is a new map, right?
Or is this...
Yeah, wait.
Is this... No, no, no, this is not.
This is not the new map.
This is an old map.
It just... It looks a lot better.
Wait, they like changed stuff.
I just realized.
Alright, so bond time!
You two!
You're so bonded, even if you did not want to be.
Congratulations!
Oh God to reload there is not a lot of ammo by the way There
is not a lot of ammo
Holy shit Get here Get here, oh, I guess Get here I keep
thinking I keep trying to shoot the heal right now.
This is not good Come on, Magneto's load!
So bond!
Even if he didn't want to, you're so bonded now!
I don't like the lack of ammo.
I'm not gonna lie.
I feel like I do not have a lot of ammo.
It's so bonded!
It's okay.
Phew!
Oh wait, he's one, he's one!
Nice, I got him.
Okay.
Yeah!
Well, poor Spider-Man, I already used up my abilities.
Wait.
Who's that?
Who did that?
Oh god, get healed!
So bounded even you didn't want to!
Oh my god, clap to heal!
Nice, easy, it's so fucking easy.
Aggressive.
Heal.
I don't know what some of these items are.
Alright, nice.
What is that?
Who is that guy?
Heals.
Get healed!
Get so bounded!
That's fucking right now, your best friend!
Heal!
Wait, I snapped a heal.
That's cool.
I like that I'm snapping to heal.
So bound!
Raze!
I have Raze!
There you go!
Best decision of my life!
I am blue!
Woo!
There you are.
Oh, the punch!
Snap!
Oh, I can't snap!
I can't snap, snap!
I snapped, guys!
Snap to here!
Snap!
I'm trying my best.
So bounded.
You're best friends now.
You're welcome.
You're now best friends.
Alright.
It's only the Sephora live right now.
But I can headshot though.
So it's fine.
Guys!
Where's our tanks?
They're getting closer!
Guys.
Where's our tanks?
I feel safe!
Friend maker!
Oh, get away healer!
Only I get- Snap!
Snap!
Oh shit!
I like the snap ability, it's actually really fun.
Bro, who keeps healing this bitch?
Best friends!
What does the Soulbound do?
Basically, like, it makes it so, um...
Snap!
Oh no.
Oh no, I don't want to fear.
Oh, he missed!
That's fucking right, bitch!
Get shit out.
Snap!
He's too far away and can't snap!
He's oh, I don't have abilities.
That's why.
That makes more sense.
I just did it.
What the fuck?
Is he that?
Not him?
Is that...
Why is he moving?
Oh god.
I am at your service.
Die!
I have friends!
Damn point!
Die on point!
I don't think I should like spam that though.
I should use that when like we're actually in danger.
Oh no, he's gonna dance!
He's gonna dance now!
So bound!
Okay, nice.
This is so easy.
Wait, already?
That's a really fast ult.
This is such an easy game.
should have been my first game no I'm shipping my own team
that's different bro this is sad this is so this should have
been my first game yay so bonding I'm just making sure
they're like best friends now they are bots no they're real
people they're real people so fucking easy i know because i
got absolutely fucking destroyed in my first game like
there's no way there's no way these guys aren't real i got
destroyed in my first game chat I have Jesus Christ 9000
damage there's no way a Bob would not be there's no way this
has to be a real person I refuse I will prove to you this
guys that this is a real person I'm gonna add them as a
friend I will I will prove to you they're a real person
because I will add them as a friend if they real
No way AI best friend
All right, what if bots then AI is truly taking over if bots
can add friends?
I don't know.
I think Adam's pretty fun.
I don't like his projectile speed that much though His
projectile speed is not like the best no they took Adam no
um hell is fun to play all right over I remember she was fun
uh let's see shift E project an explosive no I forgot her
abilities please I wanted to read a little longer they magic
but magic has like portals and melee, and I get very
confused.
Okay, there's that.
And then...
What was the E again?
How do I look at her thing?
Okay, there you go.
Uh, E, okay, it's a stun.
Okay, that stuns.
And then...
This is my escape ability.
Okay.
Uh, okay, I can fall slowly.
Wait, how do I fall slowly?
Oh, there we go.
Wee!
all right three two I know Hella is like really strong like
especially at all what the fuck oh that's a that's just the
the decoration okay sorry I got really confused I was like
what the fuck is that on oh that's that's the card wait
that's I swear to God that was not what it looked like
before that was not what it looked like tank us someone save
the tank someone save the tank Oh no, I'm so bonded.
Who are my best friends with?
Who's my best friend?
Okay, I need to know who it is.
Okay, all right I need to use my more our Loki is like
tanking so hard Get over there.
That's right.
No, he didn't block that.
Wait, that's new That is new.
We got to get the tank Come on!
Headshot!
No!
A stupid Ryan shield!
What the fuck?
Who's that?
Oh, that's Iron Man.
Come on!
Come on, anime!
You can't glide forever!
God damn it.
Okay, he can.
Come on, Iron Man!
That's right!
Get over here!
That's fucking right!
Wait, why am I flying?
How did I start flying?
got me up in the sky who got me there all right get that
rocky raccoon goodbye goodbye rocky raccoon oh shit oh no
it's magneto it's magneto guys he has Zarya bubble okay I'm
gonna just let's just walk guys let's just walk away we
don't have to be there wait no this is a new map it's I've
never seen this map all right get that rocky raccoon get
over here get over here your rodent oh shit i'm joking jk jk
jk where am i getting shot from oh it's it's you no so by me
so by me so by me okay we're there Oh, nice.
That's fucking right.
Oh, I see you.
I have was.
Nice.
Don't choke.
I never choke.
Watch this.
Wait, where am I getting shot from?
Oh, shit.
So bomb me.
I know we have an atom.
I know we have atoms.
Oh my god.
Oh god.
Where am I getting shot from?
No, that's not I'm so confused like where am I getting shot
from?
Oh, that's you That's fucking right.
You can't fuck with me Yeah, hell is damage.
It's insane She used her damage used to be really really
good, but like I feel like they buffed her damage not gonna
lie Oh, we have high ground I have to go up Where are they?
Get over you think flying is gonna stop you?
Oh, I see you little guy.
I see you.
Oh, where did he go?
Oh, wait, it's Adam.
Get over here, Adam.
That's fun.
Get your ass over here.
Oh, no!
Ah!
Save me so funny!
Oh, thank God.
Alright.
I'm okay.
Sorry, I was just an overreaction.
Sorry, it was just a little overreaction, but I'm okay now.
They know the carry.
They're always trying to...
Oh.
Oh my god.
Oh, that was scary.
I don't... I don't know what that was.
I have no idea what that was there.
Okay.
Am I going high ground?
Maybe?
Okay, I can only literally hit one person.
Guys, break the area!
Oh, nice!
No!
It's fine, we're fine.
We're fine.
And then...
Where's my team?
Wait, did everybody die?
I am not fine.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, everybody.
I didn't realize everybody was dead.
How long is this point?
I swear, Venom, are you okay?
But also, how long is this point?
I swear.
I swear to God, this is...
Okay, I can fucking kill you.
Wait, where?
Wait, that's not fair.
He just flew away.
That's not fair.
That's fucking right.
Okay, I did a backup.
up a little bit.
I do have the soul bond, so we're fine.
Jesus, this is so hard to push.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, where did you come from?
It's okay, I'm a crow.
I'm crow now.
And he heals.
Thank you.
He snapped a heal.
Jesus Christ.
This one area is so hard to push.
This is like the Anamura.
Oh, he's insane.
Get him!
He's insane!
no bot would just fucking stop moving that's when you know
he's real why did he stop moving or this is good I have all
soon the all that's so strong for this area wait do we do it
that's it they backed off wait they just backed off and
That's fucking right.
Sorry, the bot's not...
Endorse me.
Oh my god!
Okay, she is so strong.
Wait, she's actually so fucking strong.
Holy shit.
11,000 damage.
Oh my god.
That's actually crazy.
That's really...
That's a lot.
Compared to everybody else.
That's right.
You all...
Who the fuck is she?
What does she do?
She had 6K.
You guys are stacking, you fucking losers.
And...
She did nothing.
You're really gonna get...
Give the person who has 6K half my...
damage the same amount of endorsements
there's no way a bot do a stack affiliate they give a 10 get
the ships they get the ink too all right oh I'm flicking
okay they have zero support oh I know they have rocket
raccoon it's Adam Todd don't Don't worry.
It's Adam time.
Snap to heal.
Don't worry everybody.
I am ready.
Where do I go?
Guys, the moment I figure out this map, do not worry
everybody.
Snap.
So bonded.
Best friends forever.
Snap.
Where are they?
I think the only issue...
Jesus Christ, guys, guys, I don't have a lot of snaps to
give you guys.
Guys, I'm running out of snaps!
Chill!
Snap!
Guys, I'm running out of snaps!
We got so fun!
I'm trying to snap!
Guys, I don't...
Guys, these guys are good.
We're still bonding!
Oh, God.
I'm running out.
Snap!
Okay.
Guys, I can't snap forever, guys.
You guys can't be best...
I don't have enough friendship bonds for all of you.
I don't have enough friendships!
Guys, I'm running out of friendship bracelets!
Snap!
Please!
Snap.
Oh my god, I snapped so many times.
So bad!
Oh god.
No!
It's okay, I have cocoon.
Goodbye.
Oh, I should not have cocoon there.
Oh little spiders get over here little spiders Oh Leave me
alone Snap Oh god I'm sorry you're fucking dead I'll do born
again here I don't think our team is good Guys I have a
feeling my team is dog shit Just a little bit Oh my god
these guys Snap!
Snap!
Oh, fuck that!
They know!
Please, somebody soul bond right now!
Oh, God.
There's so many soul bonders.
Oh, no!
No!
Oh, thank God!
Oh, thank God he's bad!
Thank God!
Snap!
This is so, so hard to control sometimes.
Oh, who's feasting?
Who's feasting?
I don't have Snap!
I'm sorry, sorry, Lauren!
I'm sorry!
I didn't prep enough friendship bracelets for everybody!
Okay.
Snap.
Alright.
This is actually so difficult.
Oh My god, I'm so disoriented.
Who are you Peter Parker?
Oh God, Peter Parker.
So bot.
No, yo, you're dead Somebody get Peter Somebody get him Oh,
God.
Oh, God.
It's okay.
I have health back Try my best I don't I don't do enough
hands for this Snap!
Snap!
Raise!
Don't die on point!
I'm so disoriented right now, guys.
Oh, God!
Spider-Man's beating my ass!
Please, just one!
He's literally one!
Oh, God.
I'm snapping!
I'm snapping out of fear!
Oh god, okay, we're good.
We're okay.
We're okay, guys.
Everything...
Everything is fine.
Sorry, I'm getting...
This is a lot.
Get away!
Friendship!
Oh no, I can't do friendship.
Right now I need two seconds cooldown.
I feel like I see somebody behind us.
behind us?
No.
Friendship!
Okay.
That's good.
Oh, no.
They went...
They went Marvel Aquaman.
I'm sorry for all.
Namor?
Where is his movie?
Oh, shit.
No, I have to heal myself.
I have to heal by myself now.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no!
Please live a little bit longer!
Okay.
I don't have enough heals.
Don't have enough snaps for everybody.
Please calm down.
Okay, nice.
We're good.
Where is he?
Alright, he's over there.
I mean, we're doing a lot better than the other team last
game when they had to defend.
Honestly.
He does not want friendship.
Get him from the turret for him.
friendship on I feel like it's good to give that to oh he's
one oh I think our tank died I think guys I think our tank
died guys that's right I can fucking
that fish was insane though that fish was scary as hell all
right nice all right nice I think we're doing really well
that is not a bot a bot would not have a twitch name did you
not see that I saw the twitch name a bot would not have a
name Oh my god, was that a fucking nuke?
Come on, that's fucking right you think you can oh wait
never mind you can okay friendship bond.
Oh, oh friendship bond, please please Oh god, I need help.
I need help Let me live snap All right, good.
We're fine.
We're fine We're fine Snap.
Oh, I snapped the wrong person.
I'm sorry.
You might, you're gonna die now.
I snapped the wrong person.
I'm sorry.
You were so far.
Nice, we got an assist.
Dude, they're all air.
They know like fucking bots can't, sorry, my teammates can't
shoot air characters.
Nice, we're good.
We did it!
Don't know bots have CTV.
Let's make this bots a CTV name.
Yeah, I'm MVP.
Nice.
What is it?
Oh, okay.
It's because I healed.
Oh, yeah.
Wait, how am I MVP?
Wait, what?
That's right.
Endorse me.
Come on.
Come on, everybody.
I am literally the healer.
You have to endorse me.
That's the rules.
Guys, what?
This is not a team.
gain.
This is my teammates aren't team players.
Wait, I don't even have the most damage.
How do you have 626 damage?
You literally only have a thousand more heals than me.
Wait, how did I get MVP?
Like, did I get MVP?
He has more damage than me.
Oh, the second highest kills?
Oh, oh, it's because I have like Justin has like 21 praise
me exactly look see TTV they're I knew they were real I knew
they were real oh I can see their highlights what's my
highlight what did I do oh oh it could be my KDA too I had a
really good KDA I think I think Adam's pretty fun to play um
all right can i play dps no cannot play dps blues uh
requesting back you know scarlet no fuck off i play you'll
see i feel like adam's a more fun version of low-key not
gonna lie uh all right we'll do low-key i didn't get a
chance to actually play low-key
I need to remember how to play him.
But Loki bird.
Alright, let me...
I need to remember how to play Loki, though.
It's been a while.
Okay, ship, shift into target enemy and use...
Okay, that was the...
All.
Okay, magic field that converts damage.
Oh, this is the damage.
Okay, shift this damage.
Double gangion.
Swap.
Backstab.
And conjure an illusion.
Okay.
I need to remember all I I forgot that Loki was I forgot
that was why Loki was four stars.
Holy shit.
That is a lot
There you go.
Okay, I forgot how complicated Loki was That was that was a
lot of information not gonna lie Oh, God.
There you go.
We're fine.
We're in our little orb.
Get the venom.
Guys, we gotta get venom.
Jesus Christ.
Somebody help!
Jesus Christ!
Magnino, you're taking so much damage!
Guys, you're all taking a lot of damage guys guys you're
taking a lot of damage everybody
did they nerf Loki she does not do a lot of heals or they're
taking a lot of damage it's one or the other I can't tell
everybody is taking it so much damage Jesus Christ I am
healing so much too I'm actually healing a lot okay no is
that new is that new all wait is that new what that is that
a new all let's That wasn't his alt before!
I swear to God!
That was not his alt before.
Like, I remember his alt was not like that.
Yeah, that has to be new.
I do not remember his alt being like that.
That's why I was not- I didn't care.
That's why- that's why I was like, because I- Because I did
not remember his shit.
Okay.
What?
What happened to the spider?
Why did he stop?
Oh.
There you go.
He's one.
Guys, our team.
Our team is struggling.
I'm going to be venom too.
I don't know what his moves are, but I'm going to fuck you
up.
Wait, where did he go?
Oh my god, these guys are good.
Don't mess with the amazing spider.
These guys are good.
Because, like, what the fuck is going on?
What is going on?
Okay, I think they nerfed Loki.
I think they nerfed it.
I swear to God, his heels are so weak.
This game, look, this game in store is inspired by
Overwatch, I'm pretty sure.
I swear like his heels I think it's because like the reason
why I think that he nerfed him is that his heels is so low I
don't like how low his heels are Like the damage to he used
to look he used to be so strong, but like but his damage is
so weak Oh god, oh god, no Had you!
That shit is so broken!
That shit was actually so broken!
Oh my god.
Friendship.
Like even the damage.
Look, like the damage is fucking stronger too.
Like, I feel like I'm actually killing people more easily.
So bad!
I think it's because Adam is new.
So, since Adam is new, they gave him more...
They buffed his damage for sure.
Like, I can feel the buff.
That's fucking right.
You can't run from me.
Like, it feels easier.
There you go.
Res.
Oh, I am sorry.
Whoops.
I had to... I had to do that.
All right, nice.
Oh, it's 99 now.
So fun!
Friendship!
Keep giving us friendship!
Oh shit!
Okay, we're fine.
We're fine.
I just need a snap.
Yeah, Adam hasn't been rebalanced.
Yeah, Loki has definitely got nerfed hard.
Like, like, heals the heals on him is like a lot worse um
the heals on him is definitely like less than what he was on
alpha and his damage for loki is not as strong as adam i
felt like i i tickled people i was like tickling even with
like three loki's i wasn't doing shit yeah but adam is
fucking strong as hell though uh focused on heal damage.
They retooled him!
Like, oh, so he's more like a spy then.
So, like, Loki is a spy.
Instead of, like, a healer.
Uh...
I hope, like...
I hope, um... I hope...
I think most likely we'll retool Adam.
He's way too strong.
I can literally, like, uh, survive for so long because of
it.
Support isn't supposed to be DPS, but I wasn't even healing!
as much.
Snapping was doing more heals than shooting my friends.
I was doing more heals, but snappy!
That's fine.
That's fucking right.
So fun!
Friendship!
Guys, guys, no!
It's okay.
Guys, Finn have tried to destroy friendship, but I'm still
alive!
Okay, the fucking... The bull...
fucking res back is so fucked up oh god he's coming for me
guys he's coming for me he knows no he wants the ruined
friendship oh my god he wants the ruined friendship i
thought yeah that guy's a really good venom player holy shit
that guy was like venoming all over the place friendship is
dead don't worry friendship is coming yay everything is good
okay that spider-man is dog shit that's so bad all right
snap i'm just gonna chill here Oh, he's low, he's low.
He's low.
What is he doing?
You guys hear that?
Friendship.
Oh, there he is!
That's fucking right.
You can't destroy friendship, Venom!
You can't destroy him!
Where did he go?
Oh, there he is.
Oh!
I didn't realize that was not my venom!
That was not my K-pop star!
Rooze!
Yeah!
That was so bossy of me to do Wait, I still died Where's my
raise?
I didn't get the raise I thought I would get the cacood Nice
at least my teammates get the raise I thought that was my
kpop star No one expected the lunacy no yeah we did it oh
yeah do we win that's two points suddenly kpop idol oh it's
on cool down i thought like every time you die you get it
yeah it's like it's a cool down okay i get it now
oh my god that venom that venom did not like me he's like
fuck this one person in particular
I don't endorse myself Their venom was really good It was
like only cuz yeah, that's right endorsed me Endorsed me I
healed you guys.
I gave you guys friendship You kept fucking diving me that
was crazy.
I just kept snapping he was a friendship hater.
Yeah, he He really did that was so fucked up that was so fun
I was like, bro, what if I'm just, I'm just trying to give
friendship to the people?
I won't play DPS.
I don't know, I don't like playing tank.
I think tank is really boring for me.
I want to play...
I'll play tracer.
Alright, what's tracer like?
Uh, engage in a free fight and walk on to enemies in sight.
Loosen sword forward.
Frenzy of shots causing damage to enemies within.
I didn't get a chance to finish reading.
Is this a spider again?
All right, let's see.
We have a tank.
Three DPS.
I think we're gonna do good.
All right.
Dodge in direction in the movement and swiftly reload.
Fire a frenzy of shots causing damage to enemies within
range.
Okay.
So it's like Okay, that's that and then All right, that's
reload.
Okay, I got it.
Wow
Nice.
Oh Charge is really nice actually, but where did it where
did they show up?
Yeah, he's like Reaper.
Wait, he got rid of the dash Didn't he have more of a dash?
I swear he had more
Whoa what the fuck Spider-Man what the fuck No he had He had
like um He had a more of a bigger dash I remembered Didn't
he?
Yeah didn't he have a bigger dash The venom team up Yeah I'm
pretty sure I'm pretty sure he had like a bigger dash before
uh now like dude he doesn't have it anymore this is up this
is up this is up this is up i don't like i don't like him
guys i don't like him i don't like star lord all right let's
see oh we have three deep we do not even have okay we have
all right let's see let's try no i didn't get chance to
figure out what i want to play i was trying to figure out at
least because i don't know how to play him i i don't know
how to play this cat because of the range the cooldown is
insane though.
You can get the cooldown really fast.
Goodbye!
Wait.
No!
All right, let's play.
Let's try it.
Let's do soldier.
I don't know.
I thought I...
Alright, what's that?
Oh, it's a zip.
And then...
That's the smoke.
Okay.
And then I have turret for him.
Alright.
I am soldier now.
Phew!
That's fucking right.
What are you gonna do?
Get in here!
Get over here, Spider-Man!
Wait.
Get over here!
Ha ha ha ha!
It was worth it.
It was fucking...
Whoa!
Oh!
Get him away!
Okay.
Woo!
I'm on high ground now.
That's fucking right.
This is revenge.
No!
That's so fucked!
He destroyed my platform!
Now I don't have high ground anymore!
That's so fucked!
He got Get rid of my high ground!
Yeah!
That's so fucked.
Imagine getting rid of my high ground.
Let's see.
We're fine.
Oh, right click is a shotgun.
Alright.
Where is he going?
Where's Spider-Man?
You can't fucking swing forever, Spider-Man!
I can track!
Spider-Man, I see you!
you can't stay up there forever oh he can guys he can I
learned that he actually can I have the low ground now oh
god that's fucking right oh no oh no yeah don't mess with me
no wait stop stop stop
Wait, it actually stopped.
Okay, it's all right.
Oh, there's too many high ground players.
I had to play soldier to get them down.
I had to...
I can't forget about turret.
Why does Spawn on his shirt always?
Because he's always in the sky.
Okay, I need to...
I need to grab the zip.
Okay, it's okay.
I have high ground again.
five oh turret turret right here no i can't i can't put a
turret here that's fucked that is so fucked come on no no
that's so why wait i'm so why will i ever get high
i'm so sad they i'm so sad Because they keep getting rid of
my high ground.
No, he's won.
He's actually won.
It's not fair.
Why do they all hate me?
I can't believe it.
We don't need to keep taking away my high ground.
It's not fair.
I just want high ground.
Bro, all you're getting healed so...
What the fuck?
I just got set up.
This is fucked, guys.
Like, I can't do anything.
I'm getting cyberbullied.
I ever believe but Scarlet Wish.
Get the fuck hit Venom out of here.
Get Venom out of here.
I'm fucking, this is my forte.
Scarlet Witch, I fucking got you, Scarlet Witch.
That's fucking right.
You're not, you're not doing shit to me this time.
Fuck you Scarlet Witch Oh no oh no I'm sorry I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry I'm so sorry Please I'm so sorry Get away from
me Oh my god I'm sorry get away She won't leave me alone She
won't leave me alone the hood i i don't know what to do oh
my god i need heels i think oh there you go okay nice okay
that was worth the risk i knocked two that was worth it okay
this guy is so good like this guy is actually crazy insane
Oh, God, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys!
Guys!
We have the VM point, guys!
Oh, God.
Guys, we can't get off this point!
This is fucked up because they have...
Because they have, um...
Oh, God.
Get him up.
No, knock back.
No, no.
No.
Oh, boy.
Y'all see a point?
No!
I did.
I right clicked.
I didn't have the cooldown.
Oh, you have to swap?
Oh, yeah, you can swap weapons?
I didn't realize you can swap weapons.
I was like, what are you guys talking about?
I'm doing it.
I just got the smoke.
Okay, we're going to do that.
Alright, we're gonna try soldier again.
Now I know we can swap weapons.
We're gonna play soldier again.
Bro, I was getting cyberbullied by the scarlet witch!
Bitch!
Oh my god.
Just some guy.
Thank you for the magenta soup, but thank you.
Keep an eye on Punisher as a main There's probably gonna be
an update where to give Frank his space guns bike chain and
flaming skull head bro Fuck that scarlet witch though.
This is This fucking scarlet witch.
I don't want it Holy shit I got I got bullied so high Okay,
oh my god.
There it is guys Guys, there it is.
Oh my god, he has two weapons?
He didn't have two weapons before, right?
Oh, it's a black...
No, that venom... Yeah, that venom was...
No, not that venom, that's Scarlet Witch!
Taz guy, thank you for the super chat, thank you.
Thank you.
That's Scarlet Witch fucked me up!
What he did?
I just never used it.
Wait, where's the entrance?
Here, okay.
Guys, I just never used it.
I didn't realize that was the thing, guys.
I'm gonna get in.
It's fucking right.
Get in.
Come on.
You know you want to get in.
I have the high ground.
Oh, there's a Scarlet.
Oh, my God.
It's the same Scarlet Witch, too.
It's the same one.
It's the same one, guys.
I'm scared.
It's her.
Oh, no.
No, I need to get off the thing.
Guys, it's her.
It's her, guys.
Get the Bruce Banner.
Get the Diva Bruce Banner.
Oh, no.
Wait, do we have a Scarlet Witch?
We don't.
Okay, I'm going to be Scarlet Witch if I die to her.
I'll prove to her that I'm the better Scarlet Witch.
I still love that.
Bruce Banner is a diva of Marvel Rivals.
I think that's so funny.
I think that's really cute.
Where's that coming from?
I hear shots.
Oh, no!
Oh, no, she's coming over.
She's coming over.
She's so low.
She can fly twice!
This bitch.
I'm not letting you go.
I know!
Bro, bro, bro, no.
she's coming over no I got baited I got baited the cooldown
is so fast she really was a thing and then she was a thing
again why is your cooldown insane how is I supposed to know
I didn't play scarlet witch yet oh no oh no she has it
shield?
Okay.
Oh no, I'm trying to like find people.
That's fucking...
Oh no, she's hulking up.
She's hulking up.
No.
No!
It's time.
I shall become the Scarlet Witch.
I don't know how to play her, but I shall become the Scarlet
Witch.
That it hit.
on a target or press the generator force field that stuns
the enemy old space consume chaos to fire explosive okay he
stuns and then okay all right it's time it's fucking time
okay and then that's that and then that's what she did to me
wait oh she has two charges oh okay that makes sense now Now
that I'm actually that character, it makes sense.
It's okay.
Oh no.
I can't.
Everybody is so far away!
It's fine.
It's not fine.
That's fucking right.
Oh, that's not fucking right!
It's hella time.
Never mind.
Hella is stronger.
Hella is more fun.
Hella, I feel like I'm actually strong.
Wait, I hear a scarlet witch near us.
I hear a scarlet witch.
right next to us oh no she's like right there oh guys guys
where's our healer guys I need yous please please snap me
just once guys I need some snaps right now I need snaps why
do they all fly please snap snap I really need snaps.
I don't know why they don't snap Okay Okay, where's the
crow?
Hellamon that's fucking get closer.
Oh, oh, that's embarrassing.
Hey guys guys, I Sorry, I I wanted to live
I Oh no, big Hulk, big Hulk.
I'm sorry, I just wanted to live.
Get Baby Diva!
Look, I really wanted to live, okay, guys?
Like, it was very important to me.
It was...
Somebody get the scarlet.
She's literally one.
I'll get her myself.
Guys, it wasn't that big of a...
ways, right, guys?
Oh!
Crow.
Adam!
Get out of there, Adam!
No!
Adam!
Oh, God.
Guys, we are not doing so well right now.
Oh, snap.
I need snaps.
Guys, somebody healed me.
I'm one.
Guys.
Oh, he's gonna catch me.
Yes, oh, thank God.
My friendship.
Oh, they got friendship saved me.
Oh, come on, I have to read no.
Wait, I hear somebody.
Oh, there she is.
I fucking knew it.
That's right.
You can't fucking...
You can't hide from me.
That's right.
Get shit on.
Alright.
We're okay.
Everything is fine.
Oh, there she is.
I need to kill that cosmic I'm fine.
I'll be okay
Oh no Oh god, I'm reloading This is a little scary right now
I can't there's so many things on my screen Nice Oh shit
turret mode turret mode crow
Bitch Get fucking crowed Oh Nice Nice, I made violence over.
Oh Oh Crow, where's my crow Crow She's getting Oh, yeah, oh
thank god Oh, thank God.
It's okay.
Hello, Moe Tap.
That's fucking right.
That's right.
You're gonna go inside!
That's cheating.
That's actually cheating.
He went inside.
How the fuck do I...
Endors.
I can't believe it.
Oh, oh, oh, no more group for him.
He went inside.
that's so cheesy that should be illegal guys I need heals
guys please please hella needs heals please are do we have
zero I think we have do we have zero healers like what's
going on oh there you go Adam friendship friendship came
back to save me
I need to remember to use E.
I keep forgetting about the existence of...
He's one, he's one!
No, he used the fucking tank shit!
No, don't tell!
Kill Adam!
He's literally my only ears!
You can't kill him!
I need the ears!
Yes, I don't know how to... Oh, Adam!
Nice.
We're fine.
I know my place.
I'm very good at Hella.
I know.
Oh, God.
Crow!
There you go.
We're okay.
Don't worry.
Don't worry, Adam.
I got you.
Okay.
Penny.
Oh, I'm not hitting anything.
Penny's dead.
And we have res so we're okay.
We die.
We're okay We're okay I'm just a hella main out She's just
so good Oh my god the moment I swapped the hella look at
that I'm fucking shutting people down.
Oh no, it's overtime.
Oh no Not the whale.
Not the whale.
No, I fucking looked at the wrong way.
I went backwards.
Hello, bones.
Oh, I didn't throw.
Okay, I thought I was throwing again.
I thought I was throwing again with that.
Okay, I got one.
No.
No, I'm sky.
I'm in.
No, we're so...
Is everybody dead?
No, no, everybody's dead.
No, I did so much team, please I did so much team No I die
and we lose I can't believe it.
I got welled and then we lose It's so and then I lost MVP I
Oh my god!
I lost MVP for that!
I'm getting my summoner endorsement.
I did so much!
I actually, I did so much!
We- T was too heavy!
T was too heavy!
Oh my god!
I'm sad.
We- we- we did so much!
you'll need a top-notch team to win this one i can't believe
it i can't fucking believe it i'm gonna all right this is
gonna be a chill game i'm gonna show you guys i'm gonna show
you guys the key pop star the scarlet adventure delayed the
hell i'll show you guys what i mean when i said hella when i
said luna was basically juno you have only one healer it's
time to dance it's time to clap everybody
she's like an ice an ice wizard who sings too all right i
need to look at her stuff again it's been a while all right
so her alt is basically dance to heal and then damaging
enemies are healing whilst during her own health okay fires
attached allies will also restore his health while luna snow
is healing others cast the clump of ice to freeze okay
that's freezes people.
All right.
So watch this.
So she does this.
This is literally Juno's run.
This is literally how Juno runs.
All right.
I don't know.
I haven't.
This is my first time thing.
Whoa.
Okay.
We'll give her that.
It's okay.
Do we have a tank?
Okay, we're gonna give that to our tank then.
All right.
It's all right, I'm healing!
Because we only have one healer, Pandy!
All right.
We're five.
I don't even know if I hit her.
Oh yeah, that should be going towards our fucking...
Oh gosh.
Let's see, I need the tank to have it.
Because it makes sense.
This basically gives her passive over.
Ooh, that Frieza.
Yo, where I got you?
Oh my god, where the fuck?
Where did Spider-Man go?
He died so fast.
I gotta make sure I don't die, because I'm literally the
only healer.
That's fucking right.
Don't attack my fucking team again.
have one tank i have to put it in there i don't i have to
put an aura ball in our guy okay i need to remember what was
shift again shift is oh oh yeah this is the the clap to heal
clap to here clap clap clap that one was clap to heal no i
want to give the thing to our mac meadow where's mac meadow
there you are taco all right Alright, it's almost time to
dance, guys.
It's almost time.
I'm ready to dance.
Holy shit, I built my alt so fucking fast, though.
I just realized.
It literally took, like, less than 30 seconds, I think.
It's time!
Clap!
It's so dumb.
That's so dumb.
Tank isn't even like up there.
Get, get healed!
There's like no point in me ulting.
Alright, I guess we're gonna chill here for a little bit
because I don't think...
Don't make me clap!
Clap!
That's fucking right.
That's right!
It's dancing time!
Get healed everybody!
Get healed!
Woo!
Oh!
Okay, you can't heal from that.
You can't heal from a fucking nuke.
That's good to know.
Chat, that's good to know that that you can't, you can't
survive.
Dancing does not save you from from a nuclear bomb.
You know, I needed to learn that now.
Yeah, I needed to learn that.
Fuck off!
Clap.
How can dancing not protect you from nukes?
I know, right?
How was I supposed to know?
I thought dancing was gonna save us!
With the power of dance!
I can't believe it!
Oh no.
Why does nobody shoot at the top?
Wait, that's it?
Nobody shot me when I was up there.
I just noticed that.
That's all it took?
Nobody shot me.
Oh no, it's time to dance.
Oh no!
Dance, dance, dance, dance, dance!
Oh, dance!
Oh, that was fast.
That's the deepest dump.
up that's true that's so true nice but yeah that's the that
was the kpop healer uh what that was basically the kpop
healer how much healing did I do that's why you guys would
not have done any would not been able to survive without me
just remember that um seven zero zero zero zero zero zero
seven thousand yeah that makes that that yeah their other
their other support had a thousand heels oh my god the
rocket raccoon had a thousand heels that's embarrassing bing
bong i got seven thousand
all right but i think i think yeah that's right upvote me i
think uh luna snow is definitely the Healer.
Um, the easiest Healer in the party.
Ain't No more me.
Alright.
I don't want to play.
I just, like, okay, I'll try.
I don't know.
I feel like Venom is also seems like really difficult too.
I could try Venom.
I could try it.
He has, like, he was like, he seems all over the place when
I was, like, watching people play it.
Venom swing People who are good at Venom were like crazy.
They were like everywhere.
Generate a bonus health.
Okay, that's the bonus health.
Dash to target.
Oh, no, I didn't finish reading.
No, Venom's a tank.
He's a tank.
Oh, shit.
We have team up activated.
Alright.
Let's see.
Dash to target location from a certain height upon landing.
Damage, knocking them back towards the landing point.
Unleash tentacles to slow enemies within reach.
Enemies on your break free in time will suffer your damage.
God, that is so complicated.
Uh, shift dash to the target location from a certain height.
Upon landing.
Oh my God.
Okay, I'm going to try.
I'm going to try my best.
Oh, shit.
Okay, movement.
Okay, I did not expect to be there that fast.
Fucking movement right there.
Holy shit.
Oh my god, I need to be, like, closer.
No!
I'm going to look at my health.
Oh!
Goodbye!
Woo!
Nice.
Oh shit guys, I forgot my thing loses HP guys come to heal
me
That's fucking right What the fuck you just read you thought
you think you can run from me Guys, I'm not very good tank
guys Get over here Oh, oh god.
Okay, guys.
I'm not very good tank guys.
I'm
That's fucking right.
That's right.
Get over here.
I'll fucking brawl with you.
Oh, go brawl.
Don't brawl.
I'm stuck.
Guys.
Here's my heels.
You take requests, assistance.
Clap.
Right now.
Keep.
Clapping!
It's very important you keep clapping!
Keep clapping!
Okay.
I fucked up.
That was not what I wanted to do, but that's okay.
Oh god.
I need to run.
Where's my claps?
Oh shit!
I gotta go over there!
Gotta go over there!
Get the heels!
Okay.
Okay, that's good.
I've got the claps.
Oh What is going on?
What the fuck is going on?
I'm trying to survive
Where's where's claps?
How the fuck do you bloody better?
I?
I don't know how to play venom.
It's so fucking difficult.
Jesus Christ.
Okay.
All right.
We're okay.
Do we have two healers?
We have one healer.
Okay.
That makes more sense, guys.
We literally have one support.
Oh my god.
Guys, I think we need another support.
Please clap what I'm ever saying clap because yeah, we need
another healer Please clapping is not enough
Guys we need more Oh, we did Oh, it's because the the Luna
the the other healer The Luna snow um she claps to heal she
her her ability whatever abilities is that whenever she
claps she heals you all right we're fine over the amount of
shipping clapping that's going on marble rivals will have a
population boom in a couple of years you know what's gonna
make marble rivals blow up if those 3d models become pop
public
True.
That's the only way Marvel rivals will survive.
Will become popular.
What the fuck?
Oh god.
That's fucking right!
Clap!
I'm fucking gonna kill you, you little raccoon!
Get over here.
Do you think you can run from me?
Holy sh- What the fuck?
What is going on?
Guys, I think everybody is dead.
Every time I'm not DPS, guys, I think.
Every time I'm not- That's fucking- You wanna do this?
You wanna do this?
That's fucking right.
Every time I'm not DPS, like, I think I think I was carrying
guys.
Yeah, devour!
Oh my god!
Somebody clap for me right now!
I'm on it.
Oh god, please.
Oh, please, please, there's so many things on me!
Oh!
I killed somebody.
I'm not, I was confused.
Who did I kill?
Oh, I crushed her.
I crushed her.
Okay.
I fucking crushed the shit out of that one.
I don't know how.
I...
Okay, to be fair, I did kill her before it.
Okay, guys, I did kill her, guys.
Oh, my God.
All right.
Tricking, I'm out.
I'm out.
Oh, I'm not out.
I don't know how fucking disoriented playing Venom.
He's so dis...
He's so fucking...
All right.
There you go.
It's okay.
I'm getting slowly learning.
I got somebody down with me.
Okay guys.
That's like a win on my book.
Here you go.
Oh no.
Wait, where are they?
Where?
Where are the people?
There you go.
I don't know.
They're all just, they're everywhere.
Why are they everywhere?
Get over here!
Get over!
Oh, shit.
I'm fucking... Goodbye.
They're, like, literally everywhere.
I don't know what to do sometimes.
Woo!
Alright, whoops.
Where are they?
Oh, shit, there you are.
where's that get over here where are you no you don't shoot
them I'll beat the shit out of you get over here get over
here I will fucking eat you I'll eat a tree guys I'm getting
better get over here no okay there you are I did it.
I figured it out.
I figured out how to play Venom.
I ate a tree, guys.
Yeah!
No, I'm just wrong.
This works.
What were you going to say?
Did you see that or eat that whole tree?
Did you guys see that?
I fucking ate a tree.
Oh Jesus Christ this guy is hard to play I like how did I
start fucking solo altered the tree I was like fuck that
tree in particular Oh my gosh
Oh my this is gonna be a bit harder because it's like I'm so
little tanky now your veggies guys is good for you all right
time to go back
whoo I'm getting a little better I'm figuring him out a
little more all right guys oh oh I fucked guys clap clap
yes please
please oh god oh my god we got him I need heals though I I
can't take this guys I literally can't keep taking this,
guys!
My HP is so low!
Okay, nice.
Alright, I'm gonna wait a little bit.
I don't want to go up yet.
I need heal, though.
Where's... Nice.
Okay, he snaps.
That's fucking right.
Where are you?
There's so... Where are you?
Shit, where are they?
I'm just like, oh, that's a lot.
Just keep snapping.
Oh, shit.
Okay, okay.
It's fine.
We're fine.
He snapped.
He snapped enough.
Okay.
I got, I got Groove.
I got Groove.
Okay.
It's time to eat somebody.
Oh, y'all, y'all, y'all, y'all, y'all, y'all, y'all, y'all.
No, you ran away.
All right.
Nice.
We're fine.
I couldn't eat trees this time, but where did he go?
Where did he go?
Okay.
We gotta wait.
Boom.
That's fucking right.
Get over here, Groot.
Get over here.
Oh, goodbye, Groot.
I Had enough trees jk.
Oh, I have enough trees Oh no, I can do it too much damage.
I thought I was getting healed I thought I was getting
healed guys, but I wasn't All right, well wait We're in
obsession with the tree.
He fucking deserved it No star lord.
Are we soul bounded?
Who's my best friend?
Somebody's my best friend, but I don't know who.
Okay, we gotta wait, we gotta wait, we gotta wait, guys.
We gotta wait.
Oh, what's that?
Oh no, it's the fucking panther.
It's okay.
Where did he go?
There's too many things on the screen!
Get away!
Get away, we need the support!
Okay, are we good?
Alright.
Alright, I'm gonna go up It's okay, we're fine I'm fucking
trying to oh shit Oh god, please I need heals guys no Look
up I needed heals My teeth I needed more snaps Holy shit,
what is that man's sense Oh no guys group guys we're in
group guys we have one fight we gotta wait we gotta guys
mantis i swear to god don't you dare we have to wait we have
to wait guys mantis look at me oh no i pressed the wrong
button okay i think i'm gonna go in i'm gonna go in just
keep me up Just keep me up.
I would.
As, like, the only tank here.
I don't.
This is just DPS tip, to be honest.
I don't think it was a me issue.
I did my job.
I literally did my job.
I can't.
I ate trees.
Come on.
What do you want me to do?
I blocked 22,000 damage.
I... I blocked a lot.
I did what I was supposed to do as a tank.
Like...
Venom is gonna turn so many people in tank players.
The thing is, the only issue with Venom is that it's so hard
to like um it's so hard to play him when you don't have
heals because he's bouncing around i feel like you need to
know know where the health packs are when you play venom all
right uh you know what let's try iron man i want to try iron
man but it worked out for everybody what's her abilities
okay activate hyper velocity state activate armor overdrive
enhancing damage when hyper velocity or armor overdrive is
wait what what was the last statement
all right uh when hyper velocity armor is used iron man can
launch a bombardment okay Okay, I need to use...
I want to fly, I can launch missiles.
Okay.
And then...
Okay, so...
If I have...
Do I damage a repulsor, blast, or a uni beam?
Oh, okay.
That makes my attacks stronger.
And then...
Okay.
Okay, I'm going to try and remember that.
So...
So this would...
need to do is capture the machine oh whoa whoa i'm still
flying i oh okay all right this is that's right yeah that's
right that's fucking right get over here all right this will
oh my god what the fuck what is he doing what what he
fucking deactivated me The mission area is...
He uses radiation!
That's fucked up!
He literally uses radiation for that!
Okay, Iron Man sucks.
I hate Iron Man.
Alright, what's my ult trying?
I'm gonna try and get the...
I'm gonna try and get an ult.
Literally, the only fun thing is this ult.
like like I don't like the wait how do I oh I have to hold
it oh this is the tracker okay never mind he's pretty fun
now never mind I like it oh fuck y'all fuck never mind this
is easy never mind this is easy this is easy
As long as I just have to track, I'm fine.
No.
You think you could get away?
That's fucking right.
I can track.
That's fucking...
That's not fair!
He's just fudging!
Oh, what the fuck?
Oh, shit.
What?
never mind the moment i found out i can track it's over it's
fucking over i figured it out i figured it out it's a zarya
tracking i can track all right i'm gonna waste my all jk i
want to fucking kill this guy though that's right don't get
healed you know what
What the fuck?
Alright, I need like a...
Okay.
Yeah!
Shit!
Holy shit!
That shit is so fucking broken.
That was worth it.
We lost, but like, that was worth it, though.
I figured out how to all right let's see we have two
supports all right it's time to win this for the team it's
totally worth it all right it's time for my team to win I
lost but I got a taste of that shit is crazy I don't
remember what it's like old all was like a beam or something
I remember I'm pretty sure.
Alright, I think we unlocked rank, apparently, so after
this, we'll go into rank.
Time for my minute of it.
I remember his old alt was not like that.
Yeah.
Well, his right click is good.
I think his right click is really good.
You can aim.
It was the uni beam.
The uni beam is fun.
I didn't like his... I don't like his left click, but his
uni beam is really good.
Okay, let's see.
Now it's time to carry this team.
Oh, if I can find people.
Okay, how?
Guys, I have not played a...
Okay, now...
know what happens to me guys guys i don't know what happens
what happened to me i was what happened oh my god i used to
be queen of the world i i don't know what happened it just
just disappear i just couldn't aim anymore i don't i don't
know what happened It's just it's just stopped working
What's that I don't remember what that sound was The thing
maybe they hot fixed it guys I know what they did they like
hot fixed it so like
Wait no I'm lagging oh Wait am I lagging or are they lagging
who the fuck happened to the guys guys I think guys it's
because I'm lagging Guys, it's not Guys, I think I'm
actually lagging.
Oh my god actual lag
Actually no
Oh my god, thank god.
It was actually lag.
It's actually lag
oh my god thank god i knew it i knew i was my aim was still
good i knew it i'm just lagging guys we figured it out see i
know my aim
Oh, fuck!
I thought I had a healer next to me.
I'm happy for lag.
The only reason I'm happy for lag is because my aim is still
there.
Oh my god, thank god.
It's not me.
Also I have really dog shit healers.
This is the only reason why I like playing support is
because when your healers are dog shit and you have to like
see look nobody looks up oh there he is is he look there he
there he goes there he goes nobody looks up all right this
is literally the only reason why i play support because like
it's so tempting having bad support players that you have to
support yourself
let us.
That guy was a really good Hulk, though.
Lord Ven was actually really good as Hulk.
Alright, let's go play Rank.
How do I...
Alright.
Wait.
No, it's not.
Unlocked it.
No, I don't want to fill it.
Whoa!
I got so many stuff.
Wait, I got lied to!
It opens on the 24th!
It opens tomorrow!
You guys lied to me all right maybe this time guys maybe
this time we can do conquest yeah we're like oh you can log
rank now i was like yay i
got baited so hard somebody was like oh now you can play
rank i'm like really all right now that i've learned how to
play this game rank is conquest is nothing now Conquest will
be so easy.
We got this, guys.
We got this.
Alright, here you go.
There's no one playing Conquest.
Okay, nobody's playing Conquest.
Maybe Conquest is a bad game.
Okay, never...
It's a bad game.
Guys, I think Conquest might be a bad game mode and nobody's
on it.
Nobody's...
Okay, I found a match.
already all right nice nice yeah
how is conquest and oh my god is the spider-man guys I will
bring peace to this holy shit I'm now I'm now an Adam main
friendship ended with Loki Adam is now my new best friend
it's him it's the real spider-man It's not my fault they
fucking butchered the shit out of Loki.
He's literally dog shit now.
Loki is so, the heals for Loki is just so bad.
Until Adam gets nerfed.
Yeah, until Adam gets nerfed.
He's my new best friend.
I like it when I snap the heal.
Loki is, no, Loki's not even that.
going what I like got confused nobody knows how to walk
there hope everybody's following me nobody knows guys it's
not guys it's not that way everybody's confused you can see
everybody doesn't know how to get there like where do we go
snap so bonded okay snap I love snapping to here it's so fun
oh my god snap snap I can't snap anymore I'm sorry somebody
help me I couldn't Skylet, you just...
What are you doing, Skylet?
Guys, I don't think Skylet's a good player.
She literally was just watching us get shot at.
That's so fucked up.
Snap.
Oh god, people learning how to play this game now.
Oh god.
Guys!
I need more heals this team I have a dc how how do I have it
this is a quick play oh god you dc where's the fill oh
there's the fill guys it's time to clap
Oh god.
I'm trying my best right now.
Get away from me.
Get away from me!
Get away!
Oh god, we have tanks.
Holy shit.
Thank god.
Like, you have to play Luna Snow for consistent heals.
I'm pretty sure.
I love to play her so that I can keep the team up
get away freeze
oh my god Spider-Man's a flank killer is so scary I'm glad I
tried my best to clap I'm clapping so hard
We're dancing we dance we keep dancing I can't dance forever
Magneto, I can't dance forever Magneto Guys stop I can't
I'm just getting fucked over by the spiders.
Because I think this is GG's.
My team is bad.
I have a feeling my team is bad, Kat.
Just why is she just standing there?
Please!
Scarlet, aren't you lagging?
Because why are you just lagging?
Why are you on the DPS line?
And we are just getting...
Oh my god.
Holy shit!
Somebody get her up!
Oh god, thank god.
Oh thank god.
Thank god.
Please get him away from me.
Oh god!
Scarlet, please wake up!
Scarlet!
Wake the fuck up!
Get away.
I will clap.
And I won't regret it.
Okay.
This is so difficult.
This team.
This fucking team.
Please.
I will.
We'll dance if I have to!
Please live!
Oh, I missed the thing.
Okay.
He's low though.
He's low.
I'll clap!
Clap!
Where did he go?
Get over here!
Guys!
Please!
Get over here!
Goodbye!
He's won!
He's literally won!
I'm dancing!
I keep dancing the best I could right now!
I'm trying so hard to dance!
Wait, Spider-Man isn't on Spider-Man!
What a scam!
Spider-Man's on fucking storm!
What are you?
Clap for life.
Oh no.
It's gonna be me again.
Oh no, I missed.
Oh, thank God.
Thank God.
where's venom oh god oh god no the scarlet witch please team
what are you what the fuck please I live for so long team
please do not I will dance I will fucking dance if it's the
last thing I do I'll keep on dancing.
You're fine.
You're you're get healed.
Get healed.
Clap.
I will clap.
Clap!
Yay!
Now it's attack time!
Kill everybody!
We're fighting our group.
Yeah!
Okay.
Oh, God.
Oh, please.
Trying to be alive right now.
Okay, he's dead.
Thank God.
And a big heal.
You can also...
It's like Lucio where you can change into damage boost too.
Or not Lucio.
Wait, it's like Juno!
Where you can change into damage!
Alright.
Who has my...
Okay, I'm getting rid of the low-key puppet though.
oh god oh god clap clap come on come on scarlet witch live
oh god oh no venom oh that was close wait wait that's you
wait what the fuck who killed everybody who's dead like
who's fucking died i got like assists and everything Oh God,
oh, I missed.
It's okay.
Clap, clap, clap.
Oh Yes, oh it's okay.
It's still okay.
We're still okay.
We're healthy, we're so healthy guys Guys, we're so healthy.
We're so healthy guys Where's my Don't worry.
I killed just in time.
Now fight!
Now heal!
Now leave!
I think I froze it.
Wait, I froze the all.
Wait, that's fucking cool.
I think I froze it.
Okay, where's the...
No, no, no.
Please don't die because I'm dead.
Oh, nice, nice.
Good job, Iron Man.
Track him.
Oh, it's overtime.
It's overtime.
I'm heading over to everybody's credit card.
Oh, we did it.
He's getting a pocket.
No.
Oh, my God.
It's so painful to me.
It's so painful playing the only support.
Oh, my God.
It's deep.
the lid because of me I did 18,000 heal holy shit oh my god
you better fucking endorsed me after all I did for you I oh
my god they did so much damage though 12k 13k 12k like our
team had the most damage but I have to keep all of these
shitters alive All right, last game.
That's Scarlet Witch, though.
I wish I could...
I wish there was a void system so I can avoid the Scarlet
Witch right now.
Like, I...
I don't...
I do not want hair on my teeth.
You'll need a top-notch team to win this one.
All right.
Let's see.
Last game.
You know what?
I will try I am going to try I'll try mad Alright let's see
magic Transform into dark child Jump through a transporting
a short distance dash forward and launch an enemy Magic
slash Oh god that is so fucking What?
Okay And then I can charge it And then Okay Okay, and then
Okay, that's the charge all right Boom, all right, let's see
Nobody seems to play her I know like during the alpha launch
she was really broken during alpha But like I don't know
about now obviously it could be different now Alpha version
was broken that's That's all I remember.
Oh my god, why are they always in the fucking sky?
This is bullshit.
Okay, um, how do I do this?
How do I...
Oh shit!
Wait, I want to kill her!
It's not fair!
She's in the...
This is literally not fair!
She's literally in the sky!
She's nearly in the sky!
How can I kill something in the sky?
It's not fair.
How do I kill something in the sky?
I'm so mad!
Oh, I'm dead.
I am so mad.
Okay.
How do I oh, okay, that's the cool down All right, that's
the cool down you can't cook He fucking he was in the sky.
I can't fucking do anything about it Okay, I never know the
cool down for that get over here get over here get over here
get over here Fucking get over here Like what do I do?
Oh!
That's what I do.
Because that's what I do.
Okay.
I thought there would be more people.
Mosquito gods.
It's bullshit!
Get over here!
You can't block a sword!
Wait, that's not fair!
Get over here!
You can't fucking stay up there forever!
Stop being!
He's literally stayed up there forever!
Get over here.
No!
There you go.
That should be enough.
dude get over get away get away oh no it's the eye okay i
don't have that that's right get over here get you can't run
away from me i have a sword where are you i have a sword
that's right yeah that's right loki you scared oh Oh shit,
I'm scared.
Oh
Shit, oh, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, yeah, he went for me.
That's fucked up That's fucked up He fucking ran at me.
Oh, they have Spider-Man and Tony Stark
We're okay Okay, right behind you nice all right I can do is
that
JK I JK I live can be out of here be out of here Bro, he's
fucking a mosquito That's the only thing that sucks a
mosquito shit like I don't know what to do when that happens
Get over here.
Yeah, that's where you're stuck!
You're stuck!
You're fucking stuck!
Oh, wait.
He's literally one.
Somebody just...
Just shoot him!
I can't shoot him because I have a sword!
He's gonna get this guy out of the way.
We'll get the Spider-Man.
Get him.
Get him too.
You can't block a sword!
Okay, I find it really dumb that you can't block a sword
though.
I think that's stupid.
That's fucking right.
Where are you?
That's fucking right!
Yeah!
Oh, Luna!
You're scared, Luna, aren't you?
Wait, where did you, Luna?
Where did Luna go?
Is she dead?
She was scary.
Alright.
What the fuck?
Judge, jury, executioner!
Pshum!
That's fucking right!
Get over you, Loki!
Yeah!
Oh, goodbye!
Okay, I live long and I thought I was going to.
She straight up locked out.
coming back guys magic's coming back don't worry I'm coming
back where is he where the fuck is he where are you
spider-man where the fuck are you oh you're trying to run
get out I'm the spider kill here get over here That's
fucking right!
Get over here!
Where are you?
Where are them last?
Actually, where are they?
That's fucking Tony Stark.
Oh, hey there, buddy.
Hey there!
Is there?
Who's healing you?
Fucking bullshit, healers.
That's fucking right.
What a little funny.
There we go.
I'm the best control I squashed some bugs I feel like I
don't die I like I don't know I think I had really good
healers because like yeah holy shit 15k healing our rocky
raccoon like clutched up he actually healed me so much
because I was just going in and fucking going in yolo style
I must be so tilting to heal I will not be surprised if I
was a bitch to heal that time uh there should not be a
leaderboard yet oh that was a good support player he like
enabled me to do whatever the fuck I want there all right I
think that's a good time to call it.
That's really fun.
I had a great time checking out the beta test this time.
I'm looking forward to trying out the rank system to see
what they changed to it.
But that's really, really fun.
I hope you guys enjoyed Marvel Rivals and the shit you can
do.
It's definitely right now for me, Marvel Rivals feels very
casual.
Maybe it's because I'm not playing rank at the moment.
But it feels very casual.
the play to like just like like uh just to like fuck around
with but it was really fun i definitely enjoyed it a lot i
think it'll be definitely more fun with friends but like as
a solo player playing it today i definitely had um a lot of
fun playing it and just like playing around the different
characters i did not like tank playing tank there uh and you
like the reason why is that tank you have to realize so much
on your healers and like i don't trust healers i don't trust
like random trust randoms at all so so that's why i don't
like playing tank and dps is fine because dps are more
squishy but like at least they do damage at least they do a
lot more damage to to justify it um my favorite support
currently is adam adam seems really fun to play as a support
um they nerf the shit out of loki so like he's not as fun
anymore and like his heels are actually like pretty bad
compared to adam imo um because like at this point if you
want a lot of healing then you play luna snow because her
healings are insane her healings are really good and the
reason why i liked loki was because of like his dps and
heals but like his dps was so low i felt like his dps was
not as high as before so i'm pretty sure they nerfed the
shit out of that um dps in general I think I like Hella the
most Hella was the most fun for me When it came to DPS And
Other than that Hella and Yeah I think Hella was I guess
Punisher for like soldier for Call of Duty Um And everything
I felt like I was tickling The enemies yeah Uh for Loki so
it just didn't feel Worth it because like okay Loki was Like
a good balance between DPS and Heals but even then like it
did not feel like I was healing and I feel like I was
actually healing anybody like i felt like everybody was
dying i was trying to heal people as loki i think you're
supposed to have three clones out of him you're supposed to
have like three clones or something um and so to justify the
heals but there's a cooldown when it came to that so i'm
just like oh yeah artemans all was fucking crazy that shit
was insane i was not expecting that all right guys i'm gonna
call it here i think i already lost super chats while we
were playing so um i'm gonna call it here today um as always
everybody stay hydrated posture check get up and around to
get that blood flowing and if you stay up for me head to bed
because you deserve it i'll see you guys next time everybody
bye guys also by the way um i think like thursday is there
is it thursday thursday's our first not first our second
official sponsor stream with cookie run cookie run hit me up
asking if i if i was willing to do a sponsor never played
cookie run before um never in my life before so um i'm
really excited to check it out apparently a lot of people
were like really really um hyped up that i'm trying out
cookie run um so yeah i'm looking forward to it anyway uh
make sure to support thursday stream for the sponsor cookie
run kingdom uh see you guys next time everybody bye guys um
bye I need to look for the ending screen.
Where is it?
Oh, there it is.
Bye.