Hello everybody I was not late I actually started exactly at
like five but then like the but then like because I didn't
tab into the YouTube streaming tab on Chrome it didn't
register I was like are you fucking I was like really it
didn't register because I didn't fucking tab in that's
actually shit also why the fuck is the game not showing up
are you guys do you like the sound though oh my god it
sounds so fucking cool though at least at least it sounds
cool no okay give me a sec i need to figure out why the game
i swear guys i swear to god the game was showing up earlier
i swear to god I'm not joking I could the game was showing
up I swear okay give me a sec I have an idea okay where's
marble rivals where is it marble rivals oh my god please oh
my guys I think it's one of those games I think it's one of
those games where it needs to be like it can't be getting
captured this is so dumb okay anyway I love marble rivals I
haven't sorry it's not
dumb marble rivals it's not dumb I didn't mean that I
already love it already oh my god I already love the game so
much already it's I was the dumb one not you I am dumb
anyway yeah oh shit wait give me a sec guys it is not proper
Properly guys give me a sec.
It's a little scuffed But that's how we like it here Sorry,
I need to like re redo this.
Okay, this is a little awkward.
Okay, give me a sec All right, we gotta do this and then
make sure everything is properly situated the way um i don't
know if it's me i mean it could be me honestly at this point
but like this game does not have full screen yet i think
it's because of that it's an alpha i hope it's just because
it's like an alpha test so like it's only in windowed mode
or like it's literally only in i have no choice like it's
it's literally only in windowed mode so like um so like uh
can't make But yes, surprise stream, because I got into, I
got into the Marvel Rivals Alpha Test.
I don't know, is Sound Guy here?
Mario, thank you for the Super Chat, thank you, thank you.
Your real friends?
The real rivals were the friends we made along the way.
Thank you for the Super Chat, thank you, thank you.
I don't know.
I don't know if Sound Guy is here today, or are we going to
have an anarchy when it comes to sound balancing?
So we're going to find out very soon.
It feels like Sound Guy is not here.
Just because, like, just because they didn't rate.
Wait, no, they're online.
I see you online on Discord Sound Guy.
Swap to your Sound Guy mod account right now.
But yes, I got into the closed alpha.
I know it wasn't in my schedule, but, like, it's the first
day, so I had to play it.
It's basically, like, Overwatch, but, like, what if it's,
like, Marvelous superheroes and villains instead?
So, um, so, uh, just, like, imagine, and it's six, it's,
it's, like, Overwatch 1, because it's six, six, six players
in the team.
So, it's literally OG Overwatch 1 with six players instead
of five.
I assume it'll be, like, two tanks, two supports, two DPS.
Um, it's so funny because, uh, there's no, no, there's no
NDA for Alpha.
It was just, they're just like, stream it if you want.
And I'm like, cool.
But like, you know, I was looking through it.
I didn't sign any NDA.
I just got a key.
Anyway, I'm really excited.
It's like, it's closed alpha.
And they, I knew a person, like, somebody reached out to me.
Because did you read the fine print?
Well, the first mistake is thinking that I read.
Like, yeah.
the act you're right this is overwatch 2 this is what
overwatch 2 was supposed to be i'm just like hoping it's
good i'm actually like please be good please be fucking good
that's all i want that's literally all i want i just want an
actual good overwatch game anyway um it was also like uh
when i you know when i tweeted it i was like can I please
have an alpha key marble rivals someone um someone reached
out to me because they knew the community manager in marble
rivals so they reached out to me and be like oh yeah I know
this person in my like community manager in marble rivals we
can help you get in touch with them and get you in and I was
like yay and then that's how I got in it was so funny
because the moment I posted like my like posted the waiting
room and stuff like that like so many people like DM me
Like, a lot of my, like, streamer friends and, like,
pro-player friends, like, DM me.
It was, like, how did you get in, Marvel Rival?
And I was like, do you think you could help us get in?
I was just like, I don't know.
I mean, I can ask.
I don't know.
Like, I got in because, like, somebody reached out to me and
said they'll give me a key.
So, like, oh, I don't know.
I'll try.
It was so funny.
Like, everybody was, like, reaching out to me.
How did you get in?
I'm like, nepotism, baby.
The Doki privilege.
Sound guy, where the fuck are you?
I know you're here.
Are you here to balance for me?
All right.
Okay, it's going to be a little bit of an anarchy because I
don't know if Sound guy's actually here.
So, how's the sound so far?
Let's get in.
Logged in.
All right.
Oh my god!
I can actually have my own name because nobody else is I
swear if somebody else has an alpha test and stole my
fucking name I swear to me I swear if someone else was also
in the alpha test and purposely took my name I swear the
fucking God this is also the reason why I can't use my name
and any of the games these days because people already took
doky doky bird it's like i got to fucking use the real
female real female doky all right yay okay thank god thank
fucking god i was like i swear how do i know what's a tank
all classes what the fuck okay i assume vanguard vanguard
would be tank well obviously bruce bet oh my gosh Obviously,
Bruce Banner will be the tank.
Dr. Strange is a tank?
He's a fucking surgeon.
Wait, what?
Dr. Strange is a tank?
Alright.
Dr. Strange, difficulty, three stars, as a sorcerer supreme.
Ooh, wait, this is really cool.
I know, like, Groot Magnet...
Oh, Penny Parker.
Yeah, these guys make sense.
But Dr. Strange, he's a fucking wizard.
Like, fucking The Hulk can just break his back.
Oh, he's a four-star.
Brilliant Scientist, Doctor.
Oh, wait.
Is this, like, all the skins?
Oh, no.
This is, like, middle form between them.
And this is Ultimate Hulk.
And then there's, like, skinny-ass nerd.
And there's Groot.
That's so cool, though.
Seeing all the tanks and stuff.
Are you okay?
Blink, wanna smile if Kevin is pointing a gun to you, Ninja.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Is he actually super OP now?
Dr. Strange?
comic lore oh he's like the easiest nice i love all the
animation so far oh my god he's so old now he has a beard i
only remember mike like michael fassbender magneto and oh my
gosh i'm so sorry is it eon mckellen is eon mckellen the
other the older magneto the magneto is old as fuck the
master of magnet magnetism bends even the strongest meta oh
my god he's so fuck he's like the buffest fucking grandpa
out there what a buff grandpa and then there's penny parker
i remember her from the spider verse oh she's like diva
they're like we need diva it's like they're like okay
they're like overwatch we need we need a diva character
Overwatch why don't we use Penny Parker oh my god it's
literally it's literally a diva but for spiders yeah Penny
Parker may be young but she bravely stands on the front line
to protect the web of life yeah Marvel diva exactly what's
the team team up was like oh Ragnarok rebirth Asgardian
Soul's team up abilities yeah like if you have like certain
like characters picked have like special combos and stuff
too so uh the hell lands a final hit and defeating an enemy
she can instantly resurrect loki in the respawn phase if
loki is alive a crow flying to him granting a blue armor so
you can like have like team up so like do like meta like i
don't know what the meta is but like you can have like
specific this is not fair there's three team ups what the
fuck is the three team up uh you can bring up the overall
sound okay i'll bring up the overall sound uh all right
what's the three guys hawk charges dr strange and iron man
with gamma radiation when dr strange uses master he
unleashes excess gamma energy when iron man uses armor
overdrive he will initiate a gamma upgrade i feel like the
three combos might like this can actually be like super OP
because it's three people.
Three is more than two.
DPS tank.
I guess it makes the tank a DPS too, right?
Hulk charges Dr. Strange and Iron Man with gamma radiation.
When Dr. Strange uses Malstorm and Madness, he unleashes an
excess gamma energy.
When Iron Man uses armor overdrive, he will initiate a gamma
upgrade.
But Hulk gets nothing.
Isn't that passive?
He gets like passive.
Hulk charges Dr. Strange.
Oh, he gives them.
I guess like, if you have Hulk, I guess like Hulk is the
main tank and then Dr. Strange is off tank and then he like
gives the off tank and the DPS energy or something because
like he feeds them radiation because like as we all know a
little bit of radiation is okay.
Oh, it was wonders because like Hulk is sort of like, you
know, he's like fully radiated.
So like I'm just thinking like is this fucked up to say like
Wouldn't, like, being close to the Hulk potentially give you
cancer if you're, like, a normal person?
Because he's giving up...
He's giving up radiation.
Yeah.
It's...
But he has so much.
But he'll be so smart, though.
um all right that's interesting what about the other ones
okay duelist is hella wait loki's a fucking support player
oh my god loki's the heal slot wait how much does he heal he
eats gamma fair enough what greater thrill is there for god
of mischief than to outsmart his foes the cunning trickster
trickster loki uses his illusions and shape-shifting to
weave in and out okay oh there's cosmetics i forgot about
that all right oh don't you can't say that but like am i i'm
not wrong oh my god i forgot to look at the most important
things the the abilities all right where's the heels
regeneration domain Wait, does he not heal anybody?
God of mischief.
Shape shot shifts into a targeted alley or enemy here and
use all the heroes.
Double ganger.
Wait, he doesn't even heal people.
How is he a fucking support?
He's useless.
He is.
Oh, his basic attack heals.
Wait.
Okay, there we go.
Never mind.
I didn't fully read it.
His fire missiles.
Oh, okay.
There we go.
To heal allies.
I saw deal damage.
All right.
He does heal.
Okay, he's not used.
useless wait is oh no okay no you have to aim so he's not
like the mercy wait where's the mercy character in this game
where's the i want to know who's the next mercy
okay you have to aim for this you really don't yeah loki is
like mora where's the where's the
so oh wow the skin is so cool wait i like the skin that's a
actually really cool skin i can't believe they gave bruce
all the cancer right thank you for the super chat thank you
thank you that just reminds me like of the cancer gun in
harley quinn um wait rocket is a fucking support wait is
luna snow the mercy are they all just do you have to aim for
all of them let's see fire ice that How does ice heal an
enemy?
Like, oh my god, you're injured.
Here, fucking suck on some ice.
Don't worry, I got you.
Suck on these.
It's cure.
I have no idea who Luna still is.
Yeah, it fires ice shots that damage enemies or heals
allies.
I am reading.
Put ice on it.
Oh my god, you're right.
You put ice on it.
Oh, what?
of fuck wait i am reading see fires ice shots that damage
enemies or heal allies it literally said she throws ice at
you when you get healed oh my god i don't know who to play
they're all like so interesting all right let's see i can't
believe rocky raccoon is a support player if you're not
careful with spider-man ease you can kill your ally Thank
you for the super chat, Grand Fairy.
Wait, Rocket is like the easiest.
Is he the shoot bouncing spheres to heal allies?
How does that work?
Heal those enemies, Junkie.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
He's support.
He shoots like, yeah, they're all, oh my gosh, all of them
requires aim.
I like that.
As long as it's not like melee, I'm fine with that.
Oh my god, there's so many.
It's so hard.
Oh my god, bounty hunter.
a rocky raccoon wait that's so fucking cool the skins are
already so cool too okay what about dualist storm the
punisher oh i like that i like that like when you hover over
it when you hover over it like it i feel like a lot of
people a lot of genji mains are gonna be spider-man i feel
like let me look at his abilities oh that's so cool i can't
help it i know i should play the game oh he's the hardest
too just like genji Also, sound, yeah, I raised the volume
up a little bit.
Oh, there's Spider-Punk, too.
Oh, okay.
Let's see, MVP.
Sorry, I'm, like, I'm, like, too busy looking at all the
fucking cosmetics and stuff, because it looks so cool.
Wait, that's so cool!
Holy fuck!
And then there's the emote.
Is that just a default?
And there's the spray.
What about the abilities?
Spider-Power?
Alright.
is just punching you have webs spectacular spin oh my god
what oh shit there's like rollouts oh my god get ready for
the spider-man rollouts video this here are some spider-man
rollout tech i i can see it now i can't i can see it get
over here and then you you can there's the combo you can put
them up in the air let's see oh you can crawl walls i mean
of course you're spider-man like that makes sense actually
that is actually sick fuck there's so many wait storm
apparently she flies
i like flying okay an omega level mutant oh her costume
isn't as cool though This feels like just a common variant.
Ooh.
Okay.
That's cool.
I like how, like, play the game is called MVP.
I think Spider-Man, I think Genji players are going to play
Spider-Man.
Honestly.
I feel like...
The 97...
Yeah, but it's not different.
It's not different.
It's just a recolor.
Like, literally, this is, like, default.
And then this is a recolor.
But it says 97 Storm.
But this is...
literally just a recolor.
Weather control.
Wait, I am flying.
Oh my god, I am flying.
What is this?
Switch the weather to empower allies.
Oh god, that is so confusing.
Tornado grants a movement boost.
Thunder grants a damage boost.
So it's like when Lucio swaps from healing to speed.
You can control the weather around you for speed or damage.
Yeah, it's It's literally Lucio, but not a healer.
Found the power of the weather to empower storm.
Grenado Grand Slave.
Wait, that's the same thing.
Thunder Grand Slave damage boost and summons lightning to
inflict damage.
Wait, so this is, I guess, like a stronger version of
weather control.
Storm, yeah, Storm Lucio.
And then there's the lightning ball.
And then this draws in enemies.
All right, Lucio, but fly.
All right, who should we look at next, guys?
Who do we look at next?
I think she's always just flying.
I think so.
There doesn't seem to be a cooldown.
Maybe she grants us stronger.
Oh, look at magic.
She's new, right?
I've never heard of her before in Marvel.
Oh, this is awesome.
Wait, no.
Oh, what?
What the fuck?
Wait, is this like a different form of her?
Holy shit.
Who the fuck is she?
She's an OG?
I don't remember magic.
Oh, she turns into a demon.
Holy shit.
Okay, she's pretty cool.
And there's her emotes.
Ability.
See, Soul Sword.
There's Dark Child.
Gaining Enhancements to all.
Oh, this is when she transforms into a demon, right?
I'm pretty sure, yeah.
And the stepping disc, what's this?
Oh, wait, teleport.
Oh, you can, like, dodge alts with this.
Like, if somebody wants to, like, hit you, just dodge them
with a teleport.
Teleport's behind you.
And then, Umbrell, incursion.
Dash forward and launch an enemy upward.
Holy shit.
This is all, like...
Oh, yeah.
There's, like, so many different abilities, learn so many
different like characters and abilities.
Strike forward.
This is like the melee build.
Uh, magic is just joking, bird.
George, thank you for this super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Limbo's might converge damage inflicted onto enemies into
bonus health to yourself.
Oh, that's cool.
That's pretty cool.
All right.
All right, who else do we want to look at next?
I'll look at one more person and then we're going to go
We're gonna go straight in to practice because I want to
look at the abilities in the training arena It's been like
oh my gosh, there's so much information Punisher.
All right, we'll look at Punisher Okay, Punisher.
I'm not gonna look at the tank because I'm never playing
tank No matter what game it is, I'll never play tank
Oh shit, okay, the costume's pretty sick Which?
Alright, MVP.
Oh, that's pretty cool.
Is he Reaper?
He has two shotguns?
Is this like the Reaper equivalent?
Okay, it's Reaper if Reaper and Soldier had a baby.
Because this has to be the shotgun, right?
Yeah.
They just...
They combine Reaper and Soldier.
Alright.
Alright, final judgment unleash two galling guns and
missiles to attack missiles holy shit what okay uh it's
their dad wait what the fuck you get to launch a hook to to
fucking travel far wait you can have a turret as well this
is a dps oh no you are the turret never mind this is like
like tower defense
You also, you control your own turret.
And then there's a grenade.
Oh, and then there's like Bangalore grenade.
Like Bangalore smokes too.
That's a spirit from Vioshoort.
Wait, what?
That's your passive.
You have like, you have like mini walls.
Alpha fashion.
Just so you guys know, this is the alpha test.
So you know like, after the alpha, you know that like after
all of this, Like, they're going to nerf people so hard.
Walls as a passive.
You guys know damn well.
Like, in the Alpha Bastion, Bastion had a fucking shield.
So, everything you see here, if it seems too OP, do not
worry.
They're going to fucking nerf the shit out of them later.
Because they never keep it that easy.
Okay, I want to do...
I don't want to be...
Wait, I don't want to be...
Hulk, do I...
Who do I play?
Alright.
I'll be...
I want...
I want to be low-key.
Because I can heal.
Okay, I'm going to do...
I get the tutorial.
I don't know the tutorial of low-key.
Better take advantage of it right now.
I guess like Galacta is like the announcer slash tutorial.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, the sense of...
Holy shit, the sensitivity is so bad.
Okay, I think the worst part about this being alpha is that,
uh, is that you don't have a converter yet.
There's no, there's no converter.
Oh, not the default.
No.
Okay, reticle animation.
No animation, please.
Uh, color green.
Uh, dot size.
Maybe a little bigger.
Is that big enough?
Yeah.
all right okay settings uh allied health bars okay i have no
communication let me make sure i'm not accident oh i am
lagging a little
just guys maybe we're not gonna do high medium let's go
there we go yeah that should be a little better right
communication push to talk we'll do that where's melee melee
where the fuck is melee melee there okay that should be good
okay I think that was good yeah alright okay oh that dot is
way too fucking big never mind Melee's always been V,
though.
It has always been V.
It's never...
Okay, we're going to put one.
I think, like, my melee was...
Oh, my gosh.
I actually forgot.
I always get confused between my mouse meleys.
I think this was melee.
And then my communication was this.
There we go.
Alright, let's go.
Let's run.
Oh, it's so weird.
It feels like I'm playing Soldier, but I can't run.
Hold B to scope up the structures.
Okay.
I don't break through it.
Do I shoot it?
Oh, what?
Okay.
Pass clear.
Head to the target spot.
It's so weird.
Because, like, I feel like I could run, but I can't.
And then, how do I do this?
Oh my god, Maga!
Okay.
Use.
to transform into a hulk all right i'm hulk time and then i
fucking smash smash oh okay never mind i'll just open hey
guys stand by and press to unleash indestructible oh shit
okay and then and then i clap and then what's this this is
the shield and and then i hold him there okay okay I get it
why no little smash let me smash all right this is the
support oh there you go I'm a dash okay I'm a dash thank you
thank you thank you oh my god I'm just shooting orbs it's so
slow please heal faster rocky raccoon Okay, Stampin' Button
Leash Cosmic Yarn Amplifier.
Why do I do that?
Oh, it's like damage!
Oh, okay.
Don't worry, I got you!
I got you guys!
Oh, it's like damage boost, but like all of us are damage
boosts.
Interact with it.
And hit.
Alright.
Looks like you're back to playing as the Punisher.
Rockets here.
That means the team-up ability ammo overload is now
activated.
Oh, I have the team-up.
Yeah, what's my team up?
I forgot already.
We'll just up within...
Okay, don't worry.
I'm TPS.
Okay.
Oh, I don't have to reload with this!
Yeah, that was Punisher.
I don't have to reload.
Yeah, infinite ammo for a team up.
Oh my god, there's like so much like tech.
There's so much tech you have to know.
Oh my god.
Cosmic, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
All, like, because like every, there's like team ups.
There's team ups.
There's like specific abilities that benefit other, other
like heroes.
There's like, there's like so many different abilities to
use.
Oh, like my brain's overloading.
try to like there's a lot of mechanics holy shit you know
what we don't need a practice let's go straight in nice i'm
gonna i'm gonna be a support player for now because like
they can't wait they will absolutely blame me if we die oh
my god they will absolutely blame me we have we have a tank
already oh my god someone willingly willing to play tank
let's fucking go oh my guys we have a real lineup.
We have two DPS.
Well, Ray, that's on you for not fucking picking first.
You gotta be a tank now, Ray.
Dang it, Loki.
This is why you're not meta.
Alright.
Okay, Ray, you better pick an off tank or like a main tank.
You better pick Hulk.
I mean, they already, someone picked Dr. Strange That's a
tank already I invented every trick.
Okay, so all I have to do is shoot them.
Oh, guys I did not read the abilities.
I
abilities guys Okay Oh, that's decoy.
Okay, and then oh, I can swap with my decoy.
Oh no Okay, and then all right.
Okay.
I got it.
I'm gonna put decoy here.
So if I need to, I'll swap.
Okay.
We got this.
We're so healthy, guys.
Oh, God.
Don't worry.
I got him.
Oh, God.
Don't worry.
I'm healing.
Please.
Don't worry.
I'm healing.
holy shit the visual clutter feels just like overwatch wait
my decoys can shoot as well okay not gonna lie that visual
clutter is actually insane wait we have to kill baby banner
too I killed baby banner guys wait i'm actually gaming wait
i'm better than the fucking actual dps player i should just
play dps okay get that decoy in there go in there shoot for
me oh my god i'm so fucking good at this game
okay no i'm playing against real people okay don't worry and
then we have to kill baby hulk as well wait these guys are
bad wait these guys are pretty Pretty fucking bad.
Alright, nice.
Alright, I can kill...
I can fucking kill Casey.
That's right.
We have an actual comp.
Wait, we're spawn capping.
Get in there.
And I'm playing with 620 frames.
Hulk is actually Deva.
I don't...
We're, like, actually spawn capping them.
Oh, this is so sad.
Oh, my God.
Did you see the damage?
Bro.
All right, nice.
What is my...
Oh, I can be...
I can be him.
I'm DPS now.
I'm...
Do you feel proud?
Yeah, I pretty much do.
There you go.
I'm so proud of myself.
I'm literally spawn camping these guys.
I'm DPS now.
Yeah, shoot for me.
Bro, they're so fucking babies!
Look at me, I'm DPS.
This poor team.
Don't worry, I can heal too.
Okay, never mind, he's dead.
Whoa, what are you doing?
I can aim!
What the fuck are you doing?
I can- I know how to aim!
What is the objective?
We're defending.
They haven't defended yet.
I mean, they haven't attacked yet.
That's the objective.
Look at our Genji Go.
Look at our Spider-Man Genji Go.
Holy shit.
That's so sad.
Can you swap out?
Yeah, but then like, I might as well be a fucking DPS
because I can actually the aim like what is he gonna do he's
dead there you go oh hulk is the baby diva penny doesn't go
out of mech form that's okay we can kill fucking raccoon too
fuck raccoons oh shit let me heal you don't worry don't
worry i've regent don't worry guys typical genji they're
like swapping characters
Oh, that's actually so sad.
Don't worry.
I got you guys.
I can aim
Where's the surrender button?
Let's get rid of this tiny spider.
Bro, I'm sorry.
This is not balanced.
Don't worry.
Here you go guys.
Easy.
I feel like Honestly, like if this is not fair for this
enemy team.
And my Loki's also shooting, too.
It's funny.
Don't worry, I got you.
Don't worry.
Alright, I want to copy.
Copy you.
That's fucking right.
I'm tank now, too.
Get over here.
I'm also tank.
I don't know what I'm doing, but I can fly now.
There you go.
I can copy.
I don't know, but I'm doing a lot of damage for...
There you go, he's dead.
20 player streak.
I don't think I've died.
She's him!
This game is broken already!
Fucking easy!
Did you kill anybody?
I only got 20 kills!
Does there a leaderboard?
I don't know.
Oh, wait, here.
Tab.
There you go.
I literally...
Holy shit!
We're creating a mapboard!
Oh, my God!
Bro!
Okay, to be fair, I did a lot of damage for a support,
though.
I did more damage than the Ray guy.
To be fair.
You played against Toddlers.
Oh, my God.
fucking easy bro there's like people there's like zero kills
on the enemy team 23 assist hey look i fucking healed a lot
okay thank you super chat thank you thank you thank you
don't keep it i need thank you i really appreciate it look
at us look at us i'm gonna endorse our mvp and then i'm
gonna endorse myself too can i endorse everybody wait i can
yeah i can okay one more round Team is now queuing.
Wait, can we queue together?
Smash about.
You made them uninstalled.
No, they were real people.
I didn't queue up bots.
I queued up against real people.
Do we keep bullying kids yet again?
I think one of my biggest issues, like, straight up just
from this, is the fact that the visual clutter is pretty
bad.
I would admit that the visual clutter is not great.
let's try all right i want to i don't want to do like
shooting i won't be able to shoot people we'll try uh let's
see you know what let's try no i want to play hela okay we
got two tanks i can do dps you know what now we're has to be
shooting right what is his abilities uh power we are wait
fuck where is oh profile no i don't have f1 okay whatever
okay and then all right okay projectile all right and then
what am i doing oh shield and then what's this oh go shoot
for me squid boy all right we're attacking now aquaman let's
go oh my god guys it's aquaman
Is I pronounce it?
He's twerking.
Oh my god.
All right.
We'll send our squid boy out there.
I can't believe Bruce.
I can't believe the Hulk is Diva.
The fan art is going to go fucking crazy.
It's going to go fucking crazy, guys.
Need more.
Sorry, need more.
Go squid boy.
I'm DPS.
Oh my god, bro.
Okay, look at him.
Oh, wait, King of the Hill.
Wait, this King of the Hill.
Wait, these guys are coordinated.
These guys are actually fucking coordinated.
What the fuck?
That's not fair.
Guys, guys, okay, I think I am not meant to do projectile,
maybe.
Projectile might not be it.
Okay, that's the decoy.
Oh, guys, I'm not good at projectile, guys.
Can you tell?
guys can you tell i'm missing projectiles wait wait wait a
minute unless i can kill no way grude is so strong oh god
nope protect me please okay okay it's fine it's fine oh it's
so okay guys i need a swap i can't do projectiles i forgot
about my weakness projectile.
Yeah, Groot has Mewa's.
This is not fair!
Okay, we need a swap.
Change.
Alright.
It's alright.
I know my place.
It's okay.
I'm a tracker.
I know what my aim is like.
Holy shit oh my god oh my god he just walks up to me
oh my god okay this is the way to go fast here holy shit
okay i need to know like where the health packs are too okay
guys i don't guys these guys are At least we're not babies
this time, you know?
At least it's not like we're babies.
Guys, I feel like...
Maybe I was meant to be a support.
Because...
Because at least I'll actually get healed, you know?
Fuck you, Groot.
Down with nature.
Down with nature!
You can't block all of this!
That's fucking right!
There we go.
Nice.
she's falling right all right nice okay we know my place
though wait what oh shit they're over here oh no where are
they coming oh 39% don't make me bring up that turn oh oh
god manga times manga time please get him away from me oh Oh
my god, he's fucking sick of life!
Oh, shit!
Let's stop the hawks!
Oh!
Bro, the Loki turned into another hawk!
Oh my god!
There's two!
That's not fair!
What do I do on two hawks?
Okay, wait.
Oh no.
This is bad.
I'm like fucking in.
Okay, maybe...
want to play support just because like i'm fucking where is
my healers that was crazy unfair look strong guys it like
pisses me off because it makes me want to play healer
because of the fact that like my team didn't heal me
It makes me mad.
Okay.
Wait, it's because we have one healer!
Alright.
It's okay.
I know my place.
I fucking know my place.
It's hard.
Now we have two healers.
What is she doing?
Why do you think we...
I'm mad, I didn't get healed, so now I have to heal.
Back to heal their life.
Don't worry, I can turn into the Hulk this time.
I'm going to do what they did to me.
Don't heal.
Sad.
All right, I need to know where the health packs are, too.
Like, it's crazy that this is Alpha, because it already
looks pretty good for Alpha.
But, like, obviously, like, there's a lot of stuff they can
improve.
I'm going to put that here.
Oh my god, please, please start turning!
Please, please don't let him kill me!
Oh, nice, okay.
It's fine, it's fine, it's fine.
What?
Oh my god, who killed me?
Scarlet Witch?
Oh my god!
That's right, let your- Oh my god!
Okay, if I do this and then shift...
Wait, no, and then...
Okay, I'm trying like figure out how to do like wait that's
that's actually not fair it's actually not fair we actually
know it is fair I can kill no it's not it's actually not
fair it's actually not fair oh okay I'm like trying to like
figure out okay and then we do this to get there faster okay
don't worry we We have four heals now here.
Oh my god.
Wait, these guys are actually crazy.
I want to be Hulk.
Wait, how do I Hulk out?
I'm hulking.
That's fucking right.
I'm coming over.
I want revenge.
Hulk smash.
That's fucking right.
I'm so dead.
But I'll take you down with me.
Get over here.
No!
I fucked up, but I can swap back.
Guys, I fucked up, guys.
I fucked up a little bit.
I'm being less of a healer, more of a DPS.
Okay, this one, and then swap here.
Don't worry, don't worry, I'll heal this time.
For real.
Guys, do not worry, I will heal for real.
Oh, God.
Okay, don't worry.
worry.
I'm making sure you guys don't die.
I'm doing my job.
Oh, God.
Oh, do not worry.
I'm healing.
Oh, somebody's critical.
I don't know who that is, but like, I hope you're okay.
Oh, my God.
How did he do that?
Holy shit.
Okay, it's fine.
I'll put self-rejection.
here oh there's Iron Man he wants to kill me don't worry I
got him oh I should I got you I'm sorry I was distracted
they're too good I'm giving back the Children!
Wait, give me back the children!
Please!
Okay, we're okay.
Wait, we're okay, guys.
We did it.
Oh, wait, there's the Star Lord.
Oh my god.
Goodbye.
Please, keep trickling in.
Please keep trickling in.
I really appreciate it.
Okay.
Oh, nope, there's Maximals.
someone for us here.
I'm sorry.
Wait, please.
Peek me!
Okay.
Alright, nice.
We are undefeatable!
Alright, I don't know about that, though.
I don't know.
Oh.
Okay, we're good.
We're good.
I'm putting that decoy there.
Deco, do your thing!
Oh, no.
I'm like, fucking shape-shaped.
Fuck you.
If you're gonna fly, I'll fly too.
Wait, how do I?
There you go.
Get Bruce Bannon!
No!
Echo, where you can still be!
Oh my god, look at that fly fight.
Oh, Hela did it!
She did it!
Hela fucking revive me!
Alright, nice.
I'll do it here.
Alright, go Doki.
Go second Doki.
Okay, we gotta get rid of the other Doki too.
Nice.
Okay, don't worry.
No!
Wait!
Can I go?
Fire?
Please, Hella!
Nice!
Regent!
Alright, Hella got me again.
Thanks, Hella.
That's not even mom.
She killed my mom.
Wait, okay.
We're, like, actually working together this time.
We're actually...
Is that crazy?
We're actually working together this time.
Oh.
Oh my god, this is actually crazy broken.
The Hela team up is actually crazy broken, duh.
Oh no, Bruce Banner going in.
I'm going to put this on regen for me.
Please.
Please, team.
Don't die, team.
Don't die.
I'm keeping you all up.
Oh!
The support life!
I'm going to turn into you.
That's fucking right.
We did
Okay, we're okay.
We're okay.
Guys, I might become a low-key one-trick.
Look, he seems to be the only character that works for me.
What?
I'm back.
The pre-revise.
Oh my god.
dokey you know it just works we had we beat a yeah we beat a
team that wasn't babies
all i'm saying is that loki seems to be like the easiest in
terms of support no they can't nerf loki look at him they
can't nerve him
Okay, dokey, lokey.
And then I swap.
Woo, look at that.
It's like a symmetrical portal.
I like that.
Look at that.
I'm inventing new tech now.
New movement tech.
Guys, I literally invented new movement tech.
I need to remember how using the swaps, though.
Like, I think, like, the one thing I need to, like, know how
to do is just swapping care.
characters.
Okay.
Am I getting flanked?
No, I'm not.
Okay.
I was like, I thought I was getting flanked.
It seemed like I was getting flanked there.
Okay.
Don't worry, I got you.
I got you.
Okay, they're all up top.
It's fine.
The support can't fucking tank this.
We're okay.
Wait, did he like make a- No, no, Bruce!
We can't have you go back to Bruce!
Okay.
Oh, no.
I need to be able to hit that, too.
Okay, that's fine.
That's fine.
Go, Bruce!
Go!
No, Bruce!
No, we can't have you, Bitani!
Oh, no.
Bruce is out of his mech form.
That's bad.
We can't have...
Oh, I don't like how, like, you know, the environment's
gone, too.
Don't worry, Scarlet!
I got you!
oh no wait no they're capping i didn't even realize they're
capping oh no it's okay he's back somebody get her nice i
need to like remember where my hp is get in the back bruce
bruce get in the back nice i got him i like the projectile i
cannot do the projectile and neymore neymore but like Loki's
projectile is easier.
Oh, goodbye.
No!
What?
What is that damage?
Okay, Scarlet Witch is actually busted.
I did not think she would fucking just destroy me like that.
What?
It's literally one shot.
That's actually crazy.
It's okay.
That's fine.
Oh my god, someone saved the Hulk.
Don't make him a fucking weak flesh bag Don't worry Here we
go Hook time It's hook time Wait where are they It's hook
time for real Where are you Get over here That's fucking
right I'm a bigger version of you please oh i'm okay that
ended very fast
yeah okay the first game was pretty rough the first game was
really rough but we we survived we managed
really fucking good at the game though she was actually
pretty good jk i got 11k what the fuck what i had 11k damage
oh i was not healing i was absolutely not healing
guys look damage was more important in chat you don't
understand battle look for the mora moment oh my god all
right again let's go all right we'll give him and i'll give
myself what's my highlight oh i can't find the accuracy
support by killing the enemy we won't try scarlet witch your
fucking chaos shit was so busted low-key bird sweep hey
thank you for the super chat thank you thank you support
yeah fire support All right, I want to be Skylar Witch.
I don't know what her abilities are, but she seems like
really strong.
She seems really strong.
Oh, and she's like a one star, too.
She's like literally one star.
I really like the aesthetic of the game.
Penny Parker, but she's a tank.
It doesn't matter.
I don't want to play tank.
Tank is terrible.
I see no tank, but we don't need tank.
tanks.
No more they said no more mutants and no liberated everyone.
It looks really good.
The fact that tank has a maywall is like so scary.
Okay.
What is this?
This is like attack.
This is what?
Oh, this is like a mora beam I assume.
And is this shift?
And then what is...
This is the portal, right?
Wait, what is this?
What is the E?
I assume Yeah, left click is the more of, like, more of
suck.
I'm pretty sure.
And then, guys, we have zero tanks, guys.
But we don't need that.
Wait, how did they get up there?
Alright.
I don't know what the...
It's okay.
We're five.
Guys, we're fine.
They can heal us.
Okay, wait.
Okay.
And then...
No, we have a tank!
Okay, what is E?
Oh, it's like a mine!
Oh my god, Dr. Strange has, like, the Rhyme shield!
Guys, get closer to me so I can suck.
Guys, I need you to get closer to me for the suck.
Guys.
Wait, what?
There it.
Suck.
Get over there.
Okay.
Oh, this is confusing.
Because I have limited ammo for the left-right click.
So I have- Oh, still a tiny healer.
I need heals.
Please.
Guys, I need heals.
I can't suck that far.
No, I tank!
I have one tank!
Oh, God.
Goodbye.
Oh, goodbye.
Guys, this is bad.
I've limited ammo when it comes to close range.
How do they do this?
No!
Okay, no, fuck.
I think like...
I think like, uh, Scarlet Witch, um, not as good as I
thought.
She's only good at close range, I noticed.
Wait, I can fly!
There's still a chance to stop that!
Wait, I can fly?
Oh, wait, no, I can- I can glide?
No, I can glide.
Okay, I- I can glide, okay.
I can glide, guys.
Oh, yeah, Star-Star Lord seems like Tracer, yeah.
Okay.
How far does this go?
All right, I just need to know how far that goes.
Where's my range for this?
Oh my god.
I don't know my range for this.
Alright.
She can hold space to glide.
Yeah, I think it's like glide.
Yeah, I can do that for...
Wait, my chaos is strong though.
Chaos time!
Okay.
Oh, did I kill anybody?
I can't tell!
Oh, and then...
That's right, suck.
It's not fair.
He's getting healed!
What the fuck?
Get closer to me!
No, okay, never mind.
I hate Scarlet.
Scarlet's only good with her alt.
Not gonna lie.
I've noticed it.
Scarlet's only good with the alt.
Because the others are like...
Guys, please.
I need healing.
Please.
Where's my...
Loki, please!
I need healing!
Loki!
Loki, there's a squid in front of me!
I'm scared!
Okay, I'm here, it's nice.
Alright, that's good.
I'm here now.
Get closer.
I can't get closer because there's like 200 enemies in front
of me!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Okay, I'm safe.
Guys, I can't Can't just fucking get closer, guys.
There's literally three people in front of me.
Look.
Oh, God.
Oh.
No!
Okay, I'm going to try Hella.
I think Hella might be it.
Okay, taste of her own Loki.
I think she's like a flanker.
It seems like a flanker.
Hella does this.
And then she has that.
And then, oh, she teleports.
Okay, what's this?
I don't know what the E does though.
Oh no, they made it.
What does the E does?
Can't tell.
Oh no.
That's fine.
They only have 60 seconds to get there.
You don't see me up here.
God, there's so many squids!
Why is there so many squids?
Okay, we got...
Fuck.
No, no.
Loki!
What is the E?
Loki, please help me.
Okay.
I don't know what the E does.
Alright, but I can teleport, though.
It was a nice corner.
Oh, controlling the bird.
Controlling the bird is so difficult.
Okay, I have another.
I can fly soon.
Alright.
I need, like, a straight line to fly.
I need a straight line.
lie guys the more i play other characters the more i realize
i might be a loki one trick like oh shit oh my god nice i
got him loki please loki i killed your mom but please heal
me okay nice oh i do so much damage though holy shit okay
not gonna lie i should do so much headshots.
Oh, okay, I do!
Oh, shit!
Holy fuck, that was an accident.
If I hit headshots, I actually can kill so many people.
What is hella mode?
Is this hella mode?
Guys, I fucked up with my hella mode, but... Oh, wait, no, I
didn't.
Oh, you're so fucking dead.
That damage is actually insane.
Maybe I'll be an Asgardian.
Asgardian.
Asgardian player.
I just play all the Asgardians.
Asgardians only, please.
I can't play any other character but Asgardians.
Alright.
I still don't know what E does.
Oh, I think it's like...
Hey.
Oh, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
Or Norse.
Yeah, Norse god, Maine.
I'll be Norse Maine only.
No, I accidentally burned it to them.
Oh, my God.
Jesus Christ, the damage is actually insane.
as i wait who's that i feel like as long as i like uh as
long as i hit headshots it's actually crazy the thing i can
do things i can do get away from me i don't think thor is in
the game yet i think he's like he might be going in uh maybe
like in later on because i know they're releasing
This is so hard to teleport.
God damn it.
There you go.
Predicting this is hard.
No, they made it!
But I got two, though!
Loki, please.
No!
Did they make it?
No, I think they did it.
Okay.
We're good.
This is not fair.
Okay, I'm trying to help my...
I'm trying my best to help!
I'm going in the corner!
Oh, I did not.
Okay, guys, it's okay.
We have one last point left.
No, please.
Not my win streak.
Not my win streak, guys.
No!
Look, I'm doing a lot.
I got 12 kills.
I'm, like, literally on fire.
Okay.
This way.
Fur it up.
All right.
See, guys, I'm not low-key.
I'm hella.
Because I'm hella dope.
Alright, let's see.
Maybe I should try Punisher.
They're all flying.
This is actually, like, so cheesy.
Don't make me go hell on you.
Bam, bam.
Okay, they're shielding everything.
Alright, that's right.
You can't shield this.
Alright, that was, like, pretty useless.
But, like, I did the best i could the storm storm seems like
really broken when she's in the air not gonna lie only
because like it seems like really difficult please guys i
need help tank tanks tanks tanks tanks tanks please use your
oh i'm getting hot ground i'm getting hot ground i'm
flanking i'm flanking i'm flanking they won't know What do
they do guys?
No, they turned around!
They turned around!
Okay, it's okay.
My...
It's okay guys.
My trump card.
Tracking.
There's no way.
No!
What are we losing?
We lost our healer!
It's okay.
I have my...
My tracking will save us guys.
It's okay!
Oh, God, it might not be okay.
Oh, he's leaving me alone!
Alright, if we lose, it's not me, guys.
Oh, no.
Guys, I don't know.
I think it's becoming more and more clear.
I'm meant to play Loki.
my god it wasn't me it was my team oh my god it was my team
look at this i knew it was my team look at the damage i took
like okay fucking dr strange took 27 000 okay dr strange is
actually a really good tank not gonna like not like not him
as a player Not him as a player, but like I think Dr.
Strange seems really OP as a tank Because of the shield.
The shield can block so many things The 1.6k I knew it!
This is why people become healers Because I have dog shit
healers So the only way to live is to be a healer yourself
Alright, I want to try Storm Because I got shit on by too
many Storm players I got shit on too many times by storm All
right, let's see Oh wait, I can look at here Wind blow,
transform into hair, hurricane Switch the weather Oh yeah,
this is the weather swap Switch the weather for damage boost
Channel the power, weatherton, power storm Okay Unleash a
lighting bolt forward Okay This is gonna be a little Yeah,
DPS Lucio time
okay this is is this damage boost I assume this is movement
because it's the wind and then this is damage and then
double damage let's go now okay we should be on speed for
now uh so we can all get there in time I swear I think the
flying is so broken because like because like bad players in
the air I think I think like bad you know it's true look at
all the fair players bad players can't shoot people in the
air so like I think that's OP you
know it's true
all right let's get rid of this shield what the fuck okay
let's see we'll do damage boost because we have all right
apparently i'm i can't even shoot people while i'm in the
air
i can't even okay this is like an issue though the issue is
that it's very hard to shoot people when you're flying all
right the projectile is actually pretty difficult not gonna
lie wait breaking shield breaking shield
oh holy fuck okay were you gonna do magic oh no oh no not
the turret oh okay there you go okay okay there's a range
there no we're my healers do we have healers we don't have a
healer okay guys it's not because i've won to play Loki.
We literally have zero healers.
I was like, where the fuck are healers?
Oh my god.
Guys, it's not a fucking...
Do you think I want to play Loki?
Look, I had to...
We literally had zero healers.
We have three tanks.
Like, what is this bullshit?
We actually had three tanks.
Bruce Please, Bruce.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
This is bad.
Oh, wait.
No.
Oh, no, please.
No one's healing to cease to change the DPS.
I'm pretty sure Loki has to be the meta when it comes to
healer.
Because, like, I feel like Loki does, like, a lot of...
Has, like, really good utility.
I don't maybe Loki and rocket raccoon.
I think I think Loki and rocket raccoon I don't know what
this does, but oh shit.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh shit.
Okay, don't worry.
I have like so much HP Wait, I'm fucking tanked.
Don't worry.
We do you know we needed a four fucking tank?
That's that's what we fucking needed.
Oh Nope But, okay, please, guys, I'm literally doing so much
healing!
Team!
Guys, it's okay.
It's not as bad as getting spawned camped earlier.
Oh, yeah, we do.
Guys?
Guys, please.
I can, like, just shoot people from up here.
Let me...
Wait, that works!
Nice.
I found a I found a nice spot to just chill in Nice We're
fine See everything is fine What the fuck are you doing
Punisher What are you doing over there Just like what Anna
did That's incredible tech I told you guys I'm fucking I'm
tech I'm literally tech crafting right now Oh bro Bruce is
fucking dead Fucking he's so fucking dead oh goodbye goodbye
guys we don't worry we capped right yeah we crap capped
don't worry i got you guys i got you guys i'm actually
healing for once in my life okay i feel like spider-man
seems really difficult to actually learn in general because
like uh of all the shit don't worry by the eye of whatever
the fuck that one Okay, don't worry.
I got you guys.
I'm also tanking for you guys.
Now we have zero healers, but that's okay.
Oh, shit.
No!
It's not okay.
It's okay.
My team's got this.
They don't need a healer.
They don't need a healer, guys.
Okay, let's see.
It's time to do the tech.
Nice.
All right.
Guys, I'm here.
Don't worry.
Your DPS healer is here.
Heal her down.
I'm the only healer.
Please!
Guys!
We can't have all takes, guys!
Please, I beg of you!
We need...
We can't have all takes!
I can barely heal!
all these tanks oh guys you're fucking supports dead forced
to take guys please I don't want to go back to goats guys
and we're doing goats we need more support okay can I hold
on to that?
No I can't oh scarlet oh Oh god, please!
Oh!
You guys!
I can't keep healing all of you!
There's too many!
Judge, jury, executioner!
Please, please be gentle.
Okay.
Wait, I'm gonna queue.
Oh yeah?
Oh, I'm fucking 1 HP.
God!
I'm 1HB Oh
That's so cute the real healer No, guys, stop You're all
critical, I'm trying Guys I'm trying You're all critical Oh
god Guys, I'm trying Oh My god, this is this is so
stressful.
This is actually so stressful Yeah, it's okay.
We made it we made it to the other side We made it to the
other side we have two shields We have where are my healers?
You're one healer because we went three fucking tanks Oh
Yep, it truly was.
No, please leave me alone.
Oh, she doesn't know.
Oh my god, Penny Parker, you fucking idiot.
Oh, that's me.
Okay, there you go.
We're fine.
We just got- we gotta kill Hella on the- wait.
She's so low.
No!
She's better!
She's just better!
Oh my god.
these just you know what I don't like though I don't like
how I can't crouch spam that's why I don't what okay that's
like walling basically I think the fact that I can't crouch
spam and like crouch jiggles to make it like harder to hit
like I could AD but I wish I could crouch spam that's
fucking right maybe I am Agumato I don't know if i've said
that correctly guys we don't have a healer anymore we don't
have a healer anymore i'm sorry i got a little selfish i'm
sorry guys at this point i might as well just like teleport
into a what the are you doing low-key cps is actually really
like insane not gonna lie guys why did you
Why did you build that wall, guys?
I can't go through.
Alright, we're good.
We're not good.
I think, like, his DPS is actually really, like, actually
really powerful.
When I hit those, if I hit those, against the Squishies, it
feels like the DPS is actually crazy for Loki.
Alright, nice.
Okay, go over there.
Over there, Loki.
Just heal from up there.
Please.
No, don't die.
No!
Magneto!
Hulk out!
Go Hulk!
Okay.
Hulk, just get there!
Just fucking run at her!
Oh, no!
No!
We did it!
Oh my god.
We fucking did it please just let me play a different
character oh my god at your service please all i wanted the
only healer
it's not fair i just wanted to fucking dps you should use
the aura and fight with your clothes it turns damage into
healing oh that's so cool i didn't know that Wait, that's
so, okay, I'm pretty sure they have to nerf Loki.
I feel like Loki, oh my god.
Guys, look at the endorsements.
They know!
They were like, thank you for going healer.
Oh my god!
I got appreciation.
They know.
They gave me all the endorsements because I was the only one
that was willing to suck up my ego to play fucking healer.
I want to play Star Lord.
Okay, Star-Lord.
Engage in a free flight and lock onto enemies in sight.
Boost and soar forward.
Five frenzy of shots causing damage.
Dodge in the direction of movement and swiftly reload.
Ooh, wait, this is like Tracer.
And the calm moments.
What are the other supports?
It's like Rocket Raccoon, Mantis, and Lunar Snow.
I don't like the other support.
I think, okay.
This is, how many do we have?
have two.
Okay.
We have two.
And then... Then we have that.
And then we have the glide.
Oh, I can fly with this.
Okay.
All right.
That's interesting.
I want to be Star-Lord.
I'm already Star-Lord.
All right.
We're fine.
I think, like, Storm, Storm is like i'm not a projectile
person like that's the only issue i'm so bad at projectile
oh my god i'm so fast here we go all right i think i have to
play flanker for this i'm pretty sure i think starlord's a
flanker i don't know the map so i don't know how i'm
flanking but the only issue is i gotta figure out the map no
all right let's Let's see, how do I...
Oh my god, I like pepper damage.
Whoa!
Wow!
Okay, nice.
Oh my god, I fucking...
I am... Please.
No!
Oh god, oh god, oh god, Oh god, yes!
Please!
Okay, I think like at Starlord, you have to know, like, all
the health facts, just like Tracy.
Oh my gosh, damage is so tiny.
Bro, I might as well fucking... Whoa!
Okay okay.
I gotta I gotta fly I gotta fly Okay, oh my god move oh shit
okay not gonna lie though that movement
Okay, I might be dead, but like that movement though
Okay, but that movement though that movement okay I need to
get closer all right i think they got it bro is moving with
no damage i think you have to be i think it is like tracer
we have to be like super fucking close to do any damage yeah
because like look at how little like bullet like she doesn't
have like that's rocky raccoon what the fuck is that like oh
wait that's like the portal oh my god we're gonna play with
portals Yeah, because, like, look at the damage I can do
with, uh, oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, I need
healing, I need healing, oh, I need healing, no,
no, no, guys, I need figure out how to spam, I need healing,
guys, this is, like, the one thing I need to know, okay, I
need healing, okay, uh, guys, this is, like, the most
important, Please, okay, wait, controller, keyboard.
Okay, communication.
Need healing.
Okay, uh, there we go.
Has been, oh, shit.
No, I don't want to, okay.
Restore, deep, restart.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, I don't want to restart.
No!
Okay.
X?
No!
Okay, okay, okay.
Guys, I fucked up.
Guys, please don't kick me.
Please don't kick me.
Okay, Z, we don't need team up ability.
Yeah, this is much more, this is much more important.
Didn't you mean to have, like, 10 hockey?
Wait, I know!
Okay, no, wait, that's the ping button.
Okay, I was AFK for a little bit, but, like, it's fine.
Okay, don't get close to me, don't get close to me!
Okay.
Wait.
That's fine.
I'm gonna break his armor.
Where are they?
Come on, give me...
Let me in.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom,
boom, boom, boom.
Oh, my God.
Wait, I can do so much damage when I'm closer to them.
Who would have thought?
Guys, who would have thought you'd do a lot of...
No!
Please, I did so much!
I did so much!
Nice play.
god i can actually shred so hard oh my god the team of
abilities i need like remember to do them i actually have to
i have to flank as starlord yeah who is that guys i forgot
the spam i need healing
i need to remember the spam i need healing guys
Yeah, I'm so fucking...
I'm so fucking, uh, fleshy.
Starlord, yeah, he melts when he's flanking.
But I don't know the map good enough, well enough to, like,
flank yet.
That's Bruce Banner!
What do you mean?
He just wasn't in his diva mech form yet.
I mean...
Guys, I need health, guys.
Healers, what are you fucking doing, healers?
I'm only dying because of my healers.
Okay.
All right.
How do I flank this?
Yeah.
Oops, that was an accident.
I was trying to do that.
It's okay.
I'm going to try and figure out how to flank this.
All right, guys.
Don't worry.
I got this.
Oh, no.
Holy shit.
Did you guys see that?
Oh my god Boy Looks like the mission area is yours to
capture now Oh Holy shit Where Oh shit oh no She fled Wait I
melt so fast That actually like fucking kills so fast Oh my
god okay I understand I have to like flag and like be like
super close you can do yeah star lord is like extra squishy
but if i flank correctly i can do so much what oh wait wait
wait wait wait wait i got regen i got regen that's fucking
right that's that's fun no i got star lord in the sky i got
fighting tanked in the sky i'm such a glass cannon i'm so
fucking fleshy it's not fair it's time for the creator clash
wait go so be the first in wait guys i'm leaving i have to
leave and you're gonna have to turn no guys i want to go
through the creator clash though it's not fair no my honor
oh my honor though oh my god
bro what the fuck bro
guys no okay bro please
tell the team to lose guys lose faster okay well i want to
go to the creator clash i want to be part of the cool people
oh my god thank god wait over time die just die just die no
don't win don't win don't win
I beg of you, don't win!
There's a creator clash!
There's a creator clash going on!
Guys, it's over time, just lose!
Oh, thank God, okay.
See you on yourself now!
Guys, quick!
Oh, thank God!
Goodbye!
This is faster!
I wanna do the creator clash!
Okay, did I get in?
Did I get in the creator clash?
Creator clash?
No, it's okay.
Am I in?
Am I in the creator clash?
This is it.
Oh no, we lost.
We're missing out on the fun, the creator clash fun.
Did I get in?
I'm not judging.
Is this the creator clash?
I don't know.
It's like you get to play with the developers and other like
you get to play with the developers and stuff.
I want to play with the devs.
Alright, so we know what's how Star Lord's going to be like.
How about?
Uh, you know what?
Let's try out.
Okay, let's try out.
Uh, what do we want to do?
We need another strategist.
God damn.
No, not Okay, uh, you know, I won't try Spider-Man.
Does Spider-Man punch?
Okay.
Oh, I hate punching, though.
Wait.
I have two of webs.
It's like Doomfist.
I'm gonna be so bad with Spider-Man.
Okay, let's see.
And then the Mega Punch.
Oh, I'm gonna be so bad with melee.
I don't think this is the creature.
later clash guys no we already have we already have two d we
have two dps two tanks okay we have three dps okay maybe not
so ideal okay we have one support all right you know what
let's try let's try uh we can try out mantis okay releasing
it your spirit assistant no what about luna oh take center
station start dancing heal allies or grant them fire ice
shards for short durations damage attach idle aura allies
with to restore health while oh cast the clump oh wait this
is cool okay we'll try this music makes people happy he may
okay this is gonna i'm so used to okay what is he again he
attaches people right all right we'll try oh wait what i
guess if i run enough if i run enough it does that Okay,
there you go.
There you go.
So I can, the healers can heal themselves.
Alright, that's interesting.
What was right click again?
Guys, what was right click?
I don't remember.
Oh, it like, it like, sucks on people, right?
That was right click.
It, like, stuck on people.
Okay, I remember now.
We gotta go up.
Meow.
Alright.
And then, I I put it on the tank, so it should be fine,
right?
And then, yeah.
Yeah, we're double healing.
Don't worry, I got you.
Okay, I...
Don't worry, I got you!
Don't worry, I can DPS her.
Oh my god, your DPS is so weak.
Wait, this DPS is so bad.
Okay, I think I found the mercy.
She does so much healing though.
She actually does so much healing.
It's actually crazy how much healing she does.
But her DPS is actually garbage.
I am not a fan.
I'm not a fan of the...
I'm not...
Okay, almost...
Okay, you can't say that because like...
Because like fucking Loki's...
Loki's DPS is actually insane.
Like you can't say that.
I can solo tank a tank.
So I'll kill a tank on Loki if I want to.
No, Kiriko's DPS is crazy as well.
I wonder if I have the headshot.
Maybe if I headshot?
If I headshot?
No, the DPS is still pretty bad.
Alright, it's time to dance.
We're dancing.
Let's go.
Yeah, let's fucking go.
Woo.
Now it's damaged.
Oh shit, I need to back that up.
It's like, okay, so her alt, what her alt does, this is
officially awkward.
What her alt does is she can either damage boost or heal
everybody.
That was her alt.
Let me break it down.
It looks stupid.
Yes, it actually does look a little stupid.
It's fun, though.
I'm actually having a lot of fun.
How do you use sprays?
Hey, guys.
You guys want to see my spray?
Wait, how...
Guys, what the fuck?
You guys lied to me.
I can't use it.
Okay.
But, yeah, this is...
Man, she's so easy.
Holy shit.
I see this go.
Okay, attache.
aura uh restore his health castle to hit the enemy and
restore health okay i have to use my right click to hit an
enemy and then yeah so it like damage boosts if i keep
moving forward um if i keep moving forward uh i'll just go
for it see the real people i win because i'm good at the
video game my damage is dog though i honestly think loki's
the best healer i have seen she's so cute She is pretty
cute.
Like, even Kierko has more damage than this.
I think she just has, like, insane heal output, though.
I would admit her heal output is actually insane.
Like, I admit that.
Oh, my God, guys.
It's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
Guys, it's going to be okay.
Don't worry.
I'm healing.
Oh, God.
It's gonna be okay.
Oh, my God.
I actually got that healing.
nice nice I got that here clap wait what was my shift again
guys here here here what was my shift again she yeah she
heals she does a lot of healing and then I could like put a
I think like I don't know I think if you want to do super
offensive you do rocket and Loki I don't know what her I
forgot what her I forgot what her shift does.
Is it Hira?
Oh no.
Guys, get me away.
Get me away from that.
Don't worry.
I got you.
I'm going to clap.
I'm going to start clapping.
Don't worry.
Clap to win.
Alright, nice.
Don't worry.
I got you.
If you fly too much, I don't got you.
Clap, get healed, starts clapping.
Oh god.
Please!
Oh!
Don't wait!
It's time to dance.
It's time to dance, guys.
Let's fucking go.
Whoa!
Okay, here all this is really stupid.
Oh, it's fucking stupid.
It looks so silly.
It is.
It does look so silly.
Alright, nice.
I got my healing in.
There you go.
God, I love...
Wait, it is!
It's like Xenob, but like, more fabulous.
Wait, you're fucking right.
It's just like Xenata.
Oh shit.
Don't let him get near us.
Don't worry, guys.
Wait.
That was easy.
Nice.
I assisted.
Oh, guys.
Don't worry.
It's clapping time.
Zen throwing the dumpy.
It could be a Zen ult if they weren't cowards.
It's a yada, but nice.
Oh, yeah.
If he didn't become a monk What could have been What could
have been for our boys Zenyatta Okay nice Can I do a lot?
Yo I did the most healing Endorse me Endorse me guys I did
the most healing guys If it wasn't for me You guys would
never get healed I know you guys are voting for yourself How
could you?
Oh and you guys are voting for yourself How dare you?
Oh nice, see guys they voted for me now I knew it I'm so
confused How could you do this?
Vote for yourself
Alright Please let me play it non-healer How dare All right,
let's see.
I want to play I play Okay, now I want to play Spider-Man
Let me play Spider-Man All right, let me see Oh my god, I
forgot how many Okay, here's a warning Press face to crawl,
shoot a web cluster That deals damage and attacks a
Spider-tracer to hit the enemy Perform a double jump, launch
it Oh my, this is why it's five star Launch an enemy upward
dealing extra damage Uh Oh shit Guys I'm not No!
Oh my god, okay Does he dance?
Oh my god, okay I haven't even finished reading it Shoot a
web Okay Shoot a web If the enemy is tied Spider-Man will
get pulled to them Instead Launch an okay EF There's an F
attack too EF Okay Alright All right, there's an F attack as
well, and then there's E, and then there's this.
This makes me go up to them.
Okay, we got this.
All right, oh yeah, all right, there's a lot of moves.
All right, movement tech tap.
Oh my god.
Oh god, oh god.
That's fucking right.
Where are you?
Wait, wait, wait!
No!
He got away!
Guys, I need healing!
Guys!
Okay, we have one healer again!
When can I play TPS?
One day.
one day i can also enjoy enjoy the freedom back i go back i
go i know my place i know my place
i guess i was meant to be a healer okay here we go go into
the aura don't worry guys we're fine we're fine but what the
fucking secondary healer because I'm a fucking team player
please let the reload he's so low see I oh my god he the
game knows I'm a team player Tokyo's a healing slave I can I
play guys support is also so fun too guys i'm having a lot
honestly i am having a lot of fun on support not gonna lie
like i would say how many clones can i put out i don't think
i've jesus christ bro did you see the movement tech on the
hawk oh my god there's hawk movement tech oh my god bro the
fucking hawk all right we're gonna fucking not deal with
that the hog jump bro he's just fucking doomfisting
everywhere he's doing some fucking rollouts goodbye dokey is
forever lowkey don't worry I got you don't worry no oh it's
Bruce better Bruce better no Bruce better No!
Who's bat?
Anyway, how many fucking...
How many fucking clothes can I put out?
The beginning of a Loki main.
Always have been.
I knew I would have been a Loki main for the rest of my
life.
I always was a Loki main.
You just didn't know.
Okay, let me reload, guys.
Don't worry, I got you.
Please!
Your movement is too...
good bro i might as well just fucking kill this guy okay
nice two clones okay i can put two clones okay wait i want
to be penny parker yeah that's fucking where i'll spider you
okay nice i'll fucking oh goodbye goodbye i don't know what
i'm doing but goodbye Oh, nice.
Here we go.
We're fine.
We're okay.
Oh my god, our team is fucking busted.
We're rolling them so hard.
This is actually not fair.
Holy shit.
Bro, our Hulk is actually going fucking ape shit right now.
He's wintening right now, guys.
Like, holy shit.
look at him go he fucking the rollout is insane the rollout
is actually insane okay let's get rid of fucking Star Lord
all right nice okay I'm gonna put another one here oh I got
you oh I'm back we all have one respawn nice nice don't
worry win?
Oh, Master.
Oh, doing things as usual.
Okay.
No, he 100% deserved that.
This guy went fucking absolute nuclear.
It was actually crazy watching him bounce everywhere.
Oh, my God.
Hello.
Hey, guys.
Oh, yes!
Endorse me!
Guys, yes!
Yes!
Oh my god, they know I guess you also get an MVP too, Mr.
Hulk.
Easy clap.
Hulk actually smashed.
Oh my god.
He was fucking insane, dude.
This is actually crazy.
His gamma radiation.
He went gamma.
loki-dokie i'm gonna be a loki main every time i try to not
be a loki main it drags me back in wait did they oh wait did
people like leave their team oh no wait i won't try mantis
oh we lost hey guys i came oh i was i was a fill what the
fuck i just got here what I just got here!
You are fated to be Loki.
What the hell?
I literally have zero zeros.
I didn't even get a chance to pick my character.
I don't even exist.
I literally don't even exist in the fucking game.
I just got backfilled.
I can't believe they backfilled me.
what a bad teammate oh my god i barely existed toky isn't
real i hope they i'm pretty sure they're gonna make the ui a
lot better because like it's it's alpha guys can i play
spider-man now guys please please can i please play
spider-man guys can i can i please play dps right if if the
marble rival devs are watching please make roll cute that's
all i want i please please make roll cute
please loki doki smile
please that's all i want Please, I beg you, Fluffy.
Please support.
It's so fun.
I swear to God, support is so fucking fun.
I loved role...
As a support player, I loved role queue.
I fucking...
I don't know if, like, lower eels hated role queue, but,
like, higher eelob players loved role queue.
Because, like, I fucking hated, like, being a support player
in Overwatch and having to play, like, tanker DPS because
there were just too many supports.
I remember one time in Overwatch 1, We had a team where it's
just six support players and we actually won.
It was actually crazy.
And then we were like, oh my god This looks like fucking
Hanamura.
Wait.
Is there a choke point like Hanamura?
Wait, what the fuck?
This almost okay, the choke looks like Hanamura, but other
than that it's different Okay, oh god guys, guys.
Oh, it's fine.
Oh, it's not fine.
It's not fine.
The tank wants to get me Oh my god This is when you...
This is a person that actually knows how to play Loki.
Because look at all these lokies.
Oh, please!
Leave me alone!
That's fucking right.
Get you!
Got you!
That's fucking right!
Yes!
Got the fucking healer, guys!
Spider-Fifton, ready to punch!
I got the healers!
Oh my god, this is like Genji, but like harder.
Holy shit!
Bro, this is so hard because...
I need a higher sensitivity.
Holy shit.
To play Spider-Man, you need such a high sensitivity.
It's actually crazy.
Oh my gosh.
This is actually so...
Oh!
Guys, just go, girls, please.
I wonder if you can make goats in the Marvel Rivals.
That would be so funny if you can.
Oh my god, I got him!
Get me in the air!
That's fucking right!
God, so many things are happening on my screen!
I'm getting disoriented!
No.
Oh god.
Okay.
Spy.
No!
What is happening?
Guys, I can't, I cannot, I cannot play Spider-Man.
I can't, it's too, oh my god.
I, like, get too disoriented playing Spider-Man.
I'll just be Storm.
Clearly, Storm would be easier, right?
Because I'm in the air, you know?
And then I'll do damage boost right here.
And then I'll do fucking mega damage boost here.
That's fucking right.
I just can't.
Like, it's actually so difficult.
I need healing!
Packs!
Oh!
Wait, do we have enough tanks?
Oh, we don't!
No!
Okay, we need to try tank.
You know what?
I'll try Magneto.
What is Magneto?
Okay, shift, change the magnetic field to form, blocking all
four, conjuring magic shield, damage taken, oh my god, what?
Wait, what is this space?
Oh, space to fall slowly.
Okay, we're gonna try.
We'll try Magneto because we need a tank.
Guys, we will actually play Magneto.
Guys, don't worry.
You're all glad.
Wait, what?
I thought that was the...
Okay.
Okay, that's the shield.
Okay, I got it.
I got- I had to learn!
Guys, how do I not have heals anymore?
Guys, we have literally two supports!
Oh god.
Bro, there's a fucking hell up behind!
Minus!
She's just...
No!
Guys!
Get the fucking hell out!
Please.
Oh god.
Oh god, this is so difficult.
I'm trying so hard to take!
Bro, I'm just getting frozen!
Bro, I'm getting...
Fuck this guy.
I'm going to get rid of that fucking hella.
If it's the last thing I do.
Bro, I'm so mad.
No one's killing this hella right now.
I'm actually...
I'm so mad.
She's, like, just chilling in our back lines.
Where is she?
Oh, my God, she's literally... Guys, just fuck... Guys!
Oh, my God!
Guys, please just kill my whole life in the back line!
That's all I asked.
Guys, she's literally in our back lines, just farming us.
Guys, okay.
Where is Oh god, I need healing.
Wait, what?
Oh my god, what?
No.
That's fucking right.
Hit it.
Okay, it might be a little overkill, but like, I swear it
was worth it.
It was so 100% worth it.
Is she still up there?
Is she actually?
Oh my god, she is!
Are you fucking kidding?
Somebody, please shoot her down.
I'm gonna fly to her.
I'm mad.
Worthy.
Somebody, please.
Fly to this fucking bitch.
Okay.
That's not fair because I get shot from the side.
And I should have been shot on the side.
I can't get your Where's my help?
Okay Fuck oh my god, it's over Literally the only person
Fucking shooting her Oh my god Literally the only one I'm
actually I can't I believe I'm the only one actually
shooting guys.
I need healing Guys I swear to god if I see that hella back
there in the side.
I swear to god I swear to fucking god oh my god and our
fucking bro she's heading back there
He's actually heading back there.
That's actually fucking crazy that she's trying to get back
to high ground.
I'm actually so mad.
Bro.
Bro!
I'm getting out of DPS.
She's there again.
Storm clouds gather.
God the only way I can actually fight her is if I fucking
play storm only because oh god oh my god bro she's so good
at hella she's so good her projectiles insane
you can't strike holy she knows the projectiles speed
already that's actually that's cringe
Bro, fuck you!
I don't care!
It's okay.
I got her in the end.
It's because she had her fucking...
She was camping us in the fucking back.
Oh my god.
That's literally the only person.
I was the only person that dealt with the hella.
You guys are off
Literally the only person that was willing to shoot the dumb
hella Time to play hella.
It's time to play hella
It's time to play hella.
We're so back.
Okay, let's see.
I need to remember what the E was.
I still don't know what the E is Okay, let's see.
Fire multiple E.
Projection, Explosion, Hellsphere.
Oh, okay.
Stunned people.
Okay.
Now I know what it does.
Alright.
It stuns people.
Okay.
You can't beat him.
Join him.
Exactly.
I think I've been having a lot of fun, though.
Honestly.
Language Jokey.
This is a family game owned by Disney.
Thank you for the super chat.
Alright.
Imagine having a lot of fun.
I think this is actually a really fun game.
I don't know if it'll like live for I think if they change
the UI I honestly think um they have to change the UI a lot
to make this like a better game because I'm not like a huge
fan of the visuals like the not like the character models
but like the attacks and stuff and you have to change the
the health bars I think they should change the health bars
and the um because like um I always like I don't like the
help bars being in the middle at the bottom Because I always
forget what my health is I don't like the UI But I'm
assuming because this is alpha Because this is alpha, right?
So like a lot of things are going to change Because like
Overwatch UI during alpha test was so fucking bad It was so
bad It was like not Okay Alright I'm gonna do what she did
to me Ha ha ha It's fine It's fine It's like the mission
area is yours Here we go It's fine, that's fine Guys,
where's my teammate?
Woo!
Guys!
The end glitch Where the fuck is my teammate?
I did so much!
I actually did so much!
It's fun, it's a fun game.
It's actually a really fun game And like, it rewards good
players, like If you can aim, it feels so good.
It just feels really nice being, like, when you can aim and
then, like, you know, kill them.
It feels so rewarding being, if you're, if you're, like,
decent aim.
Alright, nice.
I got rid of...
Guys, I did.
I got rid of the fucking squid.
Guys, I clutched.
The squid is gone.
He no longer can hurt you.
That's fucking right Oh Loki please Loki Loki Kill me Where
the fuck is the healing?
Guys?
Okay
All right, it's a DPS.
I'm like, I'm fucking like hanging in there right now.
I'm fucking hanging in there at the moment.
Guys, that's all right.
98 HP, I'm fine with that, I guess.
Oh, now I'm 83.
Woo!
It's okay.
As long as I don't peek, it's fine.
Guys.
Oh, nice.
Oh, oh, oh!
Okay, Hela is like, oh my god, I'm finally past, guys, it's
actually crazy.
I'm finally past, like, 98 HP.
I never knew what that was like.
What the fuck?
There's a guy right here.
Is that, who's that?
Who is that?
I'm gonna save my all for the next round.
Come on, come on, Scarlet.
Come on, oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, she more sucked
me.
Lucky, please, help me, Lucky.
Please.
Lucky.
Oh, that one is a y'all.
Please, there's literally, like, three of you.
I don't understand.
Wait, what is that?
Oh, my God.
No!
Okay.
Alright, I gotta queue then.
I need to get closer.
Loki, please.
Just top me off.
Please.
Please, Loki, just top me off.
Please!
Healing is illegal.
guys why don't we have heals our low-key swapped off healing
do you think you swapped off healing because of me guys
there's no way there's okay now i forgot what her alt does
but like that was a very much of a waste of an alt wait jk
guys do you think she like do you think do you think she
because of me guys i think it was me i i think guys i think
it was me guys i might have spammed here a little bit too
much just maybe just maybe that was my bad look i needed
here it's not my I thought somebody fucking decided not to
hear?
Like, I am doing my job.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, please.
I'm trying.
I'm trying so hard.
I made my support tilted.
Oh, man.
Why did he do this to me?
We were winning.
If he's still a healer, we would have won.
How could he do this to me?
Destined to be Loki bird.
Just destined to be Loki bird.
But I mean, I feel like, oh, bear dog went healer.
Is that fair?
Oh, oh, just because I suck up my ego to go fucking healer.
They just want you to heal.
Loki-Doki strikes again.
I can't believe it.
Loki-Doki is real.
We lost our fucking other player.
I can't believe it.
Oh my god.
Born.
wanting to play dps born to be loki it just is bro what the
fuck star lord what the fuck holy what the fuck okay okay
bro okay i'm like so disoriented right now there's like way
too much stuff going on i don't like this map
Oh no, oh no, it's Xana!
Oh no.
Oh no, he's so fucked.
I'm so fucked.
Oh!
That's fucking right.
Oh, wait a minute.
Wait, that's actually...
Oh my god, wait a minute.
That's actually so sick what I just did.
Okay, that was pretty...
Like, outplayed him so hard.
New Loki tech.
New fucking Loki tech, guys.
Outplayed.
Actual Loki tech right there.
Okay, let's see.
Alright.
Alright, I need a shape shift soon.
Where's that?
Hello?
My turn, finally!
I get finally!
We might...
Guys, sorry for no heals, but this is important.
Wait, why can't I queue?
Wait, where am I?
Guys, I'm sorry.
Guys, bring them here!
Bring them here!
Okay, that was unlucky there.
That was actually very unlucky.
Nice.
It was a mistake, okay?
Okay, we had two loki's now that was like the most unlucky
loki loki all i've ever done wait where's the i hear i see
the scarlet witch okay starlord get healed scarlord oh my
god oh please scarlet your fucking movement though your
fucking movement all right nice we're doing our job all
right Star-Law is fucking dead.
He's so fucking dead.
Don't worry.
I got you.
For Mutant Kind.
Where is that?
What the fuck?
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, thank God.
Thank God for the world.
It's okay.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no.
I'm kidding!
Holy shit!
I actually game so hard there!
Keep going!
Oh my god!
Bro, I know so much Loki tech!
Oh god, whoops!
Maybe...
Yeah, there we go.
Alright, nice.
Oh my god.
I'm actually a Loki player.
Wait, actually.
Somebody fucking nerfed me.
Oh my god, somebody fucking nerfed me.
I'm actually insane at this.
Alright, I'm gonna kill our players real fast.
And then...
I'm gonna go up.
Yeah, oh my god, the fucking turret, though.
What the fuck?
Oh my god, okay.
It's okay, I got her.
Don't worry.
I'm DPS now.
Okay.
Oh, Rocket's low.
We're fine.
Bro, no, Loki is 100% getting nerfed.
There's no way.
His DPS is like, his damage is insane.
And, like, his cooldowns are so short.
There's no way they're making Loki like this out of Alpha.
It's too good.
It's actually...
Yeah, and with Rocket, too.
I think Loki and Rocket is just way too good top 500 loki
main by the way he has too many tools and he's like so
disorienting because like i can like swap between position
like i can swap between loki's if i get like dive he's gonna
get guided that's me loki and hawk oh yeah if you know the
hawk okay if you were here earlier and you saw that fucking
hawk player who in the fucking hawk move up Rollouts, it was
insane.
He was, like, jumping everywhere and sliding.
He was, like, Doomfist, uh, Doomfist rollouts there.
I know.
Actual top 500 lucky mate.
I can't wait to play Rank soon.
Rank comes out soon, apparently.
Like, in, like, a couple...
In, like, I think, like, today?
Tomorrow?
I don't remember when it's coming out.
But it's coming out soon.
Oh, don't worry.
I got you.
Oh, shit.
No, that's not what I...
No, I'm about...
What?
Okay, I actually...
No!
Wait, what is my ult?
What is my ult?
I don't even know what my ult is.
I hate Bandito!
No, they freeze me.
The Lunar Girl, if she hits her right click, freezes you.
I always come back.
I have many faces.
yeah the the lunar character freezes you if she hits it and
i always get hit i'm just so bad with tank i was never meant
to be a tank player unless it's like a damage tank i just
cannot play tank at all i just can't i was never meant to be
a tank player i have to go dps support There you go.
How is he still alive?
Rocket, shoot him!
Bear dog!
Come on, bear dog!
Oh god, we got to heal.
We got to heal dragon hell.
Okay, I got you.
I got you, Magneto.
Nice.
Are we capping?
We are, right?
Yeah, we are.
Nice.
Oh my god.
He's so short.
It makes me wonder about, like, hit boxes, you know?
Because, like, the hitboxes must be, like, for, like,
rockets.
Like, he's so fucking tight.
Wait a minute.
Yeah, I was gonna say, I'm getting hit by somebody else.
Oh, that's not what I wanted!
No, did we get our control back?
Okay.
Bye.
I got you.
I got you dragon hell.
Oh, we got yeah, we got it.
Okay, nice.
We got it.
Oh, no, she's gonna dance.
She's dancing, guys.
Guys, she's dancing.
Oh, Scarlet Witch.
Okay, Scarlet Witch.
I did not mean to be Scarlet Witch, but okay.
All right, I hope I'm gonna kill her.
That's all I have.
All right, um, DPS now.
Let's go.
nice i'm scarlet witch now all right nice we're good oh no
my one weakness okay we're doing it it's like pretty close
never mind it's not i'm just gonna put one guy up here for
him all right that he's like gonna face tank for it's fine
it's fine if i just keep shooting here i can kill him
the stairs oh no no dragon head oh god oh i'm sorry i'm
sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry he doesn't know he doesn't know
they don't know they don't know they don't know they don't
know i'm here they don't know they don't know they don't
know it's okay it's okay they don't know i'm here i
outnumber you their team's capture progress
They don't know them, though.
They don't know I'm here.
Oh, shit.
Okay, repeat, they know.
Repeat, they know.
Okay, 1v1 me.
That's fucking right.
No, no, no, no.
Don't worry about...
Oh, yeah, that's fucking right.
1v1 me.
That's right, Scarlet.
Oh, that's right.
I'm better.
getting right got it they might know now
the clone of me i'm that's cheating i baited him so hard 1v1
with clones heal it by the way yeah i'm not surprised this
guy got mvp he had he literally had like the ace tag i think
i don't know what that means though like that tag they had I
received an output from Roger guys upload me I'm important I
mean I guess he deserves it though how much did I do damage
oh my god that guy got 10k damage holy shit 11k oh my god
that meant it got 11k damage wait is competitive out yet
it's not that was really fun though I had like such a fun
time season embark on missions or the costumes green scar uh
what is the battle pass like i'm actually curious unlock at
24 unlock at level 30.
what about missions that was really fun though oh my god i
actually had a lot of fun playing this i actually had like
actually a fucking um there's going to be like tournaments
and stuff factions creative jordan and superhero team
cosmetic oh president loki guys you can now spend money
already is that looking crazy you can actually he can spend
cosmetic money that's so much fun i might play this more off
stream not gonna lie but like this actually has been like i
don't know i've been having a really fun time so far test
like that's why like as long i i it just looks really fun
and i actually did have a lot of fun playing uh solos um in
general i think like when it does get more i think like at
the ui at the ui and like the the uh the visual effects when
you're fighting changes um like it's more refined i think
it'll look a lot better but i honestly when you're playing
it might visually might not be like super polished yet i
mean it is alpha but all i care about is like I have fun,
you know?
Yeah, like, I had a lot of fun.
I really did.
And, like, I like the tech.
I like the tech for, like, the characters.
And it's super, it seems really complicated if you know,
like, more of the fucking movement tech and stuff.
And, like, all the...
Like, the shit I was doing on Loki, like, the fucking juke
shit with the clones and stuff like it forces the person to
like 180 turn around when i fucking snap my finger like yeah
i hope it does stay around long um because you know rest in
peace Gundam evolution that shit died out really fast but
honestly i hope Marvel Rivals does stay around long and that
a lot of the shit gets repolished um because i honestly
think it does seem like a really fun game and i and
development is put into it the it might actually be a very
very good game uh bite size thank you the super chat thank
you thank you thanks for the stream lowkeeper thank you guys
i hope you guys enjoyed watching i definitely i'm doing a
try and play i'm gonna play this more upstream for sure
because like um it's definitely super enjoyable hey guys as
always i'm gonna call it here as always everybody stay
hydrated posture check get up and move around uh wait get up
and move around to get I almost forgot my line.
And if you stayed up for me, head to bed.
Because you deserve it.
I'll see you guys next time, everybody.
Bye, guys.
Bye.