Sorry guys for being late.
I went outside to get food.
Cause I was hungry.
And then cause I didn't eat dinner last night.
I was like so...
Oh my god.
Sorry I don't have ADHD.
I just got distracted.
Alright.
Doki bird.
I swear to god.
Somebody claim fucking doki bird.
Doki bird.
Uh.
Terms of use.
Okay good.
Nobody claim doki bird.
Nobody else claim doki bird during the beta test.
That's great to know.
Alright.
Oh no you guys are not seeing the cool ass intro.
I'm so sorry.
No!
Sorry.
You guys missed out on the cool ass intro.
It was really fucking cool.
Because I was too... Oh my god is this window capture?
I forgot.
This is window... Oh my god I forgot.
Sorry I'm a mess right now.
I literally just got back from eating.
And then I could have went straight to do stream.
But then I also...
Teehee.
I also... Other than eating I also went over to... To pet my dog.
Because like he deserves it cause he's a good boy.
Uh.
Hahaha.
So.
And then... And I didn't realize that there was a huge ass patch that was going on.
So I had to wait for the patch to finish and everything.
But I didn't eat dinner last night and I didn't eat... Oh my gosh.
Dad is still here looking at me.
Did you miss me?
Ugh.
You know how like... Okay I don't know if like your dog does this.
Um.
But like whenever like...
My...
Whenever like I stick my hand out.
Uh.
Dad like gets two little stubby hands and like um...
And like latches onto one hand while I pick him up.
Hahaha.
And it's so cute.
Like he... He has... He just latches onto one arm.
Like... Like... Like a koala.
And then like... And then I pick him up.
Hahaha.
It's so fucking cute.
Oh my god.
And then he started tucking his head underneath my...
Arms' now.
Awwww.
Sorry.
I don't have ADHD, I'm just...
I- I think I don't have ADHD.
Um.
But yes.
That's why.
I'm really sorry for being late.
Umm.
I didn't have lunch and I didn't have dinner last night because I was so tired...
that I went straight to bed.
I went...
Straight to bed.
And then...
Um, and then I just slept all the way until 3pm.
I slept all the way until...
No not even 3pm.
I slept all the way till 4pm.
And then after that, I woke up and went out to eat at a...
You know, took a shower, went out to eat at a restaurant.
And... Oh wait, no!
JK!
I woke up to make my waiting room.
And then I went back to sleep.
I was like, I gotta make my waiting room.
And I made my waiting room, went back to sleep.
And then I woke up at 4, took a shower, and then went out to eat.
Because I was so fucking hungry.
Since I didn't eat anything.
And then I finished eating at like 4.50 or whatever.
And I fucking... I like... sprint walked over...
I hate... I hate... What is it called?
Because I know sprint walking is an actual Olympic sport.
What is it called again?
That thing where you like... Power walk!
Is it power walk?
Because I know that's an Olympic sport.
Yeah, I power walked back home.
And then dad was like pet me.
And then I was like, ooh, okay, I'm sorry, dragoons.
But if dad wants petsies, that's important.
So... So I was petting dad for like a couple of minutes before I was like, okay, now...
I... I turn on the PC.
But yes!
Anyway, speaking of Olympics, they just... literally just announced that...
E-sports is gonna be an Olympic sport now.
You know how... Okay, for those who didn't watch the collab with Zen...
And Amelie, I was talking about how like they had...
Video games as an Olympic sport, but they weren't really like...
They weren't really... E-sport titles.
They were like archery and... Like archery and soccer and all that.
And like...
It's like... It's like Wii sports, but like Olympics anyway.
So they had that back.
But today, they... The committee finally voted in...
They finally voted in...
E-sport titles as a real... As a real Olympic...
For the real Olympics.
But the funniest thing is that there's no FPS games.
I thought that was so funny!
I... I fucking... You guys were like coping.
They're like, no!
FPS isn't dying!
I fucking... Shooters are dead!
You know what?
FPS shooters... Not just FPS...
But shooters in general!
Shooting games!
It's dying!
We're not even invited!
League... Rocket League got into the Olympics!
Before us!
That's fucked up!
Mobile games are in the Olympic E-sport games!
Is that fucked up?
Like...
Mobile games are in it!
And shooters are not!
We are the new RTS of the generation!
We are the RTS of this generation!
Anyway, speaking of... Speaking of shooters...
I'm gonna be playing Marvel Rivals!
I...
Alright, you guys wanna know...
Which... Okay, these are the games I got in.
League of Legends...
Rocket League...
Street Fighter...
Tekken...
iRacing!
NBA 2K!
How the fuck do you make an Olympic sport out of NBA 2K?
Anyway, and then there's FIFA and mobile games.
So...
All I'm saying is that...
Developers... Publishers of shooting games did not give them a big enough check.
Because apparently, majority of these games that got in...
Was funded by the Saudi government.
So...
I'm surprised Apex didn't get in.
Because...
Falcon has an Apex team.
That's literally Imperial House team.
So...
All I'm saying is that Apex did not pay enough to be in the Olympics.
They literally had oil money.
We don't have oil money, guys!
The shooter...
The shooter FPS game community does not have oil money!
Where's our Oilers?
Who will represent us?
What the...
Hmm...
Yes, it's the actual Olympics.
They literally voted for the Olympic eSport games.
No!
We deserve oil money!
Please!
Big day for soccer moms who have 500 plus hours on Candy Crush!
Thank you for the super chat!
No name!
Thank you!
Yeah, unfortunately we did not have enough funding to have...
We didn't have enough funding for...
To be in the Olympics.
D-Dragon, thank you for the super chat!
Thank you!
Laughs in fighting games.
I told you guys!
I think I'm really good at analyzing the current trends.
Because I told you guys.
I was like, oh yeah, fighting games.
Fighting games are clearly like on the rise right now.
Because I mean they're expanding.
They literally announced like an expansion for Evo.
So...
I had a feeling that fighting games is like the newest gaming trend.
Um...
Alright, let's see.
Alright!
So, Marvel Rivals!
Marvel Rivals!
Um...
A huge shout out to the devs for giving me an invite to Marvel Rivals closed beta.
I did an alpha.
I did the alpha test.
And now I'm here for the closed beta!
So, the interesting about it is that there are new characters now.
Venom's in here now.
Whoa!
I hope the volume is okay.
I don't know if Sound Guy is still at Evo.
Oh, that's so cool!
Wait, I want to watch that again.
That is actually really cool.
Oh!
Yeah, the devs DMed me on Discord to give me some codes.
Um...
Let's see.
Using his symbi- Oh, it's Eddie!
It's Eddie Brock!
Oh!
That's so fucking cool!
I really like the animation.
We can be- Oh, we can be Blue Eddie!
First appears in Marvel Rivals.
Oh, this is his first appearance!
Sight and Clash.
Surrender now or I'll be feasting on you.
What's the difference between- I guess he's blue.
Oh!
Oh my god, that's so fucking cool.
Wait, I really like- Is he a tank?
What is he?
Okay, abilities.
Wait, I want to know what is he.
He is- What is that?
What is two fists?
Oh, you guys can't see it.
Uh- Okay, you can see his head.
What is two arms?
Oh, he's a tank!
Okay, that makes sense because of his hip box.
Okay, he's a tank.
Oh, he's a tank.
All right, what does he do?
Unleashes tentacles forward to attack enemies.
Oh, that's his normal primary.
Feast of- Oh!
Okay, I'll bring up the game volume a little bit.
Okay.
All right.
What is this?
I didn't get to see this.
Underground for free movement.
Oh my god!
What the fuck?
Wait, that's so cool.
That's his Q.
What's his shift?
Oh, he can swing around!
Hey, dad.
Sorry, he looked up at me and was like, kiss?
And I was like, okay.
All right.
Symbiote generates bonus health against damage.
The greater the bonus health generates- Oh, what?
Oh!
That's, um...
That's basically Hammond!
That's Hammond, Orisa, Sigma thing.
Where you press it and then you get like health back.
Oh, that's- Oh, frenzy arrival.
What's this?
Ooh.
That's the- Oh, so I brought up the volume a little bit more in the sound guide.
Thank you for the five-kithed ships!
Thank you!
Cellular corrosion.
Unleash technicals to slow enemies within reach.
Okay, that- That slows them down and also gives them that- Also damages them.
And then- Oh my- Oh, that's the Spider-Man shit!
Okay, that- No matter what this and the Spider-Man one is like, it's so disorienting.
I- I do not- I don't know how anybody can play this.
Because like, we were Spider-Man, we were like fucking everywhere and I was like- I wanted to- I don't get motion sickness, but like that shit fucking sucked.
Like- Alright, what's this?
Venom shares a part of the symbiote with Spider-Man Peter Parker, activating your symbiotic abilities.
Spider-Man Peter Penny Parker can convert this time into explosive spikes.
Oh, so like, if we have Penny and- Oh my god!
What the fuck?
Okay, that's cra- That's actually crazy.
Alright.
What's this?
Hero story.
Oh my god, you can unlock hero stories?
Alright.
I just realized I should check the- the- my settings.
My settings for this.
Oh no.
Not fucking- No, no, no, no, no.
Alright, let's see.
Limit FPS.
Uh... 120?
That's like the max?
I didn't even realize that was the max.
There's no way!
Okay, show my FPS please.
Yeah, I realized they reset everything.
Oh yeah, everything has been reset.
Okay, I'm gonna set medium.
Um...
Confirm.
I forgot everything has been reset.
Uh...
Fullscreen...
V-sync...
Audio...
Let's see...
Alright, audio guy.
Let me know what I should bring up from here.
Uh...
Playback, voice chat...
Voice over subtitles...
Yeah.
We always want voice over subtitles.
Uh...
I don't know.
I actually don't know if...
If this is the default.
I don't know.
I don't remember.
Has anyone...
Did anyone get into the beta?
Is this the default or do I have to redo my...
Um...
Uh...
Meme settings at 100?
No, it's at 200 and...
Okay.
Okay, dad, you're going down.
Alright.
Is that default?
Dad, this is the...
Okay, that's default.
Alright, I have to change that then.
Uh...
Let's see...
Dot...
Oh my god.
Everything reset.
Everything reset!
No!
I hate it when everything resets itself.
Play with dot...
Ally on...
Um...
Is melee...
Did they reset melee as well?
Melee attack.
Yeah, they did.
Everything is reset.
So guys, nothing...
Alright.
Oh.
Sorry, dad's gone now.
They actually reset everything!
Oh, that sucks.
That really sucks.
Because I know...
I know...
I know that...
Alright, bring mastery to 11...
Oh, 100.
Okay.
I know that like...
I...
I had like specific controls.
So...
Yeah.
I hate it when that happens.
Because...
Ah...
Because I...
I didn't...
Does anyone remember what my sense was?
Did anyone?
Guys!
Can anyone go through my...
My first Marvel Rival streams and tell me what my sense is?
Please, my sense is...
I need to know!
I need to know what my sense is!
Somebody check my VOD!
People are like, why don't you check your own VOD?
Because then you guys can plus more views on it and I can get more ad...
At least I'm being truthful!
At least I give it to you straight and I don't lie!
Okay?
1.09.
Nice.
Okay.
1.09.
Is it 1.09?
Is it actually?
That's not smart!
Look, I give it to you straight.
I don't...
I didn't lie about it.
Okay?
Alright.
Is it actually 1.09?
Okay.
1.
1.09.
That's great.
Thank you guys.
And thank you for giving me that plus one view on that Marvel Rival VOD so I can get one more cent.
And add revenue.
I really...
I really appreciate it.
Thank you for boosting my viewer engagement on the other VOD as well.
For those who are watching the VOD, hey, can you guys...
For those who are watching the VOD, can you comment down below what my sense is in the...
For those who are watching that VOD, comment below to tell me what sense I was using on my last VOD.
Anyway, let's see.
I think that's everything.
Okay.
I think.
I'm gonna double check.
Yeah, I think that's everything.
I think that's all I have to reset in.
Alright.
What are the other ones?
I know there was another...
They added another new hero.
Oh yeah!
There you go!
Adam Warlock!
This is the other guy.
The gold guy!
The guy with mommy issues!
The genetically engineered Adam Warlock wields mighty quantum magic, allowing him to...
Wait, is he a fucking heel slut?
I don't know.
Oh, he is!
Wait, he is?
Oh my god!
He is!
He was so strong in Guardians of the Galaxy!
Alright.
And heals souls with a gentle touch when the time comes for his allies to unite.
But like, he killed so many people in Guardians of the Galaxy!
I don't understand!
Cosmic Jade.
Okay.
So that's him but with jade colors.
That's the NC version.
He got better!
He became a support player!
He's better!
Alright, what's this?
Launch the quantum energy to deal damage.
Wait.
Is this?
Oh my god!
He's Mercy!
Mercy!
He's mercy!
He is!
He's a heel slut of Marvel Rivals!
Die!
I have Rezz!
He has the OG Rezz ability!
Everybody, die on point.
I have Rezz.
Everybody, die on point!
No way!
Guys, die on point!
I have reds!
I have karmic revival!
Guys, I have karmic die on point!
Oh gee, Brissy.
We're running it back.
Avengers never die!
Monster, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Fun fact, Adam Warlock in the comics is the primary enemy of Thanos.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
That's his ult too, by the way.
That's his ult.
Unite the souls, granting them healing over time and distributing damage taken across the bond.
Oh, okay.
So like we share the damage... wait, that's so fucked.
Wait, do they die?
Oh my... wait, that's so fucked.
Wait!
Oh, you guys like take damage.
You guys like share damage as a soul bond.
What's this?
I mean, this is actually a really cool ability.
Target an enemy for a bouncing stream of healing, which also heals himself upon casting.
Self-targets if no ally is selected.
Uh... oh, okay.
Okay, so healing them will heal me.
I see.
Uh... what's this?
And then swiftly launch... okay, that's just the attack.
And then regenerative cocoon.
Adam can freely move as a soul and reforges his body.
Oh!
So he has... he has second life.
Wait, that's... wait, he's pretty broken.
I think his heal must not be that strong then.
He must not have a strong heal because like all his heals are... all his heals are abilities.
Yeah.
He... all he... all he does... he can attack.
There's this damage.
His like secondary and primary are damage, but his healing ability are abilities.
Like, I mean... sorry, his Because healing are just abilities.
So basically, he's mostly...
He's like a DPS more than a healer.
Umm...
I feel like.
And then he can...
Okay, what's this?
Enhances the Reaper power of Starlord.
Oh, they will all... If you have Starlord and Mantis, they can also revive.
His E is strong and has two charges.
Oh, this one?
Okay.
It has two charges.
Yeah, but I feel like he's more so of a damage character.
Because he only heals from his abilities alone.
So he doesn't heal from anything else.
So there's only two new characters?
I believe... This is why I mean...
Wait, wait.
No, not her.
This is Juno.
This is literally Juno.
But like, K-pop.
This is literally her.
Alright.
Umm...
Let's see.
It's the clap healer.
Yeah, it's clap to heal.
That's her.
Alright, so...
What did sound guy say?
Bring up... Turn down sound effects and bring up... Alright.
Let's see.
Sound effects...
Let's bring you down.
And then I'll bring you down to 85.
And then I'll bring up the volume a little bit.
Boop, boop, boop.
There you go.
I brought it up a little bit.
Alright guys, time to check it out.
Time to check out the game.
It's just me.
Quick match, conquest, respond to a flexible location and eliminate as many... Oh, is this deathmatch?
I think this is deathmatch.
This has to be deathmatch.
Cause it's like conquest.
Yeah, she claps to heal.
Uhhh...
And you'll bring more effects than just healing.
Monster, thank you super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Yeah, that's very interesting.
Because like Adam is clearly a very like DPS character.
Um... Versus the healer.
So it's very interesting to like see in general.
Alright, royal palace.
Time for deathmatch.
I wanna play Adam.
Let's see what it's gonna be like as Adam.
Alright.
Where is...
To maintain a fair game environment, voice chat...
Oh, okay.
You're recording.
Alright, that's cool.
Alright.
What is everybody else playing for deathmatch?
Is this deathmatch?
I should...
I don't know.
Is it?
Yeah, but like...
Wait!
Oh!
Oh, it's a team deathmatch!
Okay, it's team deathmatch.
Alright.
And then...
Okay, I can charge the...
I can charge that.
Oh, what the f...
Oh, we're straight in!
Okay, we're straight in!
Okay!
Holy shit!
That is so disorienting!
I'm sorry.
That is actually so disorienting.
I was not ready for that.
Oh my god!
There's so many things!
Ah!
The workacoon!
Oh god.
Oh god, I'm running away!
I'm running away!
Bro, what the f...
They only have 10 kills!
Eww!
Jesus Christ!
Okay guys, I don't know if I wanna...
Guys, I...
Who am I playing against?
Are they f... in a stack?
Cause what the f... is going on?
They have to be in a stack or something!
Cause what the...
Oh god.
This is bad.
This is...
What?!
Alright, who is...
Alright, it's time.
It's time.
I don't remember the abilities, but it's time.
By the way, I don't remember the abilities at all, guys.
I think I forgot I think I remember like, the one thing I did not like is I did not remember the abilities.
Oh god!
I remember now!
I have to set these up!
I'm really...
Okay, this should not have been my first game.
I'm so disoriented right now.
I am really...
disoriented.
Holy shit.
Alright!
That was fast.
That was so fast!
Alright, we're gonna play Conquest another time.
I...
I can't.
I literally did not have time to learn the game.
I did not!
Bro!
I didn't have time to learn the game!
What?!
Alright, Conquest fucking sucks.
I'm gonna do a quick catch.
Okay.
If you want to learn the game, do not play Conquest.
I did not have time to like, register anything.
I literally showed up and then the enemy team got 20 kills in literally 10 seconds.
I don't know how that was possible.
That was so fast.
Oh, the game is over.
How did I get 10 kills that fast?
Okay, now I can learn the game.
Okay.
Let's see.
F1.
I need to remember.
Okay.
Q.
Shift is to Soulbond.
E.
Okay, Shift is Soulbond.
E is to Avatar Lifesteal.
Okay, so E is to heals and I can get Soulbond to people.
Alright, I'm just gonna get Soulbond to everybody.
Um...
I'm gonna get Soulbond to everybody I see.
Why learn when you can die?
Jesus Christ.
Alright, it's okay.
We're fine now.
We've learned how to play this game now.
Everything is fine.
I can finally learn... Wait, this isn't even a map.
This is a new map, right?
Or is this...
Yeah, wait.
Is this...
No, no, no.
This is not the new map.
This is an old map.
It looks a lot better.
Wait, they changed stuff.
I just realized.
Alright, Soulbond time!
You too!
You're Soulbonded even if you did not want to be.
Congratulations!
Oh, God.
I have to reload.
There is not a lot of ammo, by the way.
There is not a lot of ammo.
Holy shit!
Get hit!
Oh, I guess...
I keep thinking... I keep trying to shoot the heal right now.
This is not good.
Come on, Magneto's load!
Soulbond!
Even if you didn't want to, you're Soulbonded now!
I don't like the lack of ammo.
I'm not gonna lie.
I feel like I do not have a lot of ammo.
Get Soulbonded!
It's okay.
Oh, wait.
He's one.
Nice.
I got him.
Okay.
Yeah!
Well, poor Spider-Man already used up my abilities.
Wait.
Who was that?
Who's that?
Who did that?
Oh, God.
Get healed!
Soulbounded!
Even if you didn't want to!
Oh, my God.
Clap to heal!
Nice.
Easy.
It's so fucking easy.
Alright.
Aggressive healing.
I don't know what some of these items are.
Alright.
Nice.
What is that?
Who is that guy?
Heals.
Get healed!
Get Soulbounded!
That's fucking right now your best friend!
Heal!
Wait.
I snapped a heal.
That's cool.
I like that I'm snapping my heal.
Soulbound!
Raise!
I have raise!
There you go!
Best decision of my life!
Woo!
There you go.
All the buttons!
Snap!
Oh, don't!
I can't snap!
Snap!
Hahaha!
I snapped guys!
Snap to heal!
Snap!
Hahaha!
I tried my best!
Alright.
Soulbounded!
You're best friends now!
You're welcome!
You're now best friends!
Alright.
It's only the support alive right now.
But I can headshot though.
So it's fine.
Guys!
Where's our tank?
They're getting closer!
Guys, where's our tank?
I do not feel safe!
Snap!
Hahaha!
Friend!
Oh, get away healer!
Only I can... Snap!
Snap!
Hahaha!
Oh shit!
I like the snap ability.
It's actually really fun.
Hahaha!
Bro, who keeps healing this bitch?
Best friends!
What does the soulbound do?
Basically, like, it makes it so...
Um...
Snap!
Oh no!
I don't wanna fear... Oh!
He missed!
That's fucking right, bitch!
Get shit out!
Snap!
He's too far away!
I can't snap!
He's... Oh, I don't have abilities.
That's why.
That makes more sense.
I just did it.
What the fuck?
Is he that... Not him?
Is that... Hahaha!
Why is he moving?
Oh god.
I... Die!
I have friends!
Die on point!
I don't think I should, like, spam that though.
I should use that when, like, we're actually in danger.
Hahaha!
Oh no, he's gonna dance!
He's gonna dance now!
Soulbound!
Okay, nice.
This is so easy.
Wait, already?
That's a really fast ult.
This is such an easy game.
This should have been my first game.
Hahaha!
Stop shipping!
No, I'm shipping my own team!
That's different!
Bro, this is sad.
This is so... This should have been my first game.
Hahaha!
Yay!
I'm gonna make a big victory!
Big win!
Soulbinding.
I'm just making sure they're, like, best friends now!
Hahaha!
They are...
No, they're real people!
They're real people!
Hahaha!
So fucking easy.
I know, cause I got absolutely fucking destroyed in my first game.
Like...
There's no way.
There's no way these guys aren't real.
I got destroyed in my first game.
Chat.
I...
Jesus Christ!
9000 damage!
There's no way.
A bot would not be...
This has to be a real person.
I refuse.
I will prove to you this, guys, that this is a real person.
I'm gonna add them as a friend.
Hahaha!
I will... I will prove to you they're a real person!
Cause I will add them as a friend.
If they accept they're real.
Hahaha!
No way.
A.I.
best friend.
Alright.
What if...
If bots and A.I.
is truly taking over?
If bots can add friends?
I don't know.
I think Adam's pretty fun.
I don't like his projectile speed that much though.
His projectile speed is not like the best.
No!
They took Adam!
Um...
That was fun to play.
Alright.
I remember she was fun.
Uh... let's see.
Shift... E...
Project an explosive...
No!
I forgot her abilities!
Please!
I wanted to read a little longer!
Play magic!
But magic has like portals and melee!
And I get very confused!
Okay.
There's that.
And then...
What was the E again?
How do I look at her thing?
Okay.
There you go.
Uh... E... Okay.
To stun.
Okay.
That stuns.
And then...
This is my escape ability.
Okay.
Uh... Okay.
I can fall slowly.
Okay.
Wait.
How do I fall slowly?
Oh there you go.
Weeeee!
Alright.
I know Hela is like really strong.
Like especially her ult.
What the fuck?
Oh!
That's just the...
The decoration.
Okay sorry.
I got really confused.
I was like what the fuck is that?
Oh that's the card!
Wait that...
I swear to god that was not what it looked like before.
That was not what it looked like.
Take us!
Someone save the tank!
Oh no I'm so bonded.
Who am I best friends with?
Who am I...
Who is my best friend?
Okay.
I need to know who it is.
Alright.
I need to use my...
I need to know who it is.
Our... our Loki is like tanking so hard.
Get over there!
That's right!
No!
He can block that?
Wait that's new!
That is new!
We gotta get the tank.
Come on!
Headshot!
No!
Stupid Reinhardt's shield!
What the fuck?
Who's that?
Oh that's Iron Man.
Come on, man!
Come on!
Come on, anime!
You can't glide forever!
God damn it.
Okay, he can.
Come on, man!
That's right!
Get over here!
That's fucking right!
Yeeeeeeah!
Wait, why am I flying?
How did I start flying?
Who got me up in the sky?
Who got me there?
Alright, get that rocky raccoon.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, rocky raccoon.
Oh, shit!
Oh no, it's Magneto.
It's Magneto.
Guys!
He has Zarya bubble!
Okay, I'm gonna just...
Let's just walk, guys.
Let's just walk away.
We don't have to be there.
Wait, no!
This is a new map.
I've never seen this map before.
Alright, get that rocky raccoon.
Get over here.
Get over here, you rodent!
Oh, shit!
I'm joking!
JK, JK, JK!
Where am I getting shot from?
Oh, it's you.
No.
So, buy me!
Okay.
There we go.
Nice.
That's fucking right!
Oh, I see you!
I have waz!
Nice.
Easy.
Don't choke!
I never choke.
Watch this.
Wait, where am I getting shot from?
Oh, shit!
So, buy me!
I know we have an Atom!
Oh, my god!
Oh, god!
Where am I getting shot from?
No, that's not...
I'm so confused.
Like, where am I getting shot from?
Oh, that's you!
That's fucking right.
You can't fuck with me.
Yeah, Hela's damage is insane.
She used... her damage used to be really, really good.
But, like, I feel like they buffed her damage.
Not gonna lie.
Oh, we have high ground?
We have to go up?
Where are they?
Get over here.
You think flying's gonna stop you?
Oh, I see you, little guy!
I see you!
Where did he go?
Oh, wait!
It's Atom!
Get over here, Atom!
That's fu- Get your ass over here!
Oh, no!
Save me!
So, buy me!
Oh, thank god!
Alright.
I'm okay.
Sorry, it was an overreaction.
Sorry, it was just a little overreaction, but I'm okay now.
They know the carry!
They're always trying to...
Oh my god.
Oh, that was scary.
I don't know what that was!
I have no idea what that was there.
Okay.
Am I gonna go high ground?
Maybe?
Oh, shit!
Nice!
Okay.
I can only literally hit one person.
Guys, break the...
Break the area!
Yes!
Oh!
Nice!
No!
It's fine.
We're fine.
And then...
Where's my team?
Wait, did everybody die?
I am not fine.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, everybody.
I didn't realize everybody was dead.
I didn't...
How long is this point?!
I...
Venom, are you okay?!
But also, how long is this point?!
I swear!
I swear to god, this is...
Okay.
I can fucking kill you.
Wait, where...
Wait, that's not fair!
He just flew away!
That's not fair!
That's fucking right.
Okay, I did back off a little.
I do have the soul bond.
So we're fine.
Jesus!
This is so hard to push!
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh, oh!
Where did you come from?!
It's okay, I'm a crow!
I'm crow now!
Any heals?
Thank you, he snapped a heal.
Jesus Christ!
This one area is so hard to push.
This is like the Anamura.
Oh, he's insane!
Get him!
He's insane!
No bot would just fucking stop moving.
That's when you know he's real.
Why did he stop moving?!
Oh, this is good.
I have ult soon.
The ult is so strong for this area.
Wait, did we do it?!
That's it?!
They backed off!
Wait, they just backed off and let us push that!
That's fucking...
right!
Sorry, the bot stopped moving.
That's fucking right.
Endorse me.
Oh my god!
Okay, she is so strong.
Wait, she's actually so fucking strong.
Holy shit!
11,000 damage!
Oh my god!
That's actually crazy.
That's really...
um...
That's a lot.
That's a lot!
Compared to everybody else.
That's right.
You all...
Who the fuck is she?!
What did she do?!
She had 6k...
You guys are stacking, you fucking losers.
She did nothing!
You really gotta get...
Give the person who has 6k half my damage!
The same amount of endorsements?!
There's no way a bot do a stack.
Affiliate, thank you for 10k!
Give the shivs!
Thank you!
Alright.
Oh, I'm fucking...
Okay, they have zero support.
Oh wait, no, they have Rocket Raccoon.
It's Adam time.
Oh my god.
Don't worry.
It's Adam time.
Snap to heal.
Don't worry, everybody!
I am rea- Where do I go?
Guys!
The moment I figure out this map!
Do not worry, everybo- Snap!
Snap!
So bonded!
Best friends forever!
Where are they?
I think the only issue- Jesus Christ!
Guys!
I don't have a lot of snaps to give you guys!
I'm running out of snaps!
Chill!
Snap!
Guys, I'm running out of snaps!
Nooooo!
We got so fun!
I'm trying to snap!
Guys, I don't- Guys, these guys are good!
We're so bonding!
Oh god!
I'm running out!
Snap!
Okay.
Guys, I can't snap forever.
You guys can't be best- I don't have enough friendship bonds for all of you.
I don't have enough friendships!
Friendship!
Guys, I'm running out of friendship bracelets!
Snap!
Please!
Snap.
Oh my god, I snapped so many times.
So bad!
Oh god.
No!
It's okay, I have cocoon.
Goodbye.
I should not have cocoon there.
Little spiders, get over here.
Little spiders.
Leave me alone!
Snap!
Oh god, I'm sorry.
You're fucking dead.
I'll do born again here.
I don't think our team is good.
Guys, I have a feeling my team is dog shit.
Just a little bit.
Oh my god.
These guys... Snap!
Snap!
Oh!
Fuck them!
They know!
Please.
Somebody soul bond right now.
Snap!
Oh god.
Oh god, there's so many soul bonders.
No!
Thank god!
Oh, thank god he's bad!
Snap!
This is so hard to control sometimes.
Oh, who's feasting?
Who's feasting?
I don't have snap!
I'm sorry, sir lord!
I'm sorry!
I didn't prep enough friendship bracelets for everybody!
Okay.
Snap.
This is actually so difficult.
Oh my god.
I'm so disoriented.
Who are you?
Peter Parker?
Oh god, Peter Parker.
Soul bond.
No!
Yo, you're dead!
Somebody get Peter!
Somebody get him!
Oh god.
It's okay.
I have health pack.
I'm trying my best.
I don't do enough heals for this.
Snap!
Please!
Don't die on point!
I'm so disoriented right now, guys.
Oh god!
This is one...
This is really one...
Oh god.
I'm snapping!
I'm snapping out of fear!
Oh god.
Okay, we're good.
We're okay.
We're okay, guys.
Everything...
Everything is fine.
Sorry, I'm getting...
This is a lot.
Get away!
Friendship!
Oh no, I can't do friendship right now.
I need two seconds cooldown.
I feel like I see somebody behind us.
Is somebody behind us?
No!
Friendship!
Okay.
That's good.
Oh no.
They went Marvel Aquaman.
I'm sorry for all...
Namor?
Where is his movie?
Oh shit.
No.
I have to heal by myself.
I have to heal by myself now.
I'm sorry.
Oh no!
Please live a little bit longer!
Okay.
I don't have enough heals.
I don't have enough snaps for everybody.
Please calm down!
Okay, nice.
We're good.
Where is he?
Alright, he's over there.
I mean, we're doing a lot better than the other team.
Last game.
When they had to defend.
Honestly.
He does not want friendship.
Get him from the turret for him.
Ooh.
Okay, snap.
Friendship on.
I feel like it's good to give that to...
Oh, he's one!
Holy shit!
Oh, I think our tank died.
I think...
Guys, I think our tank died.
That... snap!
Oh, he's dead.
Get the fucking shit on.
That's bright.
I can fucking aim, bitch.
That fish was insane, though.
That fish was scary as hell.
Alright.
Nice.
Alright, nice.
I think we're doing really well.
That is not fair!
That is not a bot!
A bot would not have a Twitch name!
Did you not see that?
I saw the Twitch name!
A bot would not have a DDP name!
The real DDP...
Oh my god!
Was that a fucking noob?
Come on.
That's fucking right.
You think you can...
Oh, wait.
Nevermind.
You can.
Okay, friendship bond?
Oh, friendship bond, please.
Please.
Oh god.
I need help!
Let me live!
Snap!
Alright, good.
We're fine.
Snap.
Oh, I snapped the wrong person.
I'm sorry.
You're gonna die now.
I snapped the wrong person.
I'm sorry.
You were so far.
Nice, we got an assist.
Dude, they're all air!
They know like...
Fucking bots can't...
Sorry, my teammates can't shoot air characters.
Nice.
We're good.
We did it!
Don't know bots have CTV.
But the test made the bots the CTV name.
Yeah!
I'm MVP!
Nice.
What is it?
Oh, okay.
It's cause I healed.
Oh, yeah.
Wait, how am I MVP?
Wait, what?
That's right.
Endorse me.
Come on.
Come on, everybody.
I am literally the healer.
You have to endorse me.
That's the rules.
Guys, what?
This is not a team game.
This is...
My teammates aren't team players.
Wait, I don't even have the most damage.
How do you have 626 damage?
You literally only have 1000 more heals than me.
Wait, how did I get MVP?
How did I get MVP?
He has more damage than me.
Oh, the second highest kills?
Oh!
Oh, it's cause I have 6N kills.
No!
No, cause Justin has 21.
Praise me.
Exactly.
Look, see?
CTV.
I knew they were real.
Oh, I can see their highlights.
What's my highlight?
What did I do?
Oh.
Oh, it could be my KDA too.
I had a really good KDA.
I think Adam's pretty fun to play.
Alright.
Can I play DPS?
No.
Please?
Uh, requesting back Nito's Scarlet.
No, fuck off.
I'm gonna play Lowkey.
I feel like Adam's a more fun version of Lowkey, not gonna lie.
Uh...
Alright.
We'll do Lowkey.
I didn't get a chance to actually play Lowkey.
I need to remember how to play him.
But Lowkey bird.
Alright, let me...
I need to remember how to play Lowkey though.
It's been a while.
Okay, shift shift into target enemy and use...
Okay, that was the...
Okay, magic field that can bring damage.
Oh, this is the damage.
Okay, shift this to damage.
Double Ganyan.
Swap.
Back stab.
Uh, and conjure an illusion.
Okay, I need to remember all...
I forgot that Lowkey was...
I forgot that was why Lowkey was four stars.
Holy shit!
That is a lot.
Oh!
Oh, like...
There we go.
Okay.
I forgot how complicated Lowkey was.
Hahaha!
That was a lot of information!
Not gonna lie.
Oh, god.
There we go.
We're fine.
We're in our little...
orb.
We're fine.
Get the venom.
Guys, we gotta get venom!
Jesus Christ.
Somebody help!
Jesus Christ!
Magneto, you're taking so much damage!
Um, guys, you're all taking a lot of damage.
Guys.
Guys, you're taking a lot of damage, everybody!
Wee-woo!
Hahaha!
Did they nerf Lowkey?
She does not do a lot of heals.
Or they're taking a lot of damage!
It's one or the other.
I can't tell.
Hahaha!
Everybody is taking so much damage.
Jesus Christ!
I am healing so much, too!
I'm actually healing a lot.
Okay, no.
Is that new?
Is that a new orb?
Wait, is that...
What?
Is that a new orb?
That wasn't his orb before.
I swear to God!
That was not his orb before.
Like, I remember his orb was not like that.
Yeah.
That has to be new.
I do not remember his orb being like that.
That's why I was not... I didn't care.
Hahaha!
That's why I was like, ee-ee!
Because I did not remember his shit.
Okay.
What happened to the spider?
Why did he stop?
Oh!
There you go.
He's won!
Guys, our team!
Our team is struggling!
I'm gonna be Venom, too!
I don't know what his moves are, but I'm gonna fuck you up!
Wait, where did he go?
Oh my God, these guys are good.
These guys are good.
Because, like, what the fuck is going on?
What?
What is going on?
Okay.
I think they nerfed Loki.
I think they nerfed him.
I swear to God.
His heals are so weak.
This game... This game in sort is inspired by Overwatch, I'm pretty sure.
I swear.
Like, his heals...
I think it's because, like, the reason why I think that he nerfed him is that his heals is so low.
I don't like how low his heals are.
Like, the damage, too.
He used to...
Loki used to be so strong, but, like... But his damage is so weak.
Oh, God.
No!
Had you...
That shit is so broken!
That shit was actually so broken.
Oh, my God.
Friendship.
Like, even the damage...
Like, the damage is fucking stronger, too.
Like, I feel like I'm actually killing people more easily.
So bad!
I think it's because Adam is new.
So...
Since Adam is new, they gave him more... They buffed his damage for sure.
Like, I can feel the buff.
That's fucking right.
You can't run from me.
Like, it feels easier.
There you go.
Riz.
Oh, I am sorry.
Whoops.
I had to do that.
Alright, nice.
Oh, it's 99 now.
So bad!
Friendship!
Keep giving us friendship!
Oh, shit!
Okay, we're fine.
We're fine.
I just need a snap.
Yeah, Adam hasn't been rebalanced.
Yeah.
Loki has definitely got nerfed hard.
Like, the heals...
The heals on him is like a lot worse.
Um, the heals on him is definitely like less than what he was on Alpha.
And his damage for Loki is not as strong as Adam.
I felt like I...
I tickled people.
I was like tickling.
Even with like three Lokis.
I wasn't doing shit.
...
Yeah, but Adam is fucking strong as hell though.
Uh, illusion focused and heal damage.
They retooled him?!
Like, oh, so he's more like a spy then.
So, like, Loki is a spy.
Instead of like a healer.
Uh...
I hope like... I hope, uh...
I think most likely we'll retool Adam.
He's way too strong.
I can literally like, uh...
survive for so long because of it.
I think the support isn't supposed to be DPS.
But I wasn't even healing as much!
Snapping was doing more heals than shooting my friends!
I was doing more heals by snapping!
That's right.
That's fucking right.
So fun!
Friendship!
Guys, guys, no!
It's okay.
Guys, Finnum tried to destroy friendship but I'm still alive!
Okay, the fucking double...
The fucking res back is so fucked up.
Oh god.
He's coming for me, guys.
He's coming for me.
He knows.
No!
He knows!
He wants to ruin friendship!
Oh my god!
I thought...
Yeah, that guy's a really good Venom player.
Holy shit.
That guy was like Venoming all over the place.
Friendship is dead.
Don't worry!
Friendship is coming!
Yay!
Everything is good.
Okay, that's Spider-Man is dog shit.
That's so bad.
Alright, snap.
I'm just gonna chill here.
Oh, he's low.
He's low.
What is he doing?
You guys hear that?
Friendship.
Oh, there he is!
That's fucking right.
You can't destroy friendship, Finnum!
You can't destroy him!
Where did he go?
Oh, there he is.
Oh!
I can't believe that that was not my Finnum!
That was not my K-Pop star!
Where is...
Yeah!
That was so ballsy of me to do.
Wait, I still died?
Where is my Rez?
I didn't get the Rez?
I thought I would get the Cuckoo Hood.
Nice.
At least my teammates get the Rez.
I thought that was my K-Pop star.
No one expected the Luna Snow.
Yay!
We did it!
Oh my god.
Did we win?
That's two points!
Suddenly K-Pop idol.
Oh, it's on cooldown!
I thought like every time you die, you get it.
Yeah, it's like, it's a cooldown.
Okay, I get it now.
Oh my god, that Venom.
That Venom did not like...
He was like, fuck this one person in particular.
The Venom was good though.
I don't know, I endorsed myself.
Uh... Their Venom was really good.
It was like, only cause... Yeah, that's right.
Endorsed me.
I healed you guys.
I gave you guys friendship.
He kept fucking diving me.
That was crazy.
I just kept snapping.
He was a friendship hater.
Yeah.
He...
He really did.
That was so fucked up.
That was so fucked.
I was like, bro, wait a minute.
I'm just...
I'm just trying to give friendship to the people.
Um, I wanna play DPS.
I don't know, I don't like playing tank.
I think tank is really boring for me.
Um...
I wanna play...
I wanna play Tracer.
Alright.
What's Tracer like?
Uh...
In the age in a free fight and walk onto enemies in sight, loosen sword forward, fire a frenzy of shots causing damage to enemies within.
I didn't get a chance to finish reading.
Is this a spider again?
Alright, let's see.
We have a tank.
3 DPS.
We're... I think we're gonna do good.
Alright.
Dodge in direction in the movement and swiftly reload.
Fire a frenzy...
frenzy of shots causing damage to enemies within range.
Okay.
So it's like...
Okay, that's that.
And then...
Alright, that's reload.
Okay, I got it.
Nice.
Oh, charge is really nice.
Actually.
Wait, where did it show up?
Ah!
Yeah, he's like reaper... Wait, he got rid of the dash.
Didn't he have more of a dash?
I swear.
He had more.
Whoa!
What the fuck, Spider-Man?
What the fuck?
No, he had... he had like...
Um... he had a... more of a bigger dash.
I remembered.
Did he?
Yeah, didn't he have a bigger dash?
The Venom team up, yeah.
I'm pretty sure.
I'm pretty sure he had like a bigger dash before.
Uh... now like...
He doesn't have it anymore.
This is fucked up.
This is fucked up!
I don't like... I don't like him.
I don't like him.
Guys.
I don't like Star-Lord.
Alright, let's see.
Oh!
We have three deep... We do not even have... Okay, we have...
Alright, let's see.
Let's try...
No, I didn't get a chance to figure out what I wanna play!
I was trying to figure out!
At least because I don't know how to play him.
I don't know how to play this guy.
Because of the range.
The cooldown is insane though.
You can get the cooldown really fast.
...
Bye!
Wait.
...
Alright,
let's play.
Let's try.
Let's do Soldier.
I don't know.
I thought I...
Alright, what's that?
Oh, it's a zip.
And then...
That's the smoke.
Okay.
And then I have turret for him.
Alright.
I am Soldier now.
Phew!
That's fucking right.
What are you gonna do?
Get in here!
Get over here, Spider-Man!
Wait.
Get over here!
It was worth it.
It was fucking...
Whoa!
Oh!
Get him away!
Okay.
Weeew!
I'm on hard ground now.
That's fucking right.
This is revenge.
No!
That's so fucked!
He destroyed my platform!
Now I don't have high ground anymore!
That's so...
That's so fucked!
He got rid of my high ground!
He got rid...
That's so fucked.
Imagine getting rid of my high ground.
Let's see.
We're fine.
Oh!
Right click is a...
shotgun.
Okay.
Alright.
Where is he going?
Where's Spider-Man?
You can't fucking swing forever, Spider-Man!
I can track!
Spider-Man, I see you!
You can't stay up there forever!
Oh, he can.
Guys, he can.
I learned that he actually can.
I have the low ground now.
Oh, God.
That's fucking right!
Pew!
Oh, no.
Yeah, don't mess with me!
No, wait!
Stop!
It actually stopped.
Okay.
It's alright.
There's too many high ground players!
I had to play Soldier to get them down!
I had to...
I keep forgetting about Turret.
Why does Spider-Man always...
Because he's always in the sky!
Okay, I need to...
I need to grab the zip.
Okay.
It's okay.
I have high ground again.
We're fine.
Oh, Turret!
Turret!
No, I can't!
I can't put a turret here?
That's fucked!
That is so fucked!
Come on!
No!
That's so...
Why?
Wait!
That's so...
When will I ever get high ground?
I'm so sad.
Because they keep getting rid of my high ground.
No!
He's won!
He's actually won!
That's not fair!
Why do they all hate me?
I can't believe it.
They keep...
They keep taking away my high ground.
That's not fair!
I just won high ground!
Bro, don't you get healed so...
What the fuck?
I just got set up!
This is fucked, guys.
That is fucked.
I can't do anything.
I'm getting cyber bullied.
I'm getting cyber bullied by Scarlet Witch.
Bro, get the fuck...
Get Venom out of here.
I'm fucking... This is my fort.
Scarlet Witch, I fucking got you, Scarlet Witch.
That's fucking right.
You're not...
You're not doing shit to me this time.
That's fucking right!
Fuck you, Scarlet Witch!
Oh no!
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
Please!
Get away from me!
I can't!
Oh my god!
I'm sorry!
Get away!
She won't leave me alone!
I don't know what to do!
Oh god.
Oh my god.
I need heals, I think.
Oh, there you go.
Okay.
Nice.
Okay, that was worth the risk.
I knocked two.
That was worth it.
Okay, this guy is so good.
Like...
This guy is actually crazy insane.
Oh god!
Guys!
We have the VF point, guys!
Oh god!
Guys, we can't get off this point!
This is fucked up, cause they have...
Cause they have...
Oh god.
Get him up.
No, no, knockback Nino!
Knockback Nino!
No!
Oh boy.
Yes!
No!
I did it!
I right clicked!
I did have the cooldown!
Oh, you have to swap?
Oh, you can swap weapons?
I didn't realize you can swap weapons.
I was like, what are you guys talking about?
I'm doing it!
I just got the smoke!
Okay, we're gonna do that.
We're gonna try Soldier again.
Now I know we can swap weapons.
Now I know...
We're gonna play Soldier again.
Bro, I was getting cyberbullied by the Scarlet Witch!
Bitch!
Oh my god.
Just some guy taking a little bit of the soup.
Thank you.
Keep an eye on him.
If I get the cooldown Punisher as a main, there's probably gonna be an update where they give Frank his space guns, bike chain, and flaming skull head.
Bro!
Fuck that.
Fuck that Scarlet Witch though.
Just fucking Scarlet Witch.
Holy shit.
I got bullied so hard.
Okay.
Oh my god, there he is.
Guys.
Guys, there it is.
Oh my god.
He has two weapons?
He didn't have two weapons before, right?
Oh, it's a black...
Yeah, that Venom was...
No, not that Venom.
That Scarlet Witch!
That's good.
Thank you, Super Chat.
Thank you.
That Scarlet Witch fucked me up!
What he did?
I just never used it.
Wait, where's the entrance?
Here, okay.
Guys, I just never used it.
I didn't realize that was a thing, guys.
I'm gonna get in.
That's fucking right.
Get in.
Come on!
Come on, you know you wanna get in!
I have the high ground!
Oh, there's Scarlet...
Oh my god, it's the same Scarlet Witch too!
It's the same one.
It's the same one, guys.
I'm scared.
It's her!
Oh no!
No, I need to get off the thing.
Guys, it's her.
It's her, guys.
Get the Bruce Banner!
Get the D.Va Bruce Banner!
Oh no.
Wait, do we have a Scarlet Witch?
We don't.
Okay, I'm gonna be Scarlet Witch if I die to her.
I'll prove to her that I'm the better Scarlet Witch.
I still love that Bruce Banner is the D.Va of Marvel Rivals.
I think that's so funny.
I think that's really cute.
Where's that coming from?
I hear shots.
Oh no!
Oh no, she's coming over.
She's coming over.
She's so low.
She can fly twice?!
Oh no!
This bitch.
I'm not letting you go.
I know!
She's coming over.
No!
I got baited!
The cooldown is so fast!
She nearly was a thing and then she was a thing again!
Why is her cooldown insane?
How was I supposed to know?
I didn't play Scarlet Witch yet!
Oh no.
Oh no, she has a shield?
Okay.
Oh no, I'm trying to find people.
That's fucking...
Oh no, she's hulking up.
She's hulking up.
No!
It's time.
I shall become the Scarlet Witch.
I don't know how to play her.
But I shall become the Scarlet Witch.
Let it hit on a target or press the generate force field that stuns the enemy.
Hold space, consume chaos to fire explosive.
Okay.
Stuns and then...
Alright.
It's time.
It's fucking time.
Okay, and then that's that.
And then that's what she did to me.
Wait.
Oh, she has two charges!
Oh!
Okay, that makes sense now.
Now that I'm actually that character.
It makes sense.
It's okay.
Oh no.
I can't.
Everybody is so far away!
It's fine.
It's not fine.
That's fucking right.
That's not fucking right!
It's hella time.
Never mind.
Hella is stronger.
Hella is more fun.
Hella I feel like I'm actually strong.
Wait, I hear a scarlet witch near us.
I hear a scarlet witch right next to us.
Oh no, she's like right there.
Oh.
Guys.
Guys!
Guys, where's our healer?
Guys, I need you guys to heal me.
Please.
Please snap me just once.
Guys, I need some snaps right now.
I need snaps!
Why do they all fly?
Please!
Snap!
I really need snaps.
I don't know why they don't snap.
Okay.
Oh god.
Where's the crow?
Hella leave!
Hella move!
Get closer!
Oh, that's embarrassing.
Guys, I...
Sorry, I wanted to live.
I wanted to live.
Oh no.
Big Hulk.
I'm sorry, I just wanted to live.
Get baby D.va!
Look, I really wanted to live.
Okay, guys?
Like, it was very important to me.
It was...
Somebody get the Scarlet!
She's literally one!
I'll get her myself.
Guys, it wasn't that big of a waste.
Right, guys?
Wooo!
Crow.
Adam!
Get out of there, Adam!
Oh, god.
Guys.
We are not doing so well right now.
Oh, snap.
I need snaps.
Wooo!
Guys.
Somebody healed me!
I'm one!
Guys!
Oh, he's gonna catch me!
Yes!
Oh, thank god!
I got friendship!
Friendship saved me!
Oh, come on!
I have to reload!
Wait.
I hear somebody.
Oh, there she is!
I f***ing knew it.
That's right.
You can't f***ing...
You can't hide from me.
That's right!
Get sh** on!
Alright.
We're okay.
Everything is fine.
Oh, there she is.
No, I need to kill that Cosme.
Judge!
Jury!
Executioner!
I'm fine.
I'll be okay.
Oh!
She got me on high ground.
Leave me alone!
Oh no.
Oh, god.
I'm reloading.
This is...
This is a little scary right now.
I can't... There's so many things on my screen!
There's so many things on my screen!
Nice.
Oh, sh**!
Turret mode!
Crow!
Oh, sh**!
Turret mode!
Crow!
Bitch!
Get f**king crowed!
Oh!
Nice.
I made violence over.
Oh!
Crow!
Where's my crow?
She's getting...
Oh, god.
Oh, thank god.
It's okay.
Hello, Moe time!
That's f**king right.
That's right.
You're gonna go inside!
That's cheating.
That's actually cheating.
He went inside.
How the f**k do I...
...endorse?
I can't believe it.
No more group for him.
He went inside!
That's so cheating!
That should be illegal!
Guys, I need heals.
Guys, please.
Please.
I need heals.
Do we have zero...
I think we have...
Do we have zero healers?
Like, what's going on?
Oh, there you go, Adam!
Friendship!
Friendship came back to save me.
Here we go.
I need to remember to use E.
I keep forgetting about the existence of...
Oh!
He's one!
No!
He used the f**king tank sh**!
Don't teleport Adam!
He's wearing my only heals!
You can't kill him!
I need the heals!
Guys, I don't know how to...
Adam!
Nice.
We're fine.
Okay.
I know my place.
I'm very good at Hella.
I know.
Oh god.
Crow!
There you go.
We're okay.
Don't worry!
Don't worry Adam!
I got you!
Executioner!
We're okay.
Penny...
Rise, my friend!
Oh, I'm not hitting anything.
Penny's dead.
And we have rez, so we're okay.
We die.
We're okay.
I'm just a Hella main now.
She's just so good.
Oh!
No!
Oh my god!
The moment I swapped to Hella!
Look at that!
I'm f**king shutting people down!
Oh no, it's overtime.
Oh no, not the whale!
Not the whale!
No!
I f**king looked at the wrong way!
I went... I went backwards.
Whoops.
Hella boi!
Oh, I didn't throw.
Okay, I thought I was throwing again.
I thought I was throwing again with that.
Okay, I got one.
No!
No, I'm sky... I'm in!
We're so...
Is everybody dead?
No!
No, everybody's dead!
I did so much!
Team, please!
Team!
No!
I die and we lose!
I can't believe it!
I got whaled and then we lose!
It's so...
And then I lost MVP!
Oh my god!
I lost MVP for that!
I'm getting my summoner.
I did so much!
I actually...
We...
Team was too heavy!
Oh my god!
I'm sad.
We...
We did so much!
You'll need a top notch team to win this one.
I can't believe it.
I can't fucking believe it.
I'm gonna...
Alright, this is gonna be a chill game.
I'm gonna show you guys...
I'm gonna show you guys the key pop star.
The Scarlet Adventure Delayed the Hella Switch.
I'll show you guys what I mean when I said Hella.
When I said Luna was basically Juno.
You have only one healer?
Alright.
It's time to dance.
It's time to clap everybody.
She's like an ice...
An ice wizard who sings too.
I need to look at her stuff again.
It's been a while.
Her ult is basically dance to heal.
And then damaging enemies or healing while storing her own health.
Okay, fire is attached.
Allies will also restore health while Luna's snow is healing others.
Cast the clump of ice to freeze.
Okay, that freezes people.
Okay.
Watch this.
So she does this.
This is literally Juno's run.
This is literally how Juno runs.
I don't know.
This is my first time saying it.
Okay.
We'll give her that.
It's okay.
We have a tank?
Okay, we're gonna give that to our tank then.
Alright.
It's alright!
I'm healing!
Because we only have one healer!
Pansy!
Alright.
We're fine.
I don't even know if I hit her.
Oh yeah.
That should be going towards our fucking...
Oh god.
Let's see.
I need the tank to have it.
Because it makes sense.
This basically gives her passive.
Ooh!
That freeze though!
Don't worry!
I got you!
Oh my god!
Where the fuck?
Where did Spider-Man go?
He died so fast!
I gotta make sure I don't die.
Because I'm literally the only healer.
That's fucking right!
Don't attack my fucking team again!
Since we only have one tank, I have to put a Zenado.
I have to put an Aura Ball on our guy.
Okay.
I need to remember...
What was shift again?
Oh!
Oh yeah!
This is the clap to heal!
Clap to heal!
Clap!
That one was clap to heal.
No, I wanted to give the thing to our Magneto.
Where's Magneto?
There you are.
Taco!
Alright.
Ooh!
Alright, it's almost time to dance, guys.
It's almost time to dance.
I'm ready to dance!
Holy shit!
I filled my ult so fucking fast, though.
I just realized.
I literally took like, less than 30 seconds, I think.
Sam!
Clap!
Clap, clap, clap, clap!
Clap, clap, clap, clap, clap!
Clap!
So dumb!
So dumb.
Our tank isn't even like up there.
Our tank isn't up there.
Get healed!
There's like no point in me ulting.
Alright, I guess we're gonna chill here for a little bit because I don't think...
Don't make me clap!
Clap!
That's fucking right.
That's right!
It's dancing time!
Get healed everybody!
Get healed!
Okay,
you can heal from that.
You can heal from my fucking nuke.
That's good to know, chat.
That's good to know that...
That you can survive.
Dancing does not save you from...
From a nuclear bomb.
You know, I needed to learn that now.
I needed to learn that.
Fuck off!
Clap.
How can dancing not protect you from nukes?
I know, right?
How was I supposed to know?
I thought dancing was gonna save us!
With the power of dance!
I can't believe it!
Oh no.
Why does nobody shoot at the top?
Wait, that's it?
Nobody shot me when I was up there.
I just noticed that.
That's all it took?
Nobody shot me!
Oh no it's time to dance.
Dance!
Oh that was fast... gamers don't look up!
That's true.
That's so true.
Nice.
But yeah, that's the...
That was the K-Pop Healer.
Uh... what the...
That was basically the K-Pop Healer.
How much healing did I do?
That's why you guys would not have done any...
would not have been able to survive without me.
Just remember that.
Seven... zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, seven thousand.
Yeah, that makes sense.
That...
Their other support had a thousand heals.
Oh my god.
The Rocket Raccoon had a thousand heals.
That's embarrassing, Bing Bong.
I got seven thousand.
Alright, but I think...
Yeah, that's right.
Upload me.
I think Luna Snow is done.
She's definitely the easiest healer.
Um... the easiest healer in the party ain't no more.
Alright.
I don't wanna play...
Okay, I'll try... I don't know.
I feel like...
Venom is also seems like really difficult too.
I could try Venom.
I could try it.
He has like...
He seems all over the place when I was watching people play it.
Venom's swing.
People who are good at Venom were like crazy.
They were like everywhere.
Generate a bonus health.
Okay, that's the bonus health.
Dash to target... Oh no, I didn't finish reading!
No, Venom's a tank.
Um... he's a tank.
Oh shit!
We have team up activated!
Alright.
Let's see.
Dash to target location from a certain height upon landing.
Damage.
Knocking them back towards the landing point.
Unleash tentacles to slow enemies within reach.
Okay.
Enemies under break free time will suffer your damage.
God, that is so complicated.
Uh... shift.
Dash to target location from a certain height upon landing.
Oh my god!
Okay, I'm gonna try.
I'm gonna try my best.
Alright.
Woo!
Oh!
Shit!
Okay!
Movement.
Okay, I did not expect to be there that fast.
Fucking movement right there.
Holy shit.
Oh my god, I need to be like closer.
No!
I mean, look at my health.
Oh!
Goodbye!
Woo!
Nice.
Oh shit, guys!
I forgot my thing loses HP!
Guys!
Come to heal me!
That's fucking right.
What the fuck you just read?
You think you can run from me?
Guys, I'm not very good at tank, guys.
I don't think I'm a fan.
Get over here!
Oh!
Oh god.
Okay, guys.
I'm not very good at tank, guys.
I'm...
That's fucking right!
That's right!
Get over here!
I'll fucking brawl with you!
Oh!
Don't brawl!
I'm stuck!
Guys!
Use my heals!
You take request assistance!
Clap!
Right now!
Keep clapping!
It's very important you keep clapping!
Okay.
I fucked up.
That was not what I wanted to do, but that's okay.
Oh god.
I need to run.
Where's my claps?
Oh shit!
I gotta go over there!
Gotta go over there!
Get the heals!
Okay.
Nice.
That's good.
I got the claps.
Oh!
What is going on?
What the fuck is going on?
I'm trying to survive!
Please!
Where's...
Where's claps?
No!
Oh my...
How the fuck do you play Venom?
I...
I don't know!
How to play Venom!
It's so fucking difficult!
Jesus Christ!
Okay.
Alright.
We're okay.
Do we have two healers?
We have one healer.
Okay.
That makes more sense guys.
We literally have one support.
Anyway.
Oh my god.
Guys, I think we need another support.
Please clap.
I'm never saying clap because...
We need another healer!
Please.
Clapping is not enough.
Guys, we need more.
Oh, we did it!
Oh, it's because the...
The Luna...
The other healer...
The Luna Snow...
She claps to heal.
She...
Her ability...
One of her abilities is that whenever she claps, she heals you.
Alright.
We're fine.
With the amount of shipping and clapping that's going on, Marble Rivals will have a population boomerang.
A couple of years.
You know what's going to make Marble Rivals blow up?
If those 3D models become public.
All you need to do is...
Guys...
Honestly...
True.
That's the only way Marble Rivals will survive.
Will become popular.
Let me help you.
What the fuck?
Come around.
Oh, god.
That's fucking right.
Clap!
I'm fucking gonna kill you, you little raccoon!
Get over here!
You think you can run from me?
Holy sh...
What the...
Fuck?
What is going on?
Guys, I think everybody is dead.
Every time I'm not DPSed, guys...
I think...
Every time I'm not...
You wanna fucking do this?
You wanna do this?
That's fucking right.
Every time I'm not DPSed...
I think I was...
Carrying, guys.
Yeah!
Devour!
Oh my god!
Somebody clap for me right now!
I'm on it!
Oh god, please!
Oh, please!
Please, there's so many things on me!
Oh!
I killed somebody!
I'm not...
I was confused.
Who did I kill?
Oh, I crushed her!
I crushed her!
Okay.
I fucking crushed the shit out of that one...
I don't know how!
I...
Okay, to be fair, I did kill her...
Before... Okay, guys.
I did kill her, guys.
Oh my god!
Alright!
I'm out.
Oh, I'm not out.
I'm not out.
I don't know how fucking disoriented I'm playing Venom!
He's so dis...
He's so fucking...
Alright.
Alright, there you go.
It's okay.
I'm getting...
I'm slowly learning.
I got somebody down with me!
Okay, guys?
That's like a win on my book.
Here we go.
Oh, no!
Wait.
Where are they?
Where... Where are the people?
There you go.
I... I...
I don't know.
They're all just...
They're everywhere!
Why are they everywhere?!
Get over here!
Get... Oh, shit!
I'm fucking...
Goodbye.
They're like, literally everywhere.
I don't know what to do sometimes.
Woo!
Alright.
Whoops.
Where are they?
Oh, shit.
There you are.
Where is that?
Get over here!
Where are you?
No!
You don't shoot them!
I'll beat the shit out of you!
Get over here!
I will fucking eat your... I'll eat a tree!
Guys, I'm getting better!
Get over here!
No!
Okay.
There you are.
I did it!
I figured it out!
I figured out how to play Venom!
I did it!
I figured it out!
I ate a tree, guys.
I did it!
I figured it out!
No, I just run!
This works!
What were you gonna say?
Did you see that?
I ate that whole tree!
Did you guys see that?
I fucking ate a tree!
Om nom nom nom!
Jesus Christ!
This guy is hard to play!
I fucking solo altered the tree!
I was like, fuck that tree in particular!
There is great chaos in you...
Oh my god!
Oh my... This is gonna be a bit harder.
Because it's like I'm solo tanky now.
Your veggies guys This is good for you.
Alright.
Time to go back.
Woooooo!
I'm getting a little better.
I'm figuring him out.
A little more.
Alright guys.
Woooooo!
Oh!
I fucked!
Guys!
Clap!
Keep clapping!
Or I will die!
Guys please.
Please.
Oh god.
Oh my god.
We got him.
I need heals though.
I can't take this.
Guys!
I literally can't keep taking this.
My HP is so low!
Okay.
Nice.
Alright.
I'm gonna wait a little bit.
I don't wanna go up yet.
I need heal though.
Where's... nice.
Okay.
He snaps.
That's fucking right.
Where are you?
Holy shit!
Where are they?
I'm just like...
Oh that's a lot.
Just keep snapping!
Oh!
Shit!
Okay.
Okay it's fine.
We're fine.
He snapped.
He snapped enough.
Okay.
I got...
I got Groot.
Okay.
It's time to eat somebody!
Om nom nom nom nom nom nom nom!
No!
You're out of my way.
Alright.
Nice, we're fine.
We're fine.
I couldn't eat trees this time, but...
Where did he go?
Okay, we gotta wait, we gotta wait.
Boom!
That's fucking right!
Get over here, Groot!
Get over here!
Oh, goodbye, Groot!
Goodbye!
I had enough trees!
JK!
Oh, I have enough trees!
Oh no, I got too much damage!
I thought I was getting healed!
I thought I was getting healed, guys!
But I wasn't!
Alright, we'll wait.
We're in obsession with the tree.
He fucking deserved it.
No, Star-Lord!
Are we soulbounded?
Who's my best friend?
Somebody's my best friend, but I don't know who.
Okay, we gotta wait, we gotta wait, we gotta wait, we gotta wait.
Guys, we gotta wait.
Oh, what is that?
Oh no, it's the fucking panther.
It's okay.
Where did he go?
There's too many things on the screen!
Get away!
We need the support!
Okay, are we good?
Alright.
Alright, I'm gonna go up.
It's okay.
We're fine.
I'm fucking...
I'm trying to...
Oh, shit!
Oh, god.
Please.
I need heals.
Guys, no!
Look out!
I needed heals!
My teeth...
I needed more snaps!
Holy shit, what is that man sense?
Oh, no, guys.
Regroup!
Guys!
Regroup, guys!
We have one fight!
We got it!
We got away!
Guys!
Mantis, I swear to god, don't you dare.
We have to wait.
We have to wait, guys.
Mantis, look at me!
Oh no, I pressed the wrong button.
Okay, I think I'm gonna go in.
I'm gonna go in.
Just keep me up.
Okay.
Guys, I would... guys...
As like the only tank here...
I don't...
This is just DPS dip to be honest.
I don't think it was a me issue.
I... I did my job.
I... I...
I literally did my job.
I ate trees.
Come on, what do you want me to do?
I blocked 22,000 damage.
I... I blocked a lot.
I did what I was supposed to do as a tank.
Like...
...
Venom is gonna turn so many people into tank players.
The thing is, the only issue with Venom is that it's so hard to like...
It's so hard to play him when you don't have heals.
...
Because he's bouncing around.
I feel like you need to know where the health packs are.
When you play Venom.
Alright.
Uhhh...
You know what?
Let's try Iron Man.
I wanna try Iron Man.
What's his abilities?
Okay, activate hyper velocity state.
Activate armor overdrive enhancing damage when...
Hyper velocity or armor overdrive is... Wait, what?
What was the last statement?
Alright.
Uhhh...
...
When hyper velocity armor is used, Iron Man can launch a bombardment.
Okay.
I'm gonna use...
When I fly, I can launch missiles.
Okay.
And then...
Okay, so...
If I have...
Do I damage a repulsor blast or a uni beam?
Oh, okay.
That makes the...
my attacks stronger.
And then... Okay!
Okay, I'm gonna try and remember that.
So...
So this would...
...
Whoa!
I'm still flying!
I...
Okay.
Alright.
This is... That's right.
Yeah, that's right.
That's fucking right.
Get over here.
This will...
Oh my god.
What the fuck?!
What is he do?
What?
He fucking deactivated me!
He uses radiation!
That's fucked up!
He literally uses radiation for that!
Okay, Iron Man sucks.
I hate Iron Man.
What's my ult trying?
I'm gonna try and get the... I'm gonna try and get an ult.
Literally the only fun thing is this ult.
I don't like... like... I don't like the...
Wait, how do I... Oh, I have to hold it.
Oh, this is the tracker.
Okay, never mind.
He's pretty fun now.
Never mind.
I like it.
Oh, fuck.
Yo, fuck.
Never mind.
This is easy.
As long as I just have the track, I'm fine.
No.
You think you can get away?
That's fucking right.
Oh, fuck.
I can track.
That's fucking...
That's not fair!
He's just fucking...
Oh, what the fuck?
Oh, shit.
What?
Never mind.
The moment I found out I can track, it's over.
It's fucking over.
I figured it out.
It's a Zarya tracking.
I can track.
Alright, I'm gonna waste my ult.
JK, I wanna fucking kill this guy though.
That's right.
Don't get healed.
You know what?
Should I...
I was gonna say...
What the fuck?
Alright, I need like a...
Okay.
Maximum pulse!
Yeah!
Shit!
Holy shit!
That shit is so fucking broken.
That was worth it.
We lost, but like...
That was worth it though.
I figured out how to ult.
Alright, let's see.
We have two supports.
Alright, it's time.
It's time to win this for the team.
It's...
Totally worth it.
Alright, it's time for my team to win.
I lost, but I got a taste of power.
That shit is crazy.
I don't remember what his ult was.
His ult was like a beam or something.
I remembered.
I'm pretty sure.
Alright, I think we unlocked rank apparently.
So after this, we'll go into rank.
Time for my meta pick.
I remember his ult was not like that.
Yeah.
Well, his right click is good.
I think his right click is really good.
If you can aim.
It was the uni beam.
The uni beam is fun.
I didn't like his... I don't like his left click.
But his uni beam is really good.
Alright, let's see.
Now it's time to carry this team.
Oh, hope I can find people.
Okay.
How?
Guys!
I have not played a...
Okay.
Now...
I don't know what happened to me guys.
Guys, I don't...
I don't know what happened to me.
What happened to me?
Oh my god.
I went highest to be queen of the world.
I...
I don't know what happened.
It just...
I just couldn't aim anymore.
I don't...
I don't know what happened.
It just...
It just stopped working.
What's that?
I don't remember what that sound was.
Maybe they hot fixed it guys.
I know what they did.
They like hot fixed it so like...
Wait, no I'm lagging.
Wait, am I lagging or are they lagging?
Guys, guys, I think...
Guys, it's because I'm lagging guys.
It's not...
Guys, I think I'm actually lagging.
Oh my god, actual lag!
Hahahaha!
Wait!
Actually...
No!
Oh my god, thank god it was actually lagged.
Oh my god, thank god it's actually lagged.
Hahaha.
Oh my god, thank god.
I knew it.
I knew I was... my aim was still good.
I fucking knew it.
I'm just lagging guys.
We figured it out.
SEE?
I know my aim.
What is that?
OH FUCK!
I thought I had a healer next to me!
I'm happy for lag.
The only reason I'm happy for lag is because my aim is still there.
Oh my god, thank god.
It's not me.
Also, I have really dog shit healers.
This is the only reason why I like playing support.
It's because like, when your healers are dog shit and you have to like...
SEE?
Look, nobody looks up!
Oh, there he is!
Is he look- there he- there he goes!
There he goes!
Nobody looks up!
Alright, this is literally the only reason why I play support.
Because like, it's so tilting having bad support players that you have to support yourself.
Alright, let us... That guy was a really good hulk though.
LordVenn was actually really good as hulk.
Alright, let's go play rank.
How do I- Alright.
Wait, no it's not.
I unlocked it!
Know I don't want to fill it.
Woah!
I got so many stuff- wait!
I got lied to!
It opens on the 24th!
It opens tomorrow!
You guys lied to me!
Alright, maybe this time, guys, maybe this time we can do a conquest.
Yeah.
You were like, oh you can unlock rank now and I was like yay!
I got baited so hard.
Like, oh now you can play Ranked.
I'm like, really?
Alright, now that I've learned how to play this game...
Ranked is... Conquest is nothing now.
Conquest will be so easy.
We got this guys, we got this.
Alright, here we go.
Is no one playing Conquest?
Okay, nobody's playing Conquest.
Maybe Conquest is a bad game.
Okay, nevermind.
Haha, it's a bad game!
Guys, I think Conquest might be a bad game mode and nobody's on it.
Nobody's... Okay, I found a match already.
Alright.
Nice.
Yeah.
How is Conquest and... Oh my god, it's the Spider-Man, guys.
Holy shit.
I'm now...
I'm now an...
I'm now an Adam main.
Friendship ended with Loki.
Adam is now my new best friend.
It's him!
It's the real Spider-Man!
It's not my fault they fucking butchered the shit out of Loki.
He's literally dog shit now.
Loki is so... The heals for Loki is just so bad.
Like...
He's so...
Until Adam gets nerfed.
Yeah, until Adam gets nerfed.
He's my new best friend.
I like it when I snap the heal.
Loki is... No, Loki's not even that.
Where is he going?
What?
I like got confused.
Nobody knows how to walk there.
Nobody's following me.
Nobody knows.
Guys, it's not... Guys, it's not that way.
Haha!
Everybody's confused!
You can see everybody doesn't know how to get there.
We were all like, where do we go?
Snap.
So bonded!
Okay.
Snap.
I love snapping to heal.
It's so fun.
Oh my god.
Snap!
I can't snap anymore!
I'm sorry!
Somebody help me!
I couldn't!
Scarlet, you just...
What are you doing, Scarlet?
Guys, I don't think Scarlet's a good player.
She literally was just watching us get shot at.
That's so fucked up!
Snap.
Oh god.
People are learning how to play this game now.
Guys!
Scarlet!
I don't live my dream!
Guys, I need more heals.
This team.
I have a DC?!
How?!
How do I have a DC?!
This is a quick play!
Oh god!
You DC!
Where's the fill?!
Oh, there's the fill.
Guys, it's time to clap.
Oh god.
God.
I'm trying my best right now.
Get away from me!
Get away!
Oh god.
We have tanks.
Holy shit.
Thank god.
You have to play Luna Snow for consistent heals.
I'm pretty sure.
Get away!
I have to play him.
I have to play her so that I can keep the team up.
Get away!
Freeze!
Oh!
Guys!
Clap!
God,
Spiderman's the flank killer.
It's so scary.
Clap.
I'm trying my best to clap.
I'm clapping so hard.
Behold!
Dark Child!
Don't worry!
We're dancing!
We dance!
We keep dancing!
I can't dance forever!
Magneto!
Please!
Guys!
Stop!
I can't!
Guys, please!
Stop!
I'm just getting fucked over by the spiders!
I think this is GG's.
My team is bad.
I have a feeling my team is bad, guys.
Why is she just standing there?
Why?
Please!
Are you lagging?
Why are you just standing there?
Why are you on the DPS line?
And we are just getting...
Oh my god!
Holy shit!
Somebody get her off!
Oh god!
Thank god!
Oh thank god!
Please!
Get him away from me!
Oh my god!
Scarlet, please!
Wake up!
Scarlet!
Wake the fuck up!
Get away!
I will clap!
And I won't regret it!
Okay.
This...
This is so difficult.
Please!
This team...
This fucking team...
Please!
I like the coins.
This fucking team!
I will dance if I have to!
Please, live!
Oh, I missed...
I missed the thing.
Okay.
He's low though.
He's low.
I'll clap!
Clap!
Oh god, where did he go?
Where did he go?
Get over here!
Yeah!
Guys!
Please!
Get over here!
Goodbye!
He's won!
He's literally won!
I can't dance!
I'm dancing the best I could right now!
I'm...
I'm trying so hard to dance!
Wait, Spider-Man isn't on Spider-Man!
What a scam!
Spider-Man's on fucking Storm!
I'm gonna clap for life!
Oh no!
He's gonna hit me again!
Oh no, I missed!
Oh, thank god!
Where's Venom?
Oh god!
Oh god, no!
Skylar Witch!
Please, team!
What are you...
What the fuck?
Please, I lived for so long!
Team, please!
Do not...
I will dance!
I will fucking dance if it's the last thing I do!
I will keep on dancing!
Eh.
You're fine, you're fine, you're fine.
You're... you're... get healed, get healed.
Get healed, get healed.
Clap!
Get healed!
I will clap!
Clap!
Yay!
Now it's attack time!
Kill everybody!
Yeah!
Okay.
Oh god.
Oh!
Please.
I'm trying to be alive right now.
Okay, he's dead.
Thank god.
I had the big heal.
You can also... it's like Lucio, where you can change into damage boost too.
Or not Lucio, wait, it's like Juno!
Where you can change into damage!
Alright.
Who has my...
Okay, I'm getting rid of the Loki puppet though.
Oh god.
Oh god, clap!
Clap!
Come on, come on, Scarlet Witch, live!
Oh no!
Venom!
Oh!
That was close.
Wait!
Oh, that's you.
Wait, what the fuck?
Who killed everybody?
Who's dead?
Like, who's fucking died?
I got like assists and everything.
Oh god.
Oh, I missed!
It's okay!
Clap, clap, clap!
Guys!
Oh, it's okay!
It's still okay!
We're still okay!
We're so healthy!
Oh, we're so healthy, guys!
Guys, we're so healthy!
Oh, we're so healthy, guys.
Where's my...
Oh, don't worry!
I killed just in time!
Now fight!
Now heal!
Now me!
I think I froze it!
Wait, I froze the ult!
Wait, that's fucking... that's fucking cool.
I think I froze it.
Okay, where's the...
Please, don't die because I'm dead!
Oh, nice, nice!
Good job, Iron Man!
Track him!
Oh, it's overtime!
It's overtime!
I'm heading over to everybody's critical!
Oh, we did it!
He's getting a pocket... No!
Oh my god, it's so painful to be...
It's so painful playing the only support!
Oh my god, his team... his team...
...lid because of me!
I did 18,000 heals!
Holy shit!
Oh my god, you better fucking endorse me after all I did for you!
I...
Oh my god!
They did so much damage, though.
12k, 13k, 12k...
Like, our team had the most damage, but I had to keep all of these shitters alive!
Alright, last game.
That Scarlet Witch, though.
I wish I could... I wish there was a void system so I could avoid the Scarlet Witch right now.
Like, I... I don't... I do not want her on my team.
You'll need a top-notch team to win this one.
Alright.
Let's see...
Last game...
You know what?
I will try...
I'm going to try...
I'll try magic.
Alright, let's see magic.
Transform into a dark child, jump through a... transporting a short distance, dash forward, and launch an enemy.
Magic Slash.
Oh god, that is so fucking... what?
Okay.
And then I can charge it.
And then...
Okay.
Nice.
And then...
Okay, that's the charge.
Alright.
Alright, let's see.
Nobody seems to play her.
I know, like, during the...
Alpha launch, she was really broken during Alpha.
But like, I don't know about now.
Obviously, it could be different now.
Alpha version was broken.
That's all I remember.
Oh my god, why are they always in the fucking sky?
This is bullshit.
Okay.
Um...
How do I do this?
How do I...
Oh shit!
Wait, what a killer!
It's not fair!
She's in the sky!
This is literally not fair!
She's literally in the sky!
How can I kill something in the sky?
It's not fair.
Oh my god, that is so fucking...
How do I kill something in the sky?
I'm so mad!
Oh, I'm dead.
I'm so mad.
How do I... Oh, okay, that's the cooldown.
Alright, that's the cooldown.
You can't cook.
It's off-BOOM!
It fucking... It was in the sky!
I can't fucking do anything about it!
Okay, I need to know the cooldown for that.
Get over here.
Fucking... Get over here.
Like, what do I do?!
That's what I do.
Because that's what I do.
I thought there would be more people.
Mosquito god.
This bullshit!
Get over here!
You can't block a sword!
Wait, that's not fair!
Get over here!
You can't fucking stay here!
You can't stay up there forever!
That's not fair!
He literally stayed up there forever!
Get over here.
No.
There we go.
That's literally not fair.
Get over... Get away.
Get away!
Oh no, it's the eye.
Okay.
I don't have the...
That's fucking right!
Get over here!
Get...
You can't run away from me!
I have a sword!
Where are you?!
That's fucking right!
Yeah, that's right, Loki.
You scared.
Oh shit!
Oh shit, I'm scared.
Oh, goodbye.
Bye.
Oh shit!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry!
Oh my god, he went for me!
That's fucked up!
You fucking ran at me!
Bro, they have Spider-Man and Tony Stark?!
Alright, we're okay.
We're okay.
Okay.
Nice.
Alright.
What I can do is that.
JK, I... JK, I lied!
Get me out of here!
Bro, he's fucking a mosquito!
That's the only thing that sucks.
The mosquito shit.
Like, I don't know what to do when that happens.
Get over here.
Yeah, that's right!
You're stuck!
You're fucking stuck!
Oh, wait.
He's literally one.
Somebody just...
Just shoot him!
I can't shoot him because I have a sword!
He's gonna get this guy out of the way.
We'll get the Spider-Man.
Get him.
Get him too.
Get him too!
You can't block a sword!
Okay.
I find it really dumb that you can't block a sword, though.
I think that's stupid.
That's fucking right.
Where are you?
That's fucking right!
Yeah!
Oh, Luna!
You're scared, Luna, aren't you?
Wait, where did you... Luna?
Where did Luna go?
Is she dead?
She... What?
It's scary.
Alright.
What the fuck?
Oh.
Okay.
That's fucking right!
Get over here, Loki!
Yeah!
Oh, goodbye!
Goodbye!
Okay.
I lived longer than I thought I was going to.
Straight up locked.
Coming back, guys!
Magic's coming back!
Don't worry!
I'm coming back!
Where is he?
Where the fuck is he?
Where are you, Spider-Man?
Where the fuck are you?
Ooh, you're trying to run?
Get down!
I'm the Spider-Killer!
Get over here!
That's fucking right!
Where are you?
Hey, where are them, Lost?
Actually, where are they?
That's fucking Tony Stark!
Ooh, hey there, buddy!
Hey there!
Is there... Who's healing you?
Fucking bullshit.
Killers.
That's fucking right.
Where the fuck is Terminator?
I'm the pest control.
I squashed some bugs.
I feel like I don't die!
Like, I like... I don't know.
I think I had really good healers.
Cause like, yeah!
Holy shit!
15k healing!
Our Rocky Raccoon, like, clutched up.
He healed me!
He actually healed me so much!
Cause I was just going in and fucking...
Going in YOLO style.
I must be so tilting to heal.
I will not be surprised if I was a bitch to heal that time.
Uh...
It should not be a leaderboard.
Yet.
Oh, that was a good support player.
He like, enabled me to do whatever the fuck I want there.
Alright!
I think that's a good time to call it.
Woo!
That was really fun!
I had a great time.
Checking out the, uh...
The beta test this time.
Um... I'm looking forward to trying out the rank system to see what they change to it.
But that was really, really fun!
Um... I hope you guys enjoyed Marvel Rivals and like, the shit you can do.
It's definitely right now for me.
Marvel Rivals feels very casual.
Maybe it's because I'm not playing rank at the moment.
But, um...
It feels very casual.
Something to play to like...
Just like, like...
Uh... Just to like, fuck around with.
But it was really fun!
I definitely enjoyed it a lot.
I think it'll be definitely more fun with friends.
But like, as a solo player playing it today...
I definitely had, um...
A lot of fun playing it.
And just like, playing around with the different characters.
I did not like Tank.
Playing Tank there.
Uh...
Ha ha ha ha!
And you like...
The reason why is that Tank...
You have to rely so much on your healers.
And like...
I don't trust healers.
I don't trust like, random healers.
Ha ha ha!
Like, I don't trust randoms.
At all.
So...
Uh...
Ha ha ha!
So...
So that's why...
I don't like playing Tank.
And DPS is fine.
Because DPS are more squishy.
But like, at least they do damage.
At least they do a lot more damage to justify it.
Um...
My favorite support currently is Adam.
Adam seems really fun to play.
As a support.
Um...
They nerfed the shit out of Loki.
So like, he's not as fun anymore.
And like, his heals are actually like...
Pretty bad.
Ha ha ha!
Compared to Adam IMO.
Um...
Because like, at this point...
If you want a lot of healing...
Then you play Luna Snow.
Because her healings are insane.
Her healings are really good.
And the reason why I liked Loki...
Was because of like...
His DPS and heals.
But like, his DPS was so low!
I felt like his DPS was not as high...
As before.
So I'm pretty sure they nerfed the shit out of that.
Um...
DPS in general...
I think I like Hela the most.
Hela was the most fun for me when it came to DPS.
And...
Um...
Other than that...
Hela and...
Yeah, I think Hela was...
I guess Punisher for like...
Soldier for Call of Duty.
Um...
And everything...
I felt like I was tickling the enemies.
Yeah.
Uh...
For...
For Loki.
So it just didn't feel worth it.
Because like...
Okay, Loki was like...
A good balance between DPS and heals.
But even then...
Like...
It did not feel like I was healing...
It did not feel like I was actually healing anybody.
Like...
I felt like everybody was dying.
I was trying to heal people as Loki.
I think you're supposed to have three clones out of him.
You're supposed to have like three clones or something.
Um...
And so...
To justify the heals.
But there's a cooldown when it came to that.
So I'm just like...
Uh...
Oh yeah.
Iron Man's orb was fucking crazy.
That shit was insane.
Like I was not expecting that.
Alright guys!
I'm gonna call it here.
I think I already lost Super Chats while we were playing.
So...
Um...
I'm gonna call it here today.
As always everybody...
Stay hydrated.
Posture check.
Get up and around to get that blood flowing.
And if you stayed up for me...
Head to bed.
Cause you deserve it.
I'll see you guys next time everybody.
Bye guys!
Also by the way...
Um...
I think like...
Thursday.
Is it Thursday?
Thursday is our first...
Not first.
Our second official sponsor!
So...
Thursday stream!
With Cookie Run!
Cookie Run hit me up.
Asking if I...
If I was willing to do a sponsored stream for them.
So I'm super excited.
I've never played Cookie Run before.
Um...
Never in my life before.
So...
Um...
I'm really excited to check it out.
Apparently...
A lot of people were like...
Really...
Um...
Hyped up that I'm trying out Cookie Run.
So...
Yeah!
I'm looking forward to it.
Anyway...
Um...
Make sure to support Thursday's stream!
For the sponsored Cookie Run Kingdom!
Uh...
See you guys next time everybody!
Bye guys!
Um...
Bye!
I need to look for the ending screen.
Where is it?
Oh there it is!
Haha!
Bye!