I am the most unlucky PC person in the world!
SHOWER!!!
Okay...
For those....
For those...it's not over by the way!
Cause I found out something!
But let me go from the very...
Not the very beginning, but from where we left off.
So, you guys know how The first RAM set I bought It was faulty.
Hehe!
I took my PC over because I gave up.
I gave up trying to fix it myself.
Never again will I ever fix PCs by myself.
I give up.
But the second set of RAM was also faulty.
How have I managed to buy two faulty RAMs?
Two sets from two different brands.
And the PC people were so confused because I was waiting because they're like, alright, we're gonna We're gonna check what's up with this RAM that you just bought today.
So I was like, okay Can I go out and like get dinner slash lunch because I didn't eat lunch today So I ate lunch and dinner at the same time.
Um, and then yeah, yeah, you can go out.
We're just gonna check what's up So then also I'm like getting up because I need to turn on the lights.
So give me a sec It's like echoey because there's like almost no furniture in my room I need out more So then I came back from after getting lunch slash dinner And then I just see like all the tech guys surrounding my PC I thought that was weird because you know Usually it's like divided like there's tech guys on one side of the room There's tech guys on the other side of the room,
but all the tech guys were around my PC.
So I was like, that's weird That's weird.
That's fucking weird.
Like, why were they...
Why were they there?
That's not a good sign.
That's...
So then they were like, discussing about what was going on with my PC.
And...
And they were like, Yeah, so...
Your second set of RAM is also faulty.
And I was like...
Twice in a row?
I was like...
And like...
How is that possible?
Cause like one of the...
The guy that sold me the fucking upgrade.
Yesterday.
The one that was like...
Yeah, the guy that was like, oh, you can buy this one.
Or you can buy the other one.
And it's just $20 more, but it's an upgrade.
So then they were like...
He was there.
Around the circle of fucking tech people surrounding my PC.
And he was like...
Yeah, I sold you this yesterday.
And it was defective.
But then this one is defective too.
So then I was like...
So they were like...
Yeah, it's very rare.
And I was like...
What do you mean?
And they were like...
It's very rare...
That like...
You would get two sets of defective RAM...
In a row.
And so they were like...
It might be your motherboard...
Is slowly killing your RAM.
Cause like how else would you have...
Two sets of defective RAM?
Your motherboard might have fried it or something.
Or like...
It might be slowly killing it.
I was like...
What do you mean?
So they were like... Alright, we're gonna...
So they were like...
Yeah, we're trying to figure it out.
Because it's not very common.
That like...
You would get two defective RAM in a row.
It's very very rare for that to happen.
And I'm like...
Clearly you haven't met me.
If anything can happen...
I'll do it.
That's very bad for your PC.
That's why I'm here.
So they were like...
Alright, we're gonna like grab a...
Cause like they checked that RAM...
On a different PC.
And they were like... Yeah, this RAM is defective.
They didn't just check it on my PC.
They checked it on other PCs to make sure.
So they were like...
Alright, we're gonna get the RAM test.
The RAM test kit.
To make sure your motherboard is okay.
And it's not...
Your motherboard is not killing every RAM that you put in.
Um...
So I was like...
Okay, we're gonna stress test it.
So we're not...
Yeah, it's all under warranty by the way.
So we're gonna...
That's why I'm still going back to that place.
Because it was free.
The swaps are free.
So they're like...
Alright, we're gonna do a RAM stress test.
So you don't kill the rest of our stock of RAM.
Cause like you know...
They have to keep replacing the RAM.
So they're like...
We're just gonna get like...
One of our test kits.
So you don't keep killing our RAM.
So they went through a stress test on it.
On the motherboard.
And they're like...
The RAM...
The RAM test kit...
Passed the test.
So it's not a motherboard issue.
I guess it's just your RAM.
You just got fault defective RAM.
So they're like... Alright, we're gonna try...
The third set of RAM.
And then we're gonna see...
How it goes.
We're gonna see...
If your third set of RAM...
Is gonna make it.
And they're like...
Are you sure you didn't like...
Mix and match your RAMs?
I was like... No I didn't.
I did not do that.
My chat has yelled at me not to mix and match RAM.
I'm pretty sure.
And they're like... Okay.
They were trying to figure out...
Did I accidentally fry it?
But I was like... No I didn't.
I'm pretty sure I didn't mix and match it.
My chat yelled at me...
Not to do that.
So I didn't.
But I didn't say my chat.
I know I didn't.
But they were like... Are you sure?
And I was like... Yeah I'm sure.
Because they were trying to figure out...
How the fuck...
Did this happen?
No I didn't.
I didn't turn it on.
But I did like...
I mean I did turn it on.
But I accidentally...
Had my outlet plugged in.
And then so like...
So then I was like...
They're like... Okay.
So they were trying to figure it out.
And...
Uh...
So they were like...
We're gonna like...
Put the third set in there.
So then they put the third set in there.
And...
They were like...
We're gonna stress test this to make sure it worked.
And I was like...
Okay.
So I had to wait for a long time.
At the PC store.
Because they were stress testing.
To make sure fully...
That it would work.
And it was okay!
It worked!
Yay!
I have 64 gigabytes of RAM!
And then I came home.
And then I plugged in everything.
And then...
I realized...
Oh my sound settings might be messed up.
Right now.
And then...
I looked at my sound settings.
And do you know what I had to look at?
You...
Especially how unlucky I am.
I'll show you guys what I saw.
The moment I...
The moment I went...
Into...
Went into my sound settings.
Because...
What...
Showed its face to me.
The moment I plugged...
Everything in.
What else could go wrong?
Doki?
I wonder what else that could go wrong...
In my life!
What a good question!
Oh my god.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Are you fucking...
Did my download stop?
Give me a sec.
My folder froze.
This is what I saw.
This is...
For some reason...
After all of that...
For some...
Fucking reason!
My windows...
Unactivated itself!
It unactivated itself!
So I...
I don't know what to do!
And so...
Yeah!
By the way, none of the extra keys worked!
I don't know why!
I don't know...
None of the extra keys worked!
So be the king!
I was panicking!
I was like...
Oh no!
My windows are unactivated!
So I paid $50...
To get a new key!
But then I realized...
It didn't work!
So my windows are still...
And I sent in an SOS...
To hide it and being like...
I need a new key!
I bought the official one!
Because...
Because I don't want any...
I don't do anything illegal!
I was like...
I was scared!
What if the cheaper sites don't work?
Maybe I should go with the official site!
The official Microsoft website!
To buy it!
And then I was like...
But it didn't work!
I even went on the official site!
It didn't work!
When you overfill your PC...
This can occur...
But it goes away!
Thank you!
So...
I panicked!
And I spent another $50!
I spent...
$50!
Anyway...
I don't know...
I am truly the most...
Unlucky...
PC person in the world!
I...
I'll never have good...
PC times!
I'll always have...
PC issues!
No matter what I do!
No matter where I go!
The PC...
Will always haunt me!
But hey...
I have 64 memory now!
That's pretty cool!
But guys...
Despite all of that...
Guys...
Despite all of that though...
Guys look...
Look guys...
Despite all the struggle...
I went through...
Guys look...
I only have...
It only uses...
telesh où But guys...
Guys look!
I guess it was just 36% this time...
Laugh
I'm sorry that I've been plagued with PC issues for three years now.
I won't lie, your whole ordeal is super impressive.
So, uh, funds for your Uber, food, key, and headpads.
64 gigabytes, gang.
Let's go!
Thank you for the Akasupa.
Thank you, thank you, Shady.
I really appreciate it.
It's just... I think, like, this has been the worst it's ever been for me.
Because it's, like, a build-up, you know?
So, like, it kept building up more and more and more and more.
When it came to PC problems.
And, like, that... the past two days was, like, my breaking point.
It's not about the RAM anymore.
It's about how unlucky I have been for the past three to four years.
When it comes to PC issues.
It's like... it's like... that was my breaking point.
It was actually a sigh.
I know.
I always worry.
Because I know it's, like, super annoying, too, for you guys.
Because I always have to, like, reschedule stuff.
And, like, I always feel, like, really scared and stuff.
Being like, oh, no.
You guys give up your time for me.
And then, like, I can't stream.
So I always get really nervous and scared whenever stuff like this happens.
Because I hate it when I can't control what's going on.
And I feel really bad.
But I do hope... I do hope you guys are okay with it.
Okay with the little issues that's going on.
Why does this happen to me?
I don't understand.
How do I keep...
How does this keep happening?
I just... I don't understand.
That's the worst part.
When will it stop?
Oh, my God.
Anyway.
Yeah.
I think... I think we're okay now.
By the way.
My download...
My downloads folder is, like, frozen.
There.
And, like, I don't know how to...
I don't...
I can't close it.
And it's not...
Oh, there it is.
Okay.
I'm going to force quit it.
Force quit.
End task.
Oh.
My...
The bottom thing is gone.
My task bar is gone.
Where did my task bar go?
Oh.
I can't swap.
Where did my task bar go?
I...
Where did it go?
I force quit the downloads folder.
I force quit the Windows Explorer.
And my task bar is gone.
Where did...
Where did it go?
It's gone.
It's...
I don't know what I did.
Wait a bit.
It's not coming back, guys.
It's not coming back.
Next scene.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
It's a form of entertainment.
Thank God.
Okay.
I'm glad you guys are entertained by my pain.
Because at least somebody is enjoying it.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Okay.
Windows R.
Windows R?
What did you make me do?
What did...
Oh.
My desktop is gone.
Where did my desktop go?
Where did it go?
Where
did my desktop go?
My God, what did I do?
What did I do?
I don't think...
I don't think I was supposed to do that.
Oh no!
Time from where?
I can't access anything!
Alt...
Ctrl...
Shift...
B Nothing came up.
I was lied to.
Nothing came up.
What did I press?
W-WR doesn't show up anywhere!
Wait, it just... it's the task manager!
Oh no, why did I do that?
I have the task manager out!
Now...
It's gone!
My desktop is gone!
My... my desktop...
It's gone!
Explorer... EXE...
Okay, I still have my...
Guys, I still... I still have...
I still have...
Oh, there's no Explorer EXE.
How do I...
How do I find Explorer EXE?
Guys, this is the stress test part.
Guys, this is...
Guys, I'm very stressed out.
Guys, I'm very stressed out, guys.
This is... this is the stress test...
They... they visited the studio stress...
...the Tokyo stress test.
WHERE DO I GET FILE?
Where do I... where do I get...
Everything is just a black...
Not black, it's actually gray.
Everything is just a gray space.
File in the ribbon of the task manager.
What about the manager?
What about the ribbon?
There's no file?
Where are you seeing this file that you speak of?
I see details.
I see app history.
Okay, let me see if I can pull up.
Maybe I can pull up Winoki plus R type.
I don't look for run new tasks next to processes.
Oh, run new task.
Oh, okay.
And then what do I type?
What do I...
Okay, explorer.
Okay, then explorer exe.
Okay, open.
Okay, guys, I learned my lesson.
Guys, I did it.
Okay, for those who don't know, I accidentally deleted Windows Explorer.
Now I know.
Do not end task for Windows Explorer.
Because I thought... I saw Windows Explorer.
Underneath Windows Explorer was my downloads folder.
And my downloads folder was...
And my downloads folder was next to Windows Explorer... was underneath Windows Explorer.
So I was like, okay, I'm gonna end Windows Explorer.
Because Windows Explorer comprised the frozen downloads folder.
But little did I know... little did I know, it ended my entire desktop.
You guys wanna know, like, what it looks like?
You should go to task manager and go to Windows Explorer and end it.
And then you can be trapped in the void like I was.
You can... you can also be trapped in the void like me.
Alright.
Jerry, thank you for the Akasupa.
Thank you, thank you.
Nice, the stress test has begun.
Okay, guys, did you guys enjoy...
Part 1 of the stress test?
I had a great time.
Part 1 of the stress test.
Anyway, the whole point of the reason why I got the RAM upgrade...
Was so, like, I would stop stuttering.
But it's not just for Apex.
It's for any other future games.
Because if I was stuttering in Apex, I was worried that I was gonna...
I was gonna stutter for other games as well.
So this was the only reason why I was here.
I need, like, my own IT team at this point.
I really... I really do.
Oh my god.
The stress test has successfully stressed Doki the fuck out.
Thank you for the super chat.
Akas, thank you, thank you.
Yeah, that was...
That...
That's pretty stressful.
So did it fix the stuttering?
I don't know.
We're trying it out right now.
I don't know if I wanna play.
Nah.
I'll do Vantage.
I wanna snipe.
Oh my god.
That was so stressful.
Now I learned.
Do not delete Windows Explorer chat.
Did you guys know that?
Guys.
Did you guys know?
If you close Windows Explorer, you close everything?
Now you do.
My keyboard...
My mouse isn't working.
Why is my...
Where's my mouse?
Oh.
Okay.
That's like...
Is my mouse actually not working now?
Oh my god.
Like.
How...
How is this still going on?
All right.
I have to tie it back in, y'all.
I have to tie it back in.
But it's okay, everything is oka-, everything is almost okay now.
Everything...
I am like doing my fist.
You are the reason Inter-Explorer restarts by default instead of terminating Windows...
Thank you for the super chat, Anton.
Anton, thank you, thank you.
Guys, did you guys like the stress test so far, chat?
I did not.
I don't know if you guys know this, but I did not like it.
It was not the best time.
Are you sure?
Did you change the FOV?
Did I?
Let's see.
Nope, it's 100.
It's always been 100.
It's always been that way.
Alright.
I'm stressed now?
Good.
Now you know how I feel.
Are there even people here?
Alright, the ultimate stress test.
Running a wingman.
Oh, guys, I need to... I'm going to breathe.
Guys, I want to say, like, I'm not here for lunch.
It's not even a good time, but a good time.
But I don't think it's even a good time anymore.
Guys, I don't...
Guys, I don't think it's a good time anymore.
I've been stressed.
Whoa!
Guys, I'm looking at chat!
This is fucked up.
I was reading chat.
Oh, shit.
Okay, he's going to shoot me now.
That's fucking right.
Yeah, that's right.
You don't want to come to me now, huh?
Now I hear.
Wow!
Okay...
Fuck you, I'm going to come back and kill you.
What's your name?
This is not fair.
I didn't think he was actually going to come back!
I didn't...
How is I supposed to know he actually came back?
I thought he got like intimidated.
What was his name?
I already forgot his name.
What was his name chat?
I already forgot.
But now I'm gonna remember.
Now I'm gonna remember.
Now I will remember his name.
What was your name?
Is that him?
That was him.
Okay.
Alright.
He'll come back.
He's gonna come back.
And I'm gonna kill him with his own weapon.
So I'll grab this too.
I'm gonna kill him with his own fucking weapon.
That's right.
This is personal.
He was generosity.
He wasn't like, how do you blow bubbles?
Then who's this other Pathfinder?
There's two Pathfinders?
Like who the fuck was this other guy?
Okay.
We need one more mozab.
Yeah, but I don't have the other mozab.
Isn't two Pathfinders?
I don't feel the stutters yet.
So that's good news.
My frame seems to be consistent.
So like, that's good.
That's what we like to see.
We like consistency here.
I just still can't believe it.
Like, it's been like three months of like...
PC problems and like, you know, you would think like after like the first month, it'll be over but like I even I managed to impress myself because two sets of faulty rams of two different brands being defective back-to-back, like, how is that possible?
It's actually unreal.
I don't have ammo.
I...
Well, this is my ammo.
This is my ammo.
And it was worth it.
Oh, he's so low!
No!
Run!
Oh wait, that's my teammate.
Generosity is my teammate, guys.
Oh, he's fucked.
He's so fucked.
No!
It's alright.
God damn it.
I was not expecting it.
Okay, wait.
Actually, now that like my frames are okay.
I'm gonna...
Okay, wait.
Actually, now that like my frames are okay.
I uncapped my frames.
Give me a sec.
We're uncapping frames now.
Okay, delete.
All right, guys.
Now that like I have no stutters, I'm gonna uncap real fast.
All right, I'm gonna do it.
Actually, no.
I'm gonna uncap to 240.
All right.
Guys, this is it.
This is the ultimate stress test.
This is...
This is gonna be so wrong.
No!
It's gonna be okay!
This is the ultimate stress... I told you it's a stress test.
I told you.
Daniel, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
I'll suggest you to start using two PC streaming setup.
It could help PC-kun reduce burden for stream with Skin Suit and gaming.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
I don't have two cuppy holes.
The one thing that's stopping me now...
I only have one cuppy hole.
How would I fit two?
I only have the space for one!
I don't have two cuppy holes!
For two PCs!
You can get a new desk, you know.
Okay, the amount of money I have spent...
I have spent on like...
PC stuff in general.
I am not buying a new desk.
Not this month.
Maybe I'll look into it in the next couple of months, but I have went beyond my fucking living budget right now.
Like, I spent so much on uber, on uber PC, and it's just life, surviving, moving.
I'm gonna think about the new desk.
I'll think about a new desk in the next couple of months.
I need to like, I need to like be in a better place.
I need it.
And, and, guys.
For those who didn't watch the earlier, the VOD earlier this morning, I was so stressed out I went to Korean BBQ.
By myself.
And then a lot of people were like, that's sad.
Haha!
I'm just like...
I needed it.
I didn't eat a Korean barbeque!
I haven't done that.
By the way, the leftover meat is still in my fucking fridge.
It's still...
I forgot my rice!
That's like the saddest part!
I didn't...
I asked the lady to pack up my ba... like to pack up my rice because I didn't want to...
Oh hey, that's cool.
Hey, it's like a little ride.
Yippee!
I asked the server to pack up my...
Oh, I'm a third wheel on this date.
I asked the server to pack up...
Oh my god, her fucking date is on console?
Oh my god, so they can't even get on Discord?
Sorry, I got a little distracted.
But...
So...
Jesus Christ, I feel so awkward here.
I feel like a third wheel right now.
You are a addicted.
Bro, this guy is shooting his shot.
On this map, it's weird too.
Like, I don't use your thinker, but I have a lot of loot, don't.
Yeah, um...
I don't know what you're talking about, because I'm a fully engaged...
And...
Who asked?
I have the bruiser off to you.
And I have the roller optics on this arse.
Ohhhhhhh!
You're doing playful flirting right now.
And you're like...
Who asked?
Help the bro out!
Oh, I could make it awkward.
I could make it awkward.
Do I make it awkward?
He's so in.
He's so in!
Is this on right?
I don't know.
Don't make it awkward!
Help the bro out!
It literally...
This is actually a fucking...
Gamer date right now.
Little does
The guy know
3k people are watching him!
Listen to him fumble the fact...
Can you guys hear him well?
Or should I boost it louder?
Louder.
Everyone's got favorites.
And that's mine.
I'll type something in when they talk again.
Are you and Peter still together?
Yeah.
Right next to me playing...
Warcraft.
Did you hear?
Did you?
I can't believe!
Holy shit!
The first thing...
Oh shit!
No fucking way!
Are you and Peter still together?
Oh my god!
Yeah, he's like right next to me right now.
Yeah,
he's like right next to me right now.
He actually stopped talking!
Oh my god!
It's...
Arrested beast again!
For what?
Wait!
He actually left!
Afterwards!
Oh my god!
I don't want to say anything!
That is so awkward!
Holy shit!
That's actually so awkward!
Who wants to say anything after that?
Dang.
I'm just kidding.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I DC'd as soon as I finished that sentence.
Oh my god!
Even he was like, that's so awkward!
I just saw your series of posts that I thought were kind of awkward.
Like last week or something.
Wow!
Calling me weird?
If I was a republician, I would shoot you.
I mean...
That's so funny.
But the one that got me was when you posted, what's your type?
And then it was like, I don't have a type.
And then it was like, men who are a little bit gay.
And then it dropped.
What the fuck!
I can't believe you're calling me out.
I can't even play the game!
I can't!
Holy shit!
What the...
What the fuck!
I have no shields.
Because I could not lose for any of this.
Holy shit!
I can't play!
I can't play properly!
Bro!
Oh my god!
I hate this game!
Bro!
This is mad!
I feel so mad for him!
He's like stalking her!
Are you and Peter still together?
I can't!
Oh no!
Not all of us know about salt water.
Okay, wait.
So...
Salt like a good friend of yours?
Salt like
a good friend of yours?
Was he trying to shoot a shot at you?
She is oblivious.
She is actually oblivious.
No!
That guy!
The moment he asked are you and Peter still together?
He was gauging.
He was 100%...
Oh wait, is that a window?
Goodbye.
There's no way!
Oh shit!
I died!
I'm sorry!
No!
I died of cringe.
Chat, I died of cringe.
I can't!
Give me a second to be in a room right now!
I died of cringe right now.
Okay, I'm back.
I'm back.
Dies of cringe.
I like how she was like, no!
And I'm like, bro, this med literally asked if...
Literally is asking about her taste of guys and everything.
There's no way.
There's no...
Cringe is so shocking.
I'm just farming.
Bro, he keeps DCing.
I'm gonna go get that.
No shock.
You guys hear it properly by the way.
Please.
Oh my weird squad.
Cops in Discord.
Holy shit.
Oh my god, why is my thing over there?
It's okay.
Wow!
Guys, it was not okay.
It was not okay.
Oh my god.
You can't live for four seconds!
What the fuck?
Alright, it's okay.
Now she can die.
I'm alive, though.
That's all that matters.
I'm alive.
Oh, please don't tell me I'm gonna die.
Goodbye.
Run for us.
Oh!
Why did his optics move like that?
Doki.
The absent cake is what I'm seeing right now.
What?
What do you mean?
I'm just running.
I'm just fucking running.
What do you mean?
How am I cheating if I'm running?
Oh, did I snap to somebody?
Alright.
There we go.
Hide your aimbot eye!
That's what I'm saying.
Oh god.
They really should get Discord.
They really...
I want to shoot at this team, but I have no high ground for it.
And I feel very unsafe being here.
But the team...
I'm literally a third wheel right now to the most awkward one-sided relationship ever.
I did not expect this to be my stress test.
I...
No, I'm getting stressed over different circumstances right now.
Like, when I say stress test, this is not what I meant.
This is not what I meant.
Putting me in this most awkward scenario ever of the most one-sided relationship.
Where this man literally asked the girl if she was still with Peter.
Like...
That is so fucked.
That is action.
This is the true stress test.
Yes.
Oh, I actually made it.
Nice.
What?
How does that still hit me?
I had a fucking door.
Alright.
No!
Sami, please!
Okay.
That's fine.
What is that, right?
So this is what you meant by PC stress test.
Don't leave!
Leave, Sami!
Sami's so dead.
Alright.
We are free.
We are free, guys.
We are...
We are free.
This stress test is his and Peter's.
My head.
We are free.
Jesus Christ.
Can you...
Okay we are going to try to hear voice comms.
I mean...
Like...
I could not focus at all.
That was like, so hard to focus.
That was actually so difficult.
Oh my God.
Okay.
Alright, let me turn down sound effects by 70.
7D.
And then we will turn it up.
Oh my god.
And then...
And then we can turn it up.
Alright.
Turn up by...
Let's see.
6.2.
There should be better.
What a PC stress test.
I know.
This is not what I expected today.
I honestly... How am I... Am I not cued?
If you exit the queue, the queue will be...
How am I still cued up?
So this is going to be a Doki fight.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you for the super chat fight size.
Thank you.
Doki Poki.
Thank you for magenta soup.
Thank you.
Doki.
After your issues yesterday, I saw that I was 90% of my memory.
So I went to buy more RAM.
But it's way too expensive for me.
So I looked for other ways to get RAM.
Did you know that you can download RAM for completely free?
So I'm doing that.
Make sure you download several copies too.
And if your PC tells you that...
Tells you to not run it anyway, run it.
Because that's just a lie.
Your PC doesn't want you to get stuff for free.
So make sure you download as many as you can so you can fill up your RAM.
How am I not in the game yet?
Jesus Christ.
I'm going to leave match and queue up normally.
Holy f**k.
That...
That was stressful.
That really was.
That...
That really...
That really was very stressful.
I never... You know, like I joke about these things about actually being the third wheel.
How do I have zero friends?
How...
Today truly is... How f**ked can we make Doki?
How f**ked up can we give... can we provide?
Oh my god.
I'm not soloing this.
I'm not... Why... I'm not soloing this.
Why would they do that to me?
The patch came out yesterday!
I'm not soloing it!
It's just... It came out yesterday!
You need to solo.
Oh my god.
The funniest thing is...
It's...
It's bot bot, which is lucky in Chinese tradition.
Clearly, I didn't... Clearly, I didn't get the memo.
Oh my god.
Alright.
Okay.
Today will be...
Today will end on a good day.
Alright.
We will end on a good day.
Alright, sound guy.
Let me know.
If the sound is a lot better, if I should turn down the sound effects or anything.
Ben and Jerry's deserve fun.
You sound like you need it.
Oh yeah.
Kaz, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
I am definitely going to get ice cream after today.
After today's stream.
I definitely need some ice cream.
Ended on being the champion.
Look, with how today went...
Like...
With how it's been going for today.
That's like a really tall order right now.
It seems a little too much now.
Let's not get too crazy here.
Alright.
Fuck it.
I don't know.
Let's land here.
Did my third DC?
How?
What?
Will I have a regular game?
Will I?
I fucking left.
Where's my fucking real game?
I just want a real game.
I just wanted...
Oh my god.
I wanted to fucking...
I just wanted to make sure my PC is okay.
That's it.
Alright.
Here we go.
The third wheel to solo or to duo.
Alright.
Let's see.
Everything will be fine.
I think the super...
Oh shit.
It's fine.
There's like a guy right here.
But it's fine.
It's fine.
Everything is fine.
I have my buddy here.
Derog.
Because I get to catch your stream.
I hope you get to enjoy whatever kind of stream you get after this.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
What the fuck?
Okay.
One, two, three.
Alright.
Three teams.
We're a fourth team heading into the fight.
Guys, please don't come...
Whoa!
Please.
I'm going through a lot right now.
Alright.
Where are they?
Okay.
We're gonna go from this side.
Oh!
And then there's people from this side too.
Alright.
That poor man though.
I'm still thinking about that.
Like...
I'm still thinking about...
Are you and Peter still together?
And then like...
The fact that like...
He...
He didn't say anything after she said...
Yeah.
He's like right next to me right now playing World of Warcraft.
That...
That shit blew my mind.
Like I cannot...
I cannot stop thinking about it.
I actually can.
Thank you.
He's there right here.
But they can't get to us.
Whoa!
Man!
Open the door!
Oh!
Haha!
Okay.
Nevermind.
You know what?
Yeah.
Fuck you guys.
I don't wanna deal with you guys too.
Oh.
What the fuck?
Oh no!
What?
If I hit that shot, that would've been so sick though.
Okay.
I wish I did hit those...
That shot.
No!
Yeah.
It's okay.
Please.
No!
It would've been cool if I did hit it.
Oh wait.
We're back?
It's...
Oh!
We get like second life.
I see.
Wait.
How the fuck did you die so fast?
What?
How?
I died before you.
What?
I died before this guy.
Oh no.
Am I gonna land on a team?
Oh.
Where?
Wait.
What?
Somebody shot me.
I don't like that.
Who shot me?
I'm scared I'm gonna get shot to my side.
Okay.
Oh.
God.
I've never been so stressed out before.
No.
That's a lie.
But like...
That's a lie, but like...
Why me?
I don't know why.
Why is my life like this right now?
Is that shot from behind?
That was a sentinel shot.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Alright.
I'm gonna head closer.
Can I get like a normal team?
Like...
Can I...
Can I get...
Can I get a normal team today?
Holy fuck.
Why is...
Why are my teams like this?
By the way, I still think this map sucks.
A lot of people are like, no, it's fun.
I hate the fucking high high ground.
High high ground is dog shit.
I hate it.
Wait.
What?
Where did he go?
Oh, there he is.
Alright.
Come on.
Get closer.
That's right!
Whoa!
How does this keep happening?
Every time I want to be confident!
No!
How does this keep happening?
How?
How?!
I ...
I don't understand.
How?
How?!
Has happened twice!
Bro!
This is not fair.
This is actually not fair.
Like, every...
Every time.
This is the second time.
Ugh.
This is actually the second time!
This dreadpun is not my day.
It's not my day at all.
I mean, maybe it'll be easier in rank because it's not E-District.
Because it fucking... I hate Broken Moon, but I hate E-District even more.
Alright.
Vantage time.
Oh!
Today you're being blessed by the God.
Thank God!
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you, Black.
Alright, here we go.
Maybe it won't be that bad in rank, you know?
Maybe it won't be...
My third D-Seed.
This is my first ranking of the season!
This is actually my first ranking of the season!
How did I... How did my Thane leave?
Ain't no damn way.
Ain't no way!
Oh my God.
It truly is... It truly is a day today.
Oh...
Let me grab...
Is there a gun?
Is there any gun?
Is there one gun?
One measly gun for little old me.
This game will be normal, surely.
Alright, guys!
It's alright!
I got one gun!
I got one gun.
That's all I asked for.
That's all I wanted.
One gun.
Now I have two guns!
I have no idea if there's anybody on us.
Alright, now we know.
Okay.
There's people on us.
Um...
Okay.
Oh...
They're, like, here.
Are you serious?
Wait, I don't have enough ammo!
I'm lucky.
I'm dead.
Oh my God, this is not great for me.
This is...
I...
I'll give as many craps as prisoners will take.
None.
I...
I don't understand.
I need...
I'm gonna pee out of sadness.
I'll be right back.
I'm gonna sad pee.
I'm back.
I...
I'm...
I'm back!
I'm back.
Shirley!
This match can't be that bad!
My luck will turn around here!
Okay.
This time... this time it will be different!
It will be different!
Alright.
Is there anybody landing with us?
Yes, there is!
A lot of buddies.
I'm gonna get a guarantee gun first.
Alright.
Guarantee gun.
If you guys didn't know, these lupins are like guarantee guns now.
You know what?
Let's do it for the hipfire.
Oh wait.
Shirley.
Wow!
I was fucking around too much!
Oh my god.
This sucks.
Okay.
I got one.
Where's the last guy?
Give me your fucking helmet.
I mean, armor.
Oh my god.
I scared the shit out of him because I wasn't paying attention!
To be fair, I never pay attention.
But like, I was absolutely not paying attention right now.
I'm not!
Finally!
We win our first team fight of the day!
I think my luck is turning around!
Chat!
This is it!
My luck is turning around, everybody!
I can feel it!
I can feel it, guys!
Alright.
Let me go grab this...
Let me grab this armor thing.
And then we can go in.
It can only go up from here, right?
That's what they say!
Alright.
I heard, like, people shooting from there.
I think.
It's up here?
Yeah.
Were they shooting up there?
Alright.
Here we go!
Haha, JK!
Didn't I hear shots from here?
No, it's not looted.
I thought I did.
Alright.
Let's grab some heals.
Let's grab this.
What?
Where were those shots?
They were on this side.
Yeah, what could possibly go wrong?
You're right.
What could possibly go wrong?
We already got through all the bad luck.
Surely, like, no more.
No more.
I won my first team fight.
So that means there's no more bad luck now.
After winning the first team fight.
Them's the rules!
Where?
Oh.
Oh!
Okay.
I was like, where the fuck are they looking at?
Oh, that's so far.
What the fuck?
I'm gonna loot.
That's so fucking far.
I assumed they would be closer.
I'm gonna craft two.
Yeah!
Yippee!
I'm not running the akimbo anymore.
They're just bad luck for me these days.
Haha, I swear.
Unless!
Unless I run double P20!
You know what?
Surely nothing can go wrong if I run double P20.
It's like Christmas!
Alright, let's see.
Merry Christmas!
What gives season's greetings to everybody?
Let me fucking scan this now.
Oh, I should have done the ring console.
Because it's rank.
Oh well.
I don't care about my teammates that much.
Oh, there's people behind us here.
I'm gonna fight them.
Let's do it.
You know what?
I'm feeling wild.
I feel exceptionally wild today.
I went through so much shit.
I'm fucking ready.
That's fucking right.
I tagged you.
What you gonna do, little guy?
You scared now?
Oh.
I shot that late.
That was some slow reflexes.
What?
Wait, your friend is so...
Let's see.
Come on, look at me.
Look at me.
Yeah!
Look at me again!
Look at me again, guys!
Oh, they don't wanna look at me anymore!
Look at me again!
Keep looking!
Oh, okay, wait.
I have one more bullet!
I'm going in.
There you go.
Wait.
Oh, shit!
I was like, wait a minute.
Don't you fucking lose this!
They're back!
Everything I did!
I was gonna say!
All right.
Nice.
I'm gonna take this real fast.
Oh, shit!
Wait, what?
How do I still have shields?
Okay.
Everything is fine.
I was...
I would be so mad they actually lost that fucking 3v1 after I did all that.
I would have been so fucking sad.
All right.
Let's see.
Give me that.
Ooh!
What do you have?
Nice.
Oh, my God.
Maybe this is it.
Guys, maybe, like, my luck is finally turning around.
I can feel it!
I can actually feel it!
Did I took the shield core?
Guys, things are going by so fast.
Now, my brain can't handle it.
There's so much that my brain actually can't handle.
I can't handle things any more.
Refresh on hits with ultimate.
Oh, shit!
Yeah, fuck it.
Let's do it.
I should have done the left side, but it's too late.
I can't refund it.
I was not paying attention.
I was just like, refresh hits?
But I didn't realize it meant, like, uh...
Um...
I didn't realize that, like, um...
It's not that good.
Alright.
Let's see.
Is there any...
What does my eyes see?
What does my sniper eyes see?
Nothing!
I want to scan this.
There's still, like, 12 squads, which is very surprising in this elo.
Oh, my god.
What a day.
What a fucking day.
I feel like I haven't been able to breathe in a while.
I felt like I...
What a fucking day.
It's been a rollercoaster of emotions.
Alright.
Nobody shows up.
Okay?
Nobody pop up.
Unexpected.
Okay, everybody?
I'm just having a nice walk.
Who do you scan?
I just want to scan the survey beacon.
To know what's going on.
Oh, my god.
I'm just having a nice walk.
So, be chill.
Be chill, everybody.
Okay.
There shouldn't be anybody there.
Like, what kind of freak would be there?
Anyway.
It's literally the other side of the world.
Wow!
He's, like, behind here.
Now I know what kind of freak would be here.
I was like, what kind of freak would be here?
Fucking freaks.
Freaks.
Jesus Christ.
I found the freak.
I found him.
Oh, my god.
They're chasing after this poor guy.
That poor fucking freak.
He's not deserved.
No, he did.
He absolutely did.
He scared me.
He deserved that.
Oh, my god.
Wait.
You're supposed to be the only one in here.
There should be people down here.
In this choke.
Oh, I see him.
Alright.
Oh!
I didn't hit that!
God damn.
I thought I did.
Oh, he's running.
He's running.
Come on, little guy.
Come on!
Where did he go?
Here we go.
That's it?
Alright.
Let's go.
Look at theplay.
Okay.
Wait, isn't that the same guy tagged?
No, that's a different guy.
No!
That would've been cool though.
That would've been so cool!
Wait, can they even go over this?
I don't think these guys can go over this.
Where did they go?
Where did they fly to?
Did they fly like here?
I guess here?
Would they be behind us?
Where did they go?
That was so confusing.
Did they went behind us?
I'd assume they would like go like...
Oh shit.
The fuck?
Where did all these freaks keep coming from?
That's fucking right.
Oh shit, okay.
I was the better sniper until I had to snipe somebody else.
Alright.
That's fine.
Ugh.
There's so many weird ass people.
What are you doing just crouching?
Wait, what?
What are you doing just crouching there?
He's just crouching!
Okay, we should hit this.
I don't like this spot.
It's a full squad team, people.
I don't know about standing here, but okay.
Feel like we should not be in the open.
But, you know.
That's alright.
I mean, you do you guys.
We should like head back.
Yeah, we should head back.
Let them fight that.
I'm fine with chilling.
Seems a little dangerous, you know, with no cover.
But what would I know?
I don't need any of those, but I'll take it.
I'll take it so nobody else can take it.
Does any of my team need this?
Look at that!
I'm a team player!
I saw that my teammates needed energy ammo.
Look at that!
I'm a team player!
Oh, I need that, actually.
Alright.
I did my part, exactly.
I need to remember this is not the tweaking 800 lives game.
Let's see.
I'm over here.
What?
Over there.
Oh!
Woah!
Oh god.
Oh no.
He tagged me.
Woah.
I'm safe.
I feel safe in my safe zone.
I don't have shield cells, though.
Alright.
He downed somebody behind us.
But like, I don't know if he thirsted.
He didn't thirst him.
Though I know.
Oh shit!
You know what?
Fuck you in particular.
Yeah.
What?
He has a... Oh, it was a sniper mark.
It was a sniper mark.
I was like...
What?
That was like super cocky.
I'm safe.
If you don't look at him, they can't see you.
If you don't look at them, they can't see you.
That's all.
That's all that matters!
You don't see you don't die.
Them's the rules.
There's a heat shield, but like...
God damn it!
That's a full squad!
Come back here!
Or not.
Or don't.
Well, alright, okay.
Oh!
Okay.
I feel safe here.
I do not feel safe here anymore.
Alright.
Guys!
Oh!
Okay!
That's...
Wow!
Hey!
Let's just...
Fuck everybody!
Let's party!
Let's fucking party in that room!
God damn!
Oh my God!
What the fuck did I... What was that?
I...
I got fucking...
Ran so hard down there!
Like...
I got shot by three...
It's a monster house.
Like...
Alright!
Who cares?
I know, like, real estate is, like, an issue.
Oh, that guy is actually blind.
Guys, I know, like, um, real estate is really hard to find good places.
to live these days.
Like, I know.
But, like, one at a time!
If you want a viewing, one at a time, guys!
This is not an open house!
It's not an open house, everybody!
It certainly wasn't a party in the USA.
Holy fuck!
That was actually fucking crazy.
Like, what the fuck did I went through?
Alright, Octane, you better live for us.
Crouch!
Octane!
He doesn't know how to crouch?
Okay.
This guy isn't... This guy might be Diamond, but he's not, like...
He doesn't look at game knowledge.
Like, I don't know.
Did they change it?
If you crouch in a serial, they can't see you.
They can't see you if you crouch in a serial.
So, like, I don't know if they changed it, but, like, that usually...
Octane players don't crouch.
Oh, what the fuck?
That's a spot?
Is this a ratting diamond?
What the fuck?
Okay, he knows the spots.
What a chat.
No crouching.
Way to be aggressive.
I fucking love you.
I don't know if that's sarcasm or, like, not.
I don't.
I can't tell it's Apex.
I can't tell.
Because he definitely ran away from us.
He knows that I don't know.
And then he covers his tracks.
Yeah.
I can't tell because Apex people are always sarcastic.
So I can't tell if he's being sarcastic or not.
I...
Okay.
There's still five squads?
How?
He's so dead.
Like, what is he...
What is he trying to do?
What is he...
Okay.
After all that...
I'm just like...
What was he...
What was that?
Legend.
He panicked.
He really did.
You know what?
Oh, no, no, no.
Absolutely not.
No, no, no, no.
Yay!
All right.
Before...
We're not ending yet.
We have one last ultimate stress test to do, guys.
We have one last stress test to do, chat.
To make sure everything is okay.
Guys, just one last stress test.
Swap.
Let me swap real fast.
Oh, yeah.
You guys can be big again.
Guys, I fixed it.
Apparently, it was an OBS issue, but you guys can be big now.
Congratulations.
You guys...
You guys can be big boys again.
But the ultimate...
The ultimate stress test...
What?
Wait a minute.
Wait.
Oh.
Oh, that scared me.
It said... It said my Overwatch uninstalled.
And I was like, what?
I was like, how did it...
Anyway, the ultimate stress test.
I was like, there's no way it uninstalled.
I've been playing Overwatch every day.
I was like, I'm fixing my PC.
I got it uninstalled.
How is that possible?
Anyway, that's the ultimate stress test.
Let's go.
We're only doing one game.
We're only doing one game, though.
Okay.
Alright, let me make sure what sound I have to do for Overwatch.
Overwatch.
12.0.
Okay.
Here.
Alright.
I need to make sure where my sound balancing was for Overwatch.
Apparently, it is 12.0.
I think.
Unless it's not.
Let me make sure.
Overwatch.
Yeah, that should be it.
Alright, guys.
Then we know it's okay.
Then we know.
If we lose, we lose.
Because I can gain it back later.
I'm just like two games away from, you know.
Wait.
Oh, God.
Please.
Please, no!
I saw my tap.
There's nothing I can do!
There's really nothing I can do!
She just slowly titled the way over!
What can I do about it?
Nothing!
That's the worst part!
I need this kill.
This might not be it.
Why is there a Junker and Hammond?
Oh, and a Sigma?
I heard a Sigma.
I heard him.
Please!
Oh, hey.
I be friends with him so he doesn't kill me.
Oh, my God.
Alright, here we go.
One last game.
The ultimate stress test.
Yay, I stole the kill.
That's all that matters.
No!
I can't shoot like this!
I can't shoot.
Alright.
That's fucking right.
That's right.
You can't do nothing.
Can't do nothing.
I can't do nothing either.
Alright.
Oh, my God.
Yes, it's rough.
What the fuck are you doing?
It's just me and you, Chuno.
Yay!
Now I'm killed either.
Oh, my God.
There's three stack that joined in.
I hear him.
Where is he?
I hear you.
Is he above me?
He's above me right now, isn't he?
Oh, there's the echo.
Oh, thank God.
All the tank players left.
No.
Oh, God.
Guys.
I played too much Apex.
And by too much, I meant I played Apex just then.
My aim.
My aim can't do it.
My aim's not used to Overwatch sense anymore.
Alright.
I'm trying to...
Oh, God.
There's a... No!
Leave me alone.
I hate Venture so much.
Alright.
That's good.
The Venture left.
Oh, no.
It's just me and the Venture.
How am I not in the game?
I don't understand.
Hello?
Friendly?
I'm desperate.
I'm desperate right now.
I joined Deathmatch not to have a skirmish.
Venture, if you want to say hi, join a skirmish.
This is literally Deathmatch.
Okay.
Ooh.
Ooh, Pharah.
Wait, that's good aim practice.
Oh, shit!
That wasn't a Pharah.
Please!
Why you open me?
The fuck is...
Three people.
Why did all three people showed up?
That's so fucked up.
Not gonna lie.
Holy shit.
That's actually fucked up.
No!
That Rein was so low!
What is that?
Oh, that's Pharah.
I was gonna say, why did it take so long to...
Oh my god, please.
Somebody show up.
I just wanna get in the game.
Please!
Give me a game!
No!
God damn it.
Oh.
I'm leaving.
He actually died for that deflect.
What a fucking idiot.
That guy actually died for...
You can tell how long I've been here.
Everybody else has...
Everybody else has found the game and I'm still here.
This is so sad.
Like, how am I still here?
There's nobody...
There's nobody else that's been here as long as I have.
Please.
Oh thank god.
Thank god.
Free me.
Chris and Teyv match forever.
GM5!
It's 9pm!
I didn't wanna try that hard!
Oh.
What do people play?
I don't know.
Meta?
Who GM?
I didn't wanna fucking play...
I
didn't wanna fucking play...
Oh my god.
I fucking...
I played Overwatch like on and off this past week.
And there was...
I didn't get into a single GM5.
I didn't get into a single GM game.
They were all like...
The highest was like Master 1.
And like now...
Oh!
The one game!
The one game I wanted to play on stream with you guys!
To stress test my PC!
And it's GM5!
I didn't...
I wasn't expecting...
I wanted to stress test!
I'm trying to stress test my PC!
Not...
Not my fucking...
My stuff!
Jesus Christ.
I'm not okay everybody.
I am not okay right now.
Play.
I'm not okay.
Oh shit.
Oh that was close.
I saw her at the last second.
Oh nice now I can peek.
Oh what the fuck?
I'm stressed already.
I actually need to try!
But what if I don't want to try?
What the fuck is...
Wow!
Alright.
Okay.
Can you shoot him?
No!
He was so low!
We almost got him.
For those who don't know.
GM5 is currently...
It's currently top 200.
So like...
That's why I'm like...
I did not want to do a GM...
GM game right now.
It's literally top 200.
If you're GM5.
Like why?
Alright.
Here we go.
Yeah GM5 is top 200 at the moment.
You're really close to top 500.
I'm like two ranks.
Two tiers.
From top 500 right now.
Oh shit.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Yippee!
My team is carrying me!
Let's go!
Let's fucking go!
Woo!
That was scary though.
Not gonna lie.
Yeah!
I can chill!
A little bit.
Until I can't.
Okay.
Oh!
This is where I die!
Nope.
I made it.
I think our Tracer is the top GM5.
The Tracer is like killing everybody right now.
Which is great.
I love it when like...
Oh shit!
Fucking whoa!
Oh.
The...
I mean...
You live.
This Lucio is fucking around.
Holy fuck!
This poor Lucio.
This team has a...
This team has a troll Lucio.
That's for sure.
Oh my god.
Oh nice.
Whoa!
I'm gonna stay here.
Alright.
I don't feel safe.
I don't...
I'm gonna stay here guys.
I'm gonna stay here.
I'm gonna stay right here.
Yay!
My mouse died!
When that happened!
Okay no it's just slow mode.
Okay thank god.
I'm so happy I have the GM5 on my team.
I'm so happy.
And he's not a support.
Holy shit.
Who the fuck was that Lucio?
Like...
Actually...
Okay it's either ink or...
Cause like one of them is actually throwing.
One of them is fucking not playing the game.
And he's definitely not playing the game.
Is it Lilac?
No.
He's the master 5.
He's the master 5?
Who the fuck is our GM5?
There's no way the GM...
I do not...
There's no way the GM5 is...
Um...
I don't believe...
The GM5 is on the enemy team with how they're doing right now.
Also...
Zero thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
It was I the Lucio.
Who the fuck is throwing?
Alright.
Cause this does not feel like a high elo game.
Is there a Widow?
Widows are winning the duels.
Everybody's incognito mode.
Including me.
I can hear the Lucio.
They have the Widow so I don't wanna peek.
I'm scared of peeking.
I'm gonna peek only when the...
Uh...
Wow!
He died to a Lucio!
Oh my god.
He's so low.
Wait, maybe this Lucio is...
What the fuck?
What the fuck is he doing?
Guys, I'm too tired to be doing this Ana Lucio.
From what?
From BBC?
What the fuck?
Guess I'm too tired to be...
Handling that Lucio right now.
Like...
Like really?
I'm gonna Kiriko here.
Cause like...
Oh no, I can't...
Kill...
Oh no.
I'm fucking...
I'm mis-positioning myself for you Winston!
I'm... Alright, I'm going Kiriko.
This team...
This team's a mess.
I can't position!
I can't position at all!
Everybody's everywhere!
Don't you hate it when everybody is just everywhere?
Alright, I saved the...
Uh...
Guys, I'm... I'm here.
But I don't know how long...
I don't know how long...
I can be here though.
I'm gone.
Maybe Ink is GM5.
He literally got 3k.
He literally 1v1'd the Widow.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, maybe he is.
Holy shit.
We're a mess because of this Lucio now.
Holy fuck.
Oh.
He went back to me.
I honestly thought that...
I'm not timing stuff correctly right now.
Which is bad.
Because I need to time my stuff better.
Oh no.
I don't know why we went rigged.
Like, none of our...
None of what they're playing is...
Oh my god, we did it!
Raid boss is down!
I repeat!
The raid boss has...
Where is the Winston?
Oh my god, there he is!
I was like trying to find him.
Oh no.
Whoops.
Oh, I hear the Lucio.
I hear him.
Nice.
I need to save the Brig though.
Oh my god.
No, he's not throwing.
He's playing very aggro.
And...
He's dead.
Jesus Christ.
Okay, we're fine.
For now.
We're fine for now.
We're fine.
Okay.
Alright.
Hey guys.
Hey.
Oh, goodbye everybody.
Please.
Please, why are we playing Brig?
Get off Brig.
We don't need Brig right now.
Everybody...
We don't have dive characters.
Brig.
Ma'am.
We don't have dive characters.
Nobody's playing dive.
Why?
Why are we on Brig?
Nobody is diving anybody.
They're all there.
They're...
I don't understand.
How are you dying to win?
I really, really wish he was not playing Brig.
No, it's cause like, the comp does not need a Brig right now.
That's why.
That's why like, there's no reason to play Brig.
Because like, we're not brawling on point.
Maybe both teams are just equally bad.
Both teams are just not good.
Not good at defense.
Honestly?
Yeah.
I think...
I don't...
I think we're both not good at defense.
Now that I've seen it.
He definitely has.
Alright.
God damn it!
Really?
Alright.
Nice, we got the Soldier.
They have...
He has Sigma ult.
There it is.
Oh, there they go.
They are both dead.
There's no saving that.
There's no...
We're both just really bad at defense.
Like, that's good to know.
That's good to know.
That is very good to know!
I blame the Brig pick.
100%.
Okay,
I wanna like, make sure that our Hog is alive.
Okay.
There you go.
Alright.
Please.
All I ask is that you all fucking get one pick.
One pick!
Oh, thank god!
Two picks!
Let's go!
Oh, he's living on the edge right now!
And I'm gonna stand here because I feel like that Lucio's gonna backcap.
I think that Lucio's gonna backcap.
So I'm gonna stay right here.
I'm gonna stay right here.
Alright.
This is fine.
It's not fine.
But like, I gotta be optimistic for a little bit.
So like, this is as fine as it can get.
This is as fine as it can be right now.
What?
That hit?
That didn't hit him?
That sucks.
That fucking sucks.
Okay, now the Brig is good.
Now this is the perfect time to stay Brig.
Because Brig is very good against D.Va.
Because D.Va is a Dive character.
And he can knock off.
Okay, now I can like go back up.
Whoa.
Okay, that's not good.
Oh.
Oh, okay!
I literally went to...
Okay, my buddy.
My buddy.
We are dead.
Alright.
Can anybody touch?
Can you guys touch?
Okay.
The dragon is becoming!
Oh!
Genji, no!
Alright.
Wait, Temmin is still alive!
Oh, okay!
Alive is a good word.
A good statement.
Okay.
I'm not kidding.
Oh my god.
This is rough.
We are both really bad at defense.
We're both really bad at defense.
Go Astrid, go.
Okay, you know, I feel a lot better with that pick.
I feel...
I feel a little bit better with that pick, you know?
Alright,
here we go.
This is one game!
I'm still in that one game!
I'm still...
I'm still in this one game!
Oh, I had to jinx it when I was like, Yay!
I'm so happy that, like, I'm getting carried right now!
Yippee!
In the GM5 lobby!
Let's go!
And I had to jinx it.
I had to jinx it.
I had to make this harder for myself.
I really did.
Yippee.
I am...
not focused at all, too.
Like, that's the worst part.
Like, I am definitely not focused right now.
This is a stress test in a whole nother level.
Zero, thank you for the five!
Get the ships!
Thank you, thank you!
Okay, I don't wanna get sniped accidentally.
Okay.
They have Widow?
They have... why?
That's interesting.
Oh!
Nice!
We got rid of...
No Widow!
Okay, I can play more, like, uh...
Whoa!
Okay.
This Hanzo's good, so I'm like...
What the fuck was that Reaper doing?
Alright.
Gotta make sure...
I was like, where's that... where is...
Oh, nice!
Okay.
Oh my god, that Lucio's so low!
What?!
That doesn't stop charges anymore!
On charge!
No, I threw!
No!
It used to stop charges!
I actually threw that!
That used to stop Ryan's charge, and I didn't realize they changed it!
I actually didn't know!
Oh my god!
It used... it actually does!
I'm not... I'm not fucking with you guys.
It actually used to stop Ryan's charges, so I was, like, not expecting that at all.
No... no...
That's so... that sucks.
That actually sucks.
I'm gonna back up.
Oh my god, I'm so sad.
I'm actually so sad that happened.
Stop.
It's okay, team.
I don't feel okay.
I do not feel okay.
How am I not real?
Yo!
Yo, what the fuck, man?
I'm not bashing one trick, man.
Come on, knock it off.
Oh my god, I actually threw!
I feel so bad!
I feel so bad, because, like...
Oh my god, if I didn't die, we would've won.
We actually would've won that.
I actually was like, kiki, I'm just gonna...
Oh no.
We need a reset here.
Oh shit.
No!
It's okay, the Zarya died too.
Oh!
Yo, why are you... yo, you're on Zarya and a Rein, bro.
Okay, they don't blame me!
They don't blame me, guys!
They don't blame me!
Guys!
It's great, they don't blame me!
They didn't blame me for the loss!
Oh my god, I'm so happy!
I didn't get blamed for it!
That's all that matters.
Okay.
Alright.
They don't know what I did.
Oh, thank god.
When did they change that?
When did they change the charge?
Oh, thank god.
They don't blame me.
Not our fault.
They're blaming each other.
That's like my...
That makes me so happy.
In the end, nobody expects that I threw there to cause the momentum.
Nobody expects it.
And that's all that matters, everybody.
As long as they don't think it's my fault.
But now I know!
Now I literally know.
Now...
Now I know!
For future's sake!
We know what you did!
Shhh!
It doesn't matter, bro.
It was a free win, bro.
Put it down.
Shhh!
They don't know it was me!
When I thought it...
But actually, when did they change that?
Did they change that?
Like, what season was it?
How behind was I in Kiriko Tech?
That they...
They made it so that Suzu doesn't stop charges anymore.
No one tell anybody!
Okay?
I literally was like, he...
I can just Suzu myself and he can't charge me.
Was it actually last season?
Oh my god.
This...
Was it actually this season?
I am...
I can't believe it!
It was like two months ago when I didn't play this game!
As frequently!
Why does, like, all the tech I know, they just... they just change it?
That is actually so unlucky.
That's two months ago.
They changed it two months ago and I wasn't playing that game two months ago.
Guys, I don't think we're gonna win this.
Guys.
I...
I have a feeling...
That...
Um...
We're not gonna win this.
I have...
I...
Ooh...
Sorry, Zanebotter.
I got the Lucio.
Oh, shit.
I wanna heal...
Okay.
Oh, there is a Widow again.
And I don't...
I'm gonna push the cart.
We need as much time as possible.
Like, I...
I don't know if we're actually gonna win this, but, like, you know, I don't want them to think it's my fault.
They don't know.
That's okay.
Nobody blames me.
I'm so happy.
In the end.
Knowing that...
Knowing that no one actually saw what happened...
Will help me.
It's what gives me life.
Oh, they're running full, like, alt counters, though.
They're making it so that...
So that...
Oh, they're like...
Whoa.
Hello.
You guys didn't see anything.
Guys.
Shhh.
They think it's the Hog and the Blados' fault, guys.
Not me.
Not me, though.
I need to push the cart with our guy.
Um...
This is so hard, guys.
We need to keep up the momentum right now.
Jesus Christ.
Like, I'm trying so hard.
Like, Weaver and I are trying so hard.
It's like, I know what you did last summer.
Or, like, pretty...
Or, either pretty-lyring this, or, like, I know what you did last summer.
Oh.
That was a dink.
Right there.
Woo.
Nice.
Tracer, please tell me you have recall, Tracer.
She did not have...
She didn't have recall.
Oh, no.
Our momentum.
They
knew.
They knew.
I should have died instantly.
Our momentum.
Oh, my God.
Oh, our momentum.
I'm just gonna stay back here.
I don't... I don't feel safe up here.
I'm just gonna go stay here.
Hey guys!
I feel like we should maybe not take 200,000 damage right now.
You know?
Alright.
Alright!
That is a lot of ults.
That's alright.
It's not, but like... you know... like I don't know what else to do.
Alright.
Momentum!
We have two... we literally have two fights.
Kill his D.Va.
Just in case.
I'm gonna push cart.
You save the life viewer.
You save her.
That is literally your only mission.
They have Pharah ult.
They have Junk ult.
They have everything.
We gotta kill at least... make them use something.
Oh yes!
I have C9.
I told you it was an easy win, bro.
You know?
I had that in the bag.
Never punished!
Oh my god!
Never fucking punished!
Let's fucking go!
They'll never know!
They'll actually never know!
So I can go.
I might have thrown.
But they threw harder.
They threw a lot harder than me.
Yippee!
Alright.
And I think that's where we're gonna call the stress test.
Thank you for coming to the stress test today.
When I said stress test, I didn't realize it was gonna test me mentally as well.
But here we are.
Here we are.
We got tested both mentally and physically.
And on my PC.
But I had a great time.
I hope you guys had a great time hanging out with me too.
As always everybody, say hi, join, pause, check in, and move around to get that blood flowing.
And if you stood up for me, head to bed.
Cause you deserve it.
By the way guys, tomorrow is gonna be the God of War stream.
So yeah, if you're looking for that, we're gonna have that tomorrow.
I'll see you guys next time everybody.
Bye guys!
Bye!