Hello,
everybody!
Hello, hello!
Welcome to Once Human!
So, you guys might notice that Tengen is muted right now.
Because we found out that we can't instantly play multiplayer.
We have to do like a little... we have to do a little tutorial first.
Like, in the first 15 minutes.
So, because of that, we were like, okay, I'm gonna meet you when we're done with the tutorial.
And when we find each other.
So, like, what you guys see, like your first time seeing Tengen, will be my first time seeing Tengen in game.
Because he was like, I don't want to show my chat what I made.
So, we're gonna see that together, guys.
The first hand reaction together.
And that is why he is muted at the moment.
He's like, alright, when we see each other, we unmute.
So, Once Human.
Apparently, it is a... the newest third...
I know I wrote like... at first I thought it was first person.
And I realized it was third person.
So, then I had like edited my tweet like three times.
Because like the first time I edited it, it was like grammar mistake.
The second time I edited it, I was like, oh, it's a shooter game and not an FPS game.
So...
I edited my tweet multiple times.
Because I kept making mistakes.
Anyway, so Once Human is the newest shooter game.
Newest PvE shooter game.
Extraction shit or whatever.
And like today, we're gonna figure out...
This is launch day.
Launch today.
I've always seen a lot of trailers of this leading up to Once Human.
And like, you know, it finally launched today.
And judging by the...
Judging by the reviews...
It might die soon.
Judging by what the reviews were saying.
It doesn't look...
It doesn't look too promising.
It does have PvP and PvE.
But we're gonna be doing PvE.
Because Tenjin was like...
He was scared of getting stream sniped and killed lots of times.
So like...
Okay, he didn't say that.
But that's what I assumed.
Because he didn't choose...
I let him pick the server.
And I was like PvE, not PvP.
And he's like, yeah, PvE.
So he's a little bitch.
So...
He's a little bitch boy.
And doesn't want to risk playing PvP.
Yeah, that's what I heard in my head.
When he was like, we're doing PvE.
Anyway...
Most likely...
It's free to play though.
Like...
Once human is free to play.
So that's like the great part about it.
It is free to play.
But like...
It has mixed reviews right now.
So...
I don't know.
Apparently a lot of it was because it's like cosmetics.
Like...
A lot of stuff is like locked behind a paywall.
But like...
That's usually what I expect from free to play.
Usually in free to play it's...
You know, a lot of stuff is locked behind...
Um...
Locked behind...
Uh...
Behind stuff.
So...
Yeah...
Um...
We'll see.
I was gonna like...
I went in.
I was like, okay, we're gonna go in.
Oh my gosh.
Why is there like zero bars?
Anyway...
Okay...
And then there's server issues apparently too.
Where people are waiting for a very long time to get into the server.
But I sort of expected that for a game that came out on launch.
There's a hand.
Whoa!
Our world is broken.
Stagnant.
Fallen into the abyss.
But everything is born from darkness.
Even the universe itself.
Now...
Alright, I'll turn up this.
The spark of life still burns.
Alright.
And evolution forges a new way forward.
I raised it a bit more.
What's the lore that we're never gonna pay attention to after this?
Cuss scene.
Yeah, I was gonna say it feels like Kingdom Hearts.
It really does.
Once you move beyond death.
Once life returns to this world.
This feels like...
Where's the door of darkness?
Oh my god.
This is the Keyblade Cemetery right here.
Beyond that path.
Keyblade but with guns.
Kingdom Hearts should add guns into its game.
That's how it's gonna improve.
The reason why Kingdom Hearts 3 was not as good as 1 and 2...
Was because the audience grew up and now they just want gun.
Change my mind.
Alright.
Oh my god.
Okay, this is like...
It's NetEase, right?
So yeah, this looks like a NetEase game.
I can tell.
I can tell because like...
You can tell when certain games are made.
Whichever company made whichever games.
Due to the fact of the faces.
This is the NetEase style.
I can tell.
Or Nexon, yeah.
It's either NetEase or Nexon.
I can recognize the faces.
You know what I mean?
Each company has its own very distinct customization when it comes to humans.
I'm like, yeah, that looks like a NetEase or Nexon game.
Alright, can I make me?
Okay.
Oh, this is RetroDoki right there.
Well, I don't know.
I don't know.
All the faces are like...
Can I say that?
I feel like they're all like...
So are the guys too.
All the faces are very similar.
Alright, let's see.
Okay, face.
Alright.
Oh my god.
It's...
Okay, like these games have like...
Insane customization as well.
Like because...
What the fuck?
Oh my god.
Okay, we need like a really small head.
There's too many things.
Forehead, tempo, hairline, jaw, jaw.
Jesus Christ, am I playing in like MMO?
Is this an MMO right now?
Alright.
Guys, the smaller the head, the smaller the...
The hip box.
Guys, believe in me.
The smaller the head, the smaller the hip box.
This is our...
You got even done!
Is it the hair?
Okay, let's get rid of the hair and just see like does it make a difference.
It has... Okay.
Alright.
Okay, we'll fix the hair later.
I just want to know if there's like any...
If I could... If there's any difference.
Like I can't tell.
I can't tell if I'm making any...
Oh my god.
The head is a little dented here.
Like...
Oh my god.
What are the changes?
Oh, here.
There's... I see it.
I see the change right now.
Oh my god.
Okay, there's a little...
There's a little dent in here too.
Holy shit.
Okay.
Alright.
At least...
You know what?
Alright.
There we go.
Oh my god.
You know how like when you wear headphones, there's like a little... like the gamer dent?
Yeah, like I wear the headphones the wrong way.
Oh no.
Oh my god.
It's so bad here.
Okay.
Alright.
Let's see.
The tempo...
Oh no.
No!
Okay.
We should not do that actually.
Alright.
Tempo size.
Okay.
Yes.
The smaller...
We gotta minimize the...
The hitbox as much as we can, guys.
As much as we can.
Okay.
Alright.
There we go.
Uh...
Ooh.
She's mewing.
Okay.
I should like that.
Yeah.
Alright.
Successful mewing right there.
What the fuck is mewing?
It's...
Yeah.
For...
Like it looks maxing.
Okay.
For those who don't know, it's basically the newest term that Gen Z has.
Has invented.
It's...
It's like...
You know how like the Sigma male with the cheekbones like that?
So apparently there's a new fad right now for Gen Z where they're like, we gotta like...
We gotta like...
Yeah.
We gotta have like the cheekbones.
And that's what they call it.
They call it like mewing.
I don't...
I don't know why it's called mewing.
I'm just being hip with the times, you know?
I'm just relating to the children, to the kids.
Or is it Gen Alpha?
They sort of... oh, Gen... I like how the Gen Z people are like, we don't claim this, we're not that cringe.
And I'm like, oh you poor...
Gen Z...
You were already cringe.
You might as well own it.
Let's see, cheek angle.
Okay, we gotta put it here.
Oh my god, the fucking...
Okay, the chin.
Okay, let's see.
Alright, we gotta have small chin and then no chin.
Oh, maybe like thicken up the chin a little bit.
And then...
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
We can keep that here.
Oh, jawline.
Jawline.
I don't... okay, let's see.
Yes.
Oh my god.
Wait.
Wait, actually, maybe not as big.
Okay, and then...
Oh!
Yes!
The butt!
Chin!
Yes!
Oh my god.
You have the butt chin!
The fucking butt chin right there.
Okay, and then...
I think that's good.
Oh no, I want more of the butt showing popping out.
Oh my god the Peter Griffin.
I'm making Peter Griffin.
Alright, jaw.
The mewing!
It's...
Guys!
We're actually getting there!
Okay.
I think... like here.
Alright, there we go.
Oh my god, wait, that's okay Thanos, you're right.
Okay, now, okay, we don't have to care, but honestly, like...
Eyebrows is like fine with me.
Unless... oh, I'm always like, huh?
I'm always like, always surprised.
And then... okay, we got dented a little bit more.
Eyebrow foot... eyebrow tail?
Oh, this part.
Okay, yeah, I don't... I'm not...
The biggest eyes possible!
Actually, the smallest eyes possible.
Actually, never mind.
This is a lot better.
I actually like that a lot.
I'm...
Alright.
Ooh, big nostrils.
I want huge nostrils so I can smell them better.
Nostril...
Okay, I want to be able to smell better.
So I can smell my enemies.
Nose...
Oh wait, can I extend the neck?
No, I can't.
Alright.
What do you see with your tiny eyes?
What do you...
Okay, wait, I should...
Wait, I like that.
Okay.
Wait, I...
Okay, I actually think the...
The pigtails... the...
Looks so good.
It looks... Okay, wait.
Let me double check.
I think the pigtails is actually perfect for this.
I think it's...
It's actually really, really good.
Okay, let me double check.
Let me make sure if the pigtails is what I want in the end.
All I'm saying is that I think the pigtails...
I think the pigtails is perfect for this.
Um...
It does hide the dents though.
The gamer dents a lot.
So it's like I worked really hard for that.
But like it's okay.
It's alright.
I think it's actually really good.
I think it's really good.
Okay.
Um...
Alright.
Okay, body.
Short so...
Alright, so we have like...
Uh...
This... Oh... Okay.
We gotta be like a little hobbit if possible.
The smaller...
Oh!
Nice.
Okay.
Maybe like...
Yeah, there we go.
There we... Oh.
Small hitbox!
Small head!
Okay.
Smaller head, smaller head hitbox.
Alright, waist.
I think we don't have to care about that.
I'm pretty sure.
Wait, chest size.
Oh!
Okay.
Ha!
Wait, what does it look like?
Oh my God!
Like the upper body!
Holy shit!
The only hitbox!
That...
Okay.
Um...
Alright.
Let's see.
Arms and...
Okay, what about like if I make like everything else like super...
Alright.
Alright, there you go.
Ooh, okay.
Yeah, the tall waist length.
And then... arms and legs.
Oh, wait, where's the legs?
There we go.
Holy shit, what did I create there?
No, it should be like... this is like the only boosted part of it.
Of everything.
The body should not be able to hold this.
Okay, there we go.
Alright, nice.
That's actually good.
That's good.
I think we're looking good.
We're looking good here.
Body paint.
Okay, no.
No, absolutely not.
We're not having body...
We're not having a random fucking hand there.
Like, what?
Why is there a hand on there?
Alright.
Uhhh...
I think we're good.
I think we're really...
I think we're looking really good, guys.
Alright, name character.
Uhhh...
Oh, wait, is this like staring?
Hair tied?
Oh, wait, what?
Oh, hair tied, hair down.
Wait, what?
Why is this hair down?
Staring, look around?
What does that mean?
Alright.
Okay, let's see.
Name character.
Yes.
This is gonna be my character.
Alright.
You will be named...
Your name will be...
Peak Dragoon.
Okay.
That's...
That's you guys, Dragoons!
We don't claim her.
Alright.
Okay, how about this?
Alright, instead of that, alright.
We will do...
Um...
Once a Dragoon.
Alright.
There we go.
That's gonna be your name.
Once Dragoon.
Uh...
Alright.
Enter game.
What do you see?
That's us!
You guys are goon maxing.
Dagger still stuck in the sheath.
Inspection 481 complete.
I wonder what Tenjin made.
Whoa!
We have magic powers!
What the fuck are we doing?
Dragoon, what are you guys doing?
Huh?
Why are shoulders so wide?
It has to carry the assets!
What do you mean?
How else do you carry those assets?
Oh.
What the fuck?
What's that in you guys?
What?
Okay, remember.
I'm gonna move.
Wait, I haven't...
Oh!
Oh, it stopped!
Okay.
I'm sorry.
The legs definitely do not match the rest of the body.
Use deactivate it.
You're so beautiful, guys.
I'm not coping!
This is you guys!
Not me!
I'm not...
Okay, I'm sorry.
Your body...
Okay.
All right.
Let's grab the...
Let's clean you all real fast.
All right.
What is this?
No.
It is an adult human.
Okay.
All right.
We don't care about these guys.
I finished the tutorial.
This is...
All right.
So, access code for chrono cage.
Update the code after completing today's experiment.
Okay.
This is the code.
Uh...
You guys are...
Dorito...
Yeah.
You guys are.
All right.
You won't last long if consumed food and drink to increase your energy and hydration.
Oh, no.
Is this a survival?
Open your backpack to check your inventory.
Okay.
Uh...
Most of the ingredients and details are in the bag.
Dishes have a durability which gradually decays over time.
Once the durability reaches zero, the food...
Oh, okay.
This is a little fast.
This is a little fast for me.
Okay, we gotta eat.
And then we gotta drink.
Alright.
Okay, I'm fully hydrated now.
Okay.
Is there anybody in here?
No, it's just me.
Okay, mouse4 is melee.
Okay, melee, roar...
Oh, and then there's flashlights.
World unlocks when the Eye of Evolution is completed?
Alright, what's this?
Input password.
Oh shit!
I read it but I didn't read it.
Give me a sec.
Let me read the memo again.
Okay.
Uh...
Is it 0728?
Okay, 0728.
I got it.
0728.
Yay!
I can read!
Yippee!
Oh hey, there's a dead guy.
Hello?
Wait, did I kill him too?
An intact critter was recovered?
With those used.
Any store within the Cradle shows unused signs of activity.
Uh...
Has been placed in a separate room for safekeeping.
Am I the Cradle?
Where's this the Cradle?
Find the access...
No, okay, no.
We have to find the access card.
Okay.
Who killed these guys?
Did I kill them?
Did I kill these people?
Will me?
But I'm so innocent.
Look at me.
Wait, is there...
I'm just wondering if there's certain, like, physics.
No.
Okay.
I was just curious.
Oh shit!
Okay.
Oops.
Sorry.
Did I break my leg?
Wait, you can break your leg?
It's okay, I'm fine.
My shins are like a little bit rickety.
My shins are just a little rickety right now.
Oh, what's this?
Med kit.
Okay, we gotta get all the meds.
Uh...
Item crate.
Food.
Boiled water.
Just water?
Where's like the tea or soda?
Deviation of unknown level detected in the research area.
Deviation appears to consist of multiple floating butterflies.
Floating butterflies?
I don't know what that means.
There's like floating butterflies in everything.
Oh!
What's that?
How's the game sound so far?
I don't know where to go.
How can I already be lost?
There's like nothing here.
Like...
Okay.
Uh...
What's that sound?
Um...
Do I have to go downstairs?
I don't know.
Find the access card.
Where is the access card?
Go to the waypoint.
Did I get the access card already?
Oh no!
My foot!
It's okay.
Just a little...
I just twisted my ankle a little bit.
How can I like the peak human being?
If I get like a twisted ankle?
I don't know.
There's fall damage?
This is bullshit.
Why is there fall damage in my video game?
Okay.
I'm
once human!
I should not have fall damage.
Wait, that's also me.
Oh my god.
Is this like Death Stranding?
Where I have a baby in the backpack?
Oh!
Crow?
What's this crow doing here?
Crow.
Talk to the strange bird.
Who are you?
I'm a metahuman?
What do you call...
You know, what do you call me?
A metahuman?
Why am I?
You don't remember.
Do you remember who you are?
Hello?
You already finished the tutorial?
I'm...
I'm making my base.
You're what?
I'm making...
I just met the bird.
You just met the bird.
I'm making a base.
What?
There's a beast?
Spoiler alert!
I'm making a base.
Don't worry about it.
I'm making it.
How far am I?
How far am I from the beast?
From the crow to the beast?
Um...
Not that far actually.
Oh, not that far.
Okay, okay.
That's good.
Okay.
I'll catch you on the other side soon.
Don't worry.
I'll be making some base.
Trust me.
Okay.
Once you got here, I will have a home.
You'll have a home?
I am not homeless.
I won't be homeless.
There's a base?
I thought this was...
I got game instances and thought it was just like an extraction shooter or something.
That's your bot?
I don't know.
I'm... I'm...
There's a home building?
Yeah, I'm making a base.
I was laughing the whole time.
Oh, I thought you said beast.
I thought you said like...
There's like a fucking companion.
No, I'm making a base.
Oh my god.
Okay, at least...
I'm gonna mooch off your house then.
Oh yeah, sure.
I'll just find where you live.
Alright.
I'll be there soon.
I'll be right back.
I'm still talking to the crow.
Okay, okay.
Oh my god.
He already has a house?
Wait, what happened?
I already forgot what he talked to me about.
It trapped me in the cradle.
It could have robbed you of your memories.
Oh, we used to be best friends!
Me and the crow.
You can call me V.
It seems that our interests are aligned, MetaHuman.
Wait, but you're a talking bird.
What are you talking about?
You're a talking bird.
I used to be like you once.
A MetaHuman.
When we die, we become crows?
But it's a long story.
And now is not the time.
No, I have lots of time!
What do you mean?
Just tell me now!
Alright.
I came to secure a deviation.
A paper butterfly.
But I think something must have scared it.
Deviation?
Right now, though, we need to move.
There's so much lore for a game that might die in a month.
But only if you help me complete my mission first.
Alright.
All you have to do is listen to what I tell you.
Okay.
I'll be right here in the cradle.
Now, let's go.
Alright, here we go.
Whoa!
Oh, this is the cradle!
Okay.
Uhh...
We have to explore this press Q to use space time to search for items.
Oh my god!
You just snapped your fingers!
Hahaha!
I have a machete now.
Oh my god!
Just snap your fingers!
Wait, what the fuck?
What the fuck is that?
Deviant has water?
Oh, so that's what the humans turn into.
Okay, give me that gear.
Oh my god, I get a hat!
Oh my god!
Nice hat!
Hahaha!
Same hat!
Snap.
Oh, there's stuff here.
Wait, there's actual stuff here.
I'll just go in here.
I'm just snapping for fun.
Wait, where the fuck did you come from?
Holy shit!
Get out of here!
This is a tutorial!
Alright, let's see.
What's in here?
Oh, a Molotov.
Snap.
Okay, the snapping is a little addicting.
Hahaha!
Whoa!
Okay, there he is.
Ha!
That's fucking right!
You're in the wrong neighborhood!
Okay, let's grab this real fast.
Uh...
Oh!
I got shoes now!
Guys!
I got shoes!
After image?
Woman.
Oh?
Where did...
Where did female take me?
Oh, okay.
Let me raise up the volume a little.
Oh my god.
What the fuck?
What are all these?
Where are these extra...
Wait, self-destruct?
What are these extra settings?
Alright.
Let's see.
I'll turn down the sound effects.
And then I'll turn up the game.
Okay.
Let's see.
Yeah, alright.
Game has been turned up.
Hahaha!
Oh.
Spiritual often cause anomalies in time.
A loud pass seems to be witnessed once again.
Activate space-time to locate...
Spatial Theors.
Where events and people from the past may reappear and potentially reveal a hidden truth.
Reappear and potentially reveal a hidden truth.
Snap!
Whoa!
Is this me?
Oh no.
This is the girl we had to find.
Yes, you killed her.
Yeah, that's right.
It is your fault.
Try and stay calm.
Yeah, you killed them all and you're gonna live with that guilt forever.
Oh shit, I'm a bit thirsty.
Not because of women.
It would be better for everyone if I just...
Just what?
Leave me alone.
Please.
Don't waste your time.
No, but this is the military.
We have to use you.
And you're not a monster.
In fact, you're very, very special.
That's right.
You need to learn how to control your power.
Once you do that, you can help fix this broken world.
We can do that together.
Yay!
Okay, we gotta drink water.
I can summon V?
Hey there!
Leave.
Okay, goodbye.
Never mind!
I thought he would want to talk to me.
I guess not.
Okay.
Let's see.
Snap!
Oh, that's a butterfly!
Oh, you can create butterflies?
That seems pretty useless.
Hey, I know like...
Tengen is waiting for me, but I'm gonna loot a bit.
I know he's like waiting for me after finishing the tutorial.
I don't know, maybe a couple minutes ago.
I'm still in the beginning.
But like, this is more important.
Whoa, she can fly!
And I think I finally found it.
You.
Hey, we can secure other new missions.
You're special!
We can use them to forge a new path.
And bring about true evolution.
This will be the Mayfly's mission.
I'm gonna go to the other side.
This is why we'll fight.
Mayflies?
That's right.
Mayflies.
Small, yet invincible.
Humanity may seem puny now.
But we'll prove we can endure.
Oh!
Okay, let's loot this crate.
There's so much lore.
Wait, where do I go from here?
Snap!
Did I loot all this?
No, I did.
Snap!
Where's the door?
Oh, there's the door!
Okay.
Snap.
Oh, shit!
Get over here.
Oh my god!
What the fuck?
Okay, the monster designs are pretty interesting.
Like, I would admit.
Alright.
Nice!
Now I have gloves!
Where do I get down from here?
Am I gonna break my legs again?
Is there like an easier way to get down?
I'm gonna break my legs.
Okay.
This guy right here.
Oh shit!
Okay.
Legs slightly injured.
It's okay.
I can get better.
Alright.
Not really a huge threat yet.
To be fair.
Like, I feel like I'm faster than them.
It's the hitbox.
Oh!
I can throw?
Oh shit!
Wait, what?
What the fuck?
Okay, approach and attempt to capture it.
Oh shit.
Uh, how do I throw this thing?
How do I throw this away?
How do I?
Oh, discard!
Okay.
Wait, that's so cool!
I can have like, I can use their like heads to fight for me.
What's this?
Wait.
Touch.
Wait, but what about my- No!
My gun!
Whoa!
I love it when my cutscenes are five five.
Frames per second.
Hahaha!
Wait, that's it?
Wait, I'm- Wait, no!
My gun!
Wait, I'm at like- You have left Victor's territory.
Wait, I'm at a house now!
What is this?
Like, The original Fortnite?
Like, what?
Whose house is this?
Wait, there's like- What is- Wait, what?
Is this like a horde?
Is there gonna be a horde mode?
Is this seven days to die?
Like...
Oh, hello.
Isolated securement unit.
Oh, no.
No, it's mine.
I'm not giving you it.
I'm not gonna give you this.
Yeah!
This is a meta.
Only just woken up.
They were kind enough to activate the cradle.
Oh, my gosh.
I still don't have pants.
So weird.
Shoes, gloves and...
Shoes, gloves and hat, but no pants.
Still...
Thank you, Meta-Human.
Your help means a lot to me.
You can call me Mitsuko.
I used to be a Meta-human as well.
Rosetta did all kinds of experiments on me.
Wait, used to?
Until V saved me.
What happened after?
You still look... You're not Qrow yet.
Wait.
Are we all Rosetta's experiments?
You still look like a human.
Sengen, you're covering...
No, Sengen covered it up for you guys.
The mayflies?
What?
What the fuck is going on?
Oh, these are the...
The ones that we had to kill.
Okay.
Yeah, this is like Lord Dumping time.
So we have to give them the butterfly.
I worked so hard!
Alright.
Butterfly time.
Deviant power.
Owner.
That's us!
Once Dragoon!
Deviant power.
Owner.
That's us!
Once Dragoon!
Get the mayflies.
We make cradles and securement units to keep deviations contained.
We're finding ways for humans and deviations to live in harmony.
This is our best chance of cleaning up Rosetta's mess.
So what exactly are deviations?
No one's exactly sure what they are.
Just that they're not bound by the physical laws of our world.
They came from another dimension.
Don't worry, gamer.
If our game survives another month, we'll tell you what they actually are.
They're just stardust.
We can put this entire world and Rift space closer together.
Sometimes it becomes possible to pass between the two planes of existence.
And when that happens, all hell breaks loose.
We believe that's what caused Starfall.
So what exactly are you trying to do?
Some deviations are friendly, like the butterfly.
But others, like the ones inside Monoliths, are extremely dangerous.
It's not practical to secure all of them.
But if we can learn more about them...
Maybe we can find ways to live alongside them.
That's the goal.
You must be prepared.
The stardust just keeps spreading.
And we aren't sure why.
Oh, they're coming!
We're here for the butterflies!
Horde mode time!
Be careful.
That must be a siren.
A siren?
They must have gotten through.
Come on, Meta.
A deviation from another world just entered this space.
And it won't go down without a fight.
Take the butterfly with you.
It can help.
Oh, God.
Okay.
I'm gonna take it.
How do I do this?
Uhhhh...
Withdraw.
Alright, it's in my pocket now.
Alright, no more weapons.
Ooh!
Okay, now we have a jacket.
Armor.
We have armor now.
Where is it?
Where the fuck... Where's my armor?
Is it this?
Oh, there we go.
Alright, we put our armor on.
I know, I know, guys.
We're gonna put...
I know, I know.
You might not want... Oh my God.
Jesus Christ.
We still have no pants?
Okay.
Alright.
Don't need no armor.
Alright, is this pants?
Am I finally gonna get pants here?
Is this it?
Oh no, it's fabric.
Apparently not.
It's still not pants time, apparently.
Oh shit.
Somebody...
Somebody's diary.
Who cares?
Alright, let's see.
Are there any pants here?
I'm just wondering if there's any pants at all.
Oh, there's med kit though.
Uhhhh... Alright.
I already took the thing.
Uhhh... Synchroize... Synchroize... Attach wire.
Building features locked.
Wait, what?
I took the butterfly.
Uhhhh...
Wait, what am I supposed to do?
Interact... Unit to view details.
Oh, I have to view it!
How do I view... Oh, okay.
Base stat, it's auto attack.
Synchroize the cradle.
Combat deviations are a special type of deviation.
While aggressive, it will take instructions.
Uh, different... Oh!
The dormancy threshold of a combat deviation cannot be adjusted and defaults to 100.
After synching, you can summon it to attack.
Oh, the butterflies will fight for me!
Oh, I see.
Okay.
Uhhh...
Target attack...
Oh!
So they're like dangerous... They're like dangerous butterflies.
Okay, use green light and mood recovery speed increases.
Okay.
Alright.
Oh, what?
Oh!
Oh, this is what tension means when...
Hahaha!
Alright, guys.
It's Minecraft time!
It's Minecraft!
Guys, it's time for Minecraft.
We gotta cut the trees.
Because we have to cut...
Equip the gathering tool before you start.
It's much faster than doing it all bare hand.
You can craft gathering tools at your campsites or supplies work.
Okay, this is a lot different from what I saw on the trailers.
I'm just gonna say.
This is...
Hahaha!
The more it's fast, the more...
This is not what I expected from the trailers.
Not gonna lie.
Or...
Or time!
Hahaha!
I think I'm playing Ark right now.
Guys, we tricked ourselves into playing Ark again.
Hahaha!
Well, we can't get scammed.
If it's free.
And we...
This is a free game.
Free Ark, guys!
Free Ark!
Alright.
We gotta cut some trees.
And we always come back to Minecraft.
This is free to play Ark, guys.
Free to play Ark.
It's in the description.
You guys know I don't read.
I just watch videos.
The videos I saw of Once Human was like people shooting monsters.
That's like what I saw.
So I was not expecting this.
I saw like...
I guess they like skipped the building part of this game.
So I never noticed.
Hahaha!
Alright.
Alright, let's see.
We need more ores.
Oh my god.
There's so many ores around us.
Alright.
Don't worry.
We're almost there.
Now I know what he's been farming.
Now I know.
Alright.
Here you go.
Let's see.
We're almost there.
Yay!
I just set up a campsite?!
Okay, I'm gonna live next to her.
Alright.
Craft a bear hands and a campsite to craft basic gear, tools, and dishes.
These will help you survive better in the wilderness.
Guys, I don't remember which is the stage where I get to actually interact with real people.
Craft with bear hands?
Okay.
Uh, items including gathering tool and... wait, do I not have pickaxe already?
Okay, yeah.
Shouldn't I have a pickaxe?
Oh, what?
Alright.
Toggle between the tables.
Ooh!
Okay, crossbow... pants!
Alright guys, just for you guys, I won't craft pants.
Uh, do I have a... I have a crossbow ready, right?
Okay, I don't think I do.
I mean, do I?
That's... that's gun.
That's sort of like gun.
Uh...
Alright.
Oh, I need to create arrows.
Uh... there you go.
I don't think I need like more than five.
Alright, nice.
Open survival to view survive... crackdown attacking deviants.
Are they coming over now?
You're a bit thirsty.
Okay, let me...
Collect water.
Alright, collecting the water.
Oh, there's a butterfly!
Do you see it?
So like, instead of a child, there's a butterfly in my backpack.
Alright, let's see.
Uh... I want to...
I wanna...
Wait, how do I boil water?
Oh, there you go.
Boil water.
Nice.
Yay!
And then I gotta drink my water.
Oh my gosh, I have so much water.
Stay hydrated, guys.
Uh, I'm not hungry yet, so we're fine.
Um, yeah, this is like the original Fortnite.
Alright, I'm ready.
Fight.
What was that?
Is this like...
Plants vs.
Zombies 2?
Oh my god, it's like Plants vs.
Zombies!
They're here to attack my butterflies!
It's everything I've ever wanted!
RTX on Plants vs.
Zombies!
It does look like Siren Head, yeah.
Oh shit, what the fuck?
That is a lot bigger than I expected.
Oh no.
Oh no, we're...
Oh no, how do I use it?
How do I use it?
Okay, weapon crate.
Open the weapon!
He's coming over!
Uh...
Where's my arrow?
You have entered...
What do you mean?
Why can't I... Do I not have equipped?
Okay, uh...
Click on... Oh no, that's not what I wanted!
No!
No, I don't want that!
Okay, uh...
Alright, equipped.
Arrow.
Oh, I hope this pauses the game.
Hahaha!
Okay.
170 HP.
Does he have a head?
Am I headshotting?
Am I...
Oh my god.
Auto attack.
Do your thing.
Okay.
Oh shit, the turrets are automatic!
Oh, what the fuck?
My butterflies are so strong!
Bro, why am I wasting my arrows?
Hahaha!
Wait...
I'm just gonna wait.
Hahaha!
It's just standing there, menacingly.
It's so strong, guys!
What was that?
Festering gel?
What did I secure?
The deviation escape?
No!
Alright, let's see.
That was easy.
Oh!
Talk to me.
It escaped.
That was a difficult fight.
Just driving it away was enough.
And it's all thanks to you, man.
Alright, I upped it a little bit.
You're tougher than you look.
That's twice now you're so weak.
Tanya's just waiting for me in the town right now.
Hahaha!
Yes.
Mitsuko created this Rift Space.
A refuge from the dangers of the physical world.
Or somewhere else.
I don't know what we thought.
Do you think that deviation will come back?
What if it returns with greater disruptions?
It's possible.
We can't just sit here and wait though.
Meta, will you go back to the physical world with me?
Alright.
Sure.
Wait, that wasn't even the physical world?
There's...
Oh, I thought...
Oh yeah, this is a deviation world.
That way, I can lend you some of my strength.
Hopefully, we'll meet again one day.
When the Stardust is stable enough.
It looks like this is goodbye.
I'm going to go back to the physical world.
Oh, it's my battle type.
Good luck, Meta.
Goodbye.
You can use any questions.
I could try and answer them for you.
Alright.
Time to leave.
It's time.
We can finally...
Bunny bump into Tangent.
We finally did it!
Hahaha.
Oh my god, I'm dropping down.
Oh my god, Fortnite!
Where am I going?
Where... where... where do I go?
Is this it?
Where's like... where's where people would like hang out?
Like, where do people hang out?
Where are we dropping?
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
Alright, I gotta make sure I don't do that.
Make sure...
Oh no, it's dark!
It's dark and scary!
Find a suitable location and press B here.
Is it a place... a territory terminal?
Wait, maybe he lives here.
Maybe that's where he is.
There's somebody house here.
Who lives here?
Oh, this is glitch's territory.
Okay, that's... I don't think that's...
Okay, forums and defies... okay.
Alright, we gotta meet up with Tenjanelle.
Hello?
Hi!
I'm fine.
You're finally here!
Yeah, I finally made it!
Where are you?
I'm...
Don't worry about it.
What do you mean, don't worry about it?
Which world are you in?
What do you mean?
We're in the same server!
It's an MMO!
There's different worlds and shit!
We chose the same server!
There's in the chat on the number six is a...
Wait, what?
Someone's sniping us.
Ten is in world six?
Where am I?
I'm world five!
How do I get to world six?
You gotta find a... teleportation tower.
Teleportate?
How did you learn so much?
Yeah, the...
What do you mean teleportation?
Yeah, teleportation!
What the fuck is that?
I honestly have no clue.
What the fuck is a teleportation tower?
I wouldn't know, bro.
I wouldn't...
It's right there.
I mean, I'm near one.
How did you learn about the teleportations?
Because I'm near one!
Okay.
How do I open the map?
There is somebody...
Oh, I found it!
I found it!
Okay, okay.
You found it?
I found it.
Okay.
How do I...
How do I pin this?
Okay, track.
Place pin.
Okay.
There is...
There we go.
Alright, I figured it out.
I'm heading there now.
You figured it?
It would have been a lot easier when I was in the sky if I knew that.
Yep, probably.
Oh my god.
There is like some deviance in front of me.
I'm gonna outrun this.
I have a gun.
How did you get a gun already?
What the fuck?
Just to let you know, I have a goddamn gun.
You have a gun?
With no suppressors.
Also like...
Okay, you've seen the trailers for this game before, right?
Yep.
This is not what I expected.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean...
I thought...
I thought everybody was playing this game and I was like, oh, that's cool.
Like, they're shooting monsters.
It was like...
What's that game called?
The other...
The other like Dark Souls-like game that's like for shooting?
What is it called?
The...
It's like shooting Dark Souls.
Rem...
Remnant something?
Yeah, yeah.
I thought it would be like Remnant.
Yeah, me too.
That's what it looked like.
And then I saw like gameplay from others and it looked like Remnant.
So I was like...
I'm like making a house.
I'm crafting.
I like...
I thought it'd be like Remnant.
Oh my god.
We should have played Remnant instead.
We should have...
Okay.
And let's...
I'm heading up to the tower.
I'm heading up.
Oh, we're running.
Oh my god.
Yeah I met some people.
I turned on voice chat just in case.
There's a lot of people that I...
I met actually.
Oh shit, that's a dude.
You met people already?
How did you meet people?
Like what were we doing?
I don't know.
I was just going around and they were like, oh, they were showing me stuff.
Oh shit, they were hearing you?
They were boosting you?
No.
Okay, they were boosting you.
I stayed away from people because I hear them.
Yeah, but you said they were helping you.
No, they're just approaching me.
I don't want to be approached.
Okay, I'm here.
I'm in the...
I'm in world six.
Where are you?
Are you at the...
I'm at the teleportation tower.
I'm at 6940.
69405041.
What?
695041.
Okay, just follow the road.
Holy shit.
What the fuck is this map?
Did you scroll back from the map?
Yeah.
What the fuck?
There's like some fucking places.
There's like level 30, like the level 32 zone.
Do you have...
Okay, I have a question.
Do you have pants?
No, I didn't.
I don't have pants.
Okay, like I could have wore pants, but for the dragoons, I did not wear pants.
Oh, I didn't.
I don't care.
There was a way you can like... you can make pants, but I decided not to make pants.
I did not have pants.
All right.
Wait, where are you?
What do you mean follow the road?
There's so many roads.
Wait, where are you?
I'm here.
I'm at the teleportation tower.
No, you're not.
World six.
I'm at world six too.
Is that you?
There's multiple...
That's you, I see.
Where are you?
Oh, there you are.
You're so lucky there's no PVP.
What the fuck?
What do we do with this game?
I honestly have no clue.
I don't know.
Trade.
Add friends.
Oh shit, yes.
Okay.
Hey, this is free.
Invite the team?
Yes.
No, no way.
Is it the other way around?
How come you have your butterflies?
We're mop...
My butterfly is...
I think my butterfly died.
I think my butterfly...
What the fuck happened to my butterfly?
Where's your butterfly?
Where did my butterfly go?
He died!
I wouldn't even know where your butterfly is.
There's no air holes.
Oh shit.
Is it the other way around?
I think you should...
You should...
All right, wait.
Why aren't you fighting?
No, it's okay.
You use your butterfly to fight.
Okay, no.
You know what?
Transfer leadership.
No, I don't want to be leader.
What?
How did you do that?
I don't know.
My butterfly is still dead!
It doesn't do anything!
What?
My butterfly is still dead!
Oh no, what happened to him?
Make a base.
Wait, we're going to make a base?
Okay.
What are we going to do?
All right, you fight that guy.
Did I just headbutt him?
Yeah, you did.
I'm going to loot your shit.
All right.
Rest in peace butterfly.
Rest in peace.
You're not head...
That's my base.
Welcome...
Wait, is that your base?
I'm...
I'm trying to find my...
Is that your base over there?
What the fuck?
This is my base.
Give me a sec, I need to beat this guy up.
I don't want to waste my arrow.
Is this their base?
Oh my god.
Yeah, yeah, this is my base.
What even... Oh, you have entered Tenjin's territory.
Oh, it's because you have your... I didn't put my thing.
I didn't put my terminal.
Oh shit!
The fuck?
What?
Oh, that guy shot you.
Oh, I can't build it here because you own that area.
Okay, this is my base too.
This is my area.
Okay.
You're building it there?
Yeah.
Holy shit.
You're just building it there.
But seriously, making a base is not what I expected in this game.
Me too.
I told you, it's Ark.
It's free to play Ark.
Oh my god.
Hello neighbor.
Hi.
Hey.
You got your butterfly?
I need to get my butterfly.
Okay, use facility.
Yeah, okay, my butterfly is here now.
Yeah, there's my butterfly.
There he is.
Okay, tab to open the function window and select Creole to enter the metric screen.
Open the... What the fuck?
There's so much information in this game.
I'll be honest.
Oh, you can like upgrade info... What the fuck?
Yeah, yeah.
There's like... What?
Yeah, there's some stuffs that...
What?
There's stoves?
What the fuck am I looking at?
Rainwater.
Might as well.
Let's grab rainwater.
I need that water.
It's important.
What the fuck?
Oh my god.
This is...
This is definitely not what I expected.
Me neither.
I don't... Defense?
No, this is like 7 days to die plus arc.
Because there's like defense stuff against the deviant slash zombies.
The copyright free zombies.
Zombies.
Hell yeah.
They're smelting?
Oh my god, I'm getting overwhelmed here.
I'm actually...
Yeah, there's so much.
This is a lot more than I expected.
Yeah.
How much more do I have?
I bought ammunition.
Okay.
Alright, I used up everything.
Uh...
Okay.
I used up all my upgrade stuff.
I did it.
And unlocked the disassembly bench.
Oh shit, I did not unlock...
I did not unlock the thing that they want me to lock.
Oh shit, there's the disassembly.
Well, I have a disassembly bench.
Yeah, they're like...
Make sure to unlock the disassembly bench.
And I was like... No.
Nah.
Okay.
I don't want this.
Alright, there you go.
Territory upgrades?
I can have more territory than this.
I think you gotta grab one?
Territory expansion.
What the fuck?
What is even happening?
I want boots.
Okay.
Uh...
Facilities.
Disassembly bench.
Okay.
Oh, I don't have gravel.
Wait.
Where the fuck is gravel?
It's in the rock.
It's in the rock?
Okay.
Take me there.
What?
I don't even know.
Where is it?
These rocks?
The bigger ones?
Yeah.
Oh, these.
When did we fucking kill them?
.
That's what I like to know.
When do we get to shoot shoots?
When do we shoot things?
When are we fighting some bosses and do shit, you know?
What the fuck?
I thought we were gonna fight bosses.
I thought this was gonna be remnant.
Bro.
So it's like, it's Palworld all over again.
Oh my god.
You can never escape from Palworld.
I need copper.
They're forcing me to build a tower.
Wait, I can share my stuff.
Wait, we can share.
You can share?
Yeah.
What do you need?
Oh, we can share stuff.
So if you have stuff, you can share it to me.
Oh my god.
It's Palworld without the pals.
Guys, we can't just suddenly switch to remnant.
Tenjin has to download something for two plus hours.
This was free.
Yeah.
At least this was free.
Oh wait, there is copper.
There's a lot of coppers.
Yeah, there's so much coffee here.
Where the fuck are the people?
You don't want...
You don't want to talk to the people.
You don't want to talk...
I just want handouts.
You just want handouts.
Any snipers in the server, we're willing to give their stuff.
We'll take a gun.
We'll take a gun or two.
Yeah, yeah.
We just want handouts.
That's all we want.
So we can go straight to the bosses.
Just boom, boom, boom.
We just want to have the boss fight.
This is the only reason.
Okay.
Alright, disassembly.
You got the stuff.
How the fuck...
Wait, I need copper ingots?
What the fuck?
I need to make ingots?
You smith it?
Yeah.
I have a furnace if you want to use it.
Yeah, I'm going to use your furnace.
Can I use your furnace?
I don't want to waste my...
I think you can.
Wait, what the fuck?
Oh, I can!
Oh my god!
Wait, how do I put my ingots?
This game is stupid.
You have a chest already.
What the fuck?
Wait, how do I...
I told you I was making a base and I'm not even lying.
Wait, how do I put my ingots in your inventory?
I can't do it.
Wait, what is this?
Why do you have two furnaces?
Because you can only smelt one item at a time.
Wait, I need the...
You need a charcoal, I think.
I need charcoal?
How the fuck?
Put charcoal in it right now.
What the fuck?
Well, I dropped...
Oh, I only have one charcoal.
Yeah.
Put it so I can start crafting.
There, I'll just... 20 seconds.
20 seconds?
No, I don't see it.
Is it because I have to use my own?
This is bullshit.
This is...
You know, I was tempted to craft a fishing rod.
A fishing rod?
Yeah, might as well just fish in this fucking...
I don't know.
Maybe I'll craft a fishing rod.
Just for old times' sake.
How do I...
Alright.
Let's see.
Oh my god, I don't even have it unlocked!
It never told me to unlock the furnace!
Ah!
Wait, how do I...
How do I share this with you?
I need to unlock a furnace.
I actually needed the furnace.
Okay.
I need to reset this.
Smithing.
Did you get this from the chest?
Alright.
Oh yeah, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna build...
I'm gonna build a furnace now.
Uh... where the fuck is the furnace?
Where is it?
I thought I bought... oh there it is.
Alright.
Oh, thank god.
Okay.
Oh yeah, okay, I got it.
Yeah, you need... it needed to...
Uh...
Like, I need... I can't use yours.
I have to use my own.
Wasabi wants to... who the fuck is Wasabi?
Is Wasabi gonna fucking boost us?
I don't know.
Probably.
You know what?
Fuck it, Wasabi.
Get in here.
You're level 10.
How do I get glass?
Wait, we have to fucking...
You're like ahead of me, so you're like...
We need glass now.
I'm like, what do you mean we need glass?
Don't worry about it.
What do you mean we need glass?
I need glass.
What do we need glass for?
You might not need it yet.
I need glass.
Oh no.
Okay.
I need to make 10...
copper ingots?
Oh my god.
Okay.
Let's keep crafting.
Just keep crafting.
You have nothing to worry about.
Keep doing it.
I was just spamming once.
And I realized I could just craft all.
Okay.
Give me...
Alright.
And I can craft more.
Oh my god.
Alright.
Wasabi wanted to join our team.
And then Wasabi...
Wasabi left us.
That's funny.
No one wants to be...
on our team.
I don't understand.
We just want to get carried.
We just want...
We just want handouts.
We need to make a guild.
Is that too much to ask for?
Customer support.
We just...
We just want handouts.
Yeah.
We don't want much in life.
Just handouts.
To share a base, it needs to be in the same guild.
How do you make a guild?
Oh!
Okay.
You make the guild.
You learn how to make a guild.
I'm gonna go fucking loot shit.
I wanna loot shit.
No!
What?
You learn how to make a guild right now.
How am I supposed to make a guild?
It's okay.
We have number six.
Who's number six?
Number six is gonna...
Number six was the guy that was like...
You're at the wrong world, Doki!
Number six is gonna...
Oh shit!
Give us handouts!
He want handouts or not!
I definitely do want a handout.
Exactly!
Number six is the chosen one.
Number six.
Number six!
Give us handouts!
I love this.
Alright, let's see.
My crafting?
Chat.
Able.
Able help me.
Alright.
Am I good to go?
Okay, I can finally build a disassembly thing.
Alright.
Hell yeah.
Is that a deer?
Die!
You're gonna kill a deer?
What do you need deer for?
We have enough food.
Wait!
We have number six to give us handouts!
Bro, I noob still.
Bro, AF.
But I'll work hard.
But well, at least show us some effort.
I'm sure I build a disassembly.
I'm sure you did.
Okay, let's see.
Uh...
I need to build disassembly.
Oh my god.
I'm always so confused when I'm building.
I have no idea what this is even for.
Building in these kinds of games gets me overwhelmed sometimes.
Yeah, no, there's so much stuff.
Yeah.
Like I unlock one stuff and then there's another better option.
I was like, ah.
Wait, disassembly scrap at...
Wait, this is like...
This is...
This is Rust.
Wait a minute.
Wait, this is Rust.
You're not wrong for that.
This disassembly thing is Rust.
But honestly, I've never played Rust.
Oh my god.
This is...
So I wouldn't know.
This is everything!
Oh shit, I get to claim rewards though.
Yeah!
The people in chat was like, it's been Rust this entire time.
It's been Rust this entire time.
Maybe Rust was us all along.
It was us all along.
Okay, how do we make a guild?
Guys, we want to make a guild.
Press U, go to guild.
Oh.
Wait.
A hive.
There we go.
Create hive.
That's what it's called?
Hive?
Yeah, what do you want?
What's the name?
Dragoon.
Give us handouts.
Oh, free handouts.
Name it Dragoons.
Free handouts.
Dragoon employers.
Shit, what's a good name?
Give me a good name, guys.
Dragoon Incorporated.
Dragoon Inc.
Help.
We're striving.
Join our guild.
Dragoon Inc.
Please.
Is it free?
Please tell me it's free.
It's free!
Tell your recruit member.
Yeah!
Recruit me.
I want to join Dragoon.
Dragoon Inc.
Oh shit.
Join Dragoon Inc.
today!
So you can provide us guns.
And we can fight a boss instantly.
How do I invite you to the guild?
Oh, fucking no.
Jesus.
Maybe you have to search it?
Wait, how do you find the guild?
Press U and then there's like a hive.
Uh huh.
Oh, find hive.
Okay.
Yeah, Dragoon.
Okay, let's see.
There is a lot.
Dragoon.
I like how there's like one that's like no game.
There's no Dragoon.
Dragoon.
There's Ethan and Jake.
We should have joined...
Who the hell is Ethan and Jake?
I don't know.
But there's a hive called Ethan and Jake.
Wait, I wanna join Ethan and...
But who the fuck is Ethan and Jake?
I wanna apply to Ethan and Jake's hive.
Why did you apply to Ethan?
I did it, but I like Ethan and Jake.
Invite to the hive.
There we go.
I sent you an application.
He sent me an application.
But Ethan and Jake!
Jake!
Ethan and Jake look so cool!
It's not fair!
I'm gonna transfer you to leadership.
No, stop transferring me to leadership!
Because it's not my ship!
It's your name and the company!
I wanted to join Ethan and Jake!
What?
Ethan and Jake...
looked like they were having fun.
Wait, what?
There's flight mode.
There's flight mode?
Okay, what do we do now that we have a guild?
I honestly don't know.
Wait, what?
You're the one that suggested the guild!
My chat says to get the guild...
Verse number 6!
Wait, number 6 has like...
a cool shirt and underwear!
Does number 6 even know what he's doing?
I don't know actually.
Hive review.
There's no Hive history.
Our Hive fucking sucks.
We're just here!
I bet Ethan and Jake...
make this place cooler.
Dispermissive.
We're just here!
Where is it?
We should join Ethan and Jake.
Come on, let's apply it to their guild!
Let's do it!
Apply to the guild!
Apply to Ethan and Jake's guild!
It'll be so fun!
Maybe Ethan and Jake will carry us.
I can't even report?
Wait, what do you mean?
I can report my own guild.
That's funny.
I made the guild and I can report it myself.
That's so stupid.
Oh shit.
Let's see...
Yeah, I can report it.
I can just leave your guild.
Just leave it.
What the fuck is Warband?
Oh, that's like the guild leadership...
Oh, they're like the guild...
rankings.
Yeah, the leaderboards.
Oh my fucking god.
Oh my god.
I hope Ethan and Jake are having a good time.
I hope.
Alright, let's figure out our first mission.
Let's figure out our first mission.
Go to the Monolith Ruin to search for supplies.
Did you go there yet?
I went there, yeah.
You already did that mission?
I did that, but I have not done the next one.
What's the next one?
Okay, I have to do it.
Where is it?
Where's the Monolith Ruin?
You come with me!
What do you mean?
Yeah, alright.
This is a collab!
Yeah, I'll follow you.
I don't even know where the fucking place is anymore.
What do you mean?
Oh hey, there's number 6.
Number 6?
There's number 6.
That's the guy that's in our guild.
No, who's this?
That's the guy that was like...
That's the guy that was...
Yeah, that's number 6.
What do you mean?
There's nobody there.
What the heck?
I'm scared.
There's no friend in...
There's nobody there.
Yo, what the fuck?
What did you see?
I don't know, bro.
I have no clue.
I'm gonna raise the volume a little bit more.
Let's see...
Alright.
Yeah!
Wait, how did you do that?
I have a whole emote list.
What's the list?
Shit, where is it?
What button is that?
Shit...
Probably in the same menu as the memetics.
Okay, I need to go to...
What the fuck is so far?
Is it this?
It's not.
There's fast travel.
There is?
How did you fast travel?
Where is it?
Yeah, you can fast travel to the base, but I'm not sure of going there.
Wait, where the fuck is the fast travel?
Teleport.
I know, but where?
Which one did you teleport?
Not the mission, but I can teleport to the home.
Oh, you go there and then you teleport back.
Is that what you mean?
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
Well, I still have to go there.
Yeah, let's go lead the way.
Alright, it's this way.
You can glide.
Yeah, that's what I'm gonna do.
I think I find...
I'm pretty sure.
Alright, it's this way.
I'm trying to figure out the movement.
Yay!
And you're actually challenged.
No, because the map tracker thing makes it look like it's...
They make you follow the road instead of the shortest way.
Well, well...
You have to follow road safety laws, you know?
Yeah.
And I'm just like, yeah, no.
I do not care.
I just go straight through.
It's not like that you have cars or anything.
I'm assuming there is cars.
Well, there is.
Oh, there's a guy right in front of us!
We should have done PvP.
No.
You're right.
They would have killed us anyway.
They would have 100% killed us.
Alright.
I can't believe it.
There's people in front of us.
Mm-hmm.
Alright, let's... I'm almost there.
I'm so smart with my gliding thing.
Oh my god.
This is rust.
Alright.
Guys.
If you guys want to stream tonight with us, then give us handouts.
Feel free to join our server.
Feel free to join our guild.
Feel free to join the server.
I can't believe this is like an MMO as well.
Yeah.
I was thinking of something else.
Like, no, I was literally thinking of...
Oh shit, a deer.
I thought this was Remnant.
I literally saw the trailer.
And it looked like Remnant.
It literally looked like Remnant.
Well...
Honestly, I can't trust anything nowadays.
Yeah, I can't trust things anymore.
Like, no, I watched the gameplay videos too.
And it was like...
It reminded me of Remnant.
And like the other extraction shooter.
The one with like...
With like monsters.
Was it Ashes?
Whatever it's called.
Ash?
Gosh, I don't know.
I'm trying to remember what it's called.
I haven't really kept up with any games.
Like upcoming stuff.
Because basically, everything has been a disappointment.
Yeah, that's so true.
I played the beta.
It was really good.
Was the beta like this?
Like somebody was like...
I mean, I wouldn't say the game sucks.
Bro, this guy has a motorcycle.
What the fuck?
How long has he been playing this game?
He has a bed!
He's level 9!
Bro, wait, I can use their bed.
I can use their bed.
You're level 2?
Crazy.
Oh my god.
It was always advertised as a survival.
It just...
When I watched the trailer, it didn't seem like a survival game.
It had more combat.
You do your stuff.
You got the thing.
Look for Rosetta supplies.
Oh, we have to look around for more supplies?
Yeah.
I'm gonna start snapping.
You talk to a lady.
And then...
Oh, and then...
Wait, somebody's house has turrets and everything.
Well...
It's Fallout 4.
No, it's Rust.
Another settlement needs your help.
No!
Alright, let's grab this.
I hear you.
Are they good friends?
Are they good people?
I mean, it's 2v2.
Who is it?
Yeah, they can't fight us anyway.
I need to collect 6 discarded items nearby.
Wait, these?
Oh, okay.
Go to the entrance of the monolith.
The fuck?
Oh, it's over here.
Yeah, the...
Mary!
Hello, Mary.
Oh.
Yeah, I don't see your name on it.
Bitch.
You are pretty cocky for someone who doesn't even have a weapon.
Quite impressive, to be honest.
Since you can fast travel, I'm gonna go back to the base for a while, just to give it a little bit of a modification.
Alright.
Oh, this guy's a meta human too!
I'm Mary.
It's a good thing I met you.
Oh, now she's nice to me.
We should be able to help each other out.
I came here to investigate a deviation that's been causing issues.
I think it's connected to a recently reopened monolith nearby.
The deer.
Uh...
I'm chasing deviation as well.
Don't tell me you're going to try and take on a powerful deviation barehanded.
Even an ordinary...
I have a bow!
...divine can tear you apart right now.
Yeah.
I was like, oh no you don't.
You don't have anything.
What do you mean?
I have a bow!
We have a guild!
It's not as good as Ethan and Jake, but like, we have a guild.
Jesus Christ.
Okay.
Oh, wait!
She gave me a gun!
The Huntsman!
So another mayfly survived.
Insufficient permission.
Why?
This is my territory.
Oh.
I can teleport back home now.
How do I not share the existence of Mitsuko?
How do I move the shit?
What are you doing?
How do I move my stuff?
That's my question.
Up into your house.
Um...
A store.
Why do you store it?
You don't want to be a scavenger.
You don't want to be my neighbor?
No.
I want to move it to a better place.
What do you mean?
You chose this area!
The only reason why!
I was following a goddamn tutorial!
The only reason why I lived here was because you lived there.
And now you're gonna disasem- Oh, I see.
I see.
Now that I moved next to you, you're gonna move away.
Nah.
You're saying stuff.
I see!
Unlock the gear workbench.
Why do you wanna move?
I need a flatter surface.
This is flat- Dude, I live next to a cliff!
Dude, I live next to a cliff!
What's wrong with that?
What's wrong with that, damn?
Okay, I need a gear workdrop.
Oh, I got a baseball bat, too!
I have all the materials, guys.
Gear workbench.
Need more copper?
Oh my god!
I need more copper!
Yeah, I love these copper ores!
I miss having handouts.
Not to play the game for real.
The structure cannot be built near a strong- How do I move?
How do I move?
I need to move my shit!
I forgot what it was like to actually play a game for real.
Goddamn.
Back to the mines I go!
Relocate.
Time to actually ride.
Move territory.
I can't.
People enable me.
Oh, I can move territory.
Okay, that's how you move territory.
All right.
Okay, let's see.
Hold up.
Is there any flatter surface in this?
Jeez.
There's a lot of people's homes.
I can't believe you moved away.
Look.
Where the fuck did you move to?
Hold on, hold on.
This is still your territory.
I'm trying to move it.
I'm moving my territory.
No, you're not.
What the fuck?
I need a flatter surface, man.
Everybody claimed everything.
It's just like my Minecraft game.
Minecraft server.
You have a minecraft server.
I logged into my minecraft server and literally everything was claimed even the oceans that were around me.
I have a game.
I'm slowly hiring a moderation team for the minecraft server and one of the mods that we had mods that we hired to do the minecraft server they are crying in the mod chat being like, there's no I don't know where to build my home!
All the dragoons have taken all the land!
And I was like, reading the chat, and I got in the server and I was like, alright, let's find you a home.
And we literally rode the boat for like, hundreds of blocks that were surrounding me.
Like, in the ocean!
In the entire ocean that surrounded the territory, the land was claimed.
We were on the boat for like, an hour just trying to find an unclaimed land.
And then I felt bad and I just like, I was like, okay, you can build on my land.
You can build on my land!
Overlaps with battle unit, what does that even mean?
Are you still trying to find land to claim?
I'm sorry!
I'm literally watching you from here!
I don't get it.
This is crazy.
There's so much prerequisites to like, fucking build a house!
I'm literally still watching you try...
This is the only game where I can have a fucking affordable housing!
I'm literally still watching you try to find a place!
Holy shit!
I'm just gonna watch you!
I'm watching you walk!
Oh my fucking god, it does not auto-build?
God damn!
This is stupid!
Is there...
Is there V?
I summoned V to talk to him.
Wait, I can open the Wikipedia?
What the fuck?
Wait, the crow is like a Battle Pass shop!
The crow is the fucking shop!
Oh my god!
Okay...
He's still there!
He's all the way there, guys!
He's all the way there!
I'm making shit, bro!
I'm making shit!
Are you still... Your house is still here!
You haven't even moved it!
What do you mean?
I have!
Wait, did you move it?
Oh, you did!
Oh shit!
I can't believe it.
I can't believe you moved away.
It's so fucked up.
What?
Okay, build mode.
I need to build a... I'm gonna stay... This is my area now.
I'm not gonna move.
What?
Nah.
You see my home?
I think you'll move.
No, that's fine.
Cause you know we're not gonna play this on day two.
I just wanna have a house.
This is the only time I can have affordable housing.
Houses was...
Not like this.
Alright.
I'm fucking trying to get my copper in.
At least it's free, guys.
It was free.
Okay, nice.
Do I have enough?
I don't know if I haven't...
Okay, let's see.
Alright.
I'm thirsty?
Am I?
Oh shit, I am!
Okay.
Uh...
I'm gonna need to eat and drink in this game.
I forgot about that.
Yeah, I know.
At least like the eating part is not like... You don't have to worry about the eating part a lot.
I feel like.
Uh... Cause like the eating... Your stomach doesn't go down as fast.
Uh...
I'm out of materials?
They said I have enough!
What the fuck?
Who told you that?
Guys, I got a battle pass plus one!
Goddamn you, why?
Why to me?
I don't have enough?
I like how...
I like how whenever you craft something successfully, it gives you a plus battle pass.
I still need two more coppers?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Okay.
Alright, get all ten.
Get in there.
Alright.
What happened to number six?
I don't know.
I don't know where number six is.
He disappeared.
Number six, give me a gun.
That's not...
I don't think number six...
Give me a gun.
Number six.
Alright, let's see.
I'mma chill here.
I need to wait for my copper to... to construct.
When does the multiplayer in this game kick in?
Like I'm...
That's what... That's what I'm curious about.
When does the multiplayer kick in in this game?
Alright.
Got all my crafting...
material.
And then...
Is there a gear workshop?
Okay, finally.
Finally, I have made the gear workshop.
I only took...
Oh my god!
How do I make guns?
Insufficient material?
What kind of material do I need?
What the f...
What the f*** is all this?
Oh my god.
There is like a lot of materials you're supposed to gather to create a f***ing gun apparently.
And build a supplies workshop?
What is a supplies workshop?
What the f***?
I need more copper.
Everything is copper.
Why are you pressing the right button?
Because I'm making my own house.
Okay, never mind.
Number six.
I need... Give me all your copper.
I don't... I don't need guns anymore.
I just want copper.
There's an alligator in front of my house.
There's an alligator?
Kill him for material!
Ow!
Kill him for materials!
Oh f***.
Okay.
I'm gonna...
Cut this tree.
Oh my god, the tree grew back.
Nice.
That's what I needed.
I needed more trees.
Hey, it stopped raining.
I don't understand.
Remember like people were... the mixed reviews.
People were complaining about how there's too many people queuing up for this game.
And I'm like... What?
Just pick different servers.
Come on.
Alright, let's see.
I think this game could be fun if...
There you go.
If it's like with people that... You know, if I made like a Dragoon server, it could be fun as well.
But like...
I have a house.
You should come to my house.
Alright, give me a sec.
I'm crafting right now.
You should... You should... You should...
I got in my chat.
I was like, no it wouldn't.
Stop coping.
Come to my house.
It could be, guys!
Okay, I'm coming over to your house.
I have affordable housing.
Where are you?
Where the fuck do you live now?
Oh, there you are.
I'm not... I'm not...
Guys, I need to figure out some way to get handouts here.
Yep.
Hells yeah.
Alright, here I come.
We haven't found a single person with a car yet.
Wait, where do you live?
Is this your house?
This is my home.
You built that?
I didn't.
It's my house.
It came with a blueprint.
Wait, what the fuck?
Did you build this?
It came with a blueprint.
Did you steal somebody's house or did you literally just build this yourself?
I literally just built this.
How did you get this?
What the fuck?
How did you get the house?
Affordable housing.
Where did you get this?
What do you mean where did I get this?
I got the material.
This is it.
Where did you get the blueprint for this?
There's a blueprint.
It comes with a blueprint.
We have it.
Which blueprint?
What?
Yeah.
Okay, wait.
Wait a minute.
Just press V and then right click.
Okay.
Then it's like on the right, house blueprints and then there's presets for it apparently.
What the fuck?
And then I saw, I was like, I saw exquisite villa and I was like, oh shit.
Oh my god, wait you.
What the fuck?
How do we?
Wait, how do I?
I made this.
This is here.
Wait, what the fuck?
Wait.
What?
Oh my god, you can actually build a house?
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Alright guys, well now I know.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm sorry man.
This is just a madly urge.
This is time.
I need affordable housing.
I can't believe they hid this from us.
I need his free real estate.
Now I need, now I need a house too.
Now you need a house, huh?
Oh man.
Wait, I want the truck house.
How do I get the truck house?
I think you need a truck though.
You need a truck for a truck house?
It doesn't give me a, it doesn't give me the truck.
There's like three different garage.
That's fucked up that the truck isn't included.
I just, yeah.
I can't believe it.
Why is the truck not included?
I don't know.
It should be included.
Water filters, solar generators.
I have the materials.
Honestly, this game seems fun.
But I just, everything is just overwhelmed.
All right.
Well, I know where I want to live.
Where's the permissions?
Prime's permissions.
Access to .
The structure cannot be built near a road?
What do you mean near a road?
Yeah, exactly.
That's why, that's why I'm trying to find some flattery areas.
All right.
That's it.
I'm moving.
It's moving time.
Yeah, I know, right?
I fucking knew it.
You bitch.
That's why I moved as well.
It's so annoying.
You didn't tell me.
You did not give me any context.
No, no, no, no, no.
You said nothing.
It's a surprise.
I made a house.
You said nothing.
Of course, I've been like, I don't want to move.
If I knew, if I knew you couldn't...
How did you, how did you, did you like, did you like, disassemble, demolish everything?
Or like...
I, it's like B and then Z.
B and Z?
B and Z and Z to move territory, you just have to walk over an area.
Oh my God, what the fuck?
Yeah.
Does chat teach you?
Your, more people play, more people on your stream play this game.
Compared to my stream.
Honestly, I don't know.
Yeah, my chat's like, I don't know what to do.
Look, man.
This is Southeast Asia.
We play anything that's free.
I swear.
Okay, let's see.
Relocation has a 10 minute cooldown.
Yeah, that's fine.
I'm fine with that.
Alright, it's time.
Let's see.
Build.
How do I still not be able to build this house?
Yeah, it's annoying, right?
God damn.
Wait, wait, I found it.
Why don't you make the shack?
No, no, no, I found it.
You found it?
I found a place.
What are you building?
I found it.
Are you building a tower house?
Oh no.
Holy shit.
Little John sits in the corner.
I'm building now.
You know, that house reminds me of those...
You know those memes?
Galvanized square beach.
No!
Why can't I build...
Where's the fastest way to do this?
I wish it's instant.
I have to move and look every fucking corner.
Are you fucking kidding me?
But I think there's flight.
There's flight.
How the fuck do I...
The flight cameras.
On the left.
Let me fucking...
Oh my god, do I have to like...
deconstruct this?
No.
It won't let me keep building.
No, the six won't help build.
Did I fuck it up?
Oh no, I cancelled it.
Do I have to redo this?
Oh no, I don't.
It exceeds territory range?
What do you mean it exceeds territory range?
There's like a white border.
Oh my god!
I have to move my house closer.
Did you build it outside?
I didn't know either!
This is stupid.
This game is so clunky.
Wait, why can't I build my door?
The door is in the territory!
What do you mean it exceeds territory?
It's literally in the territory!
How does it exceed it?
I mean...
If I look at the fucking square...
Some parts of your building is outside.
How does it exceed it?
I don't understand!
I'm gonna cut more trees.
I need to move the territory better.
Please!
I need my tower house!
I'm killing a whole deer family here.
I'm cutting...
I'm destroying the environment.
Fuck the trees.
We don't have any trees.
We don't need oxygen.
We need a house.
The house is more important.
I wouldn't worry about that.
Affordable housing is more important here.
Exactly.
Would you rather die in a nice home...
or just die in the fucking street?
I would rather die in a nice home.
I want a house.
That's all I want.
We didn't even care about the game anymore.
We just want to build.
How do I have insufficient...
I have 300 fucking...
wood!
Well, you need like...
a thousand four hundred...
Yeah, but I still have the wood!
I still have it though!
I don't know about that.
Can I help you build?
Yeah, can you help me?
You don't have permission.
Wait, how do I give you permission?
You go to Hive and then click my name.
Okay, give me a sec.
I'm fucking moving my house a little bit better here.
Okay.
How do I...
Yeah, you go to Hive...
Give me a sec.
I've left my territory.
There's like permission...
Okay.
There you go.
No, I have to wait!
Okay, go to Hive and then...
Uh...
Hive... Okay, wait, I need to...
This is the hardest game ever.
Yep.
Okay, what do I do?
Go to Hive and then what?
Click my name.
Yeah?
And then what?
And then there's like friends permission?
No, I can delete... Oh, there it is.
Okay.
Enable, enable, enable.
You can use it to store stuff too.
Okay, let's see.
Can I build stuff?
Okay, build!
Build my home!
Yeah...
There's the door!
The door!
Wait, how did you build the door?
That's your fucking door.
Holy shit, that's so funny.
How could you do that and I couldn't?
Holy shit, that's funny.
How were you able to do it?
But I can't.
You have a door that's unreachable.
Congratulations.
I have an unreachable door?
No, I can't.
Look, see?
Hello.
Yeah, you can go out, but you can't.
You can't come out.
Wait, wait.
This is an issue.
This is an issue because we can't...
We can't go up into the house.
Oh shit.
You can climb.
We know you can't.
Can you climb?
Yeah, but then the door has to always be open or we can't unlock the door.
Yeah, well...
That's not a problem.
Yeah, you know what?
This is a problem.
This is the safest home.
In the most fucking RPG survival.
We have to unlock the door here.
And then go up like this.
Yeah, no one can raid it.
Yeah, nobody can raid my house.
No one can raid your house if you close the door and just log out there.
Just no one can go there.
Alright, nice.
We're so good at this game.
Okay, okay.
I have like six more minutes before I can...
I'm gonna go crash at your house.
Let's see.
We don't even have beds.
It's so fucked up.
Yeah, furniture is just a concept to me.
Yeah.
We are just an empty house.
Yeah, my house is gonna be taller than your house.
Yeah, three floors.
Yeah.
We haven't bumped into like a single boss type yet.
We've just been building a house.
This is so much fun.
This is more important chat.
This is a lot more important.
Remember, affordable housing.
This is so much more important guys.
You don't understand.
Okay, let me see.
You guys wouldn't understand guys.
They wouldn't get it.
You wouldn't get it.
This is like the most important part in the video game.
Trying to figure out like...
Which place...
Can like guarantee...
That my house is like...
Uh...
Is like okay.
Is like... I don't know.
I've been trying to find stuff.
But then I found out my house area is like...
Swarmed with alligators.
So I'm like...
Yeah, but what are alligators gonna do?
They're gonna do nothing.
I haven't seen a single alligator that's like near you yet.
It was there.
So many of them.
Did you kill all of them?
Probably.
Yeah, right here.
I just saw it.
Wait, really?
I'm sorry.
I'm trying to figure out my house still.
It is a fucking alligator.
Holy shit.
I'm trying to figure out how to...
Where can I put this?
Where can I put...
There's nothing.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Here.
Oh my god.
Okay.
No.
What?
There.
I have a minute still?
Okay, I gotta wait here.
I gotta wait here.
I didn't realize the top right corner is my cooldown.
Oh my god.
But honestly...
The game's not bad.
It's just...
Yeah, look.
Okay, the moment we finish building our houses, we'll actually fight for real.
Right.
We'll fight.
We'll fight stuff.
We need a home first.
This is the end game, basically.
We're speedrunning this game.
Exactly.
Guys, this is like...
We just wanted to find a house first.
This is much more important than fighting.
Than shooting our guns.
Okay, guys.
Like, I don't care if those are nice gear.
They have nice house.
I surely do.
Okay.
Oh my god, one minute left.
One minute left and then I can finally put down my house.
Oh, it's cause I'm moving my...
I'm moving my tower at the same time?
Is that... Oh my god!
That's why...
That's why I was struggling.
Cause I was moving my tower.
How do I move just this?
Dude, dude.
Just demolish it.
No!
Get rid of the blue frame.
Never!
I'm too lazy!
Isn't that all of us?
I don't wanna move my thing.
It's too much work.
I don't wanna move.
I have to demolish the house!
I'm sad.
I have to demolish the house.
Goodbye, door.
Goodbye.
You were a great door.
Did you get rid of the blue frames?
Alright.
The blue frame is still there.
No fucking way.
Wait, is it?
There's no way.
No, it's not.
The blue frame is still there.
I don't see it.
Wait, it is!
What the fuck is it still doing there?
How do I demolish the blue frame?
Here's the hollow terminal.
Wait, how do I get rid of the blue frame?
How do I get rid of it?
Weird ass camera.
There's nothing I can do.
How do I get rid of it?
Oh, cancel.
Okay.
Nice.
Alright.
There you go.
It's gone.
Nice.
Alright.
Now I can move this.
Number 6 is just gathering resources.
Okay, I need to fucking do my stupid tower.
Okay, here.
Maybe here.
Whose house is this?
Oh, this is number 6.
Alright, confirmed.
He has a bed!
Number 6 has a fucking bed!
Number 6 has a bed?!
How did he progress that far?
I feel relaxed.
Alright.
This bed is very nice.
Guys, we will get there.
The tower is gonna be made.
Okay.
Alright.
I'm figuring this out.
Very slowly.
Okay.
My tower.
There's still hope.
Just don't put it over the edge of the territory.
Bro, what the fuck?
How do I not do that?
When you press B, there's like a white...
like a white square.
Bro, it's so hard to make this stupid.
I'm... fuck.
I'm...
I'm going insane.
I'm gonna demolish everything.
Fuck this.
I'm gonna...
I'm going crazy.
I'm gonna demolish everything.
I...
I did that.
I fucking fucked up.
I'm going crazy.
I'm going...
I already went through that phase.
So...
Fuck this.
I don't need this.
I don't need this at all.
Like, you know.
Alright.
This tower is much more important.
You move it.
Do it.
Okay.
Alright.
There we go.
Where's the... where's the...
I don't know.
I can't put my...
What can I...
Overlaps with battle unit?
What the fuck is the battle unit?
I honestly don't know what a battle unit is.
Okay.
There we go.
I did it guys.
I did it.
Oh, you did it.
No way.
We did it.
Let's go build.
It's time to build.
Your door is so long.
Build your door.
Oh my god.
We did it.
I finally...
We figured it out guys.
Okay.
Oh shit.
I made a stairs.
Oh my god.
You made my stairs.
Okay.
We're gonna go up, up, up.
Building formula left.
The door works.
Do I not have materials anymore?
I can't tell.
I can't tell when I stopped having materials.
Okay.
Oh my god.
The door is finally accessible.
We can finally like go through the door.
The door is actually functional now.
Why is the door gone?
Oh my god.
I made the door and it's gone.
Wait.
Is it?
I took it away.
Oh you took it away.
You took away the door that I gave you.
How do I put the door back?
I put it back.
Just put it back.
How?
It's gone.
Oh my god.
You took the door that I gave you.
The door is gone.
Put it back.
You put it back.
What do you mean I have no material?
Yeah.
That's what I'm saying.
What does it mean when it says we don't have materials?
Yeah.
Then we're out of materials.
Then get some trees.
But what materials?
Get trees.
It's a goddamn wood house.
Okay.
I'm fucking chopping.
Guys, we have to keep building.
Oh.
We gotta give number six perms.
To chop trees.
Number six.
Okay.
Tell number six to join our guild.
You're the leader.
Oh yeah.
Invite him to our guild.
Get over here.
Yeah.
Let me just talk to you real quick.
Invite to hive.
I invited you to hive, number six.
Alright.
Yeah.
Get in here.
Get in here and build my house.
Fortnite that shit.
Real quick.
Build my house.
Okay.
Dude.
Are you in the guild yet?
Okay.
Number six.
And then... You gotta give him the permission.
Okay.
We have to be friends with him.
Wait.
We have to be friends with him?
I'm not sure.
Do we have to be?
I don't know.
Okay.
I don't see the option to give him the shit.
Alright.
Number six.
But he's like in our... What's the point of being in our guild?
We can't... I don't know.
My friend says like in a guild but like yada yada.
Alright.
You get the lucky opportunity.
I'm gonna remove you after the stream.
You're so evil.
For my house!
My house is very important to me.
Build my house right now.
Number six.
Alright.
Do what you gotta do.
Holy shit.
This guy.
This guy is the man.
Go build the house.
I will supervise.
Is he gonna put a door back on?
Oh my god.
He's building.
Look at him go.
Oh my god.
Why were we doing work when we could have had number six do all the work for us?
He was collecting materials.
Give me a door number six.
Give me a door.
We need a door.
Yeah.
What happened to our door?
I actually took it off.
I don't know.
I'll put it back on.
I gave you a door and you took it away.
I don't know.
What happened to the door?
Holy shit.
What happened to my door?
I don't even know what happened.
I took the door but where did I take it?
I don't know.
Like it's gone.
I can't even put it back on.
I don't even know.
Like it's gone.
It doesn't tell me how to get my door back.
Oh I accidentally destroyed the door.
Guys we don't need a door.
In my inventory?
There's no doors in my inventory though.
What happened to it?
I don't understand what I did.
Oh my god.
He has so much materials.
What the fuck?
Look at that.
You have a house.
Not yet.
I don't have a roof yet.
It's like 40...
Well you have three floors.
Does it fucking matter?
Yes it does.
I require my house to be the tallest out of everybody.
So I can overcompensate.
Overcompensate?
Hey there's a guy here.
Wait he has... he killed a deer.
Yo that guy's high level.
He has a sniper.
He has to steal his deer.
Oh my god this guy's gaming.
He's like looking at our house.
Hey there man.
He's like looking at what we are doing.
He's actually progressing the game.
Yeah well we're technically are as well.
Just a different aspect.
What are we missing in our building?
Just a little bit of a foundations and such.
Well you have a you don't have a roof yet.
Yeah I don't have a roof yet.
Alright while number six is building the rest of our house we should go find some monsters to kill.
You wanna do a deadsville mission?
Yeah let's go do a mission.
Number six can we leave this to you?
Is that okay?
No you don't ask.
You don't have to ask them.
It's expected.
It's like pal world.
They're my pal.
He ocean.
He's the man.
He takes it to the man.
Okay do we teleport there?
Wait which one?
Deadsville.
Deadssville.
Okay wait.
Is it your mission?
Yeah uh huh.
What is it?
It's called welcome back?
Is there TP or do we have to walk there?
Recommended of teleporting they said.
But I'm not sure.
Where is it?
You wanna walk?
Just to see what the fuck is gonna happen?
Yeah let's go.
I'll follow you behind you.
One kilometer.
Are you not on the same mission?
No cause I still have to fucking build.
I haven't finished building yet.
Top left.
What the fuck is your mission?
Go build mode and build the gear workbench.
That's my mission.
I'm still at the gear workbench.
I'm gonna kill this deer cause I'm angry.
Build a workbench.
I don't wanna build.
I'm tired of building.
I'm not building.
I want to shoot stuff.
Yeah shoot stuff.
Oh wait.
This is the wrong way.
God damn.
Stupid roads.
Alright.
I don't have my butterfly to help us.
Cause my butterfly is still...
My butterfly is...
You don't have a butterfly?
Your butterfly is crying.
My butterfly was like...
Like I had to disassemble my butterfly.
Remember?
Uhhh.
You can use my building.
No.
It's fine.
I'm too lazy.
We don't need the butterfly!
We have your butterfly!
Oh, it's good to have two butterflies.
What's over here?
It's a zombie.
Well, it's literally a zombie!
It's literally a zombie!
It's literally a zombie.
So what?
Exactly.
I missed.
Like the tutorial had cooler zombies.
This is like... the tutorial not even zombies.
The tutorial had actual monsters.
These are just zombies.
Did you have a hard time fighting the tutorial box?
The tutorial box?
Oh yeah.
No, it was so easy.
I was just like...
The fucking boss was like, oh that was a tough fight.
What do you mean?
I didn't even get to do anything.
And he just stood there.
He just stood there.
Yeah, he just stood.
And then your butterfly killed him.
Alright.
I'm following you.
We're in Micah's...
Hey.
Hey there.
Person.
Goodbye.
Pretty sure he just started playing this game too.
He has nothing.
Alright.
I'm right behind you.
We should play Remnant next time.
Sure.
I should not have played Remnant 2 yet.
I tried to, but I kept crashing.
There's a second game?
I don't even know.
Yeah.
There's a second game, but I kept crashing, so I just stopped.
Thing is, I might need a new graphics card and I'm trying to save up.
If I keep buying games, I can't.
Yeah, but the Steam Cell.
There's a Steam Cell right now.
Yeah, what's the point of buying games when I can't even launch it?
Wait, can you not... not even... you don't know if you can launch it.
Maybe they fixed it.
I have a 20 series, man.
Yeah, but maybe they fixed it.
Oh yeah, never mind.
My chat was like, no.
They're like, no to you.
No, I have a 20 series.
What can I do with that, huh?
Alright, where the fuck is our boss?
We wanna fight.
Oh shit.
Wait, he actually dropped... wait, he dropped something.
Watch this.
What the fuck?
Wait, what did I do?
What is that?
It's like a... you kill them and then he drops this.
It's like a... it's like a weapon.
Can you throw it?
I must be thirsty.
Wait, oh there's him.
Wait, I wanna see if I can kill this guy.
No, you can, but like...
It also kills people.
Oh, it like beams them.
Gee... oh, what?
That's a... that kills them.
What the fuck?
Yeah.
Wait, where did I drop it?
Oh, there it is.
You can try it.
It's right here.
What is this?
Do I just aim it?
Yeah, yeah, just aim it and then it beams.
Yeah, but there's like a limited ammo.
Oh, hell nah.
I'm not using this.
I have photosensitivity.
You want me to use that?
Crazy.
Alright, I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna use it.
It's RGB time.
I gotta wear sunglasses.
Where even... where's your fucking mission?
Oh, there's him again.
There's another one of those.
Oh my god, I'm so slow with this though.
I'm gonna use it on the actual boss boss.
There's like a lot of items around us.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
He's beaming me.
I beamed him back.
I think it's like a rare drop.
No, it's like a rare drop type deal.
It'll just drop it.
Probably.
Where the fuck is your mission, Tenjin?
It's called Welcome Back.
Yeah, but where is it?
It's very far.
Told you.
Oh my god.
Wait, this is not even the area?
No.
Okay, I'm fucking... okay, I'm fucking running over to you.
I thought that was the area so I picked it up.
No, it was not.
Alright, here I come.
Was there stamina?
Where's the stamina bar?
Like, right there.
The muscle.
Oh, the muscle.
Okay.
Okay, I see it.
I see it now.
You gotta eat and drink.
Yeah, it's okay.
I feel like we have enough food on us, right?
Right.
Yeah, I have like seven...
Actually, we lost no damage boost.
I have like seven things from the tutorial.
Tutorial?
Yeah, the tutorial gave you so much free food.
What the f- when did you have a gun?
What?
Since that lady gave me the blueprint.
That's why you're hungry.
Oh!
I was not paying attention.
You did not.
You did not have a gun.
I was too busy building my tower.
Right.
You should be the area.
This is okay.
I have a bottle of soju.
What is that?
I'm gonna fucking eat too.
I run so fast now.
I run fast.
Oh, you drank alcohol?
Yeah.
There's a... there's one of the... there's a player here.
Yeah, there's a lot of players here.
Wait, is this... oh, this is like a town.
Yeah.
Oh, it's like a safe zone.
Yeah, it is.
We should have built... we should have lived here.
We should have lived near here.
Yeah, we should have lived near here.
Speak to Mary.
Oh, wait, we got compensation!
Oh, my God!
Compensation?
Where?
Yeah, look at the mailbox.
They gave us free stuff.
Oh.
Oh, my God!
I got something.
Sorry.
Yay!
They fucked up so we get free stuff!
Buy something.
You have something.
We have butterfly die.
We have... you can now create...
Based on... we have originally opened up functionality for multiple character creation.
You can now create characters on any server.
Whoa!
All right.
Yay!
We got free stuff.
She's not selling anything.
Free loot!
I gotta talk to the lady.
How do we open this loot box?
Teleport... oh, this is where we teleport to other worlds.
Yay.
Is it this woman?
That's a man.
Sorry, that's a man.
She's here.
Let's see what I...
Okay, let's see what I...
Investigate the teleportation...
Where's the loot box?
Speak with traitor on site...
Oh, shit.
Loot box?
What the fuck?
Yeah.
What the fuck... there's a loot box?
I got...
I got hairstyle.
I got grenade.
I got emotes.
I got cosmetic tokens.
Okay.
Yeah.
If you open the mailbox... did you not open the mailbox?
There's a mailbox.
I'm not sure if I'm clear.
What if I chat with her?
Do I...
Wait, she doesn't even have voice lines.
We don't even have a voice line.
Yeah, no, this random... the clear lady doesn't even have voice lines.
We both don't have a voice line.
It feels awkward.
Yeah, this feels so weird.
I don't even think I'm supposed to talk to her yet.
Because I don't have a mission.
Yeah.
I'm just gonna mooch off your missions.
What the fuck is that?
What?
What is this?
What is that?
Where are you?
Is this a shop?
Who are you?
Look at him.
Yeah, what the fuck is that?
Shop.
Oh, suppressors and stuff.
Nice.
When will we fight our first boss?
I don't know.
Where do...
I think you have to find the bosses in the world.
Do we have to find it ourselves?
Alright, let's see.
Recommend the shadow.
Someone's over there.
Let's go check it out.
Someone's up ahead.
Oh, there's like these exclamation points.
Are those exclamation point bosses?
You got a bike?
Let's go to this nearest one.
This one.
The shadow lighthouse.
There's a fucking radio.
No shot.
They have a fucking radio.
What the fuck?
How did you get that bike?
Can you get on?
No.
How did you get on it?
Can't you get on it?
There's a fuel system.
Did you talk to somebody to get it?
Yeah.
Do the missions.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Unlock the storage expansion.
How do I unlock the storage expansion?
Don't do the red mission.
I think the red missions are like...
The...
The yellow is the green one.
How do I unlock the storage expansion?
I have the purple mission...
The yellow mission.
What the fuck is a purple mission?
I've never got a purple mission.
Okay, okay.
Give me a second...
I need to unlock the storage expansion.
Do I have enough storage expansion?
Where the fuck is the storage expansion?
Where is it?
What the fuck?
Oh, is it basic storage?
I need to unlock wooden support.
Okay.
To get storage expansion.
I did it.
Build any storage... Oh my god.
It needs me to build a storage crate.
How far ahead are you?
Not that far.
Okay, can I TP to you or not?
I wonder.
Just TP to the base, no?
I know, but like, will I be able to TP to you later?
Can you?
I'm not sure.
Alright, we'll figure this out the mo... I'm gonna TP to my home and see if I can TP to you.
Just TP to the base.
I'll TP to you.
Just TP to you.
What?
Why are you going to me?
No, cause like, I need to go... cause you're there for the mission.
To progress.
Why?
What do you mean?
What is 61% done?
Why did number 6 stop?
Oh, it's cause he's still building.
Holy shit.
He's still building.
I think I like, put too much stuff...
Yeah.
I definitely... I definitely picked the house too big.
Oh my god.
The house is definitely too big.
It's too fucking huge.
Way more than mine, actually.
Oh shit, I taxed like the sky.
Oh, there it is.
Okay.
Uh...
Jesus Christ, there's so much stuff to unlock.
Oh my god, did you see someone chat that was like, I am Asian girl?
I didn't see that.
What the fuck?
Insane.
Good to know, man.
What the fuck is furniture?
Basic furniture.
Oh, I couldn't build doors and windows because I never unlocked it.
Oh shit.
Build a bed.
You never built a bed?
I never built a bed, no.
How come I can't progress your mission?
What?
Because it's... I'm not doing the optional shit.
I don't have any other mission.
It just says build a bed.
Just look at your task.
What the fuck do you have?
Build a bed!
Why did... I didn't even have... They didn't even tell me to like build a bed or some shit.
What happened to my missions?
Why am I building a bed?
Why am I building...
Why do you have to build a bed?
Okay.
I don't know.
I'm confused.
I'm just as confused as you.
Why am I building...
What the fuck?
Am I supposed to follow the Stardust?
Is that...
What your missions are?
Yeah.
Oh wait, untracked!
Why did you untrack your main mission?
I don't fucking know how to...
Attention.
I don't... I don't know 90% of what's going on right now.
Me neither, dude.
I just... I'm goofing.
Building gear workbench.
Holy shit.
Okay.
Gear workbench built.
Alright, what else does it want me to do?
Go to build a supplies...
That... that is... he's... someone's name is I Like Asian Girls!
No!
Oh my god.
Holy shit.
Free to play games experience.
Oh my god.
No!
Okay, basic gear.
We're getting there, guys.
We're gonna be able to get there soon, guys.
Give up this power through...
I don't have enough ciphers?
What kind of worthless shit do I have?
Oh, I'm gonna reset this.
That's my worthless shit that I had.
Okay.
I got the gun.
It's time to craft the gun.
Which gun is it?
Is it this one?
The DE-50BP.
It's the pistol.
DE-50P... Oh, okay.
It's this one.
I have insufficient materials?
Uh... collect the crafting materials.
The plus ones.
I don't get it why they need to make that shit, but...
Explore the... Oh, I need to disassemble the scrap.
Oh...
Yeah, disassemble the scrap.
I have a disassembler.
Yeah, I'm just gonna use your dissembler.
Wait, did you give me perms to use your stuff?
Yeah.
Okay.
Cause like last time you didn't have it.
Alright.
Let's see.
It's like they're trying to combine a lot of stuff into one.
Yeah, yeah.
The base gun... and the grass and shit.
I agree.
Like, holy shit.
It's like everything all at once.
Yep.
I'm gonna use your fucking gear shit too.
Might as well.
It's like right here!
Yeah, true.
How do I still don't have enough?
What do you need?
Uhhhh...
Excuse me.
Oh, I got it.
Never mind.
JK, I just can't read.
Yeah, well, honestly that's why I read it too.
I got a gun.
I did it.
I didn't assume so.
Craft any ammo in the supplies.
Wait, how much ammo did you craft?
Oh, you do have a fishing rod.
There's like a couple... there's like... hmm.
Oh, it's like 40 bullets?
Holy shit.
It's like 40...
40 bullets for crafts.
Wait, what the fuck?
When did you get here?
I'm right.
This is my home.
I have every right to be here.
That's not what you're talking about.
What?
That's insane.
She's kicking me out of my house.
Holy shit, how did you get here?
My house.
What the fuck?
That's insane.
She's kicking me out of my house.
I'm sorry, but... I mean, my house.
Can she do that?
Can she do that, chat?
No way.
I just did.
She just did.
Insane.
Can't believe we walked over here when we could just TP.
Yeah.
TP has cooled down.
I'm sorry.
Run now, wasted.
Wait, TP has cooled down?
Yeah.
This was the quickest way to bring you here.
These towers are even supposed to let you travel between worlds, but I haven't been able to figure out how.
This building is half.
Can't build the stairs.
I'm glad that merchant over by the old truck looks like she gets around.
Oh my God.
When do I get my bike?
You got a program.
Apparently, the longer we follow the mission, the closer we get to the boss.
I'm sorry.
I hope they're right.
I hope.
Okay.
Yeah, we don't need to know that.
We literally did that already.
Okay, speak with the trader.
You went there?
Yeah, I'm doing that.
Oh, no.
I'm doing the mission now.
Oh, you're at Dead'sville.
Oh, really?
Affordable housing.
Livable housing.
I'm just looking.
Where is the mission?
Oh, she's talking now.
Claire's talking.
I know.
I like that so many people are naked in this game.
Yeah, nobody's bothering to put any armor on.
They're just...
They're just building.
Hey, everyone's just doing their shit.
And this guy's fully geared as shit.
This guy's level 10 and not even wearing pants.
Jesus.
What level are we at?
We're at level 10.
I'm level 6.
Oh, okay.
So they just played like two more hours than us.
Yeah, probably.
You got the bike now?
Oh, yeah.
I'm still talking.
Oh, my God.
How many people did I have to talk to?
I can cut that trip.
It's very bad.
Oh, my God.
Good luck.
Oh, and I'll happily pay a reward if you can recover my stuff for me.
I'll mark Rotten Manor on your map.
Make sure to stock up on ammo before you go.
All right.
What the fuck gives you the bike?
This guy?
Oh, after that guy.
Oh, the guy?
The low?
Low guy?
Yeah.
After that guy.
The girl with the...
801.
Yeah.
Ada Wong gave the bike.
Claire Redfield.
Claire Wong.
I like how this is like...
It's like cutscenes within the game so you can see people walking around.
Do you see me?
I think I just saw you walking around in my cutscene.
Can I... Do you still see this?
Wait, wait.
I'm looking at him right now.
I don't have a POV of outside.
You seek keys with which to unlock the dark tower.
It's like the guy's talking to me.
I'm wary of what else you might open up.
Do you always speak in red?
Now it's at 8.01.
I was merely setting the mood.
The world still deserves something poetic.
Oh man.
What are you doing?
I'm emoting his...
I don't see you yet.
Don't.
Oh man.
Rift anchors across the wetlands.
It's a close up.
Those things are made by Rosetta.
If you stand next to the campfire, I'll see you.
Access to the rift space inside the monolith.
I'm at the campfire.
Spot on.
And now tell me.
Where do you think those anchors would be?
Wait, what?
No, you're not there!
I'm at the campfire.
No, man.
I'm looking forward to seeing what you can do, Mayfly.
I'm sure it will be a remarkable story to share.
Hells yeah.
I feel bad for the people that wrote the story because they clearly put a lot of effort in writing this story.
Yes.
I had to talk to Mary again.
Mary, what do you want?
Now that we know what to do, let's split up to cover more ground.
I'll find a way to hack into the monolith.
I thought she had syringes of blood on her.
Like, what is she doing with the syringes?
Who knows?
Gone for an hour and still no pants.
Yep.
This game has no concept of pants.
Nobody wears pants here.
Like, I like the fact that the tutorial gave us armor, a hat, a glove, a shoe, but not a fucking pants.
Yeah, it gave us everything but pants.
But a pants.
Holy shit.
What is wrong with the devs?
Look, there's P. Diddy.
Hey there, guys.
P. Diddy?
A P. Diddy.
Oh, there it is!
It's P. Diddy.
It's a bike!
I got bike too!
Where's your bike?
Right.
I just drive it.
I can summon it.
Wait, how do you summon it?
G.
G?
Oh, okay, okay.
It just taught me that.
Yeah.
Well...
We gotta go to Rotten Manor.
Yeah, alright.
Where's Rotten Manor?
Okay, here we go.
Fuck your bike.
Oh, fuck your bike.
No!
I was fucking over somebody else's bike.
I'm ready.
Let's get...
I follow you.
Okay, okay.
Let's see what's the closest way to get there.
What the fuck?
I'm not even gonna ride down the road.
Fuck the roads.
Okay.
But there's horns.
Beep.
There's a radio.
Oh, yeah.
Is there actually radio?
Yeah.
Old X.
I don't know what...
Oh, there it is!
Before exploring danger... Wait, what?
Before exploring dangerous areas, press T?
Oh!
Make a camp.
We're fighting some shit.
I don't know if I can join you.
Wait, can you not join me?
Where are you?
I hope I can.
Can I see you?
Wait, wait, wait.
You rode ahead of me.
Can I go over this?
No!
Okay.
I have to jump over this.
I mean, you could summon your bike again.
I love that we just materialized the fucking bike and that's it.
No!
Okay, there it is.
Wait, what the fuck?
Investigate.
Oh, you're gone.
Holy shit.
Oh shit!
You're gone too!
Oh!
Okay.
Oh no.
I should have brought the butterfly.
I should have brought the...
No, it's easy.
Just shoot the head.
Shoot the head.
Keep shooting the head.
I shot the head.
I shot it with a goddamn butterfly.
I definitely should have brought the butterfly.
Holy fuck.
I know that I fucking...
I'm fucked up.
Wait, I don't even have...
Oh my god.
I didn't bring my gun.
Wait, I did bring my gun.
Okay.
I hear it growling at me outside.
I realized that like when you're on the pause menu, you're not actually paused by the way.
No.
Yeah, it's an MMO.
What did you say?
I don't know.
I expected to pause for a minute.
Fuck.
It's a solo anyway.
That's true.
Where's your head?
What do you want?
Where the fuck is the head?
It's so tiny.
There we go.
I killed it.
Jesus Christ.
There it is.
The Rift Anchor.
Let's take a closer look.
The Rift Anchor?
I'm just gonna lay back, enjoy my coffee, and...
You're already finished?
Yeah, I did that.
Oh shit.
I'm gonna cutscene it.
Oh wait, hey, hey.
Oh, P Diddy's here.
Where's your... Okay, there you are.
P Diddy's gone.
How do we do like the bosses together then?
You gotta find it.
A lot of people are fighting in some places I heard.
Oh, okay.
Alright.
You lead us.
You seen that more than once.
You have more knowledge than me.
You lead us.
I can't read the chat, but people keep saying, boss, boss, boss.
Boss, boss, boss.
You do... Come on, where is it?
Tangents chat!
Where's the boss?
No, not the chat.
Like the game chat.
Oh!
Like everyone keeps saying boss, boss, boss, and I'm like, hmm.
Someone said we can do dungeons together.
Where's the dungeons?
Which one's the dungeons?
Yeah.
That's what I like to know.
Which one would be the dungeons then?
I'm curious now.
Like, what do dungeons even look like?
Wait, am I getting shot at?
Oh, shit.
We are.
We're just looking at her map.
We're looking at the maps.
There's a guy right behind us.
We're like, where could the dungeons be?
Pfft.
We have to do these?
The welcome back?
Oh, we do the dungeon after this quest.
Okay.
We have to go to the other ones.
And then we can do the dungeons.
Okay.
Where are you headed?
I guess we can do the closest one to us.
Like this one?
341?
Sure.
Oh, shit.
What the fuck did you...
What did you do to my bike?
Why?
You pushed me over.
You pushed me over first!
You pushed me over too.
We need to unlock...
Unlock the rift anchors.
Okay.
Apparently with the...
Oh, there's dogs!
There's like demon dogs.
Diamond dogs?
Yeah.
There was a demon dog in front of me.
I wish we can go like faster with the...
Yeah.
The bikes.
There you go.
Activate.
Okay.
Activate that.
This is not my bike.
Activate...
Wait.
There's so many bikes.
Whose bikes are it?
Where's the guy on...
I don't know.
Why is there a random bike here?
Whose bike is that?
I wouldn't know of it.
Okay.
Next one is... Where's the next one?
What the fuck is that?
What is that?
What?
What the fuck?
Is that the boss?
Oh my god!
Affordable housing!
Is that the... Is that where everybody's going?
I think everybody's going there.
Holy shit.
Are we fighting that thing?
Wait.
Is everybody there?
What is that?
Can we get close to it?
Wait.
There's nobody here.
Can we get close to it?
I'm getting close...
What the fuck happened?
Oh shit.
What is that?
I'm going to shoot it.
No.
You can't even shoot it.
What is that then?
Wait.
Can I shoot the hands?
What is this?
Wait.
You can't even shoot it.
Shit.
Wait.
The friend?
It talked to me.
Wait.
Did it talk to you?
What did you do?
He talked to me.
Oh, it didn't talk to me.
I shot it.
He's friend?
What the fuck is that?
I think he's friend.
He's friend?
Oh my.
I mean, I mean, he doesn't have a mouth.
Could be a friend.
Yeah, how did he talk to you?
I don't know.
What does it do?
I honestly don't know.
I don't know what this is.
I wonder if like we can get on top of it later.
Okay.
Something stares at the mural on the ground.
Crush the murals and find a hidden miniature.
Oh, I see.
Oh, I see it.
Oh.
Hail moving house, not even a moving house.
Everybody's confused.
Everybody's shooting.
I don't know.
You know what?
I will not mess with the Mystical Forest.
Apparently, people are saying that we have to find a way to access the secret for this.
It's apparently a secret.
Ooh.
All right.
There are faint noises.
It's your turn.
When did we do that?
We did it guys!
We did it!
We got a disco!
We leached!
Let's go!
Wait what?
What the fuck did they do?
Rewards can only be claimed once a week.
Please come back next week.
I'm not going to come back.
When did we even get it?
That's a nice stuff.
I got a disco!
Woo!
Yeah I got a disco ball.
I don't know what that does.
I don't know what it does.
But we did it.
Yeah!
How the fuck did they do it?
I don't know.
Where's the leech?
Where are the leeches?
It's just like Diablo all over again.
Wait it like became part of the environment.
Wait the hell is...
We got the shit.
Oh my god.
I can't believe it.
Unlocked house treasure and then leave this place.
Well I'm leaving it.
Yeah I'm leaving it too.
Ow.
Okay I need to get my bike too.
We gotta go to the other unlock.
Yay!
We did it Tanger!
We got a disco ball!
Yeah we did it.
Hell yeah.
Yay!
Leech!
I don't know why we needed a disco ball.
But it's good to have.
Oh shit.
Whoops.
Alright.
I... I fucked up.
Give me a sec.
I got off the road and I fucked up.
I'm going off the road.
Okay.
I'm heading over now.
I left my loot there.
It's alright.
I got the disco ball though.
Holy shit.
This game's physics is funny.
I'm just happy with the disco ball.
Apparently I only took one thing.
Seriously?
It's alright.
I'm probably just having the disco ball.
I don't even know what other stuff was there.
I just like claimed the disco ball.
Oh shit.
Okay I got the... got the rift.
Yeah I'm heading for this one too.
Where's the other one?
Where's the last one?
It's next to our base.
It is?
We might as well just fast travel if it's next to our base.
Sure.
I'm fast traveling.
Woo.
Yeah.
Holy shit.
Yeah I still don't get it.
They just decided not to give us pants.
I'm gonna check my disco ball.
What is it?
What does it do?
I have no clue.
Oh it's a deviation!
So I can have a disco ball in my...
I can have a disco ball in my backpack?
Is that it?
I see about that.
Alright I'm gonna check.
Number 6 is still going at it.
Go number 6!
Go!
I'm... you're 72%!
Who would... who will win?
Us fighting a boss?
Or number 6 building this house?
Who will win?
It's a crafting... it's a crafting shit.
Not a combat.
It's a different thing.
But it says a deviation!
I know but it's like a crafting stuff.
So I can't put it in my... I can't put it in my... in my backpack?
Hold on.
Oh somebody broke its leg.
No you can't.
Nooooo!
What's the point?
It's not a combat!
Deviation!
Nooooo!
What's the point?
It's not a combat deviation!
There's an alligator in my door!
What the fuck?
It's in!
What?
Wait wait wait wait what?
There's an alligator in my fucking door.
Holy shit.
The disco ball's in!
I put the disco ball!
It's not in my backpack but...
But it's there.
It's in!
That looks enough.
That looks so dumb.
That's all that matters!
This is the only thing...
This is the only thing I looted!
Holy shit.
But I got the disco ball.
I don't need the butterfly just with the disco ball.
Oh my god!
I got it!
It's super dumb.
I'm gonna go to the last...
Wait which way is it?
The last one.
It's over here.
That way.
Hell yeah, my motorcycle.
Even though...
Oh my god guys we can't...
Wait you like drove over it.
Even though...
Oh my god broke my leg.
You broke your leg.
Even though it can't be in my backpack...
I'm still satisfied with it just...
It's just in there in your fucking container.
In my house.
Yeah with disco ball.
It's a fucking disco ball.
It's a disco ball.
Out of all the models.
They put it in disco ball.
It's literally the only thing I looted.
That's all I care about.
Woah woah woah.
Oh shit.
Is that boss?
What level is it?
He's level 8.
We can do this.
We can do it.
This is what we trained for.
He's...
He's not taking that much of a damage man.
This is what we trained for.
I need your help man.
I'm literally shooting him!
Use your butterfly!
Oh he's...
What's his weakness?
What is his weakness?
Is it the little...
You see the leg?
The leg?
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Use your butterfly.
I did.
I have a fear of butterflies.
Jesus Christ.
Okay.
Oh my gosh I should've made more ammo.
The butterfly scares anymore aimbosses.
I should've made more ammo.
Oh wait wait.
Oh it's all...
Oh wait wait wait.
He's stunned.
We're supposed to shoot the...
Shoot his...
Yeah, shoot the flower!
What?
I mean he does look like it.
Is he dead?
Oh!
Okay...
Oh my god...
Yeah, that's... that's...
Yeah, well...
Well... to be fair...
It's launch day, you know.
It just launched today.
The ragdoll is so...
What a ragdoll.
Holy shit.
I'm heading over.
Okay, it's done.
What the fuck?
Obtain tier 1 craft...
Craft?
They keep wanting us to craft shit.
I'm tired of it.
They love crafting.
Oh, meet Mary.
No, we gotta meet Mary.
Meet Mary?
Yeah.
It says meet Mary.
What does it say for you?
Obtain tier 1 craft.
Wait, what?
What?
It doesn't say that for me.
Let's see...
What?
Oh...
Okay, I need a fucking... Prepare any kinds of ammo.
I...
I'm heading back with you.
Maybe it's because I need ammo.
Why does it say meet Mary for me?
What?
Maybe you filled the requirements and I didn't.
It says welcome... It says meet Mary.
What?
Obtain tier 1 armor.
Craft on the top.
What?
Okay, that's weird.
Uh...
Yeah, it says meet Mary under the monolith for me.
What?
Maybe I don't have enough ammo and some shit.
Well, I have like... Literally have like...
Oh, there's another phone call.
Mushy-mushy.
My sister stumbled across a huge toy rabbit downstairs.
What the fuck is this message?
What the fuck?
Alright, I'm gonna go... I'm gonna meet Mary.
You're gonna meet Mary?
You gotta craft a suit?
Yeah.
And then I'll see if I start crafting after.
It's weird that you...
You don't have the same thing as me.
I feel like you should.
I should, yes.
Yeah, we literally did the quest together.
Like...
Like what?
Enemies approaching.
Copper... copper...
Alright, I'm heading over.
Weeeeee!
Alright.
Ooh, somebody lives here.
Oh, Mary lives here.
Hello, Mary!
I need...
I need... adhesive.
I don't have adhesive.
Where do I find adhesive?
I need this.
What am I crafting throwing daggers for?
Sounds tough.
What are you doing all these things and I'm just meeting Mary?
You meet Mary and I'm doing tier one shit and I'm like what?
I was told to craft stuff and then they just like...
told you to do that and I'm like...
This is...
I find this highly oppressing.
Yeah, I get to preguess the plot.
And you don't.
What the fuck is this?
This is not fair.
Oh, she has ammo and meds.
You had to craft.
She's giving me ammo and meds.
Oh shit.
What the fuck?
My bike... vehicle is damaged.
Please repair in garage.
What the fuck?
I lost my bike.
Congratulations.
Wait, you destroyed your bike?
Yes.
That's funny.
That's pretty funny.
I know.
Follow the guidance and exp...
How did you do all that?
Like...
I still have my stuff.
Oh, apparently...
I have a boss fight here.
You have a boss fight?
The fuck?
Yeah, where are you?
There's like so many...
Everybody has their campgrounds here.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What?
Where are you?
Everybody's here.
Hold on, I'm gonna find some stuff.
Is it cause you... wait, is it cause you established your campgrounds?
I don't know.
Did you do that already?
Maybe that's why.
Yeah, maybe that's why you already established your campgrounds.
So then like it just told you to go back to it.
Hold on, hold on.
I need to make some stuff.
This is a thing.
I'm gonna wait.
I don't get it.
I'm gonna wait for you at the top of the mountain.
Can I TP back to the home?
You TP'd me?
There's a boss fight apparently up here.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Guys, not wearing pants was a choice.
Hahahaha It was a choice.
My attention, I'm waiting for you.
I don't have a bike, you little man.
Just TP!
To where?
Me!
I have to do my shit first.
I have to craft my stuff.
Oh my god.
God damn it.
Alright, let's see.
I need to...
Oh my gosh, I need to hydrate really badly.
I need to hydrate really badly.
Don't worry, I'm drinking.
I'm hydrating.
Hey, Steve-o wants to join our team.
Alright, Steve-o.
Come in here.
Steve-o!
Yeah, Steve-o.
Get in here.
Alright, uh...
I'm radiated.
I gotta cure myself.
You're radiated?
What did you do?
I jumped in the fucking water.
What the fuck did you do?
Where even are you?
I jumped in the fucking water.
Oh, there you are.
You're back home.
Yeah, I'm walking home because I don't have a bike.
Wait, don't you have fast travel?
There's teleport or fucking cooldown.
Oh, well.
Alright, goodbye.
Fuck you!
Oh my god.
Everybody's campground's here.
Oh, Steve-o left our team!
Steve-o hates us.
Steve-o hates you.
What?
How dare you?
How dare he hates me?
I'm a lovable person.
What the fuck?
Alright, Z.
You go first.
And kill everybody for me.
Woah.
Go do it.
I'm mooching off this guy.
Mooching off?
When are you not?
Don't worry.
I have somebody else to do everything for me.
He's killing everybody for me now.
Must be Z.
Let's see.
There's an alligator outside of my house.
Whoops.
I alerted him accidentally.
There's an alligator outside your house?
Yeah.
Go, Kerry.
Go.
Am I finally making a pants?
Go do your thing.
No, don't make your pants.
Pants are for cowards.
I told you to make shit.
I told you to make it.
That's the thing.
I can't progress if I can't make pants.
Hey, why do you have to make pants?
I don't know.
That's what I'd like to know.
It never told me to make pants.
I'm just playing the game.
Go, rotten guy.
Go.
That's a shit ass pants.
It's not even a complete pants.
Oh my god.
I almost shot the explosive tank.
Go, guy with gun.
Go.
Boom.
That's right.
That's right, Wylo.
We're doing it.
We don't need tension.
What?
What are you actually doing right now?
Are you fighting a boss?
No, we're just walking.
There's like an area where we have to go through.
And like this guy coincidentally was also going through this area.
I'm just kidding.
So there's like a lot of enemies too.
Oh, there is loot here.
Nice.
Yeah, so like I was lucky because like he was also going through this area too.
Okay, I fucked up.
I was trying to...
I fell.
From a really high place.
Must have hurt.
Yeah.
I think that was karma.
This game took two hours to make pants.
There's like elite monsters here.
Where can I put my garage?
What do we do, Wylo?
What are you gonna shoot?
I put the garage in the weirdest place possible.
Jesus Christ.
Don't worry, Wylo.
I'm here to help.
How do I fix it?
Repair.
Irons.
I need irons.
All I'm saying, Tengen, by the time you actually do this mission, all the monsters will be dead.
Oh, there we go.
It's normal.
Okay, so the pants is now done.
Now it says meet Mary under model.
Why did I need to make pants?
I had no idea.
I didn't have to make pants.
I just progressed.
What the fuck?
No!
That's stupid.
Why did you do that?
Don't be dumb.
Alright.
Okay, I got the stuff.
All the monsters are dead by the...
Like, the majority of the monsters are dead.
So you don't have to worry about it.
Alright.
I got the shit.
Can I TP to you?
Oh, can you?
How do I teleport to you?
Nah, I'll just go to Deadspiel.
Oh yeah, no, no.
You have to TP to talk to Mary first.
And then...
Oh my god.
That's not what I wanted to do.
I wanted to loot the item.
Alright.
Oosh.
Oh!
So many mats.
Alright, let's do this.
Okay.
What's this loot?
I'm on my way.
I'm gonna talk to Mary and then I'll go to Deadspiel.
Yeah, the moment you talk to Mary...
Then you're like at my quest area.
Right.
Hello, Wile.
What are you doing?
What are you gonna do?
What?
I can't read that.
He said there's one...
Guys!
Somebody translate!
I can only read like half that sentence and he's trying to talk to me.
He's actually...
He's random actually.
He's trying to talk to me.
I don't know.
No, he's chat.
The Wile guy.
Oh.
That guy!
That guy is...
I don't know if he's trying to talk to me.
Oh, there's a level 5 big one.
Okay.
Alright.
I'm gonna go to this area.
Okay, I'm gonna make my campsite.
Where did he go?
I don't have a log.
You're such a mess right now.
You don't have a log.
No!
I lost my carry!
Oh, he's over there killing more people.
Don't worry!
I'm coming over!
Wait!
He respawned?
Yeah, because he...
Oh my god.
One of the big guys respawned.
But I need...
I need the carry.
I need the carry here.
Wait, where did he go?
Wile!
Hey.
I need you to protect me.
Oh!
You don't eat something.
Wait, what?
I'm in... something something.
Oh my gosh.
I can only read half of it.
Yeah, well it's better than none.
Wait, I think he's not talking to me.
I think he's talking to his other...
His other clanmates.
I think he's talking...
He's talking to his buddies.
Oh dude.
Not eat food.
Okay.
Where are you?
I'm on top.
Holy shit.
What is that thing?
What the fuck is that thing?
Are you here?
Yeah, I see it.
You see it?
You see the big boy?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What the fuck is that?
Oh shit, I didn't see this guy.
Oh my god.
Jesus.
I don't even see... Oh there you are.
Yeah, that's the big guy.
Look, there's the other guy.
That was my friend.
That's my friend over there.
That's his...
The fuck is that?
Oh god, come back.
You're fighting again.
I'm behind you.
Holy...
Behind you.
Okay.
Yeah.
Okay, don't worry.
I'm shooting him.
Oh...
Nice, nice, nice, nice.
Okay, we have to go to the main quest line.
See, I told you I wait for you.
Right.
I waited for you.
What are you saying?
Surely.
That wild guy.
He's nobody.
Make it easier.
Wait, that's not wild.
Oh my god, it's P Diddy.
Yeah, I know.
It's P Diddy.
Yeah, wait.
P Diddy is still doing this quest?
We were like fucking around.
We saw P...
What was P Diddy doing?
He was probably fucking around like us.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Where did Wild go?
Oh shit.
Oh hey, it's our favorite.
Oh my god, P Diddy just like...
ran across from him.
I'm shooting the legs.
Alright, you should drop down now.
Holy shit.
That's like 700 damage through a slice.
Nice.
Yeah, I'm trying not to waste too many bullets.
Yeah.
I just realized...
Alright, there it is.
Boss fight.
Oh my god.
Somebody broke their bike as well.
It's probably P Diddy.
The Monarch and his leftover public crafting facilities available.
I recommend it to team up first.
Collect supplies and discard...
Oh, what?
Catch a glimpse.
Locate the rift.
It is recommended to team up first.
Are we teamed up?
Yeah, we are.
Oh, this is like we can get materials before we go in for a boss fight.
Grab some shit.
Press Q.
Okay.
Just to see shit.
Hello, Mary.
There's a lot of stuff.
I'm gonna talk to Mary.
Speak to Mary.
You're quite good at handling deviants, aren't you?
I have an amplifier.
Rustic hat?
How does a rustic... A rustic hat?
What the fuck was that word?
How...
I think I have enough ammo.
I wonder if I can craft...
Can I craft better guns?
Yeah.
Let's see.
Oh, I can.
Never mind.
I'm literally missing waste plastic.
I must have waste plastic here.
I just need some rusted parts, actually.
Then I'll get a better gun.
Okay, let's see.
Assembling...
I think I can... I'm gonna make a shotgun.
You're gonna make a shotgun?
Yeah, I'm gonna make a shotgun.
I found it!
What do you mean how?
What the fuck?
I need... I need rustic...
material.
Let's see.
Do I have enough?
Oh, I don't!
I don't have enough waste plastic!
Do you have waste plastic?
How much is...
Where is the waste plastic?
I need two waste plastic.
What's a waste plastic?
I don't know.
I don't know how to get it.
Let's see.
Maybe I can find...
extra waste around here.
Waste plastic... I have 13.
But I think I might need it, though.
Let's see if there's extra...
equipment here.
Snap.
Is there any stuff?
I keep snapping around.
Nooooo!
Oh, wait.
There's...
med kits.
Okay, I don't need med kits, though.
Is there... is there waste plastic here?
Is there...
is there waste plastic here?
What if outside?
Oh, that's true.
Football!
Football should be a waste plastic!
Snap!
I keep snapping around.
Alright.
I'm gonna assemble this football.
Waste plastic, come on!
Metal scraps, adhesive, rubber, shabby...
Yes!
I just got waste plastic!
I need rust material.
Oh my god!
I just got rust material!
I got the two I needed!
Oh my god!
I was so lucky!
I got a shotgun.
You got a shotgun?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hold on.
I'm still looking around.
Because I need rust parts.
You need rust parts?
Have you dissembled everything?
Uh-huh.
Okay.
Nice.
I have... I have the...
unspinning shotgun.
How many bullets do I have now?
I have... oh, I have 106.
Yeehaw, Tavis!
I'm so glad.
What do you need?
The metal thing.
I don't think we can find any.
The rusted parts.
Yeah, I used up all my parts.
I found a kettle, so let's see about that.
Please.
No!
What was it?
Metal scraps.
It's too late, Tenjin.
We gotta go in.
Do you not have rusted parts?
I can check.
Let's see.
Please.
I just need one.
I'll be honest.
I got metal scrap, adhesive rubber, gunpowder, copper ore...
Rust... oh, I do!
I do!
I just need one!
How do I give you one?
How do you give items though?
This thing...
Control X.
Oh, okay.
There.
You just need one.
I discarded one.
Next to me.
Oh, that's it?
Junk.
Alright, thanks.
It's time to make a better gun.
I'm gonna say I need a heal.
I just realized.
The moment we defeat one boss, we can leave.
We'll be done with this game forever.
I mean, it's a good game, but not for us.
Not for us.
I got a gun.
Better gun.
We're like remnant players.
Yep.
We just wanna pew pew.
Oh wait, I forgot to speak Merry.
Oh, you forgot to speak Merry.
I'll just skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip.
Alright, go.
Let's go.
It's time.
How do we get there?
Where do we do it?
Why did you jump?
Why did you...
There's stairs!
There's a big stairs.
No.
There's stairs, there's stairs.
Alright, I'm in.
Are you...
Do you go in with me?
Yeah.
You have to do the action.
Also, please select the correct difficulty.
Oh, I don't know.
Wait.
Alright, you ready?
How do we get in?
Uhhh...
Wait, do we not...
Do we not just go in?
Oh my god, the level 50 and 60.
I committed four plays.
Oh, wait!
It's cause...
It's cause number 6.
We're gonna kick you out for one second.
Okay.
We need to kick number 6 out for one second.
Number 6!
Okay, we're gonna add Motoko in here and then we're gonna kick number 6.
We will give you... We'll put you back in soon.
Number 6.
Okay.
We need to do this.
We need to do the rift.
Okay.
There we go.
Oh yeah.
I don't even know what we're fighting.
We're fighting some level 10 monster.
Oh.
What the fuck?
It's like some stranger things.
You know, it's like stranger things.
They're on the other side.
Right.
You are truly a great one.
What?
Mercy, please!
What the fuck?
Even without their submission.
Oh!
We are still legion!
What the fuck?
Damn.
Yeah, it looks like it's Souls game boss.
Oh, there he is!
Oh!
Which one is the weak point?
The head.
We'll fuck around about that.
It's the head.
Good to know.
Whoa!
It's still the head.
Yeah.
I'm doing more damage on the side than it says the fucking critical point.
Oh my god.
I wanna hit the head with the shotgun but like...
Oh shit!
Oh my god!
Wait, are you...
Give me that!
Where did he go?
Oh, he's up in the...
He has another mini gun.
Illuminate the spawners.
The spawners?
What does it look like?
It looks like an egg.
Oh, I see, I see it!
Shoot it!
Shoot the spawner!
I am!
Oh, he's got... We got the other spawner.
Oh, there he is.
He's back.
Oh, what the fuck?
He's TPing.
Okay.
Catch me!
Ow!
Here you go.
He caught me.
Oh my god.
I'm behind him.
That's fucking right.
No, I'm thirsty!
No!
No, this is the wrong time to be thirsty!
Drink your hot tea, you...
I need a hydrate!
It does more damage on the melee.
Alright, give me that!
I'm gonna...
Melee, melee, melee!
It's huge damage!
No!
Holy shit.
I'm so fucking slow.
Oh my... She has a different gun now!
No!
Holy shit.
I used the mini gun and it destroyed the egg.
Holy fuck, that's so fast.
Yeah.
Alright, he's in front of you.
He's in front of you.
Oh, he's behind us.
He has a different gun now.
It's a rocket launcher!
Holy shit!
It's explosives!
You're just taking everything.
Ow.
Oh my god, Mono!
No, you're gonna die, Mono!
Mono!
You're crazy!
Oh my god, he reloaded.
Oh my god.
Shit.
Oh, where'd he go?
He's almost dead though.
Boom!
Okay.
Call this RPG, I wanna shoot it!
I'm trying!
I'm gonna shoot that fucking RPG out of his hand.
You wanna shoot the RPG?
I'm shooting the arm!
You know what?
I'm gonna use a fucking axe.
I'm gonna use the axe!
I'm gonna use the pickaxe!
Bro, he's like 1 HP!
This guy's gonna die with the pickaxe.
Yay!
I killed him with the pickaxe.
He did it!
Okay, I want control max gain.
Whoa!
That's a lot of stuff.
I got an AK.
Oh wait, what's this?
Chastic secure?
Okay, do I get it?
I got it.
It's a new deviation.
I got a new devia- Do we get a new deviation?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh shit.
Okay, Motoko.
Thanks for- Oh I did it!
Oh my god, it's so cute!
It's like a frog!
It looks dumb.
Yeah, it looks so stupid.
Alright.
Uh, gee.
Are you ready to leave?
Wait, I'm gonna snap my fingers just in case.
Alright, I wanna see the- Oh my god, you're like 1 HP.
Yeah.
Oh, Motoko left.
Motoko- Honestly, this is a decent game.
Yeah, this is- I think when you get to play the bosses, the dungeons, it's actually pretty decent.
It's fun.
It doesn't feel- Well, it depends on how you play it.
Cause it- You know, games nowadays just kinda feel like a chore instead of playing it.
And just- This is- Depends on how you fuckin' play it, I guess.
But- Yeah, the start is too slow.
I agree.
Too slow.
The start to get to this part is too slow.
You don't have a pants.
Yeah, what's wrong with that?
I thought having no pants was the best part.
There's sanity gummies?
The ba- Uh, what does it do?
Oh, pl- Do I have sanity levels?
Where's my sanity levels?
Oh!
It's for the, uh, what do you call it?
The radiation.
Oh!
Yeah, cause you're getting radiation all the time.
It helps you.
Alright.
Find chrono cage and a monolith of greed in the basement.
On the- What's- Oh, it's this.
Investigate.
I'm investigating right next to you.
I'm investigating.
Yeah, the part where we actually get to shoot our gun is fun.
Oh!
What the fuck?
I didn't expect there's you.
Yeah, I'm here with you.
Hey, Mr. Ko.
I did it!
I don't know why I was so worried.
Okay.
Thank you.
It's a call.
This really means a lot to me.
The fluctuations in Stardust seem to have grown calmer.
Yes, I did it.
And I feel stronger now.
The more deviations we contain, the more the world will stabilize.
And the more Mitsuko's power can grow.
We still have five more monoliths to shut down.
Until then, the physical world remains too dangerous for Mitsuko.
Yes, but this is already a huge step forward.
Yeah, for chill- For chill game, it's alright.
Yeah!
It's a nice, like, chill hangout game with friends.
Mm-hmm.
What about the other game?
What's that thing called?
Remnant?
No, no, no, no.
The First Descendant.
Have you tried that?
The First Descendant?
I heard it's like Warframe and Destiny.
Yeah, it's Warframe, Destiny... shit.
Yeah,
it's Warframe, Destiny... shit.
I mean, I feel like if there was more dungeons...
I think people would like the dungeon part is like fun in general.
It is.
Yeah.
I can see.
Especially when you get like take their guns.
I thought that was fu- Oh,
wait, we're back here.
Loot time.
Chat, is there like another dungeon we can go straight to?
If there is another dungeon we can go straight to, like, I don't mind doing one more dungeon.
Yeah, me too.
Yeah.
I just need one more.
Cool.
Hmm.
Snap.
Snapping just...
To be fair, the story is horrible.
I do not think we are playing this game for the story.
We're just here to goof.
Yeah, we're just here to... we're just here to shoot our gun.
Snap.
Where are you supposed to go?
Open the... to unlock the bronze crafting.
Okay, we need bronze?
I did that and then I have to go back to the dungeon.
To the personal territory?
Um, bronze and unlock the garage?
Wait, where's the bronze?
I have a garage already.
What the fuck?
How did you have all that?
Because I don't know.
My bike broke.
I need to make it.
Oh.
Secure for starting journey.
Securement unit.
Can I have two securemen- uh, hold on.
And unlock everything?
And then you unlock, open, and unlock the garage?
I can make more than two.
That's cool.
I need to open the garage?
Where the fuck's the garage?
In my garage.
I'm still thirsty?
Why am I always thirsty?
Why am I still thirsty?
Okay, there's the garage.
Okay, back to the personal territory.
Okay.
I'm just gonna... I'm gonna TP.
You know shit.
Yeah.
TP time.
Alright.
Alright, number six.
Get back in here.
Number six.
Number six, get back into the team.
Oh my god!
97%!
We're almost there!
Number six, you're doing great.
Okay, let's see.
I need enough?
I need glass.
Okay, I need ten glass.
Okay, I'm gonna mooch off your furnace.
Yeah, 97.
Okay, we need to invite number six.
Can you invite number six into our group?
I think you can.
Oh, I have to do it?
Okay, hi.
I invited him.
Okay.
Nice.
Alright.
Uh, I need to use your furnace.
I'm too lazy to make my own furnace.
The fuck?!
What do you mean, what the fuck?
You have a furnace, so I need to use it!
Right.
You might as well.
We're sharing this.
Uh-huh.
Okay, I need like nine glass.
I wanna put the other guy... I wanna put the slime guy in my backpack.
Weee.
Is there another dungeon that's not story related that we can just like run to?
There.
Is it in there?
Oh my god, it is!
I see him!
Oh my god, he's so ugly!
Look at him!
I don't see him!
What?
Come on!
He's so ugly!
He looks like he has googly eyes on!
What an ugly little guy!
Look at him!
Ugly baby!
Baby man!
He's in my bag!
Wait, I wanna see, I wanna see what does he look like.
Oh my... what the...
What the fuck?
He looks stupid.
He looks... I swear he looks so stupid.
He looks so stupid.
I'm gonna put him in my backpack too.
Look at that baby man.
Okay.
What about the other one?
Yeah, put the disco ball.
Disco ball.
Yeah, I don't see it.
Why is it not...
Like visible?
What the fuck?
Alright.
Well, there you go.
Talk to Samuel Logue.
What does he do?
Upon being thrown, it knocks back.
Oh, I can throw it?
What the fuck?
Oh, it like blocks attacks apparently.
Look at this ugly baby.
Turn off world chat this whole fucking time.
Why would you wanna turn off world chat?
He makes a wall and it heals when you use him.
Oh!
That's so good!
That's good.
I like how somebody was like, I don't want to join your team.
Alright.
Is there like a dungeon that we can go without having to do the story, guys?
There is a dungeon I can do it right now.
Where was it anyway?
Was it Monolith of Grief?
Was that the one we did?
The Monolith of Greed?
That's what we did, yes.
So, it should be like anything like Monolith related.
It's basically like the dungeons.
Yep.
There's one that's level 15.
The Monolith Danger Zone.
I'm not even level 10 yet.
You know?
I know it's crazy, but I'm not even level 10 yet.
I'm thirsty.
Oh, we have to activate all these Monoliths to access one of them.
Oh!
I get it!
So, you see...
Remember when we were activating Monoliths and stuff?
And then, when you activate all of these anchors, like the Rift Anchor, it summons one Monolith to do a dungeon.
I see.
Oh!
I see now.
Yeah, I don't think I'm going to do that.
We had a good time.
We played this a lot longer than I thought.
Yeah, we lasted three hours.
That was pretty good for us.
Yeah.
For an FPS person who has a very short span of attention.
For attention span.
Yeah.
Yeah, honestly, not bad.
Honestly, it looks decent.
Yeah, let's check out numbers...
These kind of mechanics.
Number 6's work.
Come on, Tengen, let's go.
Is it done?
I'm pretty sure... it's 90... 97.
You know what?
It's almost done.
It's good enough.
It's missing a beam.
There, I fixed it.
98.
It's done.
It's 98.
And then it's missing a window.
It's missing one window or something.
Yeah, it's missing one window on top.
Oh, it is!
Wait, do you have it?
I don't have a glass.
No, none of us have glass.
Literally 2%.
It's missing one window.
And...
He just...
He...
He made...
Because the stair...
Okay, essentially it's done since the stair is bugged and cannot be built.
He built a different kind of stair.
Look at this.
He made a different fucking kind of stair.
That's smart.
We did it!
Yeah!
Guys!
It's just missing this window right here.
Guys, we did it!
Guys, we finished the game!
Holy shit.
Look at how tall my house is!
Honestly, the world is nice.
It is beautiful when it's fucking daytime.
What the fuck?
Number 6 did it!
Oh, it's...
Congratulations, number 6!
Look at that.
What did he do?
He gets the pride of having a Finnish house in a game that may or may not die in a month.
Don't say that.
It's...
You have the power to fight back.
I don't.
What do you mean you're indie?
What do you mean?
You're indie.
You wanna see?
You wanna speak to the alligator?
You're indie.
What do you mean?
You're speaking to the alligator?
Oh my god, look at him.
Why does he have like a backpack?
What is that?
Oh no, it's not.
It's just like...
Hello.
Hello, guys.
Oh yeah.
He's chill.
He's so chill now.
Ow!
Oh, he's not chill now.
Are you scared?
You just had to say it.
Dungeon, why are you scared?
What are you scared about?
I'm not.
Just speak your mind.
Uh...
I wish I'm happy.
Ow!
Fuck.
Speak your mind about this game.
Speak my mind about...
Um...
Well, honestly, again, it's...
It's okay.
The game's okay.
But I don't know if it'll last long.
You need to deal with it.
But then, let's just be honest.
There we go.
It's not too hard.
Alright, goodbye.
Goodbye, alligator.
Goodbye.
Die.
You die now.
We're gonna eat you up.
Om nom nom.
Nom nom nom.
You ever had alligator meat?
Uh, no, I don't...
Wait, have you?
Are there alligators in Indonesia?
I had.
Wait, there's alligators in Indonesia?
Crocodiles.
Yeah, that's not alligator.
Well, it's the same shit.
Just different smells.
What is this?
I want to build...
Okay, I summon them.
Look at him!
Oh my god, look guys!
It's Call of Duty!
Holy shit.
You can...
Oh my...
Honestly, this guy...
I can see he's more of a PvP.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's more of a PvP.
He looks so dumb!
He looks so dumb, I swear to god.
He looks super fucking dumb.
What the fuck?
I swear he looks super fucking dumb.
I wait, summon yours!
I don't have...
Oh, I'm not using that shit.
You don't have...
Oh my god, why does this guy exist?
Like, oh my god.
It's Call of Duty.
So I was like, he's so skew- Alright, let's see.
Secure it.
Flawless fortification?
Build fortification?
I don't remember which one I threw.
I threw the one on the right.
Oh my god.
There we go.
The face is here.
Whoa!
You can throw him!
Yeah!
Yeah, you can throw him and then I can be like...
Oh, and then he's gone.
He's gone.
He looks so dumb.
I swear, he is so dumb.
Oh my god.
Yeah, he looks like a good for PvP.
That was fun though.
I'm not sure if I can get him.
That was fun.
Like, I'm glad I did not do the solo.
I'm going to- You didn't have to suffer a game for a while.
I think if I played the solo, I would not have made it to the boss.
You would not have figured out the game.
Yeah.
Tengen has helped me figure out the game.
GG's, Tengen.
We're three hours of sleep.
GG's.
Oh yeah, that's true.
You were using your head more than me.
Yes.
Even though you had three hours of sleep.
You know, I remember correctly you asked to play X-Deviant.
I don't know what the fuck happened to that, but now it's here.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Because like, you know, X-Deviant was...
X-Deviant has already died, so...
Oh, I see.
That's funny.
So I was like, yo, let's just check out this game.
It's launching.
And it's free too.
You know.
X-Deviant is also free?
Yeah, but like, this game is new.
It literally launched today.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
Totally.
Like, it just launched.
Not today, but like...
Don't...
But like, eight hours ago.
Guys, when was the last...
Guys, chat.
When was the last time you watched a streamer play X-Deviant?
Don't lie to me.
You know what?
You're so right.
Dude, like, I can say this with confidence.
There's more Tarkov streamers than X-Deviant.
Whoa!
Despite the Tarkov and the Tarkov...
Got cancelled.
It still has more players.
That's a little sad.
Honestly, if X-Deviant had a better server, probably.
Wow, I mean, a lot of games are basically, if they have better servers, it could be good.
True.
Yeah.
It's just, you know, they just didn't put enough resources into it.
But even then, I don't think there's been...
I mean, we haven't had a game that's been, like, that's done well in the last four years, I think?
Five.
In the last four to five years, we haven't had a shooter game that's done well that was gonna be, like, the next big video game.
Like...
I'm pretty sure.
Yeah, they all tried to claim that shit.
I can't...
What was the last one?
I think Apex.
Apex was the last one.
And I think...
And then Rem Royale almost was, like, the next big thing, and then they killed it.
Yeah.
The Rem Royale was at the same level as Apex at one point, and then they killed Rem Royale.
Because...
Well, Overwatch is pretty huge, I guess, right now.
Overwatch has been around for so long.
That's the thing, though.
Yeah, but it's been for a long...
Oh, wait, Valorant!
Valorant was the last next big...
Yeah, Valorant was the last game.
Valorant is kind of dying, to be honest.
I haven't even touched that game.
Because the direction of the game is kind of...
Valorant is mostly about cosmetics.
It's the last game.
Yeah, but it's a lie because of cosmetics and the eSports scene.
ESports scene?
Bro, it's fucking Bumble.
It's fucking eDate app.
No!
It's where you find...
Yeah.
And that's why Overwatch was so successful.
Right.
I forgot about that.
Overwatch walked so Valorant could run.
Sorry.
Overwatch.
Oh, my God.
You reminded me of stuff that I don't remember.
Overwatch walked for the eDating scene so Valorant could fucking sprint to the finish line.
Oh, my God.
Overwatch walked for the eDating scene so Valorant could fucking sprint to the finish I forgot about that.
Overwatch created the eCouple pet names for accounts.
Oh, my God.
What was it?
Kitten and...
I don't remember.
The Mercy players would be Kitten and then the DPS player would be like Daddy.
Oh, my God.
I hate this.
They would have...
You hate it because it's true.
I hate this.
Yeah, I hate it because it's true.
Of course.
You know?
No.
Guys, it started on Overwatch.
It did not start on Discord.
I mean...
When was Overwatch?
2016?
2016, I think so.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know like Overwatch and then they did the workshop thing and then people did the Overwatch workshop and then added Tinder on Overwatch.
I'm tired of this, this is stupid.
People would be like, ew, Valorant created the cringe e-dating account names, but it was Overwatch that started it.
With the Mercy and Flash DPS duos.
Wasn't there a certain website that's like, Overwatch has the most searched fucking result?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, because of like SFM.
Yep.
That's insane.
Honestly insane.
Holy shit.
Way to go community.
I used to believe it.
RuneScape did it before.
RuneScape was like, was like a, what's the word?
RuneScape was more of a niche, but Overwatch made it mainstream.
I'm just a merchant.
RuneScape, like the e-couple dating scene in RuneScape was a niche, but in Overwatch it was a lifestyle.
Like, it means you're good at the game kind of shit.
The fucking LFG look, Mercy main looking for DPS player.
Oh my god, the global chat.
You have the LFG?
The LFG.
The global chat.
Stop reminding me of global chat.
Fuck.
Oh man.
Oh fuck, there is a global chat in Overwatch.
I forgot about that.
No, the LFG, not just the global chat, but the LFG section where people were like looking for players to play with.
And then they would do like LFGs for like the Mercy or the DPS players.
Like top 500 DPS player on Smurf account looking for Mercy pocket.
Oh my god.
Everybody blocked it from their heads because they don't want to remember.
But I will always remember the dark times of Overwatch.
Oh my god, I already forgot about most of it.
My PTSD is resurfacing.
And they would be like, do you have mic?
Oh shut the fuck up.
That's why when people are like, ew, Valorant is so cringe because of the e-dating scene.
And I was like, you guys don't remember real cringe.
Overwatch had it a lot worse.
Oh man.
Overwatch created the nightmare.
I feel like I just relived the life that I didn't have and turns out I had it and this is there.
Holy fuck.
Oh my god.
I saw the cringe.
Enough YouTube for today.
I saw the cringe being made since day zero.
I was there at day zero when the cringe started.
Oh yeah, the Genji and Mercy.
Before then, it was the Genji and Mercy duels.
That's what made it worse.
I'm a Genji main.
Yeah.
That's what made it worse.
Fucking shit.
Hell no.
Hell bro.
Genji main looking for a Mercy duo.
But is Overwatch worth to play again though?
Yeah.
It's worth to play.
Don't take it seriously.
It's not as competitive anymore.
I would have to pay a few dollars to change my name.
That's...
Yeah, you do.
I'm still on that name.
Yeah.
I'm working on it.
Don't worry.
I had to change several accounts.
I had to change several account names.
I was like, I'm trying to change it.
And I was like, oh shit, I gotta pay this?
Yeah, you don't have your free one because you used it already.
I used it years ago, man.
I was there on day one as well.
Fuck.
It's okay.
I believe in you.
Right.
Honestly.
You just know...
Okay.
You can just put streamer mode on and then you never have to change it.
The streamer mode on changes your actual name.
The name of the account.
You just put streamer mode on and then you don't have...
Your name will always be like different every time.
Oh shit.
Yeah.
But yeah, I wish...
I hope there's...
I hope there's a new game soon.
Honestly.
I know.
I hope there's a new shooter.
But I think Valorant was the last... the last like big competitive FPS game.
And even now, I'll be honest, Valorant... the direction is kind of weird.
So...
And I mean, I don't play that.
I mean, it's mostly like I said, it's... it's from Riot and Riot is mostly like cosmetics.
And...
Yeah.
They put a heavy focus on cosmetic because that's where the money is.
And every time...
I see that.
Yeah.
Because like Riot loves having cosmetics and stuff, but like, I don't know.
It's just...
I feel like...
Other than that, I don't really know what other like shooter game has been out there.
It's been decent.
Shranova, guys.
Shranova...
It's...
It's interesting, but like...
It's also a tactical shooter.
So...
Yeah.
DB and...
Shranova...
The paper mechanic is really interesting.
But like...
It...
It like...
Okay.
I think Shranova is easier than Valorant.
A hundred percent.
Because I learned the abilities...
The ability usage faster than Valorant.
I still don't know how to use the abilities in Valorant, but like, I know how to use the abilities in Shranova.
But I think like Shranova...
I think the main...
Biggest issue of Shranova is like...
Is just that fact that like...
Um...
It's just...
The mechanics itself is like...
A little...
Weird.
It's like the paper mechanics is like...
Really weird to handle.
Because you can use the paper mechanics...
Right now...
I'm just on Gacha Games...
It's not a Gacha Game...
Because I'm so bored.
Because...
I know.
I'm just bored.
I'm on the Gacha Games right now.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
I think like Shranova.
The biggest issue with Shranova is that...
The hardcore gamers...
I think the FPS gamers will not play Stranova because it's anime.
Right.
Yeah, because I saw that Stranova is really popular amongst people who are into Genshin Impact and Gacha in general.
Because a lot of people that are playing Stranova were mostly just like, Who the fuck cut that tree?
What?
The tree fell on top of me.
But Stranova, people who played it were people who played Genshin Impact and stuff like that.
And they were like, oh I love Stranova because it's a game that is different from Genshin, but it's an FPS game.
Or not FPS, TPS.
But I saw in general, not a lot of the competitive scene.
The...
Yeah, the osu!
play.
The osu!
players and the Genshin...
The Gacha players love Stranova.
But if you talk about the competitive shooter fanbase, I barely saw anybody was hyping it up.
So I think that was the biggest issue.
Because the fanbase for shooter games, especially in the West, if they see anime, they're just like, ugh.
Yeah, no shit.
Because there's a lot of normies there.
I'm in the same period.
Normies are like, ugh, anime.
They'll be like, ugh, Call of Duty, Apex, Battle Run, Call of Duty, Battlefield.
But when they see anime, even if it's a good shooter, they'll just be like, ugh, anime.
It's true!
When I got invited to the tournament, I literally had like...
I did not see Shroud play Stranova.
I did not see Timmy or Shroud play Stranova.
And Shroud would play every FPS...
Shroud would play any shooter game.
But I didn't see Shroud play Stranova.
So I thought that was like...
That basically sort of tells you what the normal playerbase would want to watch.
Oh yeah, Deadlock.
Fucking Valve's upcoming game.
Something like that.
Oh yeah, yeah, Deadlock, yeah.
Hopefully that's okay.
Deadlock?
Is Deadlock the newest Valve game, right?
Valve upcoming.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's...
Wait, I don't remember what I'm allowed or not allowed to say.
What?
Insane.
That's insane.
I think you just said something...
You shouldn't say, but okay.
I guess that's all I'll say.
There you go, chat.
No way.
Oh my god.
I didn't say anything.
I just said, Deadlock is.
That's all I said.
Right.
Right, right, right, right.
Interesting.
Totally, totally.
I can back that up.
Yeah.
She just said that and that's it.
She didn't say anything of it.
Interesting.
Yeah.
We heard nothing, guys.
That's funny.
Whose house is this?
What the heck?
Whose house?
Yeah, who the fuck built their house above us?
Where did this guy come from?
Oh, wait.
It's this guy's house.
Hey.
Without their permission.
Oh my god.
He doesn't have pants either.
Wait.
He's literally in his underwear.
Just like us.
Wait.
No.
Take off your pants right now.
What?
Damn.
Everybody else has no pants except you and number six.
Because the number six is...
Goddamn shit that has told me to not wear any fucking... to wear... what do you call it?
You gotta join the crowd.
Holy shit.
I can be naked naked.
Look.
Wait.
What the fuck?
Can I be naked naked?
Wait.
What the fuck?
You can do that?
There's like pants underneath the pants?
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Wait.
You're right.
How do I unequip it?
Oh my god.
Holy shit.
Look at that.
Oh my god.
Holy shit.
Oh my god!
Yeah!
It's possible!?
Okay...
Now put pants back on him.
Holy shit.
Oh my god.
What the fuck?
You can go beyond.
You're chilling.
Oh, why?
You can go beyond.
Oh my god.
Yeah, I do hope Trinova does do well in the future.
And like the normie shooter people would enjoy it because it is interesting.
I feel like if the normies tried Trinova and are not like, ugh anime and stuff like that, I think it could go really well because the game and mechanics are pretty interesting.
And like I hope they have the Overwatch mode as a ranking too.
Because the ranked game is Valorant.
Quick Play is Overwatch, which I thought was pretty silly.
Like...
I feel like both the Overwatch section and the Valorant section should be its own thing.
They shouldn't make one as Quick Play and the other as Rank.
Oh yeah, and then apparently the Overwatch mode was super imbalanced too because like it's like defense-sided.
Which I agree when I played it, it was 100% defense-sided.
Because it's so hard to like play attack on the maps.
Yeah, I saw a little bit of game plan.
Yeah.
Oh, Marvel Rivals.
I hope Marvel Rivals does well, honestly.
Yeah, yeah, I got you in Marvel Rivals.
Yeah.
Yeah, you got me in and I didn't play that much since the server is only available.
Because it was pretty unstable for me.
Holy shit.
But I enjoyed it so far, especially in the training.
Yeah.
Holy fuck.
Yeah, but then it's gonna...
The complexity of the heroes...
Oh, I...
Do you hear it?
The next beta test is next week, right?
The Asia server, yeah.
Next week or in two weeks, I think.
Yeah.
The next beta test.
I'm definitely gonna try it again for the next test.
I definitely had a lot of fun with Marvel Rivals, but the official game comes out in 2025.
That's still a long way.
Yeah, so like...
We gotta wait until 2025 to play the game.
Yeah.
Welcome to our like impromptu podcast, guys.
Sorry.
Yeah.
Like for... Nah, for me it's normal.
Because every game is just basically free talk for me.
Yeah.
Legit.
From here.
Out of the gate is...
Get away.
Yeah, I hope... I hope... I hope...
Uh...
Marvel Rivals is also successful because...
Like we need a new game for the shooters.
We're just so...
It's just been like...
We're all bouncing between...
Like we're all like bouncing to game to game to game trying to find a new game to play.
Like for me right now, if it's just stupid FPS, it's just again Tarkov.
The fuck is this?
It's just Tarkov, Apex or Overwatch.
And then for...
And then if you're like a tactical shooter, Valorant.
Look, I'm just like...
I don't care.
Whatever it takes for someone to get back to their lobbies or me to my back at my lobbies.
Yeah.
I'm sorry for those who are like...
As soon as possible without listening to shit.
What about CSGO?
Guys, you know...
Or CSGO 2.
I play...
Guys, you know CS is...
I play CS 2.
CS 2 is...
But...
Is only alive in Europe.
You guys don't lie.
It's...
It's alive in EU and Asia.
Yeah, it's...
But...
Yeah.
But I don't know about NA.
But...
And it...
No, it's dead.
It's like almost dead in NA.
Because the only thing I do in CS 2 now is just to sell and buy items.
Like how I used to.
And yeah, I'm up like $300 in CS already.
Yeah.
I haven't cashed it out.
Don't people like use like...
Like CSGO and CS 2 like skins and knives to like...
What's the word?
Like...
What's the word when they...
When they like use it for like money...
Trade?
Trade money legally?
RMT?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
There's like a word for it.
For those who trade money laundering.
Yeah.
A lot of people use...
Money laundering?
You guys do know that?
A lot of people use like CSGO and CS 2 skins for like money laundering.
That's why like sometimes knives go for like in crazy prices.
Because they use it for money laundering.
You know that?
I mean...
I heard.
So I heard.
But like...
Man.
The most expensive thing I had is just like $210 and that's it.
Yeah.
That's what I...
Like I know like they do that as well.
Because like...
They used to do that for like art galleries.
So like in art galleries...
Some art pieces go for like millions of dollars, but it's usually a money laundering scheme.
Like you see like very expensive paintings being sold at art galleries, but it's not really...
They're not really selling the painting.
They're just using it for like money laundering.
So they do that, but with like CSGO skins too.
Or they still do.
They still do, but it's like another way to do money laundering.
But like...
You know, they won't...
People are like, we can't confirm or deny that.
Or like tax evasion.
Yeah, I guess too.
I love tax evasion.
Huh?
Oh, and you said I said something that could be...
Potentially illegal, but you just said I love tax evasion.
Huh?
No, no, no, no.
I pay my taxes.
Do you?
I buy cigarettes.
That's a huge amount of tax.
It's crazy.
No, but...
But actually, oh yeah, I actually quit smoking.
I'm trying...
Wait, you quit...
Oh, you're trying to, right?
It's like my...
It's like my second week.
And I'm...
Your second week?
Mm-hmm.
I'm trying to...
Holy shit, are you okay?
No.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Yeah, how long have you been smoking?
How long have I been smoking?
Yeah.
Like the whole...
12 years.
Oh my God, good luck, man.
Yeah.
I believe in you.
Especially like for like an Asian guy, like it's so hard to quit smoking.
Yep.
Yeah, because like it's like sort of like...
What's it called?
Like a culture.
Yeah.
Like a culture sort of type deal.
The reason why I'm quitting is not because of health reasons.
Because it's getting expensive.
Financial.
And the taste...
Not just that.
But the number one for me, like I honestly, if the taste is all right, I'll probably still going.
But the taste is shit and they charge more.
So I'm like, what is this shit?
You don't taste like you used to.
Fuck you.
I'm buying this.
I'm mad.
I even called their customer support.
So it's like a boycott.
It's like a boycott for you.
What the hell, man?
Good luck, man.
I think you can do it.
If you like dedicate...
And you should also like look at how much you save just to motivate yourself too.
Is it bad that I go to coffee instead now?
Because like...
Well, like drinking excessive amount of coffee is not healthy, but...
Well, no shit.
No shit.
But it's healthier than smoking.
It doesn't fuck up your lungs.
It just fucks up your heart.
Well, shit.
Yeah, well, I don't drink that much of a coffee.
I mean, I'm starting to learn how to brew itself and grinding it and shit.
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
That's pretty good.
What the fuck?
What is that cover?
It's another crocodile.
Jesus Christ.
What the fuck?
This game is freaky.
It's just the crocodile out of nowhere.
Yeah, like as long as like, you know, it's like healthier than smoking.
And I think like if you track down like how much money you spent, like there are saved each week from it, I think it'll motivate you even more.
Yeah.
Because for me right now, I don't even buy like those nicotine patches or anything.
So...
Yeah.
I'm just straight drawing it.
Holy cold turkey.
You're just...
Cold turkey.
And then I'm thinking, what if I buy like, what do you call it?
A vape, but like the juice is not like without the nicotine, you know?
Yeah.
But vaping is also like similar though.
It's just going from one addiction to another.
It's just the nicotine.
The thing is the nicotine is fucking me up and I don't...
But isn't vaping more expensive?
Because you're buying like refills.
Yeah.
Honestly, it's cheaper.
Oh, it's cheaper?
Okay.
I was just thinking like...
I know like vaping can become more expensive.
Yeah.
Especially there's no nicotine.
Like...
Yeah.
So it's not taxed.
But vaping is also bad too.
Everything is bad in life.
Yeah.
But caffeine is better than vaping.
Right.
That's true.
Yeah.
You might as well do like caffeine instead of vaping because it's like...
It's like healthier.
Well, I mean like quote unquote healthier.
It's the healthier addiction.
Like to like...
It's the lesser evil.
Yeah.
The lesser of all evil.
The lesser of three evils.
Like...
I don't know.
It's pretty...
All in moderation.
Yeah.
It's how we know.
Like caffeine is bad.
Number six is so real.
But like if...
If like he has to pick between caffeine, cigarettes or vaping.
I'd rather just cut caffeine I guess.
Yeah.
Like we have...
Like because like I don't think Tenjin can like...
He could try but I feel like it's better to just like swap to like a lesser harmful addiction than going like full on cold turkey because that's also not good for you.
To just completely stop.
Yeah.
Like for the...
For the four...
First four days when I sleep, my leg just...
Yeah.
Trembles so fucking much and I woke up with a sore leg because of like the excessive shakiness like holy shit.
Like going cold turkey like quitting suddenly all of a sudden is really, really bad too.
Oh yeah.
So it's better to like do it like in moderation and like less...
Yeah.
And like less stressful than just like stopping altogether.
And then like...
Yeah.
And then if caffeine gets pretty bad, you're...
Then like he can slowly try and stop that.
And then you can swap to tea after coffee.
I do tea sometimes.
Tea or coffee.
Yeah.
That's good.
Tea is also pretty healthy.
I'm more of a...
I'm more of a both of worlds.
It's just that I need the more of a little bit more of a kick because...
Yeah.
Either way for me, tea or coffee, I will shit in either way.
I think that's for everybody.
That's what caffeine does.
Yes.
It's the same for...
Like my mom especially, she buys like high caffeinated tea leaves and I'm like, Jesus, man.
Like I keep insisting drink less or something like this, like blue tea or some stuff.
And she's like, no.
Oh yeah.
We need those extra like the Kung Fu tea, you know, like wah.
Yeah.
No.
People are like, don't start smoking.
It's very hard to...
No, that's true.
That's true.
It's very hard to quit smoking because it's just going cold turkey is like really like not cold turkey, but like, but like just stopping it.
And it's like, like I know like in like for my family, like majority is like, like my uncles, my uncles, my dad, my grandparents, they all smoked because it was like, like a bonding thing.
You know, I don't know what it was for you, but like for like my family, like they would like share cigarettes and stuff for like a bonding thing and a talk while smoking.
And stuff like that.
Oh, it's definitely normal.
Yeah.
Social smoking is a thing.
I might just do that.
Yeah.
So it's like very hard to quit and stuff.
It's like a huge cultural thing too.
So I like grew up around like a family that smoked a lot.
Yeah.
I mean same.
So it's hard to quit.
Especially.
That's why I became a smoker.
Yeah.
Like it's really hard to, because like it's hard to quit just cause like, like, you know, your entire family smoking as well.
So it's like, it's like, you know, like you're surrounded by a presence of smokers.
So it's like hard to suddenly stop smoking just cause you know, uh, just cause like, you know, it's awkward.
So like.
Yeah, it is.
Yeah.
So, but like.
And the other reason is that why I'm stopping smoking, cause apparently I'm the only one left who just still smokes.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Cause everybody slowly stops smoking for your family.
Like all of my cousins has got married and they have a son and a child now.
So I just stopped and I'm like.
What the fuck?
Shit.
The fuck am I doing?
My dad didn't stop.
Your dad didn't stop?
Oh, oh same.
Same.
Yeah.
Dad didn't stop smoking.
Dad, my dad didn't stop.
Yeah.
But he stopped.
I don't smoke though.
I don't smoke.
He, he, he.
He smoked for more than 30 years and he stopped like 2014 or 13.
My dad's so going.
He hasn't inhaled any of those in years.
It's crazy.
What the fuck?
Hey, did your dad also stop smoking too, crocodile?
Yeah.
But yeah, no.
He's fine.
No, when I was growing up, like my dad would like, uh, he would like, uh, I would smoke I think like, he wouldn't smoke in front of me, but like, I could smell the smoke, you know?
And then...
The worst, probably for me, is when we're going on a trip.
He smokes while driving.
And he just opens the window.
Oh!
Oh my god!
That feels like 2000 Asian dad right there!
Hell yeah!
Yeah, yeah, no, my dad, he would just like, go outside like, the balcony, or just go outside the smoke.
He used to like, just...
Like, go to like, the bathrooms to smoke.
Just because like, he didn't want to bring it in the house and stuff.
Yeah, because there's a fucking exhaust.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I remember like...
Because like, I remember when I was really young, because like, you know, I was raised in Canada.
And then, you know, they're like, Smokey's really, really bad!
Like, it's so bad!
I mean, it is bad, but like, it's like, in your face more so than like...
Like, it was like, it's like, so in your face.
So I would be like, stop smoking!
And then...
And then, I don't know if you've ever seen, you know, like, those museums where it's like...
It's like, those like, human body museum, where...
You know, you know what I'm talking about?
It shows like, oh, the body of a smoker.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
And then they're like, this is the lungs of a smoker!
And this is like, the lungs of a person who doesn't smoke!
And then I would point, and then we would visit those museums, and I'd be like, Dad, that's you!
These are your lungs!
I used to do that.
And then I became a smoker, and I saw it, and I just laughed.
And then, oh my god.
Yeah, I mean like, yeah, I don't... like, he used to, when I was younger, I noticed it more, but like, I think as I got older, like, he... my dad...
My dad does like, go outside, like, try to hide it more in front of me.
Then... but he hasn't quit yet.
Yeah.
Honestly, for me, as a kid, I didn't get, what the fuck, why is he smoking?
It's just wasting money, even though it was so dirt cheap back then.
It was 50 cents.
Oh yeah, like, Indonesia, yeah.
Yeah, it was like 50 cents.
And then, now it's like $2.
It's still cheap, but holy fuck, it's expensive in Indonesia.
Is it like taxes, or just like, trying to make people stop smoking?
It's both.
And either way, there's always a cheaper cigarette.
Yeah.
Literally.
But my... the one I smoke, it's like $2.
Yeah, like, yeah, it's just a lot of money to spend.
It's like... it's like a whole meal for the day.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh yeah, I understand.
Well, I hope it works.
I hope it works out for you.
Yeah.
Because you would save a lot of money, and also be healthier too.
Oh, definitely.
I started to make, like, every time I think...
Should I buy a cigarette?
I will just straight up open my mobile banking and just deposit to another saving for the same price of the cigarette.
That's smart.
That's really smart.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's good for you.
I'm like, how much do I have in there, saving?
Let me just...
How much do I have in there?
I...
Yeah, that's really good.
I have about $48.
Holy shit.
Since you started?
When did you start?
Like, like, stop smoking?
Yeah.
Like, a couple of weeks from now.
A couple of weeks?
Oh my god, okay.
It's been a...
Yeah, and it's like a pack, right?
$2 a pack.
So...
I think it's almost a month.
Oh my god, that's a lot.
Yeah.
That's... I remember, because like, I remember you used to smoke a lot too.
A lot, a lot.
So like, I hope, like, I honestly hope it goes well.
And that you can, like...
Yeah.
You don't fall...
Fuck.
Like, it's good that a lot of the people also stop too.
Like, your... the people around you stop.
It's really hard to stop.
Since Indonesian cigarettes are really good.
And oh my god, it's so fucking hard to stop.
Yeah, and all... but it's also good that, like, your relatives also stop smoking.
So like, it's easier to, like, you don't get, like, influenced by others.
To, like, stop smoking, you know, to, like, start smoking, you know, because it's not in front of you and stuff.
And as long as you don't go outside...
Yeah.
You don't see the people smoking.
My only problem is that... I don't know how to say it in English, but like, Indonesian people tend to, like, just smoke when they're bored.
Yeah, no, I get that.
Like, they don't have anything to do.
Yeah.
And they don't want to think over so much stuff.
So they'll just go outside and just light up one.
Yeah.
That's me.
That's what I find it hard right now.
I am... I'm very bored sometimes.
Yeah, and that's why we have Izatsudon here.
That's why we have our podcast.
Yes, I am...
Especially with three hours, I just, like, had a coffee and...
But yeah, I hope... I hope it goes well to everybody else who's also trying to stop an addiction.
I hope, like, you guys are able to handle it and, like, being able to, like, you know, at least... or swap to, like, an addiction that's, like, a lot healthier and stuff.
Ever heard of... ever heard of opening loot boxes?
I just work.
That's true.
My free time is just work now.
So, like, I don't have... I don't have time to be addicted to anything.
Dude, I wish I could.
I really have no time to be addicted to things.
But you know what I'm glad... you know what I'm glad?
The thing is, I live in Indonesia, right?
Yeah.
Gambling is illegal.
Holy fuck.
Yeah.
I would probably jump in that.
Yeah, holy shit.
I'm glad gambling's illegal.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm banned in a few casinos, but hey, man.
You're banned in a few... what did you do?
Did you count cards?
Uh, I win.
You count cards, don't you?
You count cards.
No.
Then how do you win?
Yeah, well, math.
You count cards!
Nuh-uh, it's math.
It's...
Nuh-uh.
Counting cards?
Math is... math is numbers.
I was like, uh, give me... give me your ID.
Like, you know, I was turning on my chips and then they're like, oh, can I see your passports?
Uh...
Okay, I don't understand how counting cards is banned because it's just playing the game better.
Like, it literally just... it's just a smart person playing a game better.
It's just math.
I don't understand why it's...
Like, I don't even need to count it.
I already know.
It shouldn't be... it's not illegal.
It's just you don't want them to win.
Like, that's basically it.
Well, I don't play poker.
That's the thing.
I play...
I don't want you to win money.
Yeah.
That's why, like, you need to count cards and then win a little bit of money and then leave and then come back another time.
A later date.
So you don't, like, you... you can... you can still... you slowly leech money off of them.
Yeah, that's why.
They didn't kick me off.
But then when they asked... asked me for my passport, I was like, hmm, you're banning me, aren't you?
Yeah, because it's a private property.
They own it.
So it's like, of course, they can ban you.
They're banning me.
That's why you play...
Yeah, but... and that's why, like... and you can't even do, like, online poker, like, online gambling regarding, like, counting cards... using counting cards because it's all an algorithm.
It's an algorithm.
It's not like you can actually, like, out... you can't really outgame the algorithm.
I won, like, $800, $700, I think.
Like, yeah.
It's not that much.
But they were, like, stupidly counting it.
Like, what the fuck?
Yeah.
Oh, oh, what the fuck?
There's a hundred... don't... what?
What?
You got an akka?
Someone donated a hundred.
That's...
Yo!
Who is it?
Rita.
Rita!
Thanks for the akka super!
Thank you, thank you!
Dude, dude, dude, what the fuck?
What's the message?
What was the message?
What the fuck?
What was the message, Tengen?
They're traveling right now in Salwa.
Oh, I wish I could watch the whole collab.
Oh, she's traveling and she donated a hundred.
That's crazy.
Oh my god, thanks, Rita!
You know, Rita surpassed you in the rank, by the way.
Oh, they surpassed me?
Oh, nice!
Yeah.
That's insane.
Good.
Good, thank god.
I was like, you can't... you can't do this to me, man.
You can't do this to me.
Jesus Christ.
That gave me a heart attack.
Drawing your ocean.
That's good!
She having a habit filing your taxes.
You need a hundred akka!
That's good!
Good for you, man!
I'm glad you're getting that money!
Yeah, you get to keep a hundred percent of it, remember that!
Yeah, not a hundred percent.
PayPal takes...
I mean, oh yeah, thirty percent.
Sorry.
Wait, PayPal takes like...
Oh, wait, no, you do Streamlabs, so it's like...
Yeah, Streamlabs.
Uh... so it's like, what was it?
It's like five percent or some shit?
Five to ten percent?
Right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, hey, I got an akka too!
That's insane!
Oh my god!
Arch, thank you for the akka soup!
Thank you, thank you!
I wish I could watch the whole collab.
That's why you were gonna watch the VOD later!
VOD's there, don't worry about it.
Yeah!
The game's goofy.
Guys, yeah, you guys gotta watch the whole VOD so you can get the podcast section too, with number six right here, like, hanging out with us too.
Number six.
You know what?
That goes to my new power supply and graphics card.
Oh, yeah.
The moment you get a new graphics card, we should play Remnant.
I hope I can get that graphics card too.
Yeah, that's fine.
Remnant's always gonna be there.
It's all pricey!
It's gonna be there.
Okay, just wait until the 500 series comes out, and then you can buy a 40.
Oh, yeah, you know what?
You're so right.
You're so fucking right.
Literally just wait until the 500 series comes out, and then fucking the 40s are gonna drop by like 50 percent or some shit.
You're so right.
Holy.
It's gonna come out eventually.
When did the 40s come out?
I'm not sure, actually.
It usually takes like, what, two to three years for a new card?
Right?
I think it's a year.
No, it's not a year.
It's like two years, I feel like.
I just need that encoding.
Yeah.
Or just buy a 30.
Most of my Indonesian viewers are watching with their mobile data.
And then...
It'll be a crocodile.
Yeah.
We're having a podcast.
And then the bitrate's crazy.
The bitrate go crazy for mobile data.
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
Or just buy 300 series after they announce the 5,000.
The 3,000 does not increase that much of my performance.
And I guess waiting for the 4,000 to drop price is better.
Yeah, just save up for the 4,000.
Aye.
Yeah.
Somebody said the 39 should be a good deal now.
I don't know if that was the case.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
That's the thing.
I can't find a 3090.
Oh.
Like most of people who bought the 3090s use for, you know, what?
Oh, for mining?
Mining stuff.
Yeah.
I mean, yeah.
I can't find a good one.
Yeah.
For mining bitcoin.
Yep.
And NFTs.
Black Show Pals, thanks for the super chat.
Good luck on all the drafts.
Yeah!
Thank you!
That was a nice podcast that we had.
Should have more.
The random podcast in the middle of...
In the middle of...
In the middle of the wilderness of...
What's human.
It was great.
I had a great time, Penjin.
And number six.
Thanks for building my house.
Number six, the MVP.
He's the real guy.
He's the man.
You know what was the MVP part?
He knew I was never gonna come back to the house, but he still built it.
He knew I was never coming back to this place, but he still did it for us.
Yeah.
He's real.
That's a real dragoon right there.
What a legend.
Not a fucking legend.
Yeah, this place shall be a monument.
I don't know if the thing will still be here.
Yeah, I don't know if they do wipes or anything, but...
Remember this place, guys.
This will be the newest tourist destination.
Historical moment.
Yeah, the tourist destination where Doki and Tenjin had their first day and only day in Wonsu.
The first and the last days of Doki and Tenjin.
It'd be like, oh my god.
It was like a tour.
Those tours were historical tours.
And here, folks, is where Doki and Tenjin had their one hour podcast.
Right here on that back.
Right here.
GG's, man.
GG's.
I had a great time.
It was great hanging out with you.
If you're looking for a friend to collab with or play stupid games, I'm honestly down.
Of course, man.
I've been looking for some stupid games instead of FPS.
Yeah, of course, dude.
We're playing Steam together.
Oh my god, no.
I played Steam.
I saw the stream.
I saw the stream you did, yeah.
It's honestly... it doesn't make me mad.
It's just... I'm tired of laughing in that game.
Alright, I'm gonna go talk to my dragoons now.
Wait, what did you do?
Look at my leg.
What the fuck?
You see what I'm seeing?
Oh my god.
Alright, I am... oh my god.
I see.
Now I know what you mean.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Alright, I'm gonna go talk to my dragoons now.
But it was nice hanging out, man.
Yeah, man.
Appreciate for the invite.
Thanks.
Yeah, of course.
Of course.
I'll see you next time, dude.
Yeah.
Alright.
GG's.
Bye bye.
Bye.
Oh!
Wow.
I did not expect to stream this long.
We had two back to back collabs that went on for like But it was fun.
I had a great conversation.
Um.
We had our impromptu podcast and everything.
And I had a great time just hanging out.
Just chatting, and hanging out with you guys.
As well as with Tenjin!
And number 6!
Six!
That was a great time, honestly.
It was.
It was a fun collab.
I... am tired.
But... I hope you guys enjoyed the stream.
I know the game was like, you know...
It was not what we expected, but it was still fun, though.
And I hope you guys had a great time.
I hope you guys rest up a lot.
You had two very long back-to-back streams and everything.
So, I'm gonna call it here, guys.
As always, everybody, stay hydrated, posture check.
Get up and move around to get that blood flowing.
And if you stayed up for me, head to bed.
Because you deserve it!
I'll see you guys next time, everybody.
Bye, guys!
Bye!