Okay, I hope I'm not jump-messing.
It says check in now!
Okay, go to tournament.
How do I check in?
Oh, you're checked in.
I'm checked in.
Don't worry guys, I'm so checked in.
Why is this overlooking my messages?
Why is this gigantic?
I have no idea.
Too much avatars are so big.
Alright, I'm warming up guys.
I'm warming up.
I'm doing the thing.
We're starting on Storm Point.
Hey look!
My trio matches in Storm Point as well!
Oh.
Okay, I checked in.
I'm checked in as well.
Oh, I... I...
It says I'm checked in.
I don't know.
Do I have to check in too?
I don't know what my email is and stuff.
Oh, okay.
No, you don't have to check in.
It's fine.
Oh, thank god.
When one person checks in, it checks everyone in.
We're learning.
So they'll give us code in five minutes.
Okay.
Nah.
Nice.
W.
Alright, I'll be right back real quick.
One sec.
Alright, I'm warming up.
My chat's not gonna see this until ten minutes later.
Alright guys, this...
Are you gonna use the bathroom?
Wait, wait.
If we're Storm Point, am I still Caustic or am I Watson?
I don't... I don't know, man.
I don't even know what I'm playing.
This is something we needed to figure out earlier.
No.
We can figure it out as we go.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Even though, what am I?
I don't even know what I am.
Alright, does this open up my game?
Those fucker people.
So now... let's...
Oh, fuck.
Oh, I did.
Oh, I'm still wearing my fucking...
I forgot to adjust my stuff.
I forgot to turn off my karaoke stuff.
I was like, wait a minute, what am I... I'm so tired from it, that's for sure.
I hope my guy dies so I can...
I need to turn off a lot of my karaoke stuff.
Okay, off, off...
My guy's still alive?
Bro, what the fuck?
Oh my god, he's rezzing me?
Bro...
Oh my... he fucking lives?!
And he wins?!
Bro, I'm not... I was not ready for this.
I'm in a trio game.
I'm in a fucking trio to warm up.
My guy actually won the fight, I was trying to...
Literally the worst timing when my landlord mentioned to me about rent.
And something happened to my account.
Literally the worst timing ever.
Oh no.
Apparently they didn't get my fucking payments for rent, dude.
Like, what?
What?
I don't understand.
Are they gonna kick you out?
I hope so.
I fucking hate this place anyway.
How long have you been living there?
Almost two years.
I'm done renting out for this year.
I'm 100% buying somewhere.
Oh shit.
Landlords are fucking scams.
You are not an entrepreneur.
You're a scammer.
You're all scammers.
Does he know your stream?
I don't fucking know.
Probably.
I live in a big ass building, bro.
It's a multi-billion dollar corporation, of course.
The ones that scam you the hardest.
You don't become a billionaire without fucking scamming.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Like the corp... you're renting from a company, right?
Oh yeah.
I'm writing the fattest Yelp review about this place, bro, when I leave.
I'm airing this bitch out on Twitter and everything.
This place fucking sucks.
Alright, where do you live?
Where do you live?
Tell it to everybody.
Where do you live, Jack?
Where do you live?
On stream right now.
On two... on three different streams.
Where do you live?
I'm fucking weak.
What is your apartment number, Jack?
Yeah, what is it?
Well, now you're... oh wait, we know your first name.
We'll just find the...
Why is my camera... my camera's been black and white this whole time.
Ten minutes later.
Ten minutes later I see why my camera's black and white.
What the fuck?
Oh, it's because I clicked video call by accident.
Oh, chat, well you just got a really interesting version of me for a little bit.
That was dope.
Hell yeah.
That was fire.
Alright, cool.
Oh my gosh, why did my guy have to win this fight?
I wanted to queue up for the next game.
I will never ever ever be paying rent ever again after this year.
I fucking hate it.
Yeah, but then you're gonna have a mortgage.
I would rather pay a mortgage every day of the week.
To be fair, mortgages are actually good for you.
Yeah.
For your credit.
Oh yeah.
But not like too bad of a mor... if you don't get a too bad of a mortgage.
Yeah.
The more you pay off your credit...
Sorry.
Your mortgage, the more... the better credit you get.
Yeah, 100%.
Because it says you're a responsible homeowner.
Responsible.
Apparently there's an earthquake in LA.
I didn't feel anything.
There was?
Apparently.
The earth is dying.
Where my friend lives.
Honestly.
This is why you need to live... like... like you need to live away from the ocean.
So you don't have to worry about the water sucking up the land.
What if there was an earthquake?
Yeah, live in a landlocked city.
Oh, New York City.
Seriously.
Is the code out yet?
You're always asking if the code is out.
I'm freaking out.
Is the code out?
When does my fucking stream... cause it says go live.
I'm waiting for the fucking stream.
No, I'm waiting for the YouTube thing to be like go live.
Oh my god.
10 minutes is so long.
10 minutes is actually so long.
It's such a long delay.
Who the fuck is... I guess it's cause like you know...
Cheater mans.
Hacker mans.
Cause it's like that's how long... it's like too into the game that at that point...
They can't do anything.
That's true.
I'm gonna go stream tonight.
But it's still pretty fucking long.
I'm so locked in.
I need you to like micromanage what upgrades to get.
If it's a character I don't know what...
It says ping an item please.
What the fuck does that mean?
Bro, I'm multitasking here.
I can't ping shit for you.
My random teammate.
I'm so fucked dude.
I'm trying to fucking... I'm trying to figure out how to fucking stream.
Figure it out.
I don't know but YouTube thing doesn't pop up and be like go live.
Wait does YouTube... can you add 10 minute delay to YouTube?
You have to be able to.
There's no way you can't.
No I have done in the past.
I just rarely added delays before but it's like...
Wait, what the fuck?
The option to go live isn't going live.
Oh wait wait guys I got good news.
And bad news.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
What's the good news?
No what is the good news?
1, 2, 3, 4, okay good news is we have 15 teams in our lobby.
So I'm guessing a lot of people didn't click check in.
So they got removed from the tournament.
Oh!
Bad news is we have Zone Davis in our lobby.
Oh really?
That's good.
Oh wait.
Okay so we just let Zone Davis kill everyone.
Exactly.
And we just kill.
Make sure we avoid him.
Okay does anyone know where he lands and scrims?
No idea.
I need to ask the comments.
Look at his bots.
Look at his bots and see where he lands.
Good idea.
Yeah yeah yeah and then we just land the opposite side.
My code's not out yet though.
I'm still waiting for the admin to create the lobby.
We're so shocked.
Look at the bots.
Oh my god I can go live!
You can't do that.
She's alive!
I can go live now!
Fucking 10 minute delays man.
Zone.com.b.
D.
Davis.
Right.
Where does he land and scrims so we can avoid his ass?
Um.
Videos.
Oh my god my guy's killing everybody.
I'm just existing at this point.
Yo all his stream titles are smiley face.
How am I supposed to know where you land and scrims?
It's time to watch all his streams.
Did you put the code in the chat table?
Yeah.
I didn't yet but I will when it comes out.
Oh it's still not out bro?
What the fuck?
I'm tripping out bro.
I wanna get in this goddamn game.
I'm so ready.
I'm not.
I'm not gonna lie.
You're not ready?
I don't feel ready.
I shot my gun like once in this trio game and I have 77 damage.
Oh my god.
You're so fucked.
I'm not ready.
We're so fucked.
Don't worry.
Viewers won't find out until 10 minutes later.
Alright he lands checkpoint and uh... checkpoint and uh... fissure.
It looks like.
Fissure?
Okay so we just avoid that.
Yeah yeah.
Just go the opposite side of that.
Tango spotted.
Wait.
I just typed code in chat.
Oh it codes out?
Yeah.
But I need to warm up my charge rifle.
You do?
You really need to warm up your charge rifle?
Yeah.
Tell me when to join the lobby cause I'm still in this goddamn trios match.
I can't leave because this guy has tried so hard to carry me.
He knows you're a streamer.
He's like...
He's done so much for me.
Alright.
Codes out baby W.
Let's go tempo.
Thanks for the code.
Let's not get round one.
No no I mean bro I'm gonna be honest if we get round one I...
If we do that would be so funny though.
That would be funny in a very bad way.
That would be so funny.
Don't worry our viewers won't know.
What do you remember when you...
Just delete.
Oh right.
Uh...
Fifteen.
Say fifteen?
Yeah.
Oh my god bro my aim's not doing so well just so you know.
Honestly if we're being real we probably should have changed our names.
For the first like...
Yeah we should have changed our names.
So we don't get stream snaked?
So some people won't know which lobby we were in.
They would definitely throw our game for the content.
Motherfuckers.
I'd win.
Yeah they probably don't even stream so there's no point.
Yeah no they don't need a stream it's the satisfaction.
I'll use stream snipers I'm turning on the mode thing.
The mode that doesn't tell you who...
That doesn't tell me who killed me.
So none of you will get satisfaction.
None of you will get satisfaction.
No one can see it.
Alright my charge is up.
I'm ready to go.
Apparently you're so quiet while I figure this out 10 minutes later.
No I can't adjust the volume because I have to fucking fight.
Oh wait I'm gonna pull a map so I can figure out whatever.
Oh shit what the fuck.
What the fuck.
Weird.
Huh?
Hm.
Oh my god oh my god nice wig oh my god oh my god high wig.
Yeah we're fucking shocked guys.
I blame wig it's all on his fault.
This is your fault wig.
If we get fucking landed on it's all wig's fault.
Alright wait wait wait let's just say where we're going.
Where are we going though?
Because actually we don't know what we're doing.
We haven't even discussed that at all.
I know.
I've been waiting for this discussion for a while.
What you mean you just woke up?
I've been asking I was like whoa where do we go guys?
Whoa.
Where do we play?
I've been asking this for a while.
Where are we going dude?
What's going on?
Um I mean where are we going?
Yeah that's a good question.
I mean...
I feel like...
I don't know.
I'm the only 15th team so.
Harvester would be pretty good for us.
Wait what do we what um what placement do we have to do?
To to like...
Top 10.
Top 10?
Okay we just need to be better than five teams.
That's it.
Top 10 all the way through.
So all we just need to be better than five teams.
Yeah which is really easy or should be.
Yeah there's already teams contesting each other so this is great.
This is good for us.
Alright yeah.
Bro.
Oh my god what the?
Oh my god this is making me...
You know Harvester Snaps baked green pea snacks?
You ever heard of these?
A what snatch?
Baked green pea snacks.
What the fuck is that?
I'm so done I'm eating right now.
I'm so not locked in from off this dude I'm so not locked in.
Bro are you eating?
Oh I haven't even had lunch yet.
Okay guys this is...
You didn't even have breakfast.
I didn't even eat.
You didn't.
Yeah.
Why are your aims so bad?
Alright wait.
Alright.
What's this?
Harvester?
Harvester is not open.
Okay.
What is open?
In the middle or surprisingly Sky West Trials is still open.
I think we should go Sky West Trials.
Okay Sky West Trials and we can go if we want to go Sanger.
Actually...
Okay I want to be that guy.
We might struggle.
Sky West Trials.
Unless...
Unless what?
Oh no wait.
No wait.
Yeah we want to avoid...
Actually we want to avoid Fissure because that's where Davis lands.
So we...
Okay big mod stacks.
It is open.
We just need to avoid Fissure.
Let...
Let Davis's team kill everyone and we'll just keep collecting free stuff.
Just collect their boxes?
Yeah.
Collect their go next badge.
Alright wait.
We actually have to think about where we're going.
Wait I'm freaking out.
Okay.
I don't want to go landslide.
That's for sure.
Staging not really either.
What's taken?
Fissure, Staging, Harvester, Siphon, Tree, Geyser.
That's taken.
Yeah.
And then Overlook and Epi Survey.
So...
So stacks is available?
Yeah.
Mod and stacks are still open.
We should take stacks I think.
Okay.
And then what about Storm Point?
Storm Point?
The middle POIs that are open are Aceto, Barometer, Pylon, and...
Oh.
Aceto.
Take Aceto.
I'm just happy to be here.
I'm going to say Aceto stacks.
Wait.
Um...
What?
Davis lands in checkpoint.
Uh Joakim, you feel like getting in the game today or tomorrow?
What are you thinking?
Wait.
What?
Do you want to get in the game any time soon or what's going on?
Wait.
Is the code out?
Oh.
Oh yeah.
I did it.
Hey guys.
I'm coming in.
We're going Aceto stacks then?
Yeah.
Great.
Awesome.
I'm locked in.
Oh, my gosh.
I didn't realize it was me.
I was just listening in.
I didn't realize that we were in.
Wait.
We're missing Team 10, too.
Yeah.
And two teams are missing.
Zone Davis is...
Bro, Zone Davis is going to fucking run at us, man.
We should...
Nevermind.
Zone Davis is full here.
Yeah.
Team 10 is down.
And team 3 is missing a player.
Is that Davis just gonna fucking run it at us?
New plan.
Land wherever we see a duo land.
Alright, so are we running?
Yeah, but what if they're landing where Zone Davis is next to?
Then we kill them and run away.
I think you're way too confident right now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's do Cito and Stax.
Those guys should be free.
Alright, Cito and Stax.
I don't remember where either of these are.
Wait, uh, so should I...
I should go Wattson, right?
Cause they're on Stormflight.
And then Caustic on World's Edge.
Okay, but where do I go?
Yeah, I'm about to say, where do we go here?
Oh yeah, Wiggs on Blood.
Yeah, cause you're the roller.
We're starting.
I'm playing Blood both maps then?
You guys cool with that?
Yeah, okay, wait, what do I play?
I mean, on this map, best.
Okay, I'll do Bang.
Okay, you guys gotta like micromanage me here.
No, you're good, you're good.
I'll do my best.
I'm locked in, I'm locked in.
Yeah, you're gonna micromanage me.
I always turn my brain off when I rank.
I can't lie bro, no Valk though.
Make sure we just prioritize evac towers.
Literally just say something, like, immediately.
Like, get an evac, you're like, hey, got an evac.
It's gonna be a super important comm just because we don't have a Valk to get in anywhere.
Agreed.
Uh, how do we loot Cito?
Um, okay, so...
Cito Station, I think one should land on the bottom side near Jurassic.
One just lands in the middle and one goes big building on the right side.
It's pretty simple.
I mean, we could stretch Bean and just maybe see if someone's going Bean.
But I think we just don't get greedy here.
Oh my god, we have hot zone.
Yay!
Whoa, don't be too... we don't even know what we're gonna be landing on yet.
No one could have said anything and they can still land here.
We might be getting tested, just watch out.
Okay, so we just chill.
Yeah, so like, here's the play.
If we're gonna get tested, make sure we just group up together at some spot on Cito Station and go from there.
Yeah.
No one has dropped from this plane.
No.
There's like one team here.
I don't know, there's no one pylon.
I mean, to be fair, there's like 14 squads.
We just gotta be better than four squads!
This is it!
We gotta be better than four squads!
To be fair, announcing where we're going is actually probably worse for us just because the people wanted to land on us.
I know, that's why I was like, I don't know if we should talk about where...
I'll land on the bottom side.
We should have typed this out.
Yeah, you're good.
I'll land on the side.
Do your thing, you're good.
Alright, so I mean, whatever guns you guys want to take, feel free.
This first round shouldn't be that hard for us.
I got an evac!
Nice!
Good call!
Look at us!
We're doing so well!
Let's fucking go!
We're off to a better start than we ever thought.
Yeah, we got an evac on the first round.
First drop, let's fucking go!
This is better than Twitch Rivals!
Oh, that's way better than Twitch Rivals.
I think actually anything is better than Twitch Rivals.
Twitch Rivals never happen.
That was so painful.
How did we have zero beacons?
Oh, just like Twitch Rivals.
We had to fly somewhere else to get a beacon.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, we could just...
This zone actually might be ending near us.
I think it's gonna be Barometer, but we can just stay here for right now and just play for the next zone.
I think we're just chillin' on Barometer side.
Or chill towards C-Diff time.
There's an R9 here in the Prowler.
There's also this here.
I haven't seen the Volt, but...
I have it, but I don't want the Volt.
Nah, you're good, you're good.
I'm actually gonna take this energy.
Oh, hey!
Volt, Volt, Volt!
Oh, nice, I'll take that over.
Am I trolling Tempo if I do that, you think?
Or what?
No.
No?
Okay.
There's a 6x here if you want.
When you get the Tri-Drival.
There's another Evac!
Guys!
I can take that one, nice.
I found a Volt too, nice.
Oh my god, there's so many Volts.
Yeah, I'm not gonna lie.
After I said that, I just found like so many.
Yeah, I found like two Volts.
Is there any Evo Caches that we can farm up on the way to?
I mean, she's gonna pull towards the outside side.
She's gonna be right side area.
So if we can get there quick and do one of those buildings, we're good to go.
I doubt we get sent on.
We might get sent on, but...
I'm gonna be honest, I'm pretty...
pretty confident in our 3v3 ability.
I think I'm on... We might not play it all the time, but I think we're better than the average player in these lobbies.
I think I'm on like 100 frames.
Oh no.
Performance...
No, no, no, no.
Okay, I...
No, we're okay.
I think we're okay.
Okay.
Are you sure we're okay?
I don't know.
This does not feel like 240 frames, but like...
Maybe it's my monotony.
We're good.
Alright, you guys ready to rip it out or what?
We're okay.
I'll play this one game on less frames.
It's fine.
Where was the other evac at, Dokie?
Where was it?
It was like in one of the buildings here.
Oh gosh.
We might be able to find it in one of the buildings.
Oh, okay.
I mean, we only need two.
We're not gonna need three to get into zone.
Should be fine.
I think I'd actually... I found it.
Okay.
No, just start ripping it in, I think.
Yeah, yeah, we're good.
Okay.
Then we just start the rotation in.
Let's go.
We're gonna rotate through the Jurassic side.
Go through here.
Charge rifle.
I'm good.
I got my hammer point recharged.
One team died!
Don't forget, we already get a potion point just from being top 15.
Zone Davis, kill everyone!
Okay, but what if Zone Davis runs up at us?
Alright, we're gonna put my evac here.
We're gonna start rotating in.
Just gonna take my evac.
We're gonna get into barometer front side if we can.
I'll go first and I'll just tell you guys where to land with the ping.
Alright.
In case my landing's awful and I'll just tell you guys where to land.
Do we wanna try and get that?
What, the evo cache?
Yeah.
We probably should.
What, you good?
Hello?
I'm okay, I'm okay.
I ran into a tree.
Do I get the tactical cooldown or the ultimate cooldown?
That's up to you.
I mean, I would probably say...
I'd probably say tactical cooldown, personally.
But it's up to you.
I got the tactical cooldown.
Just because I don't think we're gonna use the ulti that much here.
I got my ulti here too.
We can just keep my ulti in.
I wanna... I guarantee those two buildings are gonna be taken here.
I would wanna get there, but I think both are gonna be taken for sure.
Is anyone top barometer?
No, I don't think anyone looted barometer.
They just took barometer right now.
They missed the top.
Wait, wait, you wanna put your evac down too?
Can you come here?
Put your evac down?
Yep.
Oh, they just took it from us.
You're good though.
There's no one in this left side building either.
We can land in the left side building.
We're gonna land for this left building, okay guys?
And we're gonna start immediately.
Yeah, yeah, gotcha, gotcha.
There's no one on the right.
So we should be free.
Let's just make sure that we're free.
Okay, we're good.
There's no way to hit those, right?
We're good.
Yeah, no one in here and we're good to go.
Yeah, we live here now.
Don't put Jen down yet, cause there's no one across from my scan.
We're gonna go there.
There's no one there.
I think we should take the... eh, no, let's just stay here.
You can start setting up, but we're good to go.
Let's go, baby.
Look at us.
We just gotta make sure we live.
We live.
Jen down could be like up on stairs, right?
Like here, could be over... I don't know.
You can put it anywhere you want.
Honestly.
There's nothing that's really safe.
I'm gonna look west side.
I'm looking at west side.
Okay.
Yeah, do your thing.
We should be fine.
I don't think a lot of teams are gonna rotate.
There's like a team up top here.
Yeah, they're gonna be top barometer, right?
Yeah.
They're up here.
Oh, what the fuck?
You can see me from here?
That's not fair.
We have a lot of Watson gens, so we should be fine on the passive healing too.
Watson still has her passive healing, right Temba?
I swear.
That's Davis.
I swear to God.
It might be, to be honest.
I feel like they're gonna play more aggressive because they just know they're better than a lot of people here.
Yeah.
I mean, one team's already gone, so I'm pretty sure.
Dragon also said he'll coach us if we need help.
So...
Nice.
That's actually huge for us.
Yeah, I wanted to go to the other building, but I feel like I might just pull to the nutsack.
And I feel like I'd be better.
So, I would just stay here.
Alright.
Well, no.
We're gonna go to the other building.
Oh!
That has to be Davis.
Let's go!
One Bloodhound just killed two people.
Two more teams, guys!
Let's fucking go, guys!
I need to shoot someone.
Temba, is it three?
Is it three games or four?
Four, four, four.
It's four rounds?
Or like four... wait.
Four games per round.
Four games per round, three rounds.
Okay.
Four games is not too bad.
I thought it would be like six games.
No.
I want to shoot someone.
No one's rotating us down.
There's people above us.
If you want to shoot them, there's people on that side.
If you want to shoot that.
There's just no one here to shoot.
No one's gonna rotate.
This first round is usually pointless, to be honest.
Yeah.
I mean, we can have...
Oh!
Does that mean I can like fix my frames right now?
No.
Of course.
Yeah.
Okay.
If we die, it's not my fault.
I just said I could fix my...
Okay.
Should I look...
Where are you on?
Tempo, are you on the roof?
Oh, you're in the hole, right?
Never mind.
Tempo, if you go on that goddamn roof, I swear...
Tempo, you're literally Watson right now.
I forgot.
I forgot I did that with Drops.
Okay.
Can I tap out?
No.
Yes.
You're so good.
Okay.
Even if he goes hit, no one's gonna send us.
What do you mean?
What if it was Zone Davis?
Even if I get knocked, I don't think we get fought.
To be honest.
Someone's fighting somewhere.
I can't see, cause...
Alright, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna fucking double check my monitor.
Just to be sure.
Oh my god.
How do I tap to my...
You guys, I need to figure out how to get my...
Oh my god, we're almost dead.
Wait, what?
No, we're good.
Why are you sitting on a roof?
I'm not, I was first floor.
Okay, no, I'm on 280 hertz.
My eyes might just be tired.
Are you fucking kidding me?
My eyes are seeing 100 FPS.
There is no...
I'm taking away.
I still have eye boogers.
My eyes might just be tired.
It's okay.
I'm on 200 frames.
One of the craziest.
Sorry, my 200...
280 hertz is so many fucking frames.
You thought you were on 100?
My eyes just haven't booted up yet.
It's okay now.
It's okay.
How old are you, 98?
Guys, I'm hungry.
I'm hungry too.
The poor girl is EP and hungry, guys.
EP and hungry.
That is why...
Wait, where?
Over on...
He wants to know where you got shot at.
I got shot from...
Oh my god.
He knows where he got shot at.
You guys are giving a purpose.
The hell no.
They would need so much damage to get purple.
It's insane.
I would just keep putting your gen down too on cooldown too, TempoVAdam.
You motherfuckers using charge rifle because I'm in the lobby?
No, Tempo.
No, other people also use this charge rifle.
Yeah, I love you so much, but that's definitely not the case.
No one uses charge rifle.
It's not just you.
I'm gonna use these cells because I want to get this pack.
Wait, someone's landing.
Yeah, just hold strong.
They're going to the other building.
I kinda want to get this pack, bro.
Am I trolling if I do that?
I think I probably am trolling.
We're in this building.
Yo, stay still so I can charge my party.
Should I risk it for this pack and maybe die or no?
What pack?
Right here, care package.
No, because the team above is gonna fucking kill you.
I can smoke it.
Yeah, I want a smoke up top for me.
Oh, okay.
I'll smoke up top too.
I smoked it.
I'm going to die from this one guy.
I need to wait for your next smoke.
I forgot to drop my weapon.
Oh my god, my next smoke is gonna be in like 19 seconds.
No one's gonna get it anyway, bro.
They're baby-dog bitches.
They're good.
Yeah, but now I have to wait for my next two smokes.
That's fine.
Smoke double height.
Okay.
You gotta have to bet on the fact that if I hit it or not.
You'll miss one?
Yeah, you're gonna miss one for sure.
Oh, they smoked it.
They got it.
I told you.
And they got a Kraber knock.
How are you not?
You were fucking... you're not locked in.
I did my smokes.
I did my smokes, man.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
How are you not locked in, bro?
My apologies.
I headbunked him.
Only 10 more shots and then I have...
Alright, this guy has a Kraber now.
So like, just be...
We got knocked here.
It's actually bad.
Look at that sound pool, by the way.
It pulls back to barometer.
So we got to bamboozle a little bit.
A tad bit bamboozled.
Alright.
There's no one in this house, though.
We could just...
Which house?
This house?
What if it pulls back?
Yeah, I don't know.
They would just stay where that sound show goes.
We always make rotates to be underneath middle of barometer if we need to.
Team 9.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, somebody got eliminated by the ring.
Yeah, motherfuckers.
Yeah.
One more squad and we're top 10.
We could just...
If we get top 10 consistently every game, we're top 10.
We should be top 10, right?
Yeah.
Implacement.
There's no way.
There's new placements.
I love...
Guys, this is the...
I love ALGS so much.
It's so easy.
Alright.
That means like round 2 and 3, like people actually...
It's gonna be a full lobby, right?
Cause like...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They made it to the full lobby.
I hope like...
I hope like our lobby is filled with like...
I know they're building and shooting us by the way.
I don't know, guys.
I hope like our lobby first...
If we make it to second round is filled with like...
Teenagers.
So like their parents will be like...
Will be like, get off the PC.
Oh, yeah?
Just kick them out?
Yeah, yeah.
They'll be like...
Like, mom, I'm in a tournament.
Like, it doesn't matter.
You gotta...
You gotta go do some... Get the fuck off.
Yeah, yeah.
Get the fuck off.
It's my turn on the PC.
You got calculus homework.
Yeah, you got homework to do.
Fucking nerd.
It's past your bedtime.
Yeah.
Tembo, take my armor and passively charge this up, please.
Can you do that, actually?
Can you do that anymore with the evo charters?
No, you can't.
Cringe, dude.
Cringe, cringe, cringe.
Oh, wait.
Should I throw another one down?
Yeah, why not right now?
Do we wait until the next... until the...
Oh, yeah.
Wait until zone pops.
Team going underneath bridge, by the way.
That's an ass team.
That is probably zone Davis.
Nah, it's a blue armor.
There's no way it's zone Davis.
Yeah, there's no way.
Oh, I almost pegged him in the head.
Your big ass is in my way.
Sorry.
I get that a lot, actually.
Damn.
Wait, we should take bottom and middle barometer right now.
I'm gonna scan it.
One sec.
Make sure we can go.
Alright, I gotta grab... There's no first floor.
Are you guys ready?
Can you smoke height?
We going down below?
Yep.
Alright, go, go, go.
I double smoked.
Nice.
Good double smoke, Skis.
I double smoked but still got hit.
I might be dead.
Okay.
How are you getting hit?
That is incredibly easy.
I'm holding for you.
You're chilling?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I'll be here.
Yeah, you're good.
You're good.
I have no idea where I got shot.
I was too scared.
I didn't want to look at it.
I have to go.
Just fence up everywhere, bro.
And gen everywhere.
Well, gen one place, but you know what I mean.
I'll lock this door up just in case somebody shows up here.
That's fine.
I'll push up here.
Just until the fences show up.
Yeah, and get some fences in the zip line room so you can jump down.
Yeah.
You're good, buddy.
Take your time.
You're vibing.
It seems to be on bridge.
Bridge is still in too.
10 squads.
I'm trying to think of what we're going to do after this.
Is that a care pack?
Okay, we already got top 10.
It's fine.
Honestly, we're doing pretty good.
Yeah, we're doing pretty well.
I would love to hit a shot right now and then maybe get a kill, but you know.
Do we really need a kill though?
No, probably not.
Yes, no.
We need to stay alive.
5206 and the 9304.
Oh, triple red squad fighting in the back.
We know that.
That's zone Davis.
That's great.
It's huge trust.
That's awesome.
I'm going to keep pulling back then.
That's Davis right there.
That's the most risky play you guys are seeing.
I just made a fucking battery in this crafter.
That's what I'm talking about, baby.
Let's go.
Damn.
You're gaming right now.
Oh, yeah.
I'm actually streaming.
Oh my god.
Non-squads, let's go.
Let's go, guys.
Oh my god.
Most fucking...
hate round ever.
What are they doing?
Oh my god.
That was a horrible play.
Nice.
Glad we're not those guys.
Wait, what the fuck?
Who are these bloodhounds?
I've never seen those names before.
Thank god.
Those guys are fucking...
I'm going to lock out this door.
See if I can shoot anyone.
I'm not going to fucking risk anything right now.
No, you're good.
I'm just going to let it keep going forward and see if I can get any KP for us.
Ooh.
Any points.
I'm seeing anybody who's rotating in from behind.
Yeah, we're good right now.
Wait, there's a team right behind us.
They're not on my door.
Yeah, they're on my door.
Yeah, they are.
They're going through the house.
Do they want to fight us right now?
I don't know.
They're like running back and forth.
There's like a guy on the stairs here and a guy to our right.
I'm trying to look.
I'm going to scan.
It's a whole three man.
Yeah, a whole three man.
Watch out.
They're going to get me.
Look at this way, south way.
It's a tree man.
Yeah, do you have any grenades here?
Yeah, I do.
I already burned one of them.
I'm burning someone on purple.
Yeah, I'm burning people.
There goes the other door.
It's so weird.
What are they doing?
One is on the stairs there.
I'm going to ult you.
We're in a third party though.
So dumb.
Almost one killed one.
137.
I'm looking for you.
I'm covering.
I'm going to go back there soon.
I don't know what they're doing.
I don't know why they want to fight us.
I don't make any sense here.
This fight makes no sense.
Hold on.
I can now too.
I'm batting.
Peeking, peeking, peeking.
Nice.
Good job.
Batting, batting.
They're dying.
They're dying from what's up now.
Okay, that's good.
I'm batting.
How are the other guys in the house not shooting these kids?
What the fuck?
What is this green mean?
We're going to walk in 10 seconds.
We're going to have to walk forward here.
Stay healthy right now.
We're going to move forward here.
I'm staying healthy.
I have no ulti now.
This is so ass.
What are these kids doing?
I have an ult.
Do you want me to ult somewhere?
They ran already.
They ran the fucking way with their ult.
What are they doing?
She won this.
Okay.
I'm going to go.
What are these fucking idiots doing?
You're good.
Just look left and try to get your KP.
Just get your full heal up.
Nice.
They're dying right now.
Just go.
Yeah.
I'm here.
Kill this last guy.
Good armor.
I cracked him.
It's the last one.
If you can get him.
Yeah.
Take that.
100% you go for that kill.
Oh shit.
I thought that was Fuse.
I tried to get through.
Nice guys.
Now move up to the left side.
Just keep playing left.
Keep playing more left, Teppo.
More left.
You're good.
Nice guys.
Good shit.
Put your gen down too.
Yeah.
I have one, Teppo.
Do you have gen?
I'm going to ult left.
Just because I...
Get ulti.
Wait.
Behind us.
What the fuck?
There's a guy behind us.
You're good, Teppo.
Play it right.
Just leave.
Teppo.
Did you live?
You lived.
Yes.
You're good.
Stay there.
Just stay there.
Don't move.
Top 5, baby.
Top 5.
Just stay there.
Don't look.
Don't look at them.
Don't even look.
Yeah.
They won't see if we don't move.
I thought that worked.
Yeah.
It's like the dinosaurs.
Oh.
Maybe Clash of the... Whoa.
Whoa.
That is like...
And we got top 4.
Yeah.
We got a few kills.
Nice job, guys.
Let's go.
We got the kills.
We got 4 kills.
That's right.
Suck a dick.
Whoever Bangor 2942 is.
Yeah.
Whoever you are.
Good plays, man.
That's... I mean, that's probably enough for us to qualify already.
Yeah.
I think we're fine.
We can just chill now.
Yeah.
We're good.
I'll play.
I'll play next game.
That's nice.
We're good.
That was awesome, bro.
Good spit.
Are you doing it?
Good job getting the KP.
We needed that pretty much.
We did it, guys.
We got 4 kills.
KP, guys!
And 4th place!
Is there any team that's gonna chase us?
now?
Oh my God.
This is the Kraber team.
Let's do it.
That could've been us.
That Bloodhound holding that Kraber...
That could've...
Why the fuck did that team push us just to sit down?
I repeat without scanning and they're just 3 men sitting in the back.
In a bin.
I mean... But they have purple and reds too.
So it's like...
They could fight, obviously.
I'm hungry.
You are 20 something years old.
You are not hungry.
You're hungry.
Oh man, I'm not gonna lie.
We would have done a better job with the Kraber here for sure.
Yeah, that could have been you!
Yeah, I mean I would have hit at least one more shot than this guy.
Maybe it was like a blessing because then you wouldn't whiff in front of everybody.
Oh my god, that's so true.
I just three man swung a team.
I just swung a three man into a bin though and died for it.
That's pretty embarrassing as well.
But it's good that you died so you could IGL us better.
You're so right.
Yeah, I feel like my comms really just improved there actually so much.
Yeah, yeah.
The moment you died your comms just...
Your IGL just got so much better.
You're so right.
Bro, what the fuck is going on?
What is this fight?
What the fuck is this fight I was watching?
Okay, there we go.
Alright, nice guys.
Let's go.
Good shit dude.
We got that.
Guys, we did it!
We did it.
That's automatic round clutch probably.
That's a round qualification right there.
How many points is that actually?
Nine?
That's nine.
Nine.
Or wait, twelve, nine, ten, five.
Nine, yeah.
Wait, did we die fourth?
We died fourth.
We're fourth place.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's nine.
That's a lot of points right there.
Top ten is... top ten you're gonna need... fifteen.
Oh shit, okay.
We just need six more points and we're in.
Okay, team eleven... team... oh, team eleven is def... is it...
Wait, that's not even zone Davis.
Who the fuck is team eleven?
They got twelve kills.
Wait, why did zone Davis die in...
Zone Davis died ninth!
They only got three kills!
Wait, don't tell me we're getting a new code every time!
Oh.
Uh... I don't know.
I'm refreshing the page.
Oh my god, bro, zone Davis fell off, man.
They let this random team eleven get more kills.
Guys, we're in fourth place with nine points!
Oh my, look at us!
I guess we are getting a new code?
I don't...
I guess everybody's fucking leaving.
New code every game?
And then go to tournament.
Okay, yeah.
I mean...
So this is like 10 minutes later.
Okay, yeah.
We're still waiting for the code to come out.
Okay.
This is 10 minutes later, but House of Volume...
We already got through.
It's already 42 minutes deep.
But like House of Volume, guys.
Yeah, yeah.
Was that like really bad for y'all?
Or like...
How many viewers did we drop in the last 25 minutes, guys?
Can anyone let me know?
Has the volume been okay after 42 minutes?
It has not been there at all.
Just fucking noise and meaningful.
Oh, I got food.
Oh, food.
I got food.
Because my mom gave me my food.
I'm no longer hungry.
I'm still EP though.
You're hungry, EP, and your mom gave you food.
That's fucking debilitating.
I'm like a Tamagotchi.
I've never been so jealous ever in my life, bro.
Tam, put that new code in when you can.
Yeah, I'm gonna drink my soup.
I am also making food.
How?
Right now?
How are you doing that?
Do you need a toilet break too?
What?
I have a...
Fuck, what do you call it?
I have a camera on top of my stove.
So I can see the...
I can see my stove from my...
From my room.
So I know when my food is cooking.
And I can just run over.
You run over?
It's the most modest tempo shit I've ever heard in my life.
What?
You have like a dog camera on your stove?
You have a dog camera on your stove?
Wait, what?
To look over what's going on in your stove?
In your AFK?
Like a baby?
I gotta see if my water is boiling.
Like a baby monitor.
Your kitchen is your fucking baby.
You have a baby monitor.
It's the most modest tempo shit I've ever seen in my life.
The code is in the lobby.
We are ready for round two.
Let's go.
Well, technically round one.
Yeah.
Round two of round one.
I'm just going to write in.
We're doing it guys.
We're doing it.
Now if you really want to get crazy here.
If we really get like a good game here.
All I'm saying is we can just have a fun time for the last two games.
I'm not against it.
Oh shit.
That would be so great.
Yeah.
Okay, maybe like we should have our fun times at the last game.
Not the third game as well.
You're smart.
Cause you know.
Jordan.
We're in fourth place.
Yeah bitch.
Sorry.
Yeah.
I'm just trying to flex about when there's only 15 teams.
I'm pretty sure.
I'm pretty sure Jordan can get top four by himself.
Yeah.
So cute.
You wouldn't even need two more players.
Like he's good.
Uh.
Blood bang.
And then probably caustic blood bang.
On the other map.
Thanks for the raid.
Thanks for the raid bro.
Can Jordan coach us?
I'm not a beginner streamer.
Can Jordan like coach us live?
Contesting in a 15 team lobby is crazy.
Oh someone definitely could.
Yeah I saw some contesting.
Yeah.
Easy work.
I wish they had that like one.
The new thing they're gonna do for split two.
Wait did Davis got contested?
I think so.
Yeah yeah yeah.
What the fuck?
If he doesn't make the next round that's a W for us.
There was like two people that put north pad or something.
And then two people that put like launch pad or zeus or something.
And everyone's just landing on each other.
And I said okay.
I will not tell anyone that they are landing on each other.
Wait we shouldn't say what our POIs are or they'll start landing on us.
We should type it out like all the pros.
They see that we're already qualified so they're scared.
If they land on us.
We have nothing to lose anyway.
What's the deal?
We haven't guaranteed shit.
What do you mean?
We can literally die last every time.
Hey we still get one point.
That doesn't make fifteen.
That brings us to twelve.
Yeah that's three points short from qualifying.
So let's go kill a team.
And then we're solid.
Alright let me...
I mean I didn't expect a full three man in a bin bro.
What?
This guy said why did you swing solo?
I had to kill you.
I didn't expect a full three man in a bin.
Wait we're all three just hiding in a bin?
In a bin!
What the fuck?
That was hilarious.
Wait did you see that...
I don't know if it was a glitch or if it was a hack.
I saw a TikTok or something on Twitter.
Where it was like someone opened up a bin.
And three people actually popped out of the bin.
I don't know.
They like glitched themselves in behind a pill.
And then someone opened the pill and just three people popped up.
And then he died.
That is actually unreal.
That is fucked up.
This is the question I'm asking everyone in today.
I'm asking everyone and every love we're in today.
This exact question.
Like chicken parm or meatball marinara subs more?
Yeah.
Every TFT game I play that's the first thing I say in the chat.
And I don't say anything else.
Wait.
I think I have this answer to be honest.
Really?
Yeah I do.
What if I don't like either?
It depends on the quality of the sub man.
What's your judgement?
I mean dude it's just chicken color is just so much better than meatball marinara.
I think like chicken and brie is much better.
Chicken and brie with cranberry.
Oh that's a very fancy taste from you.
I respect that.
I see my street now.
You're a woman of class huh?
You can't afford this.
You can't afford my brie.
You can't afford this sandwich.
Oh shit.
You can't afford this bitch ass.
Alright guys.
Game just ended on our ten minute delay.
Yeah my whole chat was saying let's go tempo go.
And when I died they died.
My whole chat said actually washed.
Feeding washed.
I said we gotta stop going he's a fucking goat.
When your chat starts cheering for tempo.
You know something's wrong.
You know you did something wrong.
This is unreal bro holy shit.
Wait.
Woah woah woah.
You just went straight ASMR on me I kinda like that.
Okay.
Wait.
What am I typing?
No.
It's crazy.
No is crazy.
I respect it though.
But they stopped for me.
Am I important enough that they'll stop for me?
Hell no.
It's like match starting.
Oh no.
Not a fucking chance.
Alright I think we fixed the mic issue.
Okay wait so um.
Am I playing the same thing?
Bing?
I think so yeah.
I'm down for that.
Okay I can still eat then.
I don't have to pick anything.
No you're good you're good.
Eat up eat up you're chillin.
I mean if your eyes are still not seeing 280 FPS.
I need you actually to get on like 48 fucking milligrams of caffeine right now.
180 milligrams of caffeine.
Oh that's not me.
That's not what I'm playing.
I'm playing this.
I will be honest with you guys I'm not a great bot on here.
As you can tell.
I'm gonna try my best you know.
Wait did we people scan?
No not once.
Oh.
We didn't have anyone anywhere that we could do that.
Oh okay yeah yeah yeah.
We had to go all the way to Bean but I think that was a dumb route to do that.
But the scanning got us into the building.
Scanning did but also your fucking control.
Yo you see my charge rifle?
Number 74.
Nice good for you.
How many kills have we ranked worldwide in kills?
Wait no.
Can't you look at that Demba?
What's your rank worldwide in kills for charge rifle?
How do you look at that?
I think you can.
Oh okay actually.
I was number one in RE45 kills.
I was number one Mirage in Canada.
We know.
Guys look at my Mirage kills.
I just needed to remind you guys.
It's a very prestigious.
I'll never forget.
He just died.
Julia guys.
We're two for two on beacons man.
We're rich.
Why can't we have this in Twitch Rivals?
That was like actual money.
We don't win jack shit.
We don't win money from this.
Yeah but we also just.
We get 14 pros trying to run us down.
We're just fish food bro.
The bottom of the food chain in Twitch Rivals.
It was your Twitch Rivals too.
I know.
It's so sad.
It's so fucked up.
They did that to your own headline event.
I love how you love that for us though.
Makes for a better storyline.
You know when I went outside after we lost.
Like horribly.
And we got 19 and he got 20th.
I thought he was going to be laughing about it and stuff like that.
But I called him a loser and shit.
I went out there and he was mauling.
Cause we got mauled.
He was so.
He was like that was one of the worst events we ever played.
He should have casted.
Feels bad.
I was like you suck bro.
He was laughing with me.
I was like nope.
To be fair.
It's worse cause he was first pick too.
Well it's worse but dude his teammate.
Which I don't know how this happened.
But his teammate never played the game before.
What?
Yeah I don't know how that happened.
I have no idea.
That's why I was like super confused.
I had to talk like.
Why did Riptar pick him?
He was the last pick.
Oh he was the last pick.
I don't know how that works.
Alright wait did you hit the circle yet?
I didn't.
I'm going over now.
You're going to do your thing bro.
Is anyone going to grab the cash?
I'll go grab it actually.
Yeah if you can that would be great.
I'm going to run close.
Our loading patterns are so funny.
Guys my eyes are slowly seeing more frames now.
My eyes turned on.
Yeah my eyes are turning on.
So good for us guys.
Okay C note.
Oh C note cave.
That's weird that guy told me have you ever seen the C note cave zones.
Then we just go here.
That guy write the script or what the fuck.
Hackermans.
Oh my god.
We're hacking the system?
There's a...
That would raise you up tempo.
Tempo is always really quiet.
No no no I moved my mic into my mouth.
Oh that's good.
Okay good eat that mic.
Yeah eat it up baby.
Oh yeah.
And then video record it.
And then privately send it to like Wigs private channels you know.
Wigs tier 3 mods.
I mean tier 3 subs.
Yeah you know the mod.
Guys I don't have a charge rifle.
That sucks dude damn.
Alright any evac towers?
Probably not right?
No I only have a rez.
You have one evac tower?
Okay we don't want to use it yet.
Alright you guys ready to retake?
I'm ready.
I think we can hit this cannon.
You guys want to risk it for the biscuit?
Let's just hope team 11 isn't there.
Team 11 is a real threat now.
They're the ones that got like 12 kills.
Yeah we should go for team 11.
Let me go first and I'll let you guys know what's happening.
Alright.
I'll yell if I need you okay?
You guys can definitely take it you're good.
There's no one even close.
It would be so funny if they're just hiding like behind that rock.
I can't lie I'm being brave buddy.
Oh they just drove by us with a chardon.
It's all good.
They got out.
Oh I guess they won't ignore it.
They're walking out we're good.
They're walking out we're chillin.
Let them walk up and actually see where they go.
They're gonna get the package and then they're gonna probably just rotate into the cenote.
I see them.
I'm running behind this just in case.
I shouldn't shoot them.
No you can shoot them for sure.
I'm gonna shoot them.
I wanna put up maybe an evac tower down here and just get into cenote.
Do you want to point down?
Yeah put them right here buddy.
We're gonna try to just fly in this way.
We're gonna just take a building in there and see how it goes.
We can rotate in from there.
Just follow my pathing okay?
We're gonna go left actually.
Follow my pathing guys.
Follow me!
I'm not gonna hit a tree this time.
Follow me to your imminent death.
Let's go guys.
We're gonna land right on this one.
And we're gonna keep on walking in.
Yay!
Just keep swimming.
We're doing it.
We are.
We're always doing so good guys.
I believe in us.
If we do so well in this game and get like top 3 then we can fuck around.
Oh yeah now we can easily fuck around.
Alright we're gonna take this building from them.
We should like contest a team.
We should.
We could just pick Zone Davis.
Okay not Zone Davis.
We should grief him.
I mean he's gonna qualify anyway.
So we might as well grief him.
He definitely qualifies no matter what.
Oh a whole team across this building.
Okay watch out.
Whole team staring at my door from across.
Team on this building too.
West side.
White armor.
Get shit on kid.
There's a team on the west side too.
Yeah yeah.
Yeah.
We're gonna get a good spot in Zone.
I need to Pythagorean theorem.
Just keep pulling back.
That would be a pretty crazy pull if it doesn't.
Peek me.
Yeah peek her.
Peek her guys.
Peek her.
Come on I wanna shoot my gun.
I have zero damage.
Try cuz you're eating.
You know I can eat actually.
I'm gonna...
I don't know if you can take damage.
Yeah I'm gonna just eat what the fuck.
Why not?
Why don't you push me while I'm eating?
They're gonna find out 10 minutes later and I'll be done eating.
I don't know I feel like you're a very slow eater.
Am I right?
Okay maybe.
Yeah I feel like you definitely are.
I get the vibe from you that you take like 45 bites and you're like Okay it's cuz like I watch a show while I eat.
I love it.
It's a healthy thing to do.
Digesting slow is smart.
Yeah that's true cuz like you can it makes you like eat less.
I did math.
We have 12 things.
You have 12 what?
I'm like the opposite.
I literally destroy food in like 20 seconds.
Why is that healthy for your stomach if you eat too fast?
It's really unhealthy actually.
I said that once or twice.
Yeah that's why you fucking disappeared last like two days ago.
No I fell I fucking knocked out for like 8 hours.
I was dead.
I didn't know you could shoot through this.
This is crazy.
That's what I'm looking... oh okay.
I shot him already.
He already knows.
I shot him with 121.
Let him know we're here.
Yeah.
I'm having a great time guys.
I honestly guys...
This is pretty fun dude.
I can't wait to spend 6 more hours with all of you.
Guys, Pete is in the crack so I can shoot you.
You got a lot more to go.
Once the games get harder it'll actually be like way less way more fun to be honest.
It's kinda easy games are a little bit boring.
A little bit more boring.
I think it's just there's not a lot of teams so you don't see a lot of fights going.
Yeah and also like you know you know your good probably no matter what the fuck you do unless you're like really really struggling at the game.
Yeah.
You can shoot through that crack by the way.
You can yeah.
I shot someone for like 130.
That was crazy.
I wish we could still farm armors for each other.
Now we actually have to contribute.
And that's another thing that makes the game more boring too.
Like rotating this out and you just can't farm shit anymore.
It takes so much damage to do so.
Now I can't coast.
Now I actually have to farm with you guys.
Now you need to also run a sniper.
Now we have to run triple sniper.
No I don't think we should do that ever.
I have a purple R9.
R9 is fucking ass.
I didn't know it was going to be good for us.
I have a blue R9.
I mean I just have a... I might just use a bolt at that point.
I see someone's gun.
Should have honestly...
Shoot his gun bro.
Take the fucking barrel off kid.
Mad Maggie.
Maaam.
Okay I kind of like that though.
That's on Davis.
I might eat it.
They're fucking around now.
Mad Maggie everyone.
He's number one right?
He's number one.
Keep a look out to see where number one does.
Alright I'm done eating.
I'm not hungry anymore let's go.
I'm just EP.
Let's go.
You're still EP though?
Go take a nap.
I'm going to go sleep.
Just tell me how we do.
Take your power now.
It's actually so good for you.
Tembo takes power naps for sure.
Oh shit.
Look out door.
Piece of shit man.
Tembo I don't even know when Tembo... How many hours of sleep do you get daily?
Oh my god.
He knows.
I don't know.
I don't even want to know bro.
Sometimes I fall asleep on my desk.
For 20 minutes at a time.
Bro what?
Do you not take actual sleeps?
Like...
I don't think so.
Not sleep for real.
That's the team that ran over everyone.
That's the team that fucking fights everybody.
Maybe they WK Davis.
Let's go.
C Davis put him down or what?
That's not good for us though.
I want to see Davis out.
Respectfully.
What are you talking about?
C Davis doesn't qualify?
Yeah.
He's just a threat.
That's why we contest him.
Who's what.
What?
Oh, wow.
I literally don't know where people are.
Also, Tama, make sure you keep putting your gen down on cooldown.
Because we're not leaving anytime soon.
Yeah, we are living here now.
For a little bit at least, yeah.
For sure.
There's like a team... oh, I see a team.
If you guys want easy shots here.
I was shooting there.
I'm trying to shoot this team now.
Oh, they've run back.
Oh, yeah, he's running back and forth.
Wait, they're all the way up here.
What the fuck is that?
He's on this rock all the way up here.
Yeah, that's what I was saying.
Why is that so high?
Why is that allowed?
I think the zone is actually going to end back there too.
This is a really bad zone.
I can't lie.
Well, I have a thingamajig.
Oh, yeah.
I think there's going to be a bomb pulling, bro.
Evac?
Yeah, yeah.
I know.
I don't even know if I can take any back.
Oh, my God.
What did I just get with?
Oh, ouchies, guys.
You got hit with the magi.
Ouchies, dudes.
What's going on?
Oh, that's not a person.
That's a really good magi.
Oh, yeah.
Suck it, bitch.
Team 9 dead.
Nice, guys.
Team 9.
Nice.
Two more teams.
I see them up here.
I headshotted him.
He got scared and ran away.
Bro, this guy's the best player in the world or what?
Oh, yeah.
You can't out-snipe the sniper master.
He's going to break your fucking gen.
That's a really good view.
I can't lie.
He knows the angles.
Our gen still has a little bit of a chance.
He's got a little bit of HP left.
How is that even possible?
I don't know.
It's been hit for a while.
Yeah, what the fuck, man?
I'm not going to give you fucking stuff, bro.
What the fuck?
Wait, they smoked us.
I mean, yeah, if they push us, they're morons.
I hope they don't do that.
It would be so funny if they did.
I'm watching a team down here.
I know we've got the kill them at two times.
I'm kind of down for it.
They're fighting across.
No.
Just preparing shots.
I'm just going to troll them.
I mean, yeah, why not?
Fuck it.
I'm going to troll this one team and just smoke them every time.
Just block their one LOS.
Oh, wait.
You can't even get damage for that anymore?
What?
The smoking?
Yeah, now.
Yeah.
Isn't that crazy?
Wait, I think they left the house.
Wait, I don't know actually.
No, they smoked me.
Never mind.
The team's still here?
Yeah, they are still there.
Yeah, well, the team's back here.
I mean, taking the top, so like if we need to, we can go across the top left side.
Team top left.
Take the team house.
The top house.
Watch out, Wig.
The guy behind you.
Whoa!
It's our coach.
Our coach came into my room.
Wait, can he coach us too?
Yeah.
Do we just have the entire TSM coaches?
Yes.
They're all watching from behind the screen.
We need that.
Yeah, we need every help we can get.
Yeah.
Tell them to hit up Destroyer Room.
Tell them to reach out to Destroyer.
Give it to Wig.
He's too likeable for people to hate him.
Hello?
I'm getting to try to start aimbotting the whole fucking lobby.
360 spray?
People would just be like, oh silly Wig.
You're so funny.
What a silly little guy.
Oh my god, look at him.
Alright, come on.
Give us the pole.
Give us the...
Nope.
What the fuck is this zone?
Fuck?
Bro, what?
Do we even be here?
We need to take the height of this building, to be honest.
Is there...
We need to.
Is there anything that... any rocks that we can play out here?
Like, what is this?
I don't know, bro.
Do we just... I'm gonna be honest, guys.
I don't think we can survive this in any way.
Do we just die?
Do we go out the back of this house and just rip an evac tower and say fuck, wait, what happens?
Yeah, sure.
Do we...
Oh, no, we don't have an evac tower.
I evac towered us here.
Yeah, we don't have it.
We just have res beacons.
We're so dead, guys.
I'm gonna put a res beacon out.
Wait, wait, wait.
Having a res beacon is good.
We can go into the water, put two res beacons down, and hide behind it.
Wait, this show needs to... What am I watching?
Alright, we need to...
We need to get the height of this building.
Can you smoke these windows, Dokie?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Right here.
Alright, we need to climb this to get up on the building.
Oh, that was an awful smoke.
It's okay, though.
We got this, guys.
I knew that was a great smoke.
Yeah, yeah, we're gonna climb this.
Just get up.
Just take the height so we can actually play maybe a little bit.
So we can see what's going on?
Yeah.
Yeah, cause like...
They're fighting down here.
It was a great smoke cause we lived.
I cracked two over here?
I knocked one.
I'm looking for you.
There's someone here with us, right?
Okay, I'm gonna flash one.
In this building.
Yeah.
I just...
I'm just trying to look to see what the fuck's going on.
Where we can play.
They're scouting me so they know.
We can...
Oh, they can't play over here.
They're fighting.
They're over here.
Oh, there's nothing to play.
I got one.
I got killed.
Nice, nice.
I fend off my fend off.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, wait.
You guys keep doing that.
I'm gonna look to see what we can play.
Oh, I didn't...
Watson, Jen...
This is...
I'm safe.
Oh, I'm definitely not safe here.
I'm blind.
There's a team right here.
Are you listening?
I'm ready whenever.
We're gonna have to smoke our back when we jump off the height though.
Because the team is gonna shoot us.
We're gonna swing left.
We're gonna swing then we're gonna jump down.
And then you smoke our middle here to cross over the rock.
Here?
We're gonna jump down left and you're gonna smoke middle when we cross the rock.
Full heal first.
I have to smoke this now.
Yeah, you're good.
I'm watching the team over here.
Yeah, you're about.
I'm okay now?
I can go?
Okay, ready?
We're gonna cross now.
Go, go.
Jump off, slide left side.
We're gonna go to this rock.
Look at that smoke!
We're good.
Nice.
Good fucking smokes.
Just play on the rock.
We're good.
Just shoot behind us.
There's a guy right here.
I'm looking out.
Nope, I can't.
I missed every shot.
We're good.
Shoot this kid.
Bang ult this.
Bang ult this if you have it.
Okay, I'm banging.
And grenades, if you have two.
I only have one grenade left.
I have three.
I dropped one.
I fucked him up too.
We're good.
I dropped an A for you.
I didn't flash.
Somebody flashed over there.
We might want to wipe this to be honest.
Can we move up a little bit on this or no?
Can you smoke our mid or no?
We can't.
I think we just left them.
Yeah, but they're gonna angle us out probably.
I arc.
I hit one.
Hey, you guys stay there.
You guys stay there.
You're good.
I'm waiting for a scan to see what goes on.
Tell me a duo.
Can you guys come over here and wipe this with me?
We're gonna push them and wipe this.
Okay, okay.
No, no, no.
They corner wave.
We're good.
Look.
Dip.
Dive.
Dodge.
Duck.
What is this?
Bro, we're just dead.
There's actually nothing to do with this zone.
What the fuck is this zone?
I mean, we actually have nothing to do.
This is crazy.
We can run.
We can just mile run.
Let's just let them kill each other first.
Yeah, we just wait for more people to kill each other.
And we make that run at the same time.
I can try to smoke them from here.
Right here.
Yeah, I'm gonna move right over.
You guys stay there.
Wait, wait, wait.
He portaled back to here.
Oh, he did.
What a fucking moron.
Alright, we gotta move.
Let's move on.
Look out for him if we can, Ducky.
I'm trying to.
Wooo!
I hit him 70 red.
Nice.
Good smokes.
I'm gonna try to literally just put a fucking Moby Res down and sit behind it.
Me too.
I'm gonna kill Red.
What is that?
Wig shield!
I'm holding up one.
What is this zone?
Bro, that is so not red.
What is that?
Wait, wait, wait.
We got our three points.
We're at 15 now.
We got six!
That is the dumbest fucking shit I've ever heard.
I got a kill.
I got a kill for us too.
Bro, what is this zone?
What is that zone?
There's nothing you can do there.
No matter what.
Unless we're a Newcastle team, we're literally dead.
That is fucking crazy.
That was the craziest zonefall ever.
Jesus Christ.
That might be the worst zone I've seen ever in ALGS.
I've never seen that zone before in my life.
Put that in the ALGS Discord so we can get them to remove it.
That guy in our lobby is hacking.
He literally said, Have you ever seen those zones?
And it just happened.
Wow!
Destroy is in your chat!
He's in...
He's in your chat.
Bro!
What's his name?
Let's ask him what the next zone is.
Yeah!
You got a little insight on what the next zone is?
Yeah, you know what the next zone is, bro?
Come on.
Give us a little...
We love that zone.
That's actually just the dumbest thing I've ever seen in my life.
Packer man.
I can't believe that was real.
That was a crazy zone.
I wanna see my chat's reaction to that, bro.
I'd be like, what the fuck is that book?
What the actual fuck is that?
Ooh.
It's okay.
No way it could happen again.
No way.
We're gonna get a really good zone this game.
How many points does that six place?
We can play Caustic.
I gotta kill.
Three and then Doki's kill.
Oh, so four points.
We need one more point and we fucking...
No, we need two more points and then we qualify.
Well, no.
We get two more points just because there's only 15 teams in the lobby now.
No!
That's one point.
Well, I mean, one point for next game and then one point for last game.
True.
Yeah.
So we can... No, no.
We fuck around the last game.
What if like...
Yeah, yeah.
Last game we fuck around.
We still need something here.
Last game, are we contesting Davis?
Let's go down.
Yeah, fuck that guy.
I don't know who it is, but fuck that guy.
We're in sixth place.
Almost.
Okay.
I'm not worried about it.
Oh, no.
It doesn't feel that safe though.
We're in sixth place.
Yeah, it doesn't feel safe.
It feels very unsafe.
It feels like Prince Jerry.
We need Zone Davis and Team 11 to just roll everyone.
Nah, bro.
We're dealing with Team 11.
Oh, wait.
I'm caustic now.
Oh, yeah.
Zone Davis and Team 11, if you're watching this stream 10 minutes later, kill every team but our team.
Agreed.
So then you can get content more from us.
You can farm us for content.
If we get in the same game as team.
Zoom out.
Let me know you put the code in.
Yep.
So geyser, siphon, and tree should all have someone.
Okay.
And harvester.
What's the code?
That's in that direction.
The code just came out.
Let's see.
There we go.
Nice.
I'm in.
I got in before Wig did.
I am hacker, man.
I'm in.
We're fucking doing it, guys.
Good shit.
We're locked the fuck in now.
That was the worst round possible.
World's Edge is really easy.
Where are we landing on World's Edge?
Stacks.
So playing Bang Blood?
I don't know.
I don't want to play that.
I think it's a fucking combo.
Yeah, we definitely want caustic here for sure.
So what should we play then?
Fuck.
Zone Davis is going stacks.
Okay.
Wait, who's Tartman?
No idea.
Was anyone countdown?
Wait, if he's going stacks...
Oh, he said siphon.
He said siphon.
He said siphon, I mean.
Motherfucker.
Zone Davis banning you from pro league scrims after you make it into pro league.
No, we'll prevent him from making it.
Yeah.
Start trending that, bro.
Start trending that.
Use that to our advantage, big dog, honestly.
Zone Davis ban from ALGS tournament.
You'll never get into pro league if you kick us out.
If you land on us.
I'll also gatekeep.
I'll never have your POV up.
It's not a threat.
It's a promise.
I don't make threats.
I get even.
I'm realistic.
You know, I actually have to say I admire how optimistic we were we were going to make it across that water.
Honestly, if they weren't focusing on us, we're good.
I think it's because someone shot... who shot at them?
Who the fuck shot at them?
Definitely not me.
That was me.
Yeah, I was going to say they didn't know we were there.
They were shooting at us first.
No, I was literally watching.
They didn't know we were there until somebody shot at them.
I was like, who the fuck shot them?
They were not paying attention.
They were 100% shot at us.
And then I was like, oh, you want to play this game?
To be honest, that rock looked a lot closer than it actually was.
Because it looked closer when we were at our rock.
And then as I started running, I was like, it looks like this rock keeps getting further away.
That's so true.
I was like, wait a minute, I'm running but it's not getting any closer.
I was confused.
And then I was like, I'm going to run back and then it didn't work.
Yeah.
Alright, so...
You want to run back and then run again?
I don't mind running whatever.
I can do whatever.
Or should we run?
Yeah, run back and I'll run back again.
Fuck it.
Wait, why were you hesitating then?
Because like, Valk is just so good.
Like that, I don't know.
It's just so tough we don't get evac towers.
That's why.
And Wedge?
I'll go run back and you can go Valk.
Um, yeah.
Let's do that.
Yeah, okay.
People will think I'm you and it'll get scared.
Exactly.
Like, oh shit, controller run away.
And then you shoot better than me anyway.
Yeah, because obviously people will put the controller player on blood so they'll be like, that has to be Wig.
Like, I don't want to get close to them.
I mean, I can't believe that was real sound.
That was insane.
That was actually crazy.
I'm leaving you guys behind.
I'm 100% just sending you in there.
Oh, someone just said we should have grabbed a car.
And we could have put the car in front of us as we run up.
Yeah, but that's hindsight.
Like, we're weird.
We were not close to any cars.
I don't know where any other cars are.
No, our cars were so far away.
Oh.
It's time for candy.
I got worm candy, guys.
Damn, Zone Davis got the zones unlocked but damage?
Nah.
Goddamn.
Holy shit.
Oh wait, that's his teammate.
Yeah.
Oh shit, team 79 are duels.
Dan is logging over.
Had to install Origin.
Come on, Dan.
What the fuck, Dan?
Poor Dan.
I can't believe how crazy that was.
I'm hungry again, bro.
You're hungry?
Now I'm hungry but not eating.
Call your mom to bring food over.
I'll make her fly in from Florida.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm not fucking horrible, but come on, Dad.
Come on, fucking terrible.
Be like, mom, bring me food.
It's okay.
When you move here, I'll be your in-house chef anyway.
So we're good.
Oh my god, you're like his maid.
So about me moving to Texas.
Motherfuck.
You're not moving to Texas?
Nah, probably not.
Yo, taxes.
I know, bro, but like Texas.
What's wrong with Texas, man?
No, it's a great place.
Then why don't you move there?
Yeah.
It was so great.
I might need roommates, man.
I was gonna say a very, very, uh, very political joke.
I'm gonna...
Oh, okay.
Never mind.
I'm not smart enough to debate this shit.
I know where my intelligence stops.
Where it starts.
Wait, what do you mean you might need roommates soon?
Yeah, what the fuck does that mean?
Yeah, what does that mean?
TSM's not paying for the house anymore.
Oh, so you guys are all...
Bro, confirm?
That's crazy.
That's so crazy.
You guys heard it here, right here from my stream.
If any news article want a quote, quote it from Doki Bird.
From the Doki Bird stream.
Be ready to tag Doki Bird.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
TSM makes money and TSM doesn't, guys.
Exclusive, uh, exclusive news drop from Doki Bird stream.
I think every esports org is just broke.
That is true.
House isn't being covered, so everyone's gotta figure out what to do.
Everyone's splitting up.
Well, Evan and Jordan are gonna play from home.
So that they don't have to pay rent.
Oh, that's right.
But I don't wanna go back to Canada.
So...
Hell no.
Yeah, I didn't shoot them first.
I just saw my VOD.
I don't think... I think we got shot from the right side the whole time.
Not even the left.
Left side shot us.
Oh, left side shot us first?
And then I just returned fire.
And then I hit them for 70.
I thought you shot them first.
Cause they weren't shooting me.
Yeah, they shot me.
And then I was like, oh you wanna play this game?
And then we died.
Yeah, and then they're like, yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I played Bloodhound.
Where's Valk?
Top right.
Oh god, that was so scary.
That was so scary.
I got the blood on lock.
Wait, who healed in the open?
My favorite is me, bro.
I was like 1 HP.
I was like 1 HP out of about...
Bro trying to heal in the open.
That's my favorite one.
Chad just seized that zone.
Like, bro, you could've made that if you just popped 6 batteries, did a 360 times per dick show.
I heard about people who might go 3-ass would've made that one.
1 HP is a Bloodhound crossing in open water.
What the fuck you want me to do?
Just go.
Like, spawn in wing?
Honestly, we might be able to grab big mod too if...
Nah, there's some there.
They called it in the chat.
Really?
Yeah, the name's like Simple or something like that.
S-I-M-P-O.
I'm gonna go land...
I'm gonna take these buildings so I can grab the beacon.
Let's make sure.
Just stick on me right now just in case we...
Just in case.
Are you...
Okay, so that pink team is going...
Mod?
Why does it seem like they're very short?
That pink team to our left is very short.
They're going Geyser.
I don't see anyone near us for mod.
I don't either.
If you guys wanna go...
Mod?
You wanna go to mod tempo?
I can go.
No, no, no.
I have to go here because I need the beacon.
I'll go mod and just loot it up.
You guys go over here.
If I get late landed, I'll just scream.
Yeah, I mean... well, we cannot craft everyone.
It'd be like, we can craft you.
And I was like, no, we cannot.
I guess we run as a duo.
Someone lands on us.
Nah, we fine.
There's no one here.
I did find this though, first bin.
Scanning the beacon.
It's okay, it's gonna be here buddy.
He's gonna cry, no, he's gonna cry.
Okay, I forgot where it is.
Here's a 6x2.
Okay, not great for us, that's for sure.
If we landed sky...
Sky west, we would've been...
Solid.
That's right, we gotta valk.
Also, make sure to take your goddamn evac towers, please.
If I can find one...
I have...
I have 345 purple, flatline purple.
This is pretty fucking dog shit.
We can just pick up like a million Evo harvesters on our way.
And just be red when we go into zone.
That's true.
Yeah, except we're on the complete opposite side.
Nah, that's probably the right call.
I'm nooting.
I don't have a good gut.
I mean, I have nemesis, alternator, but I prefer not having these.
I have double R9.
I feel rich.
I am scout, flatline.
I only want two times, so I'm gonna drop it over here.
Can you ping it?
Yeah, I got you.
Yeah.
Alright, I guess I'll run nemesis.
I guess I'll run in our nemesis.
Actually, this is a little far.
I'll take the exile in my pocket too, just in case we need it.
I have one as well.
Ooh!
Grab as many heals as possible since we don't have...
I got an ulti-exile.
I didn't loot this if you want to loot this tempo.
I didn't loot this building.
I have a purple heavy mag for someone.
I'm not running one.
And a purple energy mag for someone.
Ooh, I need that.
Yeah, you can take that.
Oh, another purple backpack over there.
Holy shit, I'm actually finding crazy loot over here.
We're rich, god damn.
We're so rich.
I can't lie, this big mod has a lot of stuff we need.
There's a vault here too.
Is there an R9 in there?
Yeah, there's a blue one.
It's pretty nice.
I don't know what I'm looting anymore.
Definitely better than nothing if you need an R9.
You have to take it.
Yeah, but I'm already running a nemesis.
I don't think I'm going to have enough.
Oh, there's another!
Actually, I'm going to run...
Do you still have the heavy mag tempo or no?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, I'm going to run flatline then.
Instead of an alternate.
I'm dropping a...
I put pretty kidded alternate stuff.
Okay, I'm good.
I'm going to dip out and start walking forward to the paintball.
I grab that evac tower.
I'm going to grab that 2x and also that backpack.
I'm going to grab that charge rifle that's over there and then...
Go for it big man.
Make sure to remember too, we're in the zone and the zone is coming in.
So don't forget that we cannot craft like we can usually do.
Just remember that.
Yeah, how many mists can we stay in zone before we die?
Five.
Five?
Five and we are automatically timed out, yeah.
Okay.
There's no way we can fuck that up, right?
Nah, no shot guys.
No way, right guys?
Another evac here.
Okay.
I actually should take that for sure.
How did I miss that?
I'm an idiot.
Thanks buddy.
I think it has to do with scan.
Should I still... no I shouldn't.
Nah, you're good.
Where are we trying to run to?
We should probably go through side by side.
Yeah, we should grab something for...
We should grab the evos.
Yeah, for sure.
We should definitely pad our way to like get...
That one?
Yeah, 100%.
Then go through like the fragment side and do that as well.
Like monument, right here.
For sure.
Would it be funny if I ulted just to run faster?
Um, it would... I don't know.
Funny might not be the word, but...
I would giggle if you wanted me to like...
I would giggle for sure.
And then there's just a team right here?
I would definitely giggle.
Oh, balloon.
Yeah, we'll take the balloon and get in.
We'll just get the evo tower.
Or the evo cache.
Holy shit, there's two medkits here.
I'm gonna grab one.
Take that shit.
Oh, I need a sniper...
Oh wait, do I hear...
Are those shots or is that just the evo harvester?
No, it's the evo harvester.
It's a shiny.
It's just shiny.
Ooh, shiny.
Alright, don't forget to bring off this choke too.
I'm going up.
I'm gonna fly up.
Yeah, I'm coming with you.
It's okay, they'll think I'm a controller player.
Do I get Odin's glare or Raven's blessing?
Which one's which?
I don't remember what it is.
Raven's Blessing is the 25% ult when activated.
Yeah.
Or double the duration of the attack.
I would say the Raven one.
Just make sure you scan your Raven to get your ulti back faster.
So should I ult and then...
Yeah, you could if you want to.
Odin's out of here.
I get ult and so we could charge our Ravens.
Do you want to get this, Evo?
Yeah, I'm gonna go get it for us.
We're gonna go through landslide.
Or actually, nah, fuck that.
We shouldn't go through landslide.
Let's go through the top side of Skyhook.
I think it's gonna be congested.
We could do a ring scan too.
Yeah, if you guys are grabbing that, then I can do that.
Yeah, do a ring scan and then is there any beacon scans we can hit?
Yeah, let's go to top grandmas after this and hit a beacon as well for you, Dokie.
So we know which way to go.
If we want a path towards countdown, we want a path towards Skyhook to see which one's less congested.
There's only 15 teams though, so...
Two teams died too.
Two of them died.
Two dead.
Contesting when there's only 15 squads is really fucking dumb.
I can't lie.
Yeah, I can't wait to do that for the last game.
For the last game.
It's so fucking dumb.
We're gonna have a good game here.
I'm actually being ulted.
Oh, jeez.
We don't be seeing anything.
You guys, I...
Wait, did we grab that?
Evil Harvest already?
Oh yeah, we did.
So there's a team over here.
It's okay.
People will find out 10 minutes later.
Alright, bagged trials, bro.
That is ass.
Wow.
Don't see anybody, by the way.
There's our stewards.
Did we do the people scan?
No, we're gonna go do that.
I'm heading over.
We're gonna do that grandmas right now.
There's a gold light mag.
I'm good.
I will take that.
My mom's in chat laughing about how I said she's a horrible cook.
Which is very true.
It's very true.
I'm waiting for you guys.
I'm worried that I'm gonna get fucking run over on.
Yeah, you're good.
I'm coming to you.
You're showing.
I'm running.
Alright, I need...
I have four and eight.
I'm gonna go.
Alright, I'm coming.
Okay, let's see.
Let's see how congested everything is.
Let's see which way we should go.
Here we go.
If no one's on top of trials, we should just evac tower on there.
I mean, we have three evac towers.
We might as well.
Yeah.
Alright.
No one 3, 2, 1s me.
Yay.
I'm gonna send a reactor shove.
You die, I die.
Jesus Christ.
We're going straight to the top.
That's one, two, three.
That's like four things.
They're probably gonna immediately just...
They're gonna probably immediately do exactly what we did.
So we're just gonna keep moving forward.
They're gonna just follow us.
Where are we trying to go?
We're gonna go through Skyhawk and probably evac somewhere.
But there's no one for us to really go.
This zone's pretty ass.
We have to fight our way topside over here.
Oh wait, we can grab this thing too while we're here.
How much does the cash give us again?
300.
300 I think, yeah.
I'll be 150 off.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're all...
We all should be 150 off.
We're all 150.
Yeah, we're good.
I mean, if we're...
Skyhawk, is there any other beacons we can hit while we're here?
Yeah, there are.
We're gonna be able to hit more.
Hit this, yeah.
Yeah, and then that'll give us purple.
I can't... I've really...
Zones have not been kind to us at all.
What is up with us playing and having horrible fucking zones?
It's just life at that point.
That's right.
It's life for us, I guess.
Yeah, it's just life for us at that point.
If you guys can find charge rifle stuff...
I pinged it three times.
I don't know if you took it.
I pinged a six this year.
I just found a new scope.
Like a mag.
A mag.
Ooh, that's another bat.
Someone take.
I'll take it.
I dropped a medkit.
I mean, let's just go take this front side building, yeah?
Where the purple skinner is.
Because I mean, at this point, bro, there's not gonna be much to play in Skyhook.
I don't think there's anyone there, so we should be able to take this for free.
We'll see.
We'll just get in this building first and then move forward.
We can just scan it.
Oh, I think I hear someone from it.
Are we scanned?
Nah, nah, nah.
We're good.
The other building we wanna scan is up here.
Can I get that beacon or no?
Um, I would if you could, but if you can't...
Do it.
It'll be so funny.
If you die, it would be pretty funny.
Yeah, it'll be so funny.
Are we scanned?
Yeah, sure.
Scan.
Oh, they are in here.
No, they're not.
They're not.
Okay.
I'm just gonna go up there and break the wall.
I'm chilling here until I can scan beacon.
I do think it's good.
They're on the other building.
That's fine.
I hope I don't die.
It'll be so funny, though.
I hope you don't, too.
Oh, they're grenade me.
Oh, shit.
Motherfuckers.
Okay, maybe...
You're good.
I fucking stepped on the gas and traps.
Are we good, guys?
Are we good here?
Wait, wait, wait.
I have a plan.
Alright.
Bro, this zone is terrible.
Bro, what the fuck?
Why does everyone hate us?
I don't know.
I don't know anymore.
He's not really saying anything, so I have no idea what's going on.
I'm good.
We got the scan.
I'm scared of you, everybody.
Can we somehow go up north here and play on penis?
I do want to.
No, I want to play underneath Raven, I think, here.
But I don't know if there's anyone there or not.
I'm trying to skip out the scenes.
Oh, you guys are here.
Okay.
I'm trying to go Raven.
If there's no one Raven, we should go there right now.
But I don't know if there is or not.
Because there's no one for us to play.
We literally cannot do anything.
We have an evac.
We do, yeah.
I mean, I don't think we should evac though.
We could just... we could evac.
Do you guys want to play?
Okay, so here's my thing.
Do you want to play here or do you want to go to Raven side?
I think Raven might be a little bit better for us if we actually play the game.
Might as well go Raven side, yeah.
But I feel like there's going to be a lot of teams there too.
I do too, but I don't think we can go anywhere else.
Yeah, I don't think we can go out.
There's a lot of teams at Trials side.
Yeah, I think playing towards Raven and trying to get Kp might be the play.
Being able to go out.
Yeah.
I think we can get there.
Wait, am I getting walked out?
There's a team on me.
Wait, I'm going to scan?
Yeah, we're good.
We'll play here for right now and see what these guys do.
They're purple as well.
They're going to try to take our first floor.
Just pressure our guys.
Teemu, put traps down.
You can.
Down first floor and block the doors and stuff.
I'm being shot from the fucking roof.
Yeah, you're good buddy.
You're chillin'.
They're all the way out.
Well, our building isn't in, so...
No, we're in.
We're in.
We're barely in.
We're going to take our first floor.
Let's kill these kids when they walk in.
We're fine.
I'm going to the roof then.
Yeah, you're good.
Watch out.
There's bangles up there.
Scanning?
They're running.
They're rotating.
It's good.
Yeah, one on one.
Wait till I... I'm going to look at them.
We're going to go left.
Fucking...
We're in here.
We're in our first floor, I think.
I'm going to do point.
Go to Doki's side.
We're still in up here, by the way.
Barely.
They conduit-alted us.
Alright, it's fine.
When the conduit goes down, we're going to ult their first floor.
We're going to jump down and ult their first floor.
We need K.P.
here, bro.
We're not going to be able to play this down at all.
Wait, everyone's...
What?
Yeah, I've cost gold.
Wait, wait, wait.
They're shooting like...
Yeah, down there.
Wait, wait.
I think I have angles here.
Yeah, never mind.
They full died.
The team that was behind us full died.
They're like literally in this floor right here.
Wait, there's a team down here too?
Look, I can scan them for you guys in five.
We're going to kill these guys if they're still underneath us or not.
They are.
I literally scanned them.
See?
Right below.
This is so bad.
This zone is awful too.
Like, what is going on?
Wait, do we have room on the roof?
Yeah, I think we should... That team didn't die because it's still 12 squads.
No, I know.
I want to try to jump down here and play the fence line.
And maybe just Valkyrie from there.
But I don't know what to do because we're getting shot at from everywhere.
This is so bad.
I think there's a team right over here.
Or like a solo.
You're right.
I see them.
Yeah, see?
I want to jump down and take the fence and then maybe Valkyrie late game.
I just don't know how we survive this.
There's like no other way.
There's no actual chance we survive this.
Alright, so we're going to jump down.
We're going to go right now.
We're going to go on top floor.
And we're going to go to fence line.
No, we're going to go fence line first.
Go to this fence.
No, you're good.
Just jump down the fence right now.
Just come here and play the fence side.
We're going to get looked at by everybody.
We're going to play from here.
We're going to Valkyrie late.
I just don't know how late we can do it.
We're going to try.
Yeah, Tembo.
Can you look at our backside here and Kosti, go do this right here on the front step.
There's nobody here.
We're going to find them.
No Kosti.
We're good.
Okay.
We're going to hit a really risky Valkyrie.
Come here.
We're good.
Let's hope we don't die.
We're going to try to land somewhere.
I don't know where we're landing, but this is a really risky ulti.
Can we somehow get on that penis?
Penis tower?
I don't know if we can.
There's a team up there.
Let out penis.
There's only one guy.
I'm not landing there by the way because I fucked up my landing.
So good luck.
I'm going to get on him.
Okay.
It's fine.
You did a good job.
I'm alive.
There's nothing to do.
This zone is so fucking dog shit.
God damn it, man.
All right, Doki.
Play your life.
Try your best.
There's really nothing to do.
Yeah.
You could have gotten us two points.
You're good.
Doki, run on this left side rock.
If you can.
I don't know if you can.
This is so chopped.
No.
I got slowed.
Why is this so hard?
Why are we getting cooked on everything?
All right.
Wait.
That's three more.
Three more points though.
Oh my God, bro.
I'm telling you right now, these early rounds are going to be harder because teams just don't know what's happening.
Why is that team running behind us and taking our first four for 30 minutes?
I don't understand what's going on.
I'm losing my mind.
Because they saw us doing it and they're like, they can do it.
This makes sense.
Let's do it.
That makes sense.
God damn it.
You know what?
We could have played the front side of the zip line.
I don't know.
I'm just thinking that teams are going to be playing in these spots and no one is.
So I'm like, oh, okay.
Well, now I look and I'm like, wait.
I forget we're round one.
No one's even doing anything correctly.
So, my fault.
Wait, did I shoot my gun?
I did.
Oh, thank God.
Wait, wait.
Huh?
I shot my gun.
I was like, did I get chased to shoot my gun?
Everyone has some damage.
Guys, I shot my gun.
It's all that.
Guys, I don't feel safe.
I don't think I played.
No, we're fine.
We're fine.
What was that?
Three points?
We're good.
There's no way we don't get at least three points every game.
So, like, let's be honest.
We're good again.
We're good.
What did the other five teams get?
I don't know.
We'll see.
Wait, what is what?
The only time I got to use my ult is when I accidentally ulted.
No, you're doing great.
You did a great job, though.
I'm very proud of you.
We're back.
We're valid.
Don't stress it.
We're all good, guys.
We're doing it.
I believe in us.
We're doing great.
Oh, yeah.
Penis is still in.
If we three-hit penis...
Oh, we would have been winning this game, baby.
We would have won.
If three men landed on that cross, we were good.
If we just three men jump on the penis...
If we three men got on this dick, guys, we would have been good.
He couldn't handle all three of us, right?
Yeah.
What a fucking nerd.
Wait, but I think...
Wait, did you land on there?
Oh, no.
I didn't.
I didn't even land on there.
I was like, I'm on it.
I'm on the penis.
I didn't reach it.
I don't know how I didn't reach it.
That's the only one that listened.
Yeah, I don't know how we didn't reach it.
That's actually crazy, Loki.
You did reach it.
What do you mean?
No, I didn't reach it at all.
I peaced out.
I'm joking, dude.
She just landed somewhere completely...
Yeah, but I lived longer for you.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
Because I just don't know what's free and not free with these fucking guys in that game.
I don't know what's going on.
When there's going to be a 20-man lobby, it's going to be so much easier to understand what's happening.
It's just so hard.
I mean, the fact that we even got that Valkyrie off is Loki.
Alright, 11 and 1.
That's the two teams that we needed to do really well, and they farmed everyone, which is good.
Great.
Good for us, guys.
Let's go.
We're on fire right now, guys.
Honestly.
Alright, last round.
Refresh, refresh.
Let's see what happens, man.
Give me a breakdown here.
We're just in 20th place somehow?
We're at 15th spot, and we're in 20th somehow?
Don't tell me we're on the cusp of not qualifying, bro.
That would be the funniest thing if we don't make it past round 1 today.
Yeah, that would be so fucking crazy.
That would be so funny.
It would be so funny, though.
No, but that would mean we improve so much, though, the next one we do.
You know what I mean?
You know the next one is next week, right?
Oh, shit.
That's crazy.
It's just back to back weeks now.
It would be so funny if we do so well on this.
It would be so funny.
We just do horrible things.
If we somehow make it to finals, and it's just like, oh shit, we're in top 5 or whatever.
I think you're on too much copium right now, Tim.
You're literally in 6th place right now.
I'm pretty sure we should.
6th place?
But you didn't count game 3.
I don't think we're on 6th place after game 3.
No way.
It's just harder to call this shit because no one's doing anything correct in any way possible.
I think if we actually played a bad comp, we probably would do better.
I'm not even kidding.
I would put money that we do better.
I have to pee.
I'll pee right back.
Hey, it's his first pee!
It's his first pee.
Good for him.
He's never in the floodgates, though, bro.
He's about to pee 47 times.
He's about to pee 49 times, though, now.
Yes, it's true.
I'm gonna go get an energy drink.
Alright, I'll be here to entertain your chat 10 minutes later.
Oh boy.
Okay.
I'm gonna love that, trust me.
Hey guys, so, Wigs Chat, do you know anything about, like, Twitch Prime?
Um, well...
Okay, alright, alright.
You can't skip this.
This is an unskippable ad.
Alright, so, like, alright, Twitch Prime is basically you can subscribe to your favorite Twitch streamer for free.
So go to the search bar and type Doki Bird.
Um, go to the Twitch search bar and type Doki Bird.
And then, um, I am your favorite streamer right now.
You can Twitch Prime me over there on my Twitch channel.
Alright, code is in the... Oh, you got the code?
Nice.
I'm back.
We are...
We are in seventh.
I don't know, I still don't feel safe though.
We're in seventh.
Yeah, we should probably play normal.
Yeah, I feel like we should play normal.
I think we're like fourth or fifth, I feel safe.
But seventh does not feel safe at all.
Well, actually, we're in seventh, but fifth, sixth, and seventh all have the same amount of points.
Oh, okay.
But what about eighth?
How many points does eighth have?
Like, how many... There are two behind us.
There are two?
Yeah, I don't feel safe at all.
Four is... Four is twenty.
And then five, six, seven are sixteen.
And then eight is fourteen, and tenth is eleven.
Yeah, that is... No.
They can easily get, like, points for this.
Yeah, we should just be careful.
We just play normal.
Everyone's just... That means we're just the same rank as we're...
We can keep sliding by in seventh.
All tournament long.
Nice.
Wait, where did Wigg go?
Wigg went to get an energy drink.
He's coming back.
Oh my god, Wigg, run faster!
Yeah.
Wigg, run faster.
You can hear us.
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here.
Did you hear what I said, Wigg?
Um, I heard you didn't stop talking for like twenty minutes.
I just constantly heard your voice while I was in the kitchen.
What place are we in?
Fortieth?
We are in...
We're on seventh place.
Seventh, but we're tied with five and six.
Yeah, but we're not safe at all because tenth place is only, what, three points?
Five points behind us.
Five points behind us, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh my god, we don't qualify.
This is hilarious, bro.
That would be so fucking funny, bro.
That would be so funny, dude.
I would actually laugh so much.
Alright, guys, it's fine.
I'll start trying now.
Oh, yeah, now?
Yeah.
It's all good, guys.
Before trying now, I get it.
It's all good.
Oh, so that's why we're not doing well.
I haven't tried once yet.
Wait, you guys realize that...
What?
Davis is gonna be in our lobby every single time all the way until finals.
Wait, really?
That's how that works, yeah.
That's how it works?
The top ten always, like, stick together and they just combine with another top ten that's right beside them.
Oh.
That's fucked up.
That is pretty fucked up.
That's fucked up, man.
Can we, like, move to a different lobby?
Can we lose?
Can we just, like, play?
Can they swap us to a different lobby?
Can we just lose and play next week, guys?
I'm done.
Make it easier.
I mean, we can...
It doesn't matter.
We're not gonna make it all the way to the end.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Have a little faith here.
Okay, we're totally gonna...
We're winning one game.
We're totally gonna...
We make it to round two.
We make it to day two.
We're winning one game today.
We're winning one.
Will we make it from day two to day three?
Yeah, this is it.
Yeah, I totally believe in us.
Oh, yeah.
100%.
This is my believe it voice.
No, for sure.
You sound so...
Unreal.
There's no way.
No, never.
Did they just launch the fucking rank season yesterday without even announcing it?
Yeah.
Yeah, no one was doing this like...
Wasn't it the day before or something?
It was like the day before, yeah.
Why would they not say anything?
That's so bad.
I like...
It was so funny because I was looking at the Twitch thing and nobody was like doing like rank lag.
Yeah.
Like the rank one.
First team for rank one.
It was like...
You don't even fucking know what's going on.
He's like, whoa, there it is.
Oh, wait, I should turn my volume back up in game.
You're good, buddy.
We're vibing.
Alrighty, alrighty, alright.
We're so locked in, guys.
I'm totally locked in.
Ready, y'all?
Yes.
Let's go, guys.
Unless it's some Hazmine Hotel right now, we're so locked in.
We're so locked in.
It doesn't matter if I say no, they're still gonna start it.
Ready?
No.
Okay.
Yeah, they don't care about my opinion.
Yo, Wig.
Yeah, what's up?
You need some kills here.
Yeah, where's our fucking roller player?
I'm trying now, bro, I'm trying now.
Where's our fucking roller player gameplay here?
Yeah.
You need four kills, alright?
Hey, you stopped it because I said that and then started it again.
We didn't listen to you.
Yeah, why?
Because I used you as an argument.
Doki was like, no.
He didn't care what I said.
I used you as leverage.
What do you mean?
I wrote no and he didn't care.
He still started it.
That's so fucked up.
Chat, I just don't have that killer instinct anymore, chat.
I'm sorry, dude.
It's not in me.
I'm a changed man.
I'm literally Thorfin now.
You're literally a roller player.
What happened to you?
I don't fight anymore.
I have no enemies.
So you did fall off.
No, I played basketball last night and actually got extremely competitive.
But...
I played basketball last night and got actually very upset at the people I was playing with.
Are we doing a pick up 5v5 in LA?
I mean, I'm down for volleyball instead, big man.
Count me in.
Wait, why volleyball?
What happened to basketball?
Oh, you mean on the beach.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, you love volleyball.
That was the whole point.
That's what you love.
I love volleyball.
Yeah, I was on the volleyball team.
I just spilled gamer anime girl thigh juice all over my fucking lap right now.
Child gamer sucks.
Yo, use Doki Bird!
10% off!
Wait, actually, do you have one?
Yeah, I do!
What would you name your flavor if you got one?
I'll name it...
What's a good flavor?
Laugh gas.
Oh, that's a good flavor.
That's a good one.
Yeah, yeah, that's a good one.
But what would the flavor taste like, though?
I don't know, fucking ass?
What cheeks?
I want to make sure.
Oh, we're not getting that.
Okay, we still get this for free.
I'm gonna take these two biddies.
Alright, guys, I'm gonna actually get competitive now.
Let's do it.
I'm gonna lose Domi and Stax, okay?
Fucking idiots, man.
Just get in the fucking beacon, you dumbass.
Man.
We should get Hal in here instead.
The chat.
He was screaming earlier.
About what?
Where's the zone?
Why are you not popping?
Okay.
I got the carbon.
Ooh, there's a golden mastiff.
Does anyone want that?
I'm good, but that sounds fantastic.
I'm good.
Oh, okay, Overlook Zone.
We're good to go.
That's so easy for us, guys.
Yay!
Yippee!
Yippee, guys.
Okay, I'm grabbing the bat.
I'm running Carbine!
Carbine Vault!
Okay.
I swear, I haven't found a single repeater.
Haven't found a single evac.
Yes, you have.
I just found an evac right now.
Yeah, I was like, fucking idiots.
I should probably stop doing this.
Team this mad.
Backpack.
I've not found a backpack yet.
I still don't understand how to loot this.
Oh, I found a repeater, but I already have a Kitted Carbine.
Oh, I could have a Kitted...
You should probably rotate fast this one, to be honest.
I'm gonna run...
Just run for it.
Run a repeater this time.
We gotta figure out where to grab the, uh...
the, uh, harvesters from.
Yeah, we could definitely do that, but I think rotating this one might be a little bit more important for us here than this one, just if we want to get points.
And this zone is like, super easy to predict.
Alright, I'm heading to you.
Is there anything good in the thing?
Uh, purple flatlines?
We want that.
It's not bad.
I'm good.
I'm not gonna take the purple flatlines.
I guess I can take...
No, I'm running repeater, so I don't want to run double heavy.
Yeah, I wouldn't do that.
I need a scope, though, for my repeater.
You could just get it two times off the flatline if you want to.
Oh, I could.
Here's this.
Anyone running Havoc?
I have a turbo.
Now.
Nope.
I'm running Havoc.
Actually, yeah, take that, Temba.
I'm gonna pick up this Havoc right now.
Take that.
I have it.
From there.
The smoke came from this direction.
Wait, there's team on us?
Are they running away?
Yeah, they're running.
Yeah, let them run.
We want to get in front of these guys, though, for sure.
I have a balloon.
Or evac.
I don't have an evac.
I don't have a lot of ammo.
I have a kid.
All right.
I think they went to get the EVO stuff and then left.
Yeah, they did.
All righty.
No, there's a purple backpack.
It's all good.
Just come on through, Temba.
We're getting going.
I'm running.
Wait, there's a people beacon here that we did not scan.
Oh, it really matters, bro.
It really matters, yeah.
We know it's gonna be free.
By the time we rotate, there's gonna be so many teams in zone compared to what the fuck we're in now.
I'm waiting here.
Oh, wait, we're taking the replay?
Oh, you can if you want to.
I'm good.
Honestly, yeah, take it.
Where are we going to?
We're gonna go through Geyser side.
Let's go through Geyser.
Where did that other team go?
They went through Geyser as well.
But they're probably gonna go through Geyser tunnel.
We're gonna go through the Geyser choke.
And probably Valkylde and the topside Geyser choke.
Wait, you guys want to try that Valkylde from...
That Valkylde that goes like...
Do you want to try it?
I'm gonna... I've never done...
Guys, I'm not safe at all.
Like our placement is not safe.
I don't know.
I'm trying to make round two.
I'm trying to play at least eight games today.
Yeah.
I'm trying not to die to UU.
I did cancel plans this weekend.
I'll at least play one day.
Gas trap, we're good though.
Oh, you have that turbo charger now, Teba.
We were here 75 seconds ago.
Can we grab this thingy?
Yeah.
Get the evo cache and then we're gonna Valkylde.
Just come back to me after that.
I'll wait for you.
You go grab it then, Tempo.
We're gonna Valkylde immediately.
Here I see people on the hill here.
I'm not gonna shoot them because...
They're shooting at someone else, right?
Yeah, they are.
I'm not gonna shoot them because I don't want...
Oh wait.
Are we Valkylding from where you are?
Yeah, come back to me.
We're gonna Valkylde right when you get here.
Watch our back.
Make sure we're not getting walked up on by level seven.
Yep.
Come here.
Nice, huge for me.
Nice.
Here's for me.
Are we trying to just go into like...
We're gonna get through the lava.
There was a team right next to us.
That was great.
There's a redeploy.
We're gonna go right here.
Oh they're taking it.
We can't go there.
We're taking a redeploy.
We are going to the left side.
We are in a great spot.
Yay!
This might be the exact same channel I played Rival.
Remember when I told you about the...
You heard my Twitch Prime stuff, right, Wig?
Yeah, I did.
10 minutes later, I have a hype train on my channel.
Nice!
On my Twitch chat.
Nice.
Where's my hype train, guys?
Guys.
Thanks.
Thanks, guys.
Hey, guys.
Where's my hype train, dude?
Guys, Twitch Prime over here.
Twitch Prime over here, guys.
They used up all the Twitch Prime for their Prime channel.
I need to...
Tempo, can you do this a little bit differently down here?
Can you block the doors?
Holy shit, I fucking cracked him and...
Yeah, which ones?
Just block both doors.
Yeah, block both doors.
Well, actually, block the front one.
Block the front one.
Don't block this one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I broke their fucking gen.
Yeah, fuck them.
Good shit.
And I cracked them.
I'm going to try to get purple off my Sentinel, but I don't know if I'm going to be able to.
Same.
I also have a Sentinel.
Yeah, I charged it up.
I ripped a little bit.
We're in a really good spot.
I'm pretty sure...
Can I play on the penis?
You said, do you want to play on the penis?
Do you want to repeat what you dropped it to you?
I would rather you not play the cock.
No.
Because if you get knocked, then we can't do anything about it.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
I think for this zone, I think we should stay up a little bit more locked in.
So, I think teams will start to rotate in a little bit because it was the last game.
So, I think this game is going to be easier for us to play.
Like, correctly, if that makes sense.
Just keep a lookout on the right side.
You're at two temples.
You don't get walked in by all of us.
Yeah, I'm going to look at south side.
That's fine.
I'm going to keep trying to farm up.
I have only 300 or 400 damage off my purple.
I have 500.
Oh, I closed my chat this whole time.
I had no idea what it was like.
I'm 850.
Where are you guys getting the things?
Or the thing?
What?
Did you just say?
I was shooting people.
I'm 850 away.
Yeah, I shot people.
Can you guys let me know?
Can you guys let me know if I die?
Okay, yeah.
Awesome.
Thank you.
You're dying?
Oh, wait.
What happened?
Actually?
No.
Oh, my God.
I just fucking shit myself, dude.
Actually?
I was like, wait.
Hello?
That was fast.
I was like, damn.
I just literally tabbed out for two seconds, guys.
Oh, yo.
Thanks for the five gifted souls on Twitch, guys.
Thank you.
Yo, what the fuck?
I'm on level four.
Wait, guys.
Team 11 died.
That's not good for us.
Guys, if you guys didn't know, hype train is now uncapped if it's still going on after 10 minutes.
Yeah, guys.
Over at Twitch.tv.
Twitch.tv is level zero.
Yeah.
We have no hype train here, guys.
It would be pretty cool if I ever got one.
Never got one before.
I already used my one phoenix, my one gimme.
Hopefully, a fucking crafter wins near us.
Just keep looking out here for a time.
You just literally cannot die from here.
Just make sure.
Yep.
I got it.
You can even get barrels from there if you want.
One team has to make a double now.
They're moving up.
They're moving up towards us.
Right side.
I don't have an idea.
They're going to go RV.
They're going to go RV probably.
If they go RV, we...
I'm running back towards you guys.
Yeah.
You're good.
They go RV, we kill that.
We went back again.
We've got like 10 nades in this building.
You're good.
All right.
They can't go in the close RV.
They have to go...
They went down below another house.
We're good.
Oh, they went inside the house.
We're chillin'.
We're gonna find somebody to shoot at.
Nobody's peeking anymore.
Oh, well, well.
Except for that team.
Here?
I'm gonna waste all my meds.
I really want a crafter to come near us probably.
I have four bats and eight cells.
Oh, you have four bats?
I have three bats and five cells.
We're good.
Yeah, we can just share our heals.
Yo, peek me.
How is it not hitting?
What?
How is that not hitting?
Oh, from there.
I was like, where are you gonna shot at?
That's so confused.
Yeah.
Fuck, I tried to shoot his feet.
I tried to shoot his toes, but he sucked his toes dry.
Whoa!
Relax, guys.
Chill, man.
No.
Whoa!
I didn't say that, bro.
Wait, where did the...
These guys...
These people that were playing under the penis go?
They went inside the...
Where did that Joan go?
Look at that.
We've got a valkylde.
We gotta go.
It's okay.
We gotta go now.
What the fuck was that pole?
We're gonna valkylde.
Come here.
What the fuck was that pole?
Banana phone.
We're going right back to Fragment, baby.
That pole is literally terrible.
All right.
Which Fragment are we pushing?
We're going...
Diner would be best.
What?
I don't know what's going to be...
Wait, isn't Diner just...
Don't we want to play a building that...
Oh, wait.
Diner does have doors.
Okay.
Diner has doors, Temba.
Yes, he does.
Good job, buddy.
How did he get in?
And it didn't have doors.
Okay.
If you're in that building, there's people in...
I think there's people in that building.
We're gonna land right here.
Land right here.
We're good.
Yeah.
I don't think there's anyone in here.
We're good.
That was close.
Diner has doors.
A lot of these buildings do have doors.
Correct.
Nice.
Give it a take.
If it now pulls back somehow, I will be very sad and extremely disappointed, but it's all good.
It's life.
Temba, can I have one battery, please, sir?
I dropped that here.
Okay.
Nice.
Oh, wait.
We don't have this floor.
What the fuck?
No, no, no.
We're gonna...
We'll just play a little bit.
We'll play a little bit of Spastic right now.
All right.
I mean, I have two shield cells.
Temba, do you have extra shield cells or no?
I don't have any shield cells.
Okay.
Guys, they're gonna try to push us here.
Let's just stay focused here.
They're gonna try to push us.
So, we're gonna hold the top side and we're just gonna play on the second floor.
Second floor is probably up.
All right.
Let me block off as much of this bottom floor as I can.
Temba, do you have extra shield cells or no?
Yeah.
I have 10.
I have two.
Can you give me just three?
Or two?
Just two.
Oh, wait.
You're right here.
I'm dropping them all here.
I'm dropping an eight.
All right.
Temba, when you can, can you get more barrels on the second floor?
Just because we're gonna get pushed by...
Just trying to block off all of the first floor.
You're good.
This zone might pull towards no-name, but I'm pretty confident it's gonna go towards us.
We'll see how it goes.
I do...
Oh, I don't have...
Bottom floor is all blocked off.
I'm gonna go top floor now.
Yeah.
Do your thing.
You're good.
I have like 12.
Why do I have eight nades?
Bro, what the fuck?
Why do you have eight nades?
I just pulled.
It's pretty fucking crazy.
All right.
In 10 seconds, we'll find out.
We'll see what happens.
I mean, Jesus Christ.
All I know is...
Seconds.
The rotate got me a charge rifle, so we win.
Okay.
The zone is getting smaller, so I don't know.
All right.
Well, there we go.
Someone pulls no-name.
It pulled.
We evac tower into like one of the no-name buildings.
Can you...
No.
Can we...
Can you scan this RV here real quick or no?
I don't know if I can reach it.
I'll try.
I don't think you can.
All right.
I can reach it.
This team might look ridiculous.
They're leaving or not too.
There's one guy in there.
Okay.
I mean, I don't want to go there early, but I do want to kind of go there.
Can we break out left side a little bit?
I don't know if there's any way.
I want to...
Let's wait a little bit longer.
Wait for your next scan and see how it goes.
Because this team behind us on top side, Diner's going to try to fight us.
But I want to try to get to this if we can.
I don't know if we can though.
We can play inside of the...
Five seconds.
Do you want me to scan the RV again?
Yeah.
You're going to scan RV just yet again.
There's two people there.
There's two.
But like if we go up there and cost gold, it should be fucking free.
But then the team behind us is going to...
No, I know.
But we're going to have to fight someone.
We're going to have to fight something.
There's no way we get in there for free.
Do we try to run that side and then evac from behind this big ass rock?
No, because there's going to be a team on cliff that's going to probably shoot us out.
There's definitely a team up there.
No, no, no.
The team...
The Watson fence over there, that team moved down.
I just saw...
I saw them earlier.
Okay, so we should be fine then.
Yeah, I think we do drift left side then a little bit.
Let's drift to the left a little bit.
Let's go.
You have Wingman Craver in that cart.
That is like the worst.
I have one bat.
Our luck right now is pretty fucking bad.
Here, here.
Here's the bat.
Want me to give you the point?
I can put an evac right now.
I don't even know if we can land anywhere.
Try to evac.
Let's see.
Okay.
They're double red inside here too.
I mean, we might just be able to land on one of the buildings to be...
If we're getting shot off, just get off.
Okay?
Just keep coming.
Keep going.
Keep following me.
I'm going out of the direction.
We're going to land.
We're going to land for RV.
There's no one in RV right now.
We're going to go RV.
Okay?
Get in there.
Right here.
This RV right here.
Oh my God.
The door just closed.
We're good.
Okay.
Get in here and play my side.
We're chilling.
Do I have my alt?
No, I don't.
Okay.
We're good.
We're in a great spot.
We're good to go.
Nice.
Good job, guys.
Yeah.
See?
Look.
Tempo and I, we did it.
We helped.
Nice job, guys.
Big ass head was in my crap way.
Good shit, dude.
All right.
Now we somehow have to...
Yeah.
Glass side is actually probably better here.
So, we want to stay alive.
Do you want me to scan west side or east side?
What do you want me to scan?
Oh, yeah.
It doesn't matter.
Let's see.
Oh, shit.
We're good to talk, guys.
We're behind the seat.
Hey, Jones.
Play behind the seats.
We're good.
I'm so safe.
I'm very safe as well.
We're good.
Let's keep putting those barrels down.
We're vibing.
Yeah.
The seats will really help us.
We're in zone to go.
Again, we're good.
We're going to have literally tempo.
We're going to get more traps on this side of RV.
Okay?
Because we're going to get sent on from this side.
So prioritize any traps and also any in the window up here too.
If you just put them on top of windows as well, we're good.
And even blocking doorways.
I'm trying to go some light ammo.
Don't be afraid to block doorways.
I'm going to go inside from where we're good.
There's like 10 million nades down here, by the way.
One, two, three.
Oh, my God.
We are all just chilling.
Yeah, we're good.
Keep putting more traps down.
I'm cool down on this side.
Yeah.
Somebody used resing.
What the fuck is resing?
Bro, this is just like...
These kids just don't stop shooting.
I would just go in and just go in and just go in and just go in and just go in and just go in and just go in and just go in and just go in.
I'm going to take a chill pill.
Guys, guys, please.
Let us live.
Is there any way for me to charge rifle someone?
No.
That sounds this way.
Why not?
Do you guys have any cells?
I can spare two.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I saw.
I'll take one.
I can drop two more as well.
OK.
I'm good.
I don't need that many.
You guys are good.
I'm going to keep them in the southwest side.
You are still good.
I still have more cells.
So- No, you're vibing.
Why are you booking me?
Why me, man?
This team has to move now.
Yo, we have 10 million nades.
Bro, we're not... we're gonna not have 10 million nades, dude.
Yeah, we probably can't get any nades.
Fuck, it didn't work.
The other team is pushing the way.
I should get it.
Oh my god, we're just in level 6 hype train.
Thanks, guys!
Right here, right here.
Focus on the side.
Focus on the side right now.
I'm focusing on the side too.
I'm focusing on the side.
Okay, okay.
Don't be afraid of their ulti if we need to tempo on the south-west side.
You see that to the right here?
There was someone here.
No, you're right.
They're getting shot.
They're getting shot on top side.
They're getting shot on.
I'm playing outside a little bit to get them.
I'm shooting this team to the north-west.
Bro, this kid is still peeking me inside.
Get a job.
This is his job.
Please.
You horny motherfucker.
Okay.
Got one.
I got a kill.
Nice.
Full knock or... wait, that's not even your trap.
No, it's not.
I was getting fucking gassed by a different trap.
We're good.
Okay, so we're gonna move left side.
We're gonna go left side rock, okay?
We're gonna break out of your left and move outside.
Oh my god.
That's your ult.
We're good.
Are they pushing us?
Yeah, they're pushing us.
Ult this tempo.
I ulted.
Last guys to the left.
I can't do anything.
You need to go to crazy or tempo.
Yes, tempo!
Nice.
Good job.
I'm gonna push you.
You're good.
You're dead.
You're so dead.
It's fine.
We got second.
Oh, wait.
What the fuck happened?
Wait, what the fuck happened?
Wait, what the fuck?
How did everybody die?
I was so confused.
Why they were just there?
I have no idea.
Wait, there were five teams alive and then all of a sudden there was two.
Well, that's what happens bro, because there's just no one in the lobby to start.
It's so hard to predict.
How many kills did we get?
Oh, shit.
We got second place.
I think we got like three kills or something.
Yeah.
Good shit, man.
Good shit.
Let's go, baby.
Oh, we got four kills.
Yeah.
Four kills.
We're in.
Next round.
We're so around too.
Bro, bro.
11 and one got 14 and 13.
What the fuck happened?
I'm telling you right now.
I'm telling you right now, that would be...
I think that lobby is going to be harder than the next one .
I'm not even kidding.
Oh my god.
Thank you to my Twitch chat for giving me a level seven high train.
Let's celebrate.
Oh my god.
Guys.
I still have a level 0 here guys!
We still have a high train!
Guys, I still have a level 0 guys!
If anyone wants to change that, like I was...
How do you still have a level 0 high train after all that?
That's insane to make fun of your guy.
Oh shit, even I have a level 5 high train.
I'm just fucking with you.
I was gonna say that's so fucked up bro.
Why can't I hear my own stream?
Oh shit.
I'm just refreshing the page.
Come on man.
I mean we definitely qualify for sure.
I just wanna see how high we made it with that.
Cause if we got second, that's like 9.
Yo, we finished in 5th place.
Bro, we got 5th!
Alright, how about to our next...
How many minutes till we play round 2?
How much time?
Minutes left guys.
I would say...
I don't know, probably 15.
I'm gonna use the bathroom.
Entertain my chat please.
Alright guys, yo what's the challenge?
Me too.
Our game's not in.
You guys have a sub train over at DokieBurr's chat.
But listen man, Nice Week's chat's pretty rad too.
We don't have a sub train.
So if you guys wanna change that and you know...
Change history.
Oh you're not gone yet?
My bad.
I mean, guys keep going.
Dokie should get a level 100.
She deserves that.
Bro, why can't I...
Why can't I hear my own stream right now?
What is going on?
This is so weird.
Oh, someone's got dual sense controller.
What?
A phone.
I think Valve's gonna be really good for us, bro.
Alright, we're back.
Let's check the Discord.
Where's the ALDS Discord?
Let's see.
Okay, challenges record 3, we were lobby 15.
Any announcements?
I spilled a whole thing of gamer thigh juice or anime thigh juice in my fucking counter.
Wait, again?
No, I spilled it on my fucking desk now.
I don't know how long we wait.
That was a good game, bro.
We had to at least shoot our guns.
Agreed.
That was fun.
Got some kills.
I can't believe I didn't recognize the top two.
That happened so fast.
Yeah, no.
I'm usually so attentive to that.
When I went to the back side of the RV to start shooting people, there was five teams.
And then when you were like, throw your causticol, then I threw it.
Then all of a sudden there were two teams.
And I was like, oh, it's already over.
I couldn't believe that.
If I knew that was two teams alive, I would have swung on the buff side and would have fought across the tracks.
Because I don't think that was only a duo.
It's insane.
I can't believe that.
I'm usually so attentive to how many teams are alive.
And I did not believe how fast that went down.
Chaos.
Literally.
Okay,
my page is refreshing.
I'm back!
Let's see.
Where are we now?
How long until our next game?
Probably a little while.
A little while?
Yeah, 10.
Because the other lobbies have to finish too.
Oh!
We should warm up.
We can't combine unless...
Warm up!
I'm decently warm to be honest.
But the fact that you're not kind of scares me a little bit.
I hope we're seeing at least more than 40 frames.
Guys, we should totally...
We should play some trios.
Thank god this team inside that RV did not hit any wingman shots on us.
Oh yeah, thank fucking god.
Yeah.
It was so bad for us.
He went like 0 for 7 on us.
This is when we were about to fly into the RV.
And you said RV.
I almost flew into the wrong one.
Oh, wait which one?
Isn't there one RV?
No, there's one on the other side of the tracks.
Oh!
And I was like, oh wait there's people there.
Ha ha!
Imagine if you landed across.
Probably would have been so fucked.
We would have died so early if we didn't have a cost to get that RV with you there.
Oh yeah, 100% yeah.
We would have gotten knocked.
We would have been knocked around.
It's like one trio pub.
I told you guys, I think we're going to make food to be honest.
Oh, you're going to make food?
Alright, Temple get in here.
Where are you?
I invited you, let's go.
Wait, can we leave trios?
And not get a penalty thingy?
Yeah, we can.
It's a pub.
It's a fucking pub.
You can't leave Gunrun now, I know that.
Yeah, you can.
I literally left my pub.
10 kills.
What was our final score?
Like our final placement?
Fifth.
Yeah, fifth!
Two points away from fourth.
I can't believe we got nine points and only went up two placements.
That's actually crazy.
Yeah.
Well, don't forget we had a pretty fucking shit third game.
That was pretty ass.
That's true.
Our third game was pretty rough.
Gustav's our third.
Same with our second game.
We went to track across the fucking river of death.
But hey, we survived.
We got top ten every time.
We really did.
Good job guys.
That was fun.
I actually had to shoot my weapon a little bit though.
That was a good time.
I just can't believe how fast that went, the two squads.
I'm kind of sad I didn't recognize that.
I'm watching it back right now.
Yeah, I didn't realize.
Everybody just died so fast.
Yeah.
There's no reason for that either.
There's a lot of spots that are playable.
I just thought if I knew that was happening, I would have 100% told us to sneak out of the trophy.
Yeah, I saw us die and I was like, second?
Yeah.
I was like, alright, six of 4kp, we should still make it.
But I saw second and I was like, what the fuck do you mean second?
Yeah, I was like, wait a second?
Alright, I'll be right back real quick.
Alright, we're playing a pub.
Go for it.
Are we doing the same comp?
Are we going to do the same comp where there's actually 20 people at tempo?
Yes.
Yes?
Alright.
I didn't know that was our actual comp now.
Oh, we got an alternator.
Yay!
There's a gold bag over here.
Got it.
I got so much gold stuff.
I'm golden golden.
Wait, why did I not grab that...
hemlock?
There you go.
Wait, are you in here with me?
Yes, that's me stealing your loot.
Here, you take that.
I don't know how that gun works.
Did you take the scope?
No, I got scope.
I think I dropped it over here somewhere.
Yeah.
You don't know how to use the 30-30, but you play sniper.
That's not a 30-30.
No, you dropped a 30-30.
Yeah, but like...
Oh, no, I mean like, yeah, I don't know how that gun works.
That gun is confusing.
You lead off like a sniper.
That's too much thinking.
Way too much thinking necessary.
I found another.
I got him.
Oh, wait, the thing is over there.
Oh, wait, we don't need that.
We're playing pubs.
I have a...
I hear someone.
I'm going to rat them.
Let's rat them right here.
Wait, I got it.
Ready?
There.
We're going to bait that.
They're going to come grab this and then we're going to kill them.
Oh, wait, they went into the ring.
They went to the ring.
Yoink.
Yo, what the fuck?
They're on me.
Yo, let's go in and punch his ass out.
Let's go.
Fuck that guy.
Where's his teammate?
I fucking ran.
Where's his teammate though?
Hey.
Fuck him up.
I don't know where his teammate is.
Why you don't ball him in the face?
He balled you.
Oh, there's his teammate.
No, I went climbing into the ring.
I couldn't.
Oh, that's ballsy.
That fucking guy is crazy, man.
That guy is like over here.
Yeah.
He's over here.
I'm going to crawl you.
That's where the last guy is.
Oh, that bomb could give you a shield.
He's pushing in.
Left side.
Oh.
Alright, let me refresh this.
Oh, it's out.
Alright, let's go.
We got our new lobby.
Oh, no.
Why?
Why are you saying oh no?
He's not back yet.
Bro, wait.
I swear I thought I heard him.
He's not back.
Did you guys put the code in?
No, no, no.
Alright.
Alright, this one might be a little difficult.
Oh, why?
Why?
We have like five teams I recognize.
Oh.
Oh, no.
Alright, let me go into the ALJS Discord.
And what group are we in?
Group eight.
Uh, code is coming out here in a sec.
Oh, man.
Okay, code is out.
I wait.
Don't you?
What?
Are you telling me to wait?
Are you telling me that your level 10 hype train is offline?
Yeah.
Wait, what?
Wait, she's offline?
No, I'm on YouTube.
Wait, why?
What?
I thought you were streaming on Twitch too.
I would have reacted way crazier if I knew it was fucking offline.
What the fuck?
But yeah.
What do you mean?
I'm opening stream.
No, it's not.
It ended.
I'm trying to make my fucking green super greens drink.
Uh, we got a two and we're going.
Right?
Yeah.
You didn't realize it was offline?
No, why would you let 10 hype train offline?
Only you do that.
I did.
Yeah, of course you did.
Only you.
There's only one in the world that would.
I can't believe you didn't notice.
Of course I didn't say.
Okay, wait.
Where are we going for this one?
I'm trying to figure out where people are going.
I'll make my drink that I need after this game.
It's fine.
I've been taking a probiotic with like these.
What team are we?
Are we team 19?
Yeah.
Wait, even I recognize some people.
We should definitely call.
We should definitely go immediately and say something.
World's Edge first.
Let's say we're going.
I mean, Monument's not bad, to be honest.
Monument would be pretty good for us.
Easy rotations out of Monument.
Okay, ready.
Harvester.
Bomb pod.
Countdown.
Anyone Countdown?
There's one team Monument.
Team is already going Monument.
No one's Countdown.
I don't see anyone saying Countdown, right?
Probably West.
Or you can say Conk.
I don't want to fight off spawn.
We could, but I really don't want to do that, to be honest.
Four games and you get...
I'm a Tizer.
I'll rot.
I believe in Architest, but let's just say for some reason we do this.
We just fucked one of our four games, which is not worth it.
Siphon Mill.
I'll take Countdown if we can.
Honestly, we might be able to grab Mod Stacks.
It's still open.
Oh.
Thermal Elrond.
I can't lie, bro.
We're going to get fucked.
I'll just say Stacks Mod.
I said Stacks Mod.
Fuck it.
Harvester.
Climatizer.
I'm going to go to the bathroom real quick.
Harvester.
Northside.
Monument.
Stacks Mod.
Fissure.
Everyone Stacks.
Thermal Elrond.
Countdown.
Zeus.
Fissure.
Siphon Mill.
Northpad.
Harvester.
Fissure.
Zeus.
Stacks Mod.
Geyser.
Dumbbeast.
Zeus.
Fissure.
So, no one is... so right now...
Tree, Launch Site, Dome, Stacks, Mod, it's all open.
That entire Southside is open.
Okay, wait, call it Stacks Mod for us.
Yep.
So, that's our...
Wig just needs to use his...
use his streaming and bully everyone out and say you'll never be on the watch party ever again.
But that's good, they don't want to get watched.
They don't want to get the caster curse.
You will never get publicity.
That is the craziest thing.
We will never watch your stream if you land on us, so you will never get publicity.
You would the fuck.
That's what we threaten people with.
I'm an overseeing eye of Apex Legends, what the fuck.
You would never get publicity.
There's a lot of really good teams in here, by the way.
Yeah, we know exactly.
We were talking about it.
Wait, where's the thing?
We got Zone Davis, we got Ferelli and his team, we have EZ Stomps.
...
The other team that did really well from our lobby last time, we have Unorganized.
Okay.
Yeah, so there's like five...
five, six teams that I recognize.
Maybe they'll fight each other.
Cito, Tree.
Alright, so Tree is taken.
Cito is taken, so we can't land there on Storm Point.
Honestly, we probably can grab both of them.
Pylon or Launchpad.
Still, that's still open.
Pylon, Launchpad?
Yeah.
Okay, so Barometer, Pylon, Launchpad, Devastated, Echo, Coastal, that entire south...
southeast side is open.
Okay.
For Storm Point.
And then for World's Edge, Launch, Dome, Stacks, Mod, it's all open.
If someone decides to late go to Stacks or some shit, then we can veer off to Launch.
Okay.
Launch Site if we need to.
Wait, so there's someone going Mod Stacks, potentially?
No, no, no, I'm just saying if someone...
Oh, someone is going Launch Site.
Okay.
So yeah, we should have...
no one should be Mod Stacks and Dome.
Okay.
From what I can see.
But obviously, you never know.
If we do...
if someone does land on us and we don't want to fight them, we still have staging that's open that we can go to as well.
Yeah.
Which is not bad.
Let's just hope people contest each other.
Yeah.
You guys all contest each other and we'll rack up the placement points.
Yeah, we'll just be there chilling in placements.
Oh yeah.
Here we go.
This might be the place where we...
No.
But we still have next week though!
We still have next week!
We still have next week guys.
Don't worry, we're totally gonna get into Pro League guys!
Obviously.
Yeah, if we get to Pro League, who's gonna watch party?
I wanna be honest here.
Okay, ready?
Team 2 is literally just like absolute fucking early round challenge circuit.
Yeah, so we can just have them run everyone over.
Yeah, that's what I'm about to say.
They're definitely gonna go on a three.
They fall off at the end of every challenge circuit.
They do horrible in finals every time, but they are just early round women.
Run a hype train.
Oh shit!
Oh my god, Wig!
You're finally on a hype train, Wig!
Let's go!
You did it!
I knew you could.
It's cause my hype train ended.
Yeah, unfortunately.
So they transferred over to you.
Yeah, they transferred over to mine.
Oh yeah, I forgot she's not actually doing anything on this channel.
Let me just go to this one.
Oh yeah, she's actually has not even said a word yet.
Oh, actually...
Oh...
Alrighty.
Let's fucking do it, bro.
What are we waiting for?
Start!
Oh, are they like ready?
No.
Alright, so literally just watch out for those two.
That's team two.
No joke.
Team two?
Okay.
Where are they landing?
I have no idea.
We should definitely, hopefully not be near them though.
They're gonna probably take a really good POI from this.
Okay, Tempo, where are they landing?
Analysis now.
See, they don't care whenever I say no!
They don't care!
Alright, I'm back.
If it was Imperial Howl though, they would care.
Yeah, if it was Wing that said no.
Yeah, they said Doki Bird said no.
And then they listed after I said no.
Doki Bird said no.
Okay, start.
I'm gonna play Valkyrie.
We play the same comp, I think.
So we should have...
Mod stacks and domes should be open.
Yeah.
But we'll see.
Alright, we'll see what happens.
100%.
Let's go guys.
We got four games, man.
Whatever happens here, happens.
Let's do it.
I believe in us.
I do too.
I think round two will be really hard.
I mean, don't forget, I wanna also point out, there's been really good teams that do not make it past round three.
So I'm very proud of us already.
I'm very proud of us already.
No joke.
No troll.
Let's go.
Then why did Tempo say we can make it to finals?
Because he's delusional.
I don't know what's going on.
I think we can make it to finals.
What do you mean?
I think we can.
It's just gonna be hard.
What do you mean delusional?
So that team right below us should be Geyser.
Wait, there's a team right to our right.
Wait, there is a team here.
Yeah, yeah.
Are those guys going stacks then?
Or do you think they're stretching to launch?
I don't know.
Just stay on me.
They're still here.
One's going to mod.
That one team went mod.
Okay, so we go stacks and I think that team is stretching to double.
I think so as well.
Yeah, they are there.
That's fine.
Just land together here.
We should be okay.
This team is leaving.
I'll get the back side then.
That kind of fucking sucks bro.
Why are these guys taking our team?
It's fine.
They probably didn't want to contest.
I gotta be honest but I respect them not fighting us instead and just going to mod.
It's a good call.
I would have done the same thing.
Alright, one team dead.
Here we go.
Nice.
Not last.
Not last place.
I'll take that all day.
You're fucking go baby.
Me too.
I'm happy not last.
Let's go baby.
Huge win.
Alright, so let's see how this goes though man.
We should realistically here in this situation we...
Let me see real quick.
One sec.
We should be able to get to Mirage.
I think it's going to be Mirage slash staging if I had to be real.
So we should be able to move quick.
We definitely want to navigate like...
Let me scan this beacon while dome is not looking at me.
We have ring scan too.
Yeah.
This is going to be really big for us.
This ring console should help us in time.
It's right there.
Okay, there we go.
It's going to be a lot of fishers down.
It's not an easy rotate for us but we can do it.
For sure.
Still possible.
I am looking...
I'm like...
I'm the best?
Also let's just watch out for mod to push us or do some stupid shit.
No offense, they do know it's us.
And respectfully, people probably do want to push us.
Should I do the...
Do the...
Yeah.
Yeah, if you think you're safe right now for sure.
I can come up and body block for you if you need first.
Let's see.
I'm doing it?
Yeah, go for it.
Blue backpack here by the way.
I'll need that.
Oh, they're gone.
That's a really fast rotate.
Okay, then we can go to...
We can go mod and then grab their...
Before I hit the LHL?
Yeah, we should.
We should get the EO.
I'm gonna grab the Evo right now.
We should start rotating right now anyway.
I have four batteries, eight cells.
I'm actually really good on meds.
To be honest.
Me too.
Perfect.
Because my ass is broke.
Do we want to take the replay?
Yeah, we do for sure.
I'll wait for you.
Yeah, you're good.
I want to just get... Anyone have evacs or no?
Do we not get one?
Nope, I didn't grab one.
We can take this balloon, right?
Yeah, we should take the balloon for sure.
Wait, here.
I dropped that.
Oh, I'm good.
I'm good.
I don't have any energy.
Alrighty.
Where are we heading into?
We're gonna land over to lava side.
Lava side can speed us out pretty quick.
Yeah, we can grab that balloon too, to be honest.
Yeah, I think we just go there.
And hit another balloon.
Just land on this catapult balloon for now.
Alright.
And just scan inside this building and then we'll just hit the balloon.
There's no one looting this whole side.
They probably just left already, honestly.
You want me to scan?
Yeah, scan this front side building and this one.
Someone rez.
We're good.
Alright, I was hit this balloon.
Someone did rez.
Yeah, keep on moving in.
There's a team right here that we're good.
We're gonna go left side.
Just gonna keep over here.
Keep on moving in left side.
We're gonna hit a Valkyrie probably and try to get in.
Somewhere.
Kind of me on middle side.
We're gonna hit a Valkyrie from here.
Alright.
Do we need to play or scan?
Or no?
Actually, might as well.
Might as well.
100% do it.
Alright.
Watch that team.
Team behind us over at launch.
We're good though.
Nice.
Alright, I think actually at this point guys, we're pretty...
Actually, no, we're good.
This team's leaving.
They're over at the crafting right now.
We're gonna go to the harvester.
We're gonna go through the harvester.
This team's trolling.
We're going through harvester.
We're gonna go back here?
Backside?
Yeah, we're gonna go through this way.
Yeah.
We kinda know where this down is going anyway.
It's gonna go towards lava fissure.
There's something in front of me kinda though.
Guys, I still don't have a backhive for some reason.
Wait, what?
We pinged it.
Just say how.
I bought two.
It's gold.
Gonna grab some heavy.
Nice.
Wow, that was awful.
Fuck me.
What a useless...
Another one.
Where do we go?
We're gonna keep walking through harvester side.
We're good.
I have a gold helm for...
I think you can keep it right now.
To be honest.
Actually, give it to Doki right now if you can.
Take the gold helm, Doki.
Alright.
I have also double ulti excels.
You guys need your ulti late game or anything.
Yeah, I have an ulti excel too.
Can we shoot these kids?
Fuckin' in.
Okay.
Oh fuck, I'm reloading my stupid gun.
It's okay.
Crack one, crack one.
One HP over there.
Oh, I missed.
Oh, good.
He's still behind right here.
I'm gonna try to kill it when they cross.
Can we grab that Evo cache to our back left?
Yeah, go for it.
Is their team on fence though?
No, they were the team on fence.
They left.
You guys find sniper ammo.
I'll stay near him just in case.
Oh, there's people.
There is people.
We're good.
I'm trying to look for you, but they're far.
Yeah, just keep going back to my side guys.
We're good.
We're gonna move through harvester then.
Fuck the Evo cache.
Yeah, we can't.
It's all good.
No worries.
That was the team that was over in tree.
They got stuck from the team top highway, so they just rotated in.
It's all good.
Really?
We're valid.
I feel like we're a little late.
We definitely got stalled out.
I mean, stats modern.
We're gonna be late.
We should probably go and actually get this Evo cache right here.
To be honest.
And then we'll go in from there.
We can make a play.
I am two and sixteen.
Scan up just in case.
Yeah, you're valid.
Nice.
Are we safe?
Yeah, we're safe.
We're good, dude.
I also need some charge rifle ammo.
If anyone sees a .33, let me know.
Gotcha.
I'll keep a lookout.
Ooh, evac tower.
Nice.
That's huge for us, actually.
That means one team has three evacs somewhere.
Yeah, actually, though.
Alright, we're gonna keep on walking in.
We're gonna get height on this rock here, and we're gonna hit the Evo cache, and we'll go in from there.
I'm gonna take the height...
It looks like five seconds behind us.
Yeah, you're good.
I'm gonna take the height of this, and then one of you guys goes get the Evo cache.
Yeah, I'll get it.
Yeah, you're valid.
I'm looking over.
I'm gonna scan just in case.
Yeah, why not?
We're gonna go through landslide?
No, no, no.
We're gonna go through staging.
For sure.
I am...
They're just flying in.
Flying in above us.
They're going tunnel side.
Yep.
Landed on my height.
Landed on you.
They landed on you.
Yeah, yeah.
We're gonna fall right down.
We're gonna go down.
There is... T-Mates are here.
T-Mates are here, too.
Come down.
Come down to landslide if you can.
We have no smoke.
Don't forget.
Just try to stay alive.
Oh, I got deadslide.
No!
You're good.
Keep going.
Oh, my god.
I got deadslide there.
They're pushing hard.
They're sending us.
Okay, okay.
I cracked them.
Nice.
Full heal, Temple.
Can you ult the frontside, Temple?
On our height, too.
I'm batting.
Keep going.
Keep going through tunnels.
Oh, I don't think Temple's dead.
I don't think Temple's dead.
I'm dead, too.
Just keep running, Ducky.
Turn away.
I'm just gonna ult here.
What a bunch of fucking idiots, man.
Why are they doing that?
I would just honestly, honestly, Ducky, wrap through the landslide tunnel on the right if you can.
And then maybe I might go back around if you can.
Yeah.
I'm trying to get our banners.
Okay.
They both have banners, but it's all good.
I guarantee that's Pharrell and the boys.
Do we... I rat here and then come back?
Um, you could, yeah.
Or do you want me to go all around?
I don't know if you have time to go all the way around.
You don't have an evac, right?
Uh, no, I don't.
I would wait then here.
I'd just literally rat here and then go.
Like, maybe 30 seconds.
Let me know when to go.
Do you have meds?
I do.
Yeah, you should be fine.
And then you can res us over in the staging side.
Like the crack house over there.
Oh, okay.
I have like...
I have like three syringes, one phoenix kit.
Let me know when I should go now.
Actually.
I would actually start moving now.
Yeah, you guys are timed.
Yeah.
Only 40 seconds left.
There's an evac behind you.
You're good though.
If these kids are routing it, then there's not much to say, to be honest.
No!
Really unfortunate timing though, huh?
Holy fuck.
I mean, if there's none here, you definitely get our banner though.
You're good.
Just really depends if they're routing it or not.
And I think you go res in that shack.
You know the house I'm talking about, right?
Yeah.
Okay, cool.
Nice.
We can go to our loot too.
We're gonna have a valk ulti as well.
I have an ulti.
I'm gonna see if we can.
I know you have...
I'm gonna grab some of the meds too.
They took the leaf back.
Yeah.
Get the med kits if you need.
It's all good.
No worries.
Alright.
Go hit that res above us if you want.
Not that one.
The left side one.
The left side?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, the one that's like that little house.
The one in the house.
You know what I'm talking about.
Just cause we don't wanna fucking immediately get sent on.
And then we can go into staging.
Probably scan that beacon to see where to go next.
Do we get a point?
For being top 15?
Yeah, we do get a point, which is good.
That's fine.
That's great.
Wow, I can't believe they landed on my height and that's just...
That's a good situation, man.
Hit a free rotate in the landslide tunnel.
Right over us.
Probably thought you were solo.
Or at least a duo.
Cause they did... They definitely did not trigger me.
I think they're like... They're just super confident in team fights.
I think so too.
I think that was the really aggressive squad.
I'm pretty sure.
I mean, if you wanna scope out the scenes, Doki, you can go to the front of staging.
I'm gonna look for you right now.
No one's in staging.
We should probably just get there.
To be honest.
Alright.
Just go to staging?
Like bottom side?
Yeah.
Just go bottom.
You can definitely get a glass if you need to.
I'm gonna go bottom side now then.
Cause I don't have that many meds.
Yeah, you're good.
Do your thing.
I'm not gonna go get a loot time.
But we probably can't.
Sadly.
Yeah.
I'm right behind you.
Still only have two med kit... two syringes.
Damn.
I had good loot too.
Bruh.
That sucks.
I tried, right?
I know, man.
Also, my ulti excels.
I'm not gonna have an ulti or an evac.
I can give you an ulti, though.
Yeah.
We probably should.
Cause I think my ulti is gonna be super important here.
Just gonna get in the zone and see what's good right now.
Oh.
Am I gonna die from this?
I think I might die from the zone.
Alright.
Don't show too much presence here.
Just play it safe.
Yeah.
I dropped my ulti.
I dropped my ulti here.
I'm just being skinny.
Yeah.
We're gonna take this.
You're good.
Do your thing.
I'm gonna pop this ulti.
We're gonna try to fly in somewhere, guys.
Alright?
That's gonna be the play.
I should scan beacon, right?
Yeah.
If you can.
Sure.
Let's see.
Do you guys need syringes?
Cause I can give you guys one.
We're gonna play... No.
It's fine.
I'll take one.
Yeah.
We're gonna drop down.
We're gonna... We're gonna... Valkylde from down below.
Actually, we can do it up here.
We can do it up here.
Alright.
We're gonna wait 30 seconds, though.
We have to wait for my percentage to get there.
We can get up.
Just play small here for right now.
We have 30 seconds left.
I think I'm gonna get my ulti by the time, though.
By the time the zone closes.
I hope so.
I mean, I hope so, too.
Cause then we definitely don't get to the zone.
Keep moving towards me, guys.
Yeah.
Fighting on that side.
If we can somehow land in that fissure building...
I wanna try to get RV.
You know what I mean?
Down here.
Oh, okay.
RV looks great, too.
Okay.
I just don't know if we can get there.
The team above us is gonna be a real problem.
Alright.
We're gonna make a play here, guys.
I don't really know what to do.
Wait.
You know you can back off from here, right?
Where?
There?
Okay.
Yeah.
Then wait.
Then wait for it.
Yeah.
I think you can.
Wait for it, then.
Wait for it.
Can you, though?
I don't know.
If not, if not, we can just play underneath here.
Okay.
Yeah.
Should be fine.
What's that?
We're just gonna wait.
We'll figure it out soon.
Alright.
Well, I mean, this is our Hail Mary, so let's hope we get up.
Yeah.
This is our Hail Mary here.
Alright.
Ready?
Come here.
We're gonna get on immediately.
Yeah.
Ready?
3, 2, 1, go.
We might die out of the air here.
Wait.
Toggy.
Toggy, please.
I can't keep it in the air.
Let's see if Arby's free.
If Arby's free, we're playing there, okay?
Okay.
That was a scary shit-out.
I would just land on top Mirage.
Wait.
We're gonna get a better spot.
We're gonna play underneath here.
No, no, see.
No, see.
No, Arby.
Oh, my god.
You're so lucky.
You called that out.
Nice.
Good job.
I'm fallen.
And I I cannot get out.
You're good.
I'm okay.
Open the door for you.
You're good now.
Put the barrels down, Temba.
Put the barrels down this side.
This side when we're bored.
Yeah, we're gonna open this.
You're scared to pick it up, but I saw it with my eyes.
Why did my skin not pick it up?
I was like, there's people.
Oh, wait.
I can take this back.
I have a backpack now, guys.
Nice.
Great, Temba.
Good job.
Yo, I'm still broke.
I have one cell.
I'm happy.
I mean, I'm rested, bro.
You take some cells.
I'm surprised that we're even alive right now.
Me too.
Too bad.
Okay, there's a problem, though.
We have a Kraber team here with a double red.
So like...
Bro, that is a problem.
They can't push us.
Yeah, we just need to literally play small.
Temba, how long until your ulti gets back up?
It's up.
Okay, cool.
So we're gonna play small.
Do not get Kraber.
Literally do not peek this window.
And they push us for the ulti outside, Temba.
Okay?
Like immediately.
I'll tell you what.
Wait.
Ulti outside?
Yeah.
Ulti inside our RV if we need to.
Yeah, yeah.
But like, we want to make sure they can't just stand outside and just shoot us.
Yeah.
But we have next zone.
Just gonna keep looking out for these guys, okay?
All right.
I'm gonna stick...
Oh.
Oh my god.
You don't want purple.
It's okay.
It's not a big deal.
Okay, yeah, yeah.
We could all be purple.
Yeah, but like...
Wait.
You have...
I don't...
Okay, I can give you one more syringe.
I was gonna say...
Yeah, I actually don't even know if I want to cross over to get that.
Is that a...
Well, here you go.
Thank you.
All right.
We're gonna play from here.
Tempo, keep putting these traps on the side.
Providence the side 100%.
I think this is just because you need it.
Thank you, ma'am.
All right.
You can never peek again.
I hear them moving.
Okay, when you ult, Tempo, you're gonna ult the outside.
Like, literally right here.
Yeah, right here.
Yeah, if they push us.
I don't know if they're gonna be guaranteed, but they're thinking about it for sure.
You might think...
We have to be as small as possible.
Holy shit.
I'm not...
Am I in zone?
I'm in...
No, we're in zone.
We're in zone.
Okay, we're in zone.
Okay.
I'm talking this wall.
Like, when I say ulti, bro, like, you can ulti whenever you think we're getting pushed.
I can ulti right out this door, yeah.
Yeah, I wouldn't even do it yet, though, because they might try to wrap our other side.
Yeah, they're nading us now.
They're nading us.
I'm safe.
Tempo, ult the outside now.
Ult the outside now.
Right side.
Ult the side.
I ulted.
Nice.
Good ulti.
Focus this side now.
They can't peek out this side.
Only time they can peek is this.
Yeah, I'm looking.
I'm looking.
Yeah, so we got n- Those are my thermites.
I can't go out.
I can't either.
Don't peek this yet.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't feel safe.
They're still there.
They're still out there.
We're good.
Let's get barrels over here.
Tempo, if we can.
I can't.
I have no barrels left.
Okay.
It's fine.
Let them die.
They're going to die for it.
They're dying.
We're good.
We are fine.
We are fucking...
Any grenades at all?
No, right?
No grenades at all?
No more.
We are dying for it.
We are going...
Oh, you are dying for it!
You are dying for it!
We need to get across from this.
You can't push.
Nice!
Good job!
Oh my God.
Look at all these... Look at all these boxes they delivered to us!
We are getting pushed... Pushed up.
We are getting pushed up.
We are getting sent down.
We are getting sent down here.
These aren't my barrels.
It's fine.
We are getting sent down.
I have to go for this, bro.
I'm dead.
I don't know if the red box is...
I can't hold your barrel or not.
We're good, we're good, we're good.
Place low.
Just place low.
Here I go again.
Why not?
No reason not to.
Somehow we're still in zone.
Can't tell which barrel is modular or not.
The only barrel that's in here is mine though.
I got med kits and stuff.
We're good now.
They're gone, they're gone, they're gone.
We're still in zone!
Loot, loot, loot, loot.
Eat some loot, eat some loot.
Eat, eat, eat, eat.
Eat.
Okay,
we're good, we're good.
Thank god they delivered their loot to us.
I got a Kraber, guys.
We won.
Wait, I have no loot.
Another Kraber, double Kraber.
Who wants to get it?
Okay, no, not me.
I'm horrible with that.
I'll take two Krabers.
Nah, I'm not.
You're gonna run too...
Wake, are you throwing?
No, no, we're still healthy.
Wake, you're throwing.
We're good, we're good, we're good.
Give me the Kraber.
Give me one of the Kraber.
You're throwing.
I'm definitely throwing.
You're definitely throwing.
But imagine the content.
Wait, I need that light ammo.
And the light mag.
And the light stuff.
Oh yeah.
I dropped you some.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I cannot believe we're still in sound, guys.
Yo, how are we still alive?
I don't know.
I mean, you guys made that so good.
Just live here.
We live here.
Let them kill each other.
I don't think we can... we don't need a...
Does anyone have any nades?
In game.
Does anyone have...
No.
Come on, zone pull to us.
No, it's fine.
It's fine.
We're gonna play underneath.
We're good.
That's it.
Yeah, we just play underneath.
We're good.
Oh, here's more light.
How the fuck are we gonna kill them?
Thank God.
Yo, we're top three.
Wait, wait, wait.
We gotta wait for them to kill each other.
I know.
I'm gonna try to pressure them.
They're gonna force it.
They're shooting each other.
We're gonna evac up if they fight this.
If they fight, we evac up, okay?
I don't have an evac.
We're gonna play late though.
Just play here late.
Yeah.
We're good.
I'm ready.
I'm actually hitting these kids too.
I'm ready for them to A-plus.
They knocked one.
Okay, it's fine.
It's fine.
We're gonna push slow.
Wait till they trade more.
I didn't see a kill feed.
The nade.
They need it.
They full kill.
Nice.
They full kill one.
That's good.
We're good.
We're gonna play this late.
We're just gonna play late.
We can't really go up here yet because we're gonna die.
I mean...
I mean, we're gonna have to evac up for sure.
Oh, I can climb.
I'm a mountain goat.
Oh, I'm a mountain goat.
How did you climb this?
Oh shit, they know I'm here.
Oh shit.
Abort mission.
I'm trying to get second.
I move up.
I'm gonna go.
We're so dead.
It's fine.
Let's go mountain goat.
Alright, ready?
I have my crossbow.
I'm evac towering.
And you guys take this.
You guys take this.
Okay, okay, okay.
Ready?
We're gonna do this together.
Go, go, go.
Oh, they've grenade.
We win this, guys.
We win this shit.
I cost the cast to someone.
Alright, I died right out of the air.
I'm okay with second.
Kill one.
Kill one at least.
We got the win.
How did we get top two?
We got second.
Oh my god.
How did we get second?
We were so broke.
I don't know how that works.
They didn't finish the job.
I've never seen that house with that RV in for that long.
I can't believe they were dating.
We had zone knowledge.
Oh my god.
Good shit, dude.
Good shit.
They should have finished the job.
We had one kill.
It was Davis' team, by the way.
Yo, we're in fourth place.
Let's go.
Oh, fuck.
Good shit.
Chat, I don't know how y'all wanted us to fight that, bro.
When they land top rock and we have no horizon.
Bro, one...
Team one, team three, and team two are cleaning everybody out.
Those are all three teams that we knew about.
Yeah.
One, two, and three.
And even five.
To some extent.
They literally cleaned more than half the lobby themselves.
Good fucking shit, dude.
Alright, guys.
We're halfway there.
No, that's a great play from us.
I cannot believe that just happened, bro.
I can't believe we held that off.
I know.
We were so lucky.
We had zero meds and then the team just gave us loot.
And then they delivered their meds to us.
They Amazon primed us.
Let's fucking go.
Let's fucking go, guys.
Oh, wait.
Is this code for lobby two?
Is that our code?
I think this is lobby two.
There it is.
Let me post it in the thing.
Alright, guys.
Let's do it.
I have to pee again.
Wow.
I can't believe how many people just landed on me like that.
That's nuts.
That's actually crazy.
Good job to get away.
Seriously.
You fucking saved that game.
Good shit.
Thank god.
That dead side clutched it.
That's ten points that literally is gonna probably get us through if we make it.
I don't feel safe, man.
I don't know.
That's the most safe we've ever been.
That was unreal.
You fucking shit.
Oh my god.
That's unreal.
I can't believe that just happened.
Can't believe we actually...
I mean, have you guys seen when they went in the RV?
Like, you're fucking goaded for that, bro.
You're actually so good.
Oh my god.
Yeah, yeah.
Thank god.
I...
used my eyes.
I used my eyes there.
How did we not...
How did I not scan them?
I think it's cause they came out at the last second.
I think so too.
Yeah.
Can you guys let me know when the game starts up?
I'm watching our VOD back.
Someone was like, respect to the Bloodhound for going for that Krayber shot.
At the end.
That's me!
You're such a beast.
I was like, wait.
I'm the Bloodhound!
I thought my chat was telling me to play edge.
It's like, bro, play edge?
Guys.
I'm pretty sure all these teams are playing edge.
We should get one kill.
What do we mean play edge?
Yeah, we don't need a kill.
We just need to be in zone.
Unreal.
Good fucking call, Temba, by the way, that we can ulti out of that angle.
Yep.
Weren't you the one that told me to ulti out of there?
Really good call.
And also, great call by Doki to swerve back to our VOD.
Yeah!
That would have been so good.
We have such good chemistry!
I think this is like ALGS material.
We got ALGS, bro.
If we keep on going, we'll make it to the pro league.
That's what I'm saying.
Oh my god.
Let's fucking go.
That was a hell of a rotate.
Oh my god.
I'm so surprised we made it this far.
I'm so surprised all the teams behind us died.
It sounds like, do it for the content creators.
Let's pass the other round so we can make more content.
ALGS needs more publicity.
We're here for it.
Yep.
We're providing it right now.
Slowly but surely getting to pro league.
We're giving you publicity!
Let us through to the final round!
Give us the content creator pass.
I think my favorite part of this though is that I always tell chat how bad RVs are.
Yeah, our highest placements were RVed by the way.
Yo, RV is okay when you have a caustic.
I mean, true.
Yeah.
Definitely true.
Alright, so someone did land here and here.
Okay, yeah.
Here and here.
So we... okay.
How many X's is that?
5, 6, 7, 8?
I mean, thank god also that Rampart team did not try to fight us too much.
And they went on the outside of our team.
Yeah, and then they got shit on by the people on top.
I mean, they wanted to, but we got so many like fucking barrels and stuff they couldn't get in.
Yeah, if you didn't tell me to line up the barrels, I would have split like 3 and 3.
But we had 5 barrels on that side, so...
Yeah.
I mean, that's the only stop they can peek because the other team is going to shoot them the whole time.
What the hell is the game?
Where is...
They're waiting for someone.
Davis.
Okay.
Let me open up the chat.
Let me know when we start up.
Someone fucking move this guy.
Yeah, someone move him so we can start.
Yeah, Tempo get in there bro.
Someone fucking move him.
Apparently his team was like, can we have Wig over Davis?
Bro, I take Wig.
Woah!
We just got 10 points there.
I'm not trying to brag.
What are we doing?
God bro, if I had any of my loot, I would have fucking got 3 kills in this Rampart team so hard.
I was just shooting a Nomag Brower.
I was so ass.
We're now at the part where they're trying to raid us in the RV.
Yeah, I'm watching right now.
It's so fun to watch the VOD back.
Yeah, the 10 minute delay is...
Everyone was like, SCANDOKI!
I was like, I'm scared.
I don't want to move.
I didn't want to make any noise or move.
I was so scared.
We got this bro.
Let's go.
We're so fucking valid.
Let's start the game.
I'll be like, what the fuck?
Nice.
Oh my god, you guys murdered that Bloodhound that ran in.
I almost died if you didn't kill him.
I mean, I had to peek that bro because I just can't let them get the fuck inside.
Even though I died there, it was still worth it to be honest.
Hold on, I'm saying like, if you guys didn't kill the Blood that ran in, I would have died and you would have died.
Yeah, no, you guys are great.
And I'm dying to a Caustic Barrel because I have no idea which one is yours.
You're still living in the fucking Rampart team.
I was like so chaotic.
It was so chaotic and I was like trying to loot some syringes and shit.
And then two barrels showed up and I was like, oh, I don't remember throwing those barrels there.
And then they just popped.
And then I forgot to mention that they weren't mine.
I mean, I had to go for that though because I had no heals.
I would have been a useless fucking flesh bag.
You'd just be her meat shield.
I gotta get something right now.
Like, fuck me.
Alright, Wig.
Jump us to the promised land.
I got you, baby.
Yo, did you realize?
We've had...
Have we had beacon every single game?
Bro, where was this in Twitch Rivals?
Yeah, what the fuck?
We're kind of getting bitter POIs here.
Even Geyser has had beacon two games in a row.
Yeah, what the fuck?
Which is where we landed in Twitch Rivals.
We had zero beacon.
That was my own problem.
They couldn't let us win.
That's how it goes.
Yeah, cause then they'll be like, hmmm...
The organizer gets the fucking beacon.
Beacons...
Geyser is there.
Mod is there.
I'm gonna split off now and head to beacon.
I go loot these.
This is so much fun, guys.
They should play it.
I'm having a great time.
I had zero expectations going into this.
Yeah, I thought we were out after the first round.
I'm not gonna lie.
That's the new Lulu.
I love that about you, though, Tempo.
You're giving me hype a little bit.
Prime expectations.
I was like, I don't know, guys.
I don't know if we're gonna make it to the first round.
We had zero practice as a team.
Other than the Twitch Rivals.
And that didn't go so well.
Please don't shoot me, guys.
Here's the charge rifle.
I pinged it.
I can't ping it.
I'm beacon-ing.
I'm right-row.
I had another evac, too.
You can ping an L.
You did it.
There's some sniper ammo, too, here.
Wait, where's...
It's on the second floor.
Is it with the sniper ammo?
No, it's on the second floor.
I mean, we had no chance to win that game.
We did a good job getting into second place there.
Yeah, we're so lucky that they decided to push each other.
There's a lot more sniper ammo here.
Okay, nice.
I'm vault hemlock right now.
Not too bad.
I have a 6x here, too, for you.
I'm so confused.
I don't know what's going on anymore.
What happened?
What do you mean?
Why are you confused?
I'm just running in circles.
You're good, buddy.
I don't think he's okay.
I hear he just got stressed out whenever Tempo says, like, what do you mean?
What do you mean?
Yeah, it's like, what do you mean?
What do you mean you're okay?
Wait, I don't need that anymore.
I just picked one up.
You did the charge rifle?
Alright, well, I mean, I'll do this whole shot and we're good to go.
There's a 6x here, too.
I got a...
read-a-play.
I love you, bro.
At least kill one as I'm just flying into a whole three-man with Cosmic Gaps all over.
Can I kill one?
I'm just fucking dead.
I like how we all each individually...
Now me just floating around in the air.
Yeah, now me just floating around in the air not knowing what to do.
He's like, get one!
I'm like, yeah, dude.
I'm gonna find a fucking spot to land first, big dog.
Get one.
Yeah.
I love it, dude.
I love it so much.
I think my favorite part was that we each individually fought different brits.
Yes, that was fucking awesome.
Do we have a thingy?
By the way, this is a horrible zone for us and we have no EvoCache until Geyser, so...
Oh, yeah.
That's what I was about to ask about.
The EvoCache thing.
Can we people...
Do we have a people thingy?
No, we have nothing.
We got a big mod, though.
We got a big mod to do that.
We're good.
There's a heavy mag on that.
Someone grab it if you need it.
I need it, yeah.
I got the blue one.
Yeah, I'll take the blue.
Alright, let's go scan people and then also the zone over at Mog.
Are they still there or did he left?
No, they definitely left for sure.
Unless they're routing it, but the whole paintball side is looted, so I would assume they left.
I can show presence first and see what's good.
I'll fly up and if I die, just run.
That's the chat.
I can't lie, they looted this like fucking horribly.
There's so much shit left.
Do you guys need anything?
They like fast looted, I guess.
Yeah, this team wants to just get the hell out of here immediately.
Which I kind of respect.
It's like the right play to play.
Oh, there's Bats here.
Oh, yes.
I need a sniper scope.
I'll people scan it.
Yeah, you're good.
Hit the people scan and then we'll hit the console beacon again.
I think we just wait until the zone closes, to be honest.
Okay, you want me to scan now or wait?
I would wait.
I think we just play the top Mog and then scan both and then we just rotate in.
Because we're going to be late to this no matter what.
I'd rather know the next circle and see if this is a crazy pull or not.
I don't think it should...
Oh my god.
Okay.
Team over at the drop the fucking evac tower.
I see them.
They're taking the evac.
Yeah, I just want to land on us.
Play together up here.
What the fuck?
They're good.
They almost stuck me with an arc.
Are they pushing us?
They are.
They know we have white.
Oh, we're fucked.
We're fucked.
We're so fucked.
Run if you can.
I'm trying.
I'm trying to run.
I'm dead though.
I think it's either you or me.
Yeah, if you guys split, they can't get all of us.
We're not splitting.
We're next to each other.
No!
I'm in great second place!
They know it's us, dude.
They know it's us.
I think it's they know that we got white armor.
Because we didn't have evil.
Yeah, we had white armor.
Yes!
Damn!
Oh my god.
That's so stupid, bro.
They know we had white because we had no evil.
Yeah.
This is the fucking Ferelly boy kid.
Just a hard-stuck challenger circuit player.
Whoa!
It's true.
All he does is go to challenger circuit and get shit on in the finals.
Look, every god damn time, man.
Because this is how they play.
This is how they play.
They go to finals and get shit stomped.
It's just annoying.
Oh my god.
It's so frustrating.
That's okay.
You need five points a game to get into top ten.
We're still okay.
Don't worry.
We have two more games.
Wait, wait, wait.
This is only four.
Yeah, this is four.
We have two more games.
I think they land dome, right?
Yeah, they land dome.
Or no, they land launch site dome.
Yeah, so they're gonna be behind us every time.
Now we know we just gotta dip the fuck out immediately.
We should be fine.
Because we're storm point on the next one.
We're storm point for the next two.
If these guys are in the lobby again and they go launch site dome, we know they're gonna do that again.
Yeah, for round three.
Yeah, 100%.
You're good, bro.
Do your thing.
Fuck, man.
That sucks.
Because the right play for us there is to wait, to be honest.
Yeah, but they know that that's us too.
So they full sent it.
It's not a bad play.
I'm just salty, but overall it's just annoying.
Yeah, they know we had white too because we had no Evo.
Yeah, it's so rough.
The no player plan for us is pretty rough in that situation.
And also not having Evo cash in front.
Big mod is tough too.
Yeah.
I wonder if they were the same team that fucking ran at us last game too.
Yeah, yeah.
Were they?
I think it was because of the Horizon that landed on us.
Yeah, yeah.
I think that was the same team that landed on us.
So they'll always be like...
I think they'll always be like behind...
following us and mirroring us.
100%.
Without a doubt they will.
I'm pretty sure.
I think we just have to be faster in our rotation.
Because they'll always be behind us.
So we'll... we need to...
We just gotta get the dip the fuck out.
Yeah, dip the fuck out the moment we lose.
Yeah.
The only problem is though in the next round.
If we go to Worlds Edge and these guys are behind us.
If Big Mod doesn't rotate...
We might also not have stacks.
True, true, true.
Where do we want to go for Storm Point next two games?
What are we thinking?
I don't know.
I'm trying to... I'm trying to...
I think these guys land there.
Yeah, I think everything is going to be taken at Storm Point.
But we can still make it work.
Yeah, we'll see where it goes.
Has anyone... no one claimed stuff yet?
Right now?
They have.
But not everyone has.
Just when we think of all the spots that are free right now.
That's what I'm trying to think.
This guy just jumped off the fucking map almost, bro.
What am I watching?
Where's my...
Oh, I don't have it.
These guys are W-Keying everything.
Look at the...
This is what they do every time.
They just literally never make it anywhere.
Because you can't W-Key everything.
Exactly.
They just straight around.
It's okay.
They have the sick ass rank mindset.
Oh, he's dead.
Come on.
Wait, they're dead.
What did they die to?
Nice job, guys.
Seriously, great play.
They died to an actual team?
I'm not salty at all.
Yeah, I'm not salty at all, guys.
No worries.
Bro, they died to...
These guys just...
They play like it's ranked every game.
That's right.
Yeah.
They died to like...
I'm sorry.
They died to nobodies?
There's somebodies in someone's heart.
Road Knife is good.
I know him.
Oh, you know him?
Yeah, he's pretty good.
Wait, am I watching the same team as you?
I think so.
Yeah, Road Knife is really good.
Oh, okay.
So they died to somebodies.
I mean, compare to us, everybody.
I think everybody's everybody and we're nobodies.
Yeah, we're the nobodies here.
Yeah, 100%.
We're the underdogs.
100%.
Follow for follow?
Revive for revive?
What do you think...
Okay, so Tempo, how are you knowing where people are going?
Are they typing in like a Discord or something?
Oh, no.
They were typing in game chat.
Yeah, like they were typing the...
Like they were doing all the dropouts.
Oh, shit.
You're calculating that through game chat?
That's actually pretty crazy.
I was just writing down...
Crossing out all the stuff on the map.
He's analyzing.
God damn.
Thank you.
This is why we have Tempo.
Let's just double check when we swap maps here.
Well, that was a learning game for us.
Now we know we gotta leave quick.
We don't have anything.
Yeah.
We just have to make it to the next round.
I think we have stuff we have to leave quick.
Because their team...
Yeah, because they'll just be right behind us.
Yeah, and also no offense to any of us here.
They're just gonna beat us 3v3.
Yeah, no.
100%.
You're gonna win.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I have a plan.
Okay, okay.
Next round.
Assuming no one goes stacks, and we do.
Right?
We hide in one of the buildings.
And we rat those fucks.
And then we kill one.
We kill one.
And then we can't lose 3v2.
Right?
We're still gonna lose.
I think we win a 3v2.
Right?
Same armor.
Assuming there's no armor diff, I think we can win 3v2.
No, no.
I think we'll win a 3v1.
I'm confident that.
3v2?
I don't know.
No, I think we can do 3v2.
Okay, this is what you do.
When we rat them, and we kill one.
We gotta use that initial...
like, two seconds of confusion that goes through their brain.
And then kill the second one.
And then it's a 3v1.
Alright?
That's the plan.
You gotta use psychological battles.
We're gonna use the psychological battles here?
We have two seconds after we rat one to kill the second.
Cause they will be confused.
Unless they're...
Are we really gonna risk our one game for that?
I think we do.
I think we do it, and then we teabag the shit out of them.
Okay, wait.
Do you think that's a smart thing to do?
Our two games that we have left?
No, no, no.
It's next round.
It's when we make it to next round.
Okay, okay.
If we make it to the next round.
If we make it to the next round, we take...
Cause we're not on World's Edge anymore, right?
If we make it to the next round, we take stacks.
We rat them in a building.
Then we kill one from getting ratted.
Then we kill the second in the next, like, three seconds from confusion.
And then it becomes a 3v1.
Oh, come on!
Yeah, yeah.
Cause they'll have, like, three seconds of brain delay.
When they're like, what just happened?
And who just ratted?
And who's where and what?
Right?
And then we use that delay to kill the second person.
And then it's 3v1.
And after we kill them, we teabag them.
Oh, wow.
You think...
He's thinking so ahead in the future right there.
That's also crazy cause that's just an if we win.
What do you mean?
That's when we win.
We definitely get one.
It's 100% we get one if we rat.
It's like 70% we get the second one in the matter of, like, in the confusion and all the stuff.
The confusion again.
Yeah.
That's seven... yeah.
Confusion is super effective.
Confusion is super effective depending on who you're fighting.
The problem is I don't think this works IRL sadly.
Yo, it's three controller players.
Okay?
Confusion...
This is exactly why I don't think we're gonna win a 2v3.
Confusion probability for controller players is much higher than MNK.
Three controller players.
And that's like why I think we won't win a 2v2.
Instead of Tempo just shooting his gun he's gonna think about how to confuse the players.
Yeah.
He's gonna die with 13 damage be like, bro I got them so stomped that no one knew what was going on.
I gave them PTSD now.
Yo, they're so lost they don't know what's going on.
Bro, I gave them PTSD they're gonna be like, check every fucking building now because of us.
Yeah, exactly.
And then, you know what happens when they have to check every little building?
They get slow.
And then we can get ahead of them next time.
You're so smart.
Honestly.
You're also so dumb.
It's unreal.
I love it.
I thought I loved you so much.
See, I'm just dumb all around.
But like Tempo here he tries to hide his dumbness.
What do you mean hide?
Hey, my brain is still here, okay?
My brain only disappears when I go to when I go...
We literally play Apex Legends.
We don't have rings.
Yeah, true.
Come on.
After the first two years of Apex, it's fucking long going.
You're so wrong.
You're so correct.
Once you play Apex for two years, you just automatically are dumber.
That's just how it goes.
No, that's only controller players.
They get affected twice as hard.
I actually think you might be right, bro.
I have definitely gotten way dumber when I first started.
Wait a minute.
I'm a controller player.
I was pretty smart, bro.
And I'm not smart anymore.
That's for sure.
I used to be smart, too.
I've done some Apex Legends, bro, on stream.
I said that streaming is like the bimbo modification.
Oh, wait.
Are you one of those...
One of those, are you smarter than a fifth grader things?
Yeah, have you ever taken one of those?
No.
I don't think I've ever passed it, bro.
I'm not kidding.
Wait, really?
You took...
Wait, how far did you get?
If it has like geography and stuff in it, I'm just confused.
Geography is fucking stupid.
Why do we need to know where things are?
Exactly.
Honestly, low key, it's been a little bit.
If I'm not traveling, why do I need to know?
Yeah, exactly.
We just need to know where we're going.
Even if I am traveling, I have Google.
Google?
Yeah, we have Google.
We can just Google where to go.
We have GPS.
Why the fuck do we need geography?
To be fair, though, when I was in Japan, I literally just Google translated everything with pictures.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
That's not geography.
I mean, that has nothing to do with geography, but yeah.
Exactly.
Yeah, I'm saying.
Yeah, I'm learning Japanese so we can, uh, when we go again.
I can IGL us in Japan.
Well, you can just IGL us in English.
Like, what do you...
Well, no, I gotta be able to talk Japanese so that I can IGL us.
Oh!
I was gonna be like, we're still gonna be playing the same...
Let me talk to you in Japanese, okay?
No, I thought you meant like, we're gonna be like in Japan playing Apex or something.
I was like, what do you mean?
We're still gonna be talking in English.
I'm sorry.
Uh...
Uh, it's too funny, bro.
I just literally take pictures of everything I do now.
You know what's crazy?
I worked out in Japan, like a park.
And there was like yellow tape, but like not really yellow tape on the thing that says like caution.
Did you go to the...
Did you ever end up going to the One Punch Man place?
You mean One Piece?
One Piece Man?
One Piece Man is crazy.
I did not go to the One Piece gym.
What's that?
I jumped.
Okay, next time we go, we definitely have to make that a priority.
Because I wanted to go.
Wait, what happened to my Nessie plushie?
You said you'd give me a Nessie plushie.
Where is it?
I'll see you at LAN, right?
I have it.
Yeah, I'm digitally gonna go to LAN.
Wait, who's gonna grab the iPad and the...
the roller stuff?
Well, I have a tablet.
I just don't have a rolly thing.
Wait, how much is a rolly thing?
I have no clue.
Hey, you had a level 10 wave trick.
You can send us a...
Wait, wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait.
Doki had a level 10 offline hype train.
Let's see if Apex will sponsor.
Let's ask if Apex will sponsor a rolly thing for us.
It'll be content.
A rolly thing would be content.
It would be so content.
You know how in Japan you guys were on that platform thing for B-stream?
Yeah.
Imagine just having Doki just zooming around in the background and then she falls off the stage.
She's like drifting.
Her little avatar has a bandit on the forehead.
Yeah.
She's drifting too hard.
She just leads herself off.
That was so funny.
Okay, okay, okay.
They sent it while Tempo was on the roof.
True, bro.
Tempo, you and Roofs are cursed, brother.
That's so true.
Wait, weren't you on the roof when they shot you?
Yes.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, and also you were about to.
We should just get off the roof.
I should have just charge rifled them off the thing.
I didn't charge rifle them because I thought they were going to fly away.
True.
But then I should have realized it's through.
They have three controller clears.
No, you're spitting for real.
Okay, so like who's going to ask Apex to sponsor us for the Rooftop?
You, you have the most pull.
What?
Just really?
On the B-stream.
You just got a level 10 hypechain all of a sudden.
Yeah.
You got a level 10 hypechain.
Isn't your hypechain even higher now?
Yes, it's unlimited now.
It's uncapped.
Oh, no.
I mean, isn't it like higher for your stream to go to level 10 hypechain compared to like an Apex?
We probably made more in that level 10 high train than I do to get paid to get to the B stream.
Yeah.
Okay, but like... I've talked to you.
Hey, at least you're getting paid.
I'm just going there for free.
We could get like Apex to sponsor it, which means none of us have to pay.
Okay, yeah yeah.
You go ask EA.
Wait, why do I... Wig literally works for...
Because you have the most pull.
Wig literally works for B stream!
How do I have the most pull?
Because content creators.
More pull.
Wig is also a content creator!
Wig is a host and caster.
I'm a host.
I'm a co-host.
You're not even a host.
Yeah, so then you can like... you have the most pull because you literally work for Apex.
Alright guys.
We're in 8th.
We didn't... we're not 10th yet, so we're good.
Jesus Christ.
Zone Davis has 43 points.
We're not in 10th?
We're in 8th place.
Let's fucking go guys!
This is good.
Okay, we set two more games.
Now we gotta...
We gotta plan for round 3.
Now we can't fuck up.
So, you know, you know, boys, if you guys... if you guys are listening, that's right.
You might wanna double check every single room.
And then this... you know what this is?
If they are listening, then they'll double check every single room.
Wait, I thought we're doing...
So they'll be slow.
I thought we're doing that in round 3.
They'll be slow to catch up to us.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
Oh, okay.
I thought... I was like, we're not doing it in this round.
What the fuck?
JK, we're actually... we actually are here listening.
We actually are, guys.
So, if they're listening and we are actually routing them, then now they have to check every single corner.
Yeah.
So, even if they're trying to push us quick in big mod, they'll be slower now.
That's fucking right.
Check every fucking corner.
Cause we could be...
Yeah, clear the corners, guys.
Guys, check your DMs.
Check your DMs.
Alright, let's fucking go.
This is our real plan, guys.
Check your DMs.
This is our real plan.
I'm checking my DMs.
Whoa, that is such a great plan, Dempo.
I'm waiting for them to type the thingy where they're going.
How did you write that much?
In such a long... in such a short amount of time.
That is like so much knowledge.
You're so smart, little man.
So proud of you.
Alrighty, let's fucking log it in.
Alright, let's figure out where the fuck we're going here, yeah?
Oh, god.
Cascade.
Zeus.
I am a little high and the delay plus wig typing and chat is absolutely breaking my brain.
Yo, someone fucking typed tree and we're on storm point.
I think they've lost it.
Launchpad.
Cascades.
C note.
Beast.
Okay, checkpoint and stormcatcher.
Alright, let's see...
Did team 2 type where they were going?
Team 2.
Oh no, I have no idea.
Let's get the fuck away from them, bro.
I am not trying to go down with a sinking ship.
They haven't typed yet.
Okay.
They just got in.
Alright, so we got pylon wall and checkpoint still open.
Open.
Or our favorite POI.
I'm on CeloDraft.
Yeah.
Maybe because it's surrounded by scary people.
Doesn't the boys do exactly what Legacy does all the time?
I'm not sure.
Why would they do exactly what they do?
Because they both ape everything.
So they both also land at the same POIs, I feel like.
Yo guys, chicken, plum or meatball marinara?
Chicken, brie, cranberry.
You're fucking bougie.
Bougie motherfucker, man.
And the bread has to...
Look at that take from that guy.
I like that.
Good friend.
It was good.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
Maybe that's a crazy thing.
Only 12 POIs are claimed.
I feel like there's just no way pylon's free.
I gotta be honest here.
Okay, well we still have check...
Someone... I remember someone typing wall when we were on World's Edge.
So let's just pretend wall is gone.
Okay.
So we got checkpoint pylon Jurassic.
There's no way somebody takes Jurassic.
It's such a shit place.
Coastal and Devastated.
No one's typing landing spots anymore.
No one's about it anymore?
No one's talking about where to land.
Yeah, I don't know.
That makes me nervous though, because I don't know where the fuck to go.
It's because your chicken prom distracted everybody.
True, true, true.
My fault.
That's in the hard-hitting questions here.
Making them think.
Yeah, they're thinking.
They're not actually doing.
Okay.
Checkpoint pylon.
Yeah.
Jurassic, coast, and the other coast.
Where do I want to go?
Are you playing?
Yeah.
Wait, we're saying coast?
We're going coast?
Yeah, coastal and Devastated coast are both still open.
I mean, definitely.
Okay, so let's just... we're starting.
So let's just go pylon.
And if someone's there, let's go checkpoint.
Okay.
Down.
I mean, that's a really hard jump though.
We just got to hope it starts bottom right and goes top left.
Oh, fuck me.
Okay, let's try it.
Well, wait, am I still caustic?
On storm point, probably not.
No, Watson, I would say.
Okay.
Are we swapping back?
Like, you're on blood and I'm on bang?
No, I think we stay Valk, to be honest.
Okay.
I think Valk's going to be like really important for us.
Are you cool on blood or no?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I was just wondering.
No, you're good.
I don't want you to be uncomfortable.
Alrighty.
It's 645, right?
Yeah.
Go.
The thing is that I think that barbecue place is like 30 minutes away.
Oh.
Let me check.
30 minutes away from food?
Wouldn't be downtown LA.
Yeah.
Jesus.
30 minutes.
What the fuck are you guys just talking about?
Hungry.
25 minutes.
Oh, we're talking about stuff.
It's a long drive for food.
All right.
Bottom right, top left.
Ready?
All right.
The ship did not...
It's the exact opposite of what you just said, by the way.
Well, that's not bad.
If we see someone going left, we go right.
That's not bad at all.
Let's just see.
This is where we want to go.
I might just jump early, but I don't see anybody.
I got to turn my audio back up.
How about you jump, by the way?
There's one team potentially going there for sure.
Should we risk it?
I think checkpoint might be the more free one.
Go there?
Checkpoint?
Oh, yeah.
There we go.
Checkpoint.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Go now.
I'm turning around to watch.
I'm looking at the team chart, right?
I don't think anyone is going pylon, though.
So, yeah.
We know now.
I think there is one team, bro.
I'm pretty sure.
There's one team here, too, maybe.
All right.
What we're going to do is you guys are going to both land on this building back here just in case we're getting contested, okay?
I'm going to land middle.
There is someone right above us.
Someone right above us.
Right below us.
Yeah.
Go over here.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No.
We have no choice now, sadly.
Oh, we are getting contested.
We're going to make it work.
We're good.
We're better.
100%.
I'll just hold angle from here.
Okay.
I think we are for sure.
Here's a charge rifle for a fight that's in front of us.
We're good.
We can just leave.
Get your loot and then go back down below.
We're going to go down below.
Okay.
I don't want to fight this because I just don't know who's near us or what they're going to do.
I just don't know who it is, to be fair.
All right.
I'm going to jump off and we're just going to keep going mountain ride side.
We're going to go walk towards middle side, okay?
All right.
Okay.
I'm heading over now.
Yeah.
I'm going to start walking down immediately.
Steer their loot and get the fuck out of here.
We might just... Yeah.
I think we go pylon next game.
I think so, too.
Let's do it.
Yeah.
That's fine.
But also, teams might take it now because they might think it's free.
Just loot all this.
I'll go to the next building.
You guys loot this building.
Go down below.
We're going to go.
All right.
We're fine.
We're going to be fine.
I picked up a scope.
All right.
And there's a charge rifle here, too.
Let's just see what is free here.
Let's just see.
Are they low-balling up there?
I'm good.
Nice.
They're fighting over in mills right now, by the way.
There's a skull.
I'm going to go up here.
Nice.
I can't use it, sadly, but it's...
All right.
I'm going to walk down here.
I think we just... I think we need to find a beacon.
We should get this Evo cache, though, on the rotation out.
Yep.
Agreed.
For sure.
We do not want to be blues anymore.
We do not want to be whites anymore.
12 is down.
Nice.
Okay.
So, one team dead.
That's going to be the mills team that just died.
So, we should be able to rotate and get this Evo cache over near Cito.
I want to destroy these spiders, but I don't know if we want to do it right now.
We really, really need... like...
Not an Evo somewhere.
No.
For sure.
One bat, six cells.
We're going to hit this Evo cache right now.
We got to watch out, though, Tempo, because this team...
There's another nade.
There's another team fighting in there.
Yeah.
I think we just let them fight.
Okay.
We're good.
Where do we want to go?
I don't know, bro.
I want to go towards Cito, but if this team's still here, I don't want to...
Cito's looted.
Yeah.
I know, but I don't know if they're still here.
You know what I mean?
But this would be... We're pretty early right now on the rotation, and Cito takes a long time to loot.
Let's play slow here and see, because the Cito station team should be really good if they're playing Cito.
Should be a good squad.
Yeah, they are on top Cito right now.
Yeah, yeah, they scan us.
We're going to back up here.
Back up here.
We're going to go back.
We're going to go towards Bean, okay?
We're just going to walk over here and go towards Bean.
We're going to pathkill this guy.
I know it's a really shit route for us, but we don't really have another play right now.
We're kind of getting fucked.
We're good, though.
We're fine.
We need another Evo.
I know.
This blows.
Or we can... Yeah, we don't have a scanning thing either.
No, we don't.
I'm going to shield cell right now, just in case.
That's fine.
Do your thing.
We're still mating back there, yeah.
I mean, yeah.
I would third party if we didn't have fucking wights.
We just loot this up.
We're good.
We love this.
Take our time.
And we just have to literally just loot up to make sure we just C-zone.
You can also hit that prowler if anyone wants the damage for the Evo.
Do you get enough Evo anymore?
I don't remember.
I think you do, right?
We really just need...
We need like a hundred...
Guys, did you hear?
Only 15 squads already, guys.
So many teams are early fighting for no fucking reason.
This is great.
No one wants to take those.
There's a 2x on that.
I have a 3x ready.
I'm good.
I'm good too.
Let's just keep looting up.
Yeah, because teams are landing on each other, so...
Yeah, exactly.
So we should be good here.
Because they're not sure.
Yeah.
There's going to be a lot of teams fighting that don't know where the fuck to go to.
Don't forget, we saw like three POIs free and we got landed on, so that sucks ass, but that's what it is.
We can go get the care pack here too, maybe.
People were here 10 seconds ago.
Okay, nice.
They got the care pack.
You're good.
They're over here now too.
They're rotating back towards CETA, but did the barometer have a beacon?
No.
It didn't have a beacon either.
So these guys, no one near us really had a beacon at all.
We just wait for the zone to close.
I think we played big building over here near us.
And we just wait for the zone to close and go from there.
Okay.
Let's play in here.
Put together, fence up, and then we just go.
It's definitely not going to end near here, but it's fine.
Just stick together and show presence and we're good to go.
We're going to play this late, but we have a Valk for this exact reason, to be honest.
Is there any other Evos that we can get?
Any other Evo caches?
There's no one near... no, none of them are near us.
So ass, bro.
The team that fucked this checkpoint sucks because we could have got an Evo cache up there too.
It's all good.
I'm going to go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Scary.
I'm... well, I'm 12-3, so...
Okay.
Yeah, I'm 0-6.
0-16.
I have no bats.
I have cells, though.
Alright.
We're good, baby.
We're vibing the fuck out.
Just stay calm.
We got this.
Valk ulti's pretty...
I'm still calm.
Valk ulti's literally going to be our saving grace.
Like, the biggest.
I have an evac tower too.
I want to jump this guy here.
I have a West Beacon.
Someone take that back.
I got it.
Oh, Ana's on her.
We're going to run right on her too.
They're going to fight this point.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm going, going, going.
You're ready for a fight.
You're ready for a fight here.
So we're at 33.
Keep scanning when you can.
We're going to have to get opening damage here.
I already scanned once.
Yeah, you're good.
I might be down.
In from the window.
Yeah.
Yep.
I have to heal.
You're good.
I'm in now too.
Shots up top.
Oh, I'm in.
No audio?
Super sick.
Oh, no.
If one of you guys can, if one of you guys can leave, you should.
You have to leave.
Drop me.
You leave.
They're really out my door.
Armors, armors.
Run away.
Run away to armory.
Yeah, yeah.
Just run.
God, we're getting fucking old.
Nope.
They just fucking scanned me.
That's them again.
Is that them again?
I have no idea.
Just keep running tempo.
They're going to just land on you.
Just keep going.
Whoa.
That's awesome.
Bro, if it's them again, I'm actually just going to be so mad.
It's unbelievable.
I have... were they rank 41?
I have no idea.
Oh, we're getting fucking old.
Is that them again?
Is it?
Their horizon.
It's them again.
Oh, my god.
It is them.
They're right behind us.
These kids are so cringe, bro.
How did they get us again?
It must have been the mill... wait, is this their first... it's their first fight.
Yeah, it's their first fight.
So they weren't mill.
They were probably C note, I guess.
Right?
I'm trying, bro.
And look at the zone, too.
Checkpoint.
Oh, my god.
Oh.
Maybe we should have just fought the checkpoint team.
I don't know, bro.
And that situation is just so tough.
Yeah.
Like...
God damn it.
We can't make it.
It's them again.
We died to them again.
Yeah, it's actually just super unfortunate.
Are they fighting again?
Oh, no, dude.
I hope you guys get... I hope you guys get day two, you motherfuckers.
What?
That's right.
We still have one more game.
It's all good.
Don't forget.
One game, but we can still get us through.
Yeah, we just need one game.
We got one point.
Guys.
We got that one point, guys.
I mean, to be honest, as long as this team keeps rolling every other team and the teams with us don't get any points, we should still be fine.
100%, bro.
Without a doubt.
Yeah, but our third... our last game has to be good.
We need to get...
Yeah, our last game has to be decent here.
We need to find a spot.
We need to find a spot to land to.
I think pylon should be fine.
Pylon?
Okay.
Yeah.
It was open.
Like, it was open, but we only... we veered away because we thought someone was going to be there.
Well, we should have went on pylon.
Where is this team landing?
The team that just killed us?
Yeah.
Probably C note.
I would say C note.
Because we knew... someone was fighting mill and they don't have any kills from before us.
So it's either C note or barometer that they went.
Yeah, because they're like mirroring us in both maps.
It's okay.
We don't make it through.
We still have next week, guys.
No, we got this, guys.
We got this.
Wait, is it literally next week?
Like the Saturday?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's actually next week.
I'm going to send you all something.
Don't look at it though on...
Oh, okay.
Okay, I'm going to be honest.
That's the only thing I'll read.
That's...
Don't look at it.
Okay, I'm going to be honest.
I thought I did.
Because I know the first sentence you write is not going to be anything.
Yeah, no, of course, of course, of course.
It definitely wasn't her just reading out, not thinking, and being like, oh, wait a minute.
Yeah, I understand.
Yeah.
That's right, guys.
That's right, dude.
All right, we can get 10 points in this next game.
And then we Gucci.
But if this team...
One good game is all that matters, bro.
One good game.
If this team or the other two teams, if this one or Redeem or Relax just kill everyone anyway, then we actually stay in our ranking anyway.
So we're good.
Yeah.
We just now that they killed us, we need them to kill everyone else.
Okay.
I mean, they are sort of killing everybody.
Yeah.
But then, like, the thing is they're not killing people fast enough.
So, like...
They have 10 kills.
So, like, the people teams below us might just overlap us from sheer placements.
Maybe.
Yeah, we're getting zero points.
We got one.
Oh, we got one?
Oh, we got one.
Okay, good.
We died, like, 15.
I mean, if we can actually get pylon for free, though, we're going to be fine.
Yeah, I think we'll be fine.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If we get pylon for free...
This is the checkpoint team that...
This has got to be the checkpoint team that we landed with.
It's really unfortunate, bro, that that checkpoint team...
That it pulled up here?
Yeah.
I mean, to be honest, we also didn't say checkpoint.
Yeah, that's true.
To be fair, you're right.
Yeah.
Did they claim checkpoint?
We should just type 2POI so that everyone gets confused.
No one typed checkpoint.
Yeah.
Oh, no one typed checkpoint.
Oh.
So that's why we thought we should be okay there, too.
If it looked like someone was going pylon.
Yeah.
So technically, it's also their fault, too.
It's also our fault.
They should be mad at us, to be honest.
Yeah, they'll be like, what the fuck?
You typed pylon.
Why are you here?
Because no one typed checkpoint and we thought someone was going pylon.
Yeah, we hesitated.
Wait, that was team 8.
Who was team 8?
It was team 8.
I don't know the thing.
I actually don't know.
One sec.
Oh my god, I got hit by four headshots.
Yeah, did you?
Yeah.
Did you get fucking rocked?
Bro, I got no audio.
Did you watch my VOD back?
No.
If you watched my VOD back, I had zero audio on Horizon just landing right in front of me.
It was crazy.
I got jump scared so hard.
It was fucking terrifying.
That's okay.
We have one last game.
That's all it is, guys.
We got one more.
Listen.
One more game.
We already did better than what we thought.
And then next week, if we play again, we're only going to get better because we're practicing.
Oh, yeah.
Because we know.
Because this was our...
This is our practice.
Practice week.
Yeah.
And now we know what POIs we like.
We know what characters we like.
We're so good to go now this next week.
We should have done a scrim or two before this game.
But no.
Instead, this was our practice.
Yeah.
First character.
No need for that.
Yeah.
This was our practice.
Our practice for pro.
Yeah.
It's only the one practice week, guys.
We got one more of these bad boys.
Come on, dude.
Yeah.
I'll take...
No, it's not good.
It's not good.
Yeah.
I don't know why.
We can't make it to the finals if we just keep spamming it.
We also did that so we can like, you know, have off on Sunday.
Like we just care about our mental health a little bit.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
We're not done yet though.
I don't know why we're coping.
Oh, don't worry.
I already had... I was already planning on Sunday to be my rest day.
I fucking love this team so much.
That is fucking hilarious.
Oh my god.
Leaking TSM strats right now?
Oh my god, please bro.
That would be a juicy reddit post I could react to for content.
Guys, they're saying that TSM is planning on...
Oh, here we go.
They're planning on cutting Hal from TSM.
And then...
Yeah?
I'm getting Doki?
Yeah, yeah.
Cutting Hal.
And they want to bring an up and comer.
I hate Doki Bird.
I didn't do it.
Hal is planning on retiring.
No, no.
Hal is planning on retiring?
What?
Wow.
Oh my god.
Can we get a reddit post with Doki's name in the title?
Exclusive on Doki Bird's channel?
I'm listening to what they're talking about on TenpoStream right now.
And it seems like Hal is planning on retiring.
And they're planning on hosting tryouts for his replacement.
Like this week.
And Rept is going full time?
Plans for zombies?
That's crazy.
Oh my god.
And like, Verhulst is planning on becoming the new IGL for TSM.
Insane.
I heard Hal is committing to ant farms full time.
He's committing to being a housewife for his girl.
Good for him.
Yeah, good for him.
Actually, yeah.
Good for him.
He's gonna be the...
He's gonna full on housewife duties.
Good for this guy, man.
Honestly, vibes.
If I'm being honest.
Yeah, he's like...
Apex is just a great time to retire.
This is the best time.
He's retiring at his peak.
Retiring for $5 million.
Yeah, good for him.
Good for that guy.
Good for that dude.
Oh man.
Wow, wow, wowie.
You know?
Wowie is right, dude.
Don't worry.
We have...
One more game.
Honestly, it's gonna be 100% possible to qualify for us.
We just need placements.
We need better placements.
We just need fucking a beacon, bro.
That's all we need.
Not running.
We need to fucking 8th team.
8th team 6.
What were you guys talking about?
What were the TSM leaks?
Oh.
We were going to dinner.
Oh yeah?
And I heard that you guys are hiring Doki as full time...
Yeah, yeah.
You're signing me up.
Yeah, they definitely have enough money for this.
After not paying for a house anymore.
Bro, why is this guy fucking 1v3'ing by himself?
Is this still the same team?
Yes!
He's like 1v3'ing away from his team.
They have 21 kills.
No, for sure.
Yeah, all this bro just to go out literally never make pro league.
Yeah, to go out in day 2.
Cause you just can't do this against good players.
It's nuts.
I mean, we're not saying we're not good players.
I mean, they can do it to us though.
Yeah, they could definitely do it to us.
Probably every time.
They could probably beat us 3v3 99% of the time.
I mean, I'm pretty sure they could beat us 2v3 if they wanted.
Maybe even 1.
Maybe even 1, you know.
I don't wanna be surprised.
There's just one guy that's literally trying to 1v3 by himself.
They're both like all three of them are trying to 1v3 a fucking team.
Listen, this is all just setting up a crazy comeback story if we don't make it this week to go next week and ball the fuck out.
Oh, that's so true.
It's so true, dude.
Ooh.
It's so true, I believe it.
I really did too.
But I think we're gonna make this next one.
We're gonna be good to go.
That's the vibe I'm on right now.
I think we secure a W this next game.
This is gonna be the one we win.
Oh my god, and then we can... Do I get a Liquipedia now?
Now that I'm in CC?
Wait, I think I get a Liquipedia too.
Can I be on a Liquipedia?
Oh my god, are you gonna get one?
Oh my god, I'm in an official tournament!
What?
Zero earnings?
No, no, no, no.
If they add my content creator tournament earnings...
I bet you if they add all my content creator tournament earnings, I earn more than some pro players.
Without a fucking doubt.
I'm pretty sure I do too, okay?
It's not the biggest flex.
Unreal.
It's gonna be... Wait, did they just win?
They just won.
Yeah.
What point did you guys get this game?
One.
They ran at us.
Bro, tell... Who's that?
Tell them to coach us.
Doki says coach us.
Coach us!
Hop in the Discord and coach us.
Yeah!
Oh wait, we're in ninth guys.
We're tied with five people, five teams for ninth to 13.
Guys, but like if we fuck up this game, we're not gonna be called.
We need us... We need coaches.
We need coaches.
Insane.
Oh, apparently I do.
You guys are my... I don't play Valk.
Remind me to scan care packages, bro.
Okay.
Yeah, that would help us with points.
I think we would have... I think we would have had blue.
Yeah.
I just forget, dude.
All right, code's up.
Let's go.
What was that?
We're tied.
We're 9, 10, 11, 12 all tied at 11 points.
Well, I shouldn't send that.
I really want to send that message.
I'm not gonna send it though.
I'm better than that.
Mm-hmm.
I really want to send this.
Why do you guys suck?
Stop running.
We ran every time we fought them.
You want to say, why are you running?
No, no.
Why are you running at everyone?
Oh, yeah.
I thought you were gonna say... I thought you were gonna say, like, why are you running away from the visor?
Like, bro, this guy's got 30 kills.
I don't know.
All right, let's go, guys.
We got this, man.
This is it.
We're literally... They literally have a chance to qual.
And we just got two, zero... 1.0 point game, dude.
We just need... We literally need, like, good placements.
That's all we need.
All we need is literally not to die to Team 2.
That's literally all we need.
We just need Team 2 to run everyone else down.
Yes, yes, yes.
We need you to stay the fuck away from these guys, please.
In-game and out.
Please.
Please leave us alone.
Leave us alone.
Please.
What did we do to deserve it?
I scared everyone off.
We're good.
Wait, what did you say?
Nice, bro.
You think you got swing like that?
I can't think about that.
That's the minus Tempo confidence I need, bro.
Everyone... They come to me to host the tournaments anyway, so...
I'll just be like, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This guy... This team just apes everything, so they're not good for the tournament.
That's insane, bro.
That's insane.
That's unfortunate.
We should run everyone.
For actual Reddit reasons, that's a joke, by the way.
Tempo would not do that.
Yeah, for legal purposes, that is a...
I'm not joking.
For legal reasons, I'm not joking.
I can make these jokes because I'm not organizing any tournaments in Apex.
He...
I want to say it, so I'm not going to say it.
I'm not going to say it.
I'm going to...
I keep typing things and deleting it, you know what I mean?
What are you going to say?
No, type it to us, and then I'll say it.
No, no, no, no, no.
We're actually just saying what you look like, bro.
Oh, my God.
You're so smart.
Type it to me.
I'll say it.
I'll say it if you type it to me.
Yeah, it can't say it to a VTuber model.
What are you going to say?
Now I'm curious.
I'll tell you.
Bye, Asher.
Bye.
What are you going to say?
All right, guys.
Don't worry.
Exclusives.
I won't say it.
Oh, my God.
Thank God.
I'm trying to be better, bro.
I'm trying to be better.
Oh, my God.
I'm not, though.
A VTuber shit-talking you, bro, has got to be top three worst moments.
Okay.
I'm going to type it.
I'm going to...
You don't have to type that.
Yo, type it after we make it to the next round.
Okay, okay, okay.
Yeah, snap it.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, you save the shit-talk for when we're on top.
If we go out sad as fuck, we don't say anything.
No one will know.
Okay, how about this, bro?
If we lose, we don't make it past to the next round.
We go, like, literally all black profile pictures, everything on Twitter, and we go into our grind mode this week.
You go into grind mode?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God.
It's like LeBron James in basketball.
In the off time, he goes full black profile picture, everything.
It just grinds.
And then we'll go to wig to grind mode, and then he'll be like, I'm sleeping, guys.
Yeah, then we're like, we woke up, we're like, all right, guys, we're ready for the practice.
I just woke up.
I'm ready to ALGS.
Let's be honest.
How much would have ranked really helped in this situation?
We got to the same team three games in a row.
It would have helped so much.
Because I would be practicing instead of playing other games.
What games were you playing?
I was playing anything I was streaming, you know?
Dart underscore game.
Dart underscore game is crazy.
Yeah, actually.
Let's see, what was I streaming?
Time is like non-existent for me now.
I was playing Roblox.
Yeah, instead of playing Apex, I was playing Roblox.
Oh, you were playing Roblox instead of Apex?
I was playing a visual novel.
And then I was playing Halo.
I was playing a South Park game.
I was playing...
Look, I was playing everything but Apex.
The only time I played Apex was the Nessie Cup and the JP tournament I did.
There's tournaments back to back.
That's true.
Yeah, for real.
Start the... where the fuck is...
Start without him.
Start without...
Start without that team member.
Not what the fuck admin.
Not what the fuck admin Talarian did.
We could have had a chance.
We could have... alright, it would have been possible.
Okay, this really shows me though that like if we genuinely just didn't die to team 2 every game so far, that we could actually...
We would have made it.
Yeah, without a doubt.
100%.
Because we are literally just died to one point in two games and we're still almost qual.
Yeah.
We're good.
We got this shit.
Let's go.
I'm ready.
I'm ready too.
Alrighty, we go back again I guess too.
This is it.
This is the game.
Chat said we're hosting a podcast.
It's not even a game anymore.
We're just podcasting.
Who is this person?
I'm betting him from a house chat.
You're betting him from a house chat.
I was just threatening everyone.
Bro, he's...
Alright, we're going Pylon, right?
Pylon?
Yeah, Pylon.
We don't have a beacon again.
Wait, wait, wait.
But we can rotate into Jurassic if no one goes there.
Yeah, that's fine.
That's fine.
Honestly, if no one goes in this direction, I might just land...
Land Jurassic.
Is there anyone checkpoint this time?
There is.
Yeah, this team's going checkpoint.
We should definitely drop soon.
Drop now.
Yeah, I want to drop now.
Hopefully these teams are not going there.
They might be, bro.
If they are, we just sort of Jurassic.
That right team looks like they're going far right.
Yeah, they're going CETO.
I think this team might be on us here.
This team might be on us here.
This team might be right beside us on our top left.
There's a team above us too.
And the team to our left.
I mean, Jurassic's free.
I don't want to contest.
I definitely don't want to leave them.
I think it's Jurassic.
I'm looking right now.
Yeah, we're going Jurassic.
They're landing on Pylon.
There's two teams Pylon.
What the fuck?
Okay, so I'm going Pylon.
Do you think that checkpoint team just left and was like, fuck it?
No, no.
I saw them going there.
We're good.
They're 100% on there.
It would have been nice though because they had a double beacon and we went there.
We're good though.
We got the shit.
Let's do it.
I can't scan yet.
Fuck.
No, you can't.
You're good.
Yeah, we have ring console, which is literally all we need for getting these points.
Literally all we need.
We'll see what happens.
Well, our team is definitely going to run at us to get beacon as well.
True.
We don't have any like things for scan stuff.
Oh my God.
I'll give this out.
That's huge for us.
I'm going to loot inside here.
It's going to end Cito slash Bean for sure.
I'm going to loot this.
All right.
Sounds good.
We really need an Evo cache though.
We don't.
No, we don't.
Yeah, it's so bad.
We're going to loot this.
It's all good, baby.
All good.
We got this.
Where is there?
What's the closest Evo?
Oh my gosh.
There's no nothing that's close.
We're going to need you to scan like, scan the boxes then.
Yeah, this is going to be tough.
When I get the care package, I will.
But it's not going to get us enough.
Okay.
I mean, at least not awful, awful, I guess.
Just the white armor is going to be tough for now, Evo.
Fine.
We could rotate through.
I'm going to go back.
Maybe I go over.
I don't want to go there now though.
This pile on too much to come through.
I was just saying, I probably should have went over to the nut and just got the Evo cache over there.
I could still do it to be honest.
Should I risk anything or no?
For what?
Go over here to this nut and get the Evo cache?
Yeah.
I feel like you should at this point.
We don't have anything.
I think I do too because regardless of what the fuck happens, we're just, we're going to die.
Like if we don't have, yeah.
Wait, this guy's routing it.
Wait, what?
They're routing the Evo.
Okay, nevermind.
I don't.
This guy was just head coaching the Evo.
What the fuck?
I'm coming back.
Was that person?
That had to be a person.
That's why my fucking graphics were fucked up.
No, yeah, that thing's not there anymore.
Yeah, I just got scammed by pile on too.
We should just start rotating this down.
It's good to see this die.
I don't have an open cell for anything.
I have a note.
I'll give mine too.
Do you want me to hold it or you want to use it now?
I think we just, do we save it?
We're fine.
I'll walk in a little bit more.
We definitely need an Evo.
I'm going to try and grab this Evo.
It might be hard, but I can't do it.
I mean, the white armor is so...
I can't walk into the map because the team's going to int everything.
And there's Cedar Station.
They're right here too.
They're moving across.
The white armor is just really fucking rough though.
Yeah.
Well, let's just slide down.
Just play from here.
Maybe try to get some shots first before we rotate into actual center zone because you have nothing to fucking do.
Wait, I'm not ready.
I'm coming back to you guys.
Okay, I'm backing up.
I'm backing up.
The white armor is just so rough, man.
Fuck.
We're going to get sandwiched here too.
All right, we should actually rotate down here, I think, and try to get that Evo.
Okay.
I think you're right, Doki.
Just keep going this way.
I'm trying to.
Yeah, you're good.
You guys are fine.
We should be fine.
We have no choice now.
Can we grab that one at blue?
Yeah, we should be fine.
At least we get blue, which is just, at this point, way better.
Like, that's just better for us in the long run.
Yeah, we're getting fucked over right now, but we're doing good.
We're fine.
That's what it is.
We don't have a choice.
Let's get this Evo cache, and then I think we just literally play in this building.
Well, I see a trophy shop.
Yeah, there's a team there.
There's a team there.
It's okay.
Let them go.
Maybe we can get the Evo when they rotate out.
I'm just going to play in this building right now.
I'm going in.
Yeah, you're inside.
We're good.
We don't really have a choice.
This team left the Evo cache, though.
But there's still a team on the left side.
I don't want to go over there yet.
Barometer team's going far.
Flying up and seeing if I can actually see what they're doing.
I think I got the Evo cache.
You guys stay here, alright?
Yep.
I'm going to charge rifle.
I'm going to charge rifle barometer.
Yeah, if I die, then fuck it.
We can... I mean, we have evac and your ult, so we can use either to try and get a better position.
No, we definitely want to try to get in somewhere and get a good spot for some.
I got the Evo, by the way.
Alright, nice.
That's good.
Good start.
Should we go to you or...
Okay, they're top barometer now.
Yeah, they're just showing top barometer.
I don't know.
So, like, here's my dilemma, guys.
Like, I want to go over there, but they're going to run me.
They're going to run down everything from Cedar.
Like, even with blue armors, I still think they're going to just fight us regardless.
Yeah, I agree.
They have prowlers and probably burp purples, which is so fucked.
What we could do, though, is we could hit an ulti and fly into front side Cedar right there over on the back side.
I just don't know if it's going to be safe or not.
I think like...
If it's not, we're fucked.
I think it's better than being here, right?
We want to just stay here and see more teams dying first.
I think it's going to be better over there, for sure.
Yeah.
I think we just go on roof and we hear my Valko.
Okay, we're here.
Let's try it.
Why not, right?
Okay.
We got to make a play for a zone here, I think.
Here we go.
All right, we're going to try to get to the front spot and see what happens if there is a team in there.
If there's a team in there, we're dead.
There's a team here.
There's a team...
Not one in here, right?
Not one in here.
I can't see.
I can't see right now.
Nothing's pinging.
Door's open.
We're good.
Just land inside.
It's the right side of the door.
Oh, I...
We're good.
Pinging off the door.
Okay.
We have a good spawn zone right now.
We shouldn't get inted.
I just want this team to run down everybody that's not us.
Okay.
Where's the best place for this?
Jen?
Jen would probably be like literally right here.
There's a rez in front of us too.
Or back to your tempo to be honest.
Right here too.
It's really good.
There you go.
That's fine.
I want to put it away from what's their face.
Yeah, and if you could fence the outside tempo a little bit too instead of inside as well.
Oh yeah, do you want the ulti-exile or do you want to charge it up passively?
I think you're good.
I think it's charged up passively.
Good job.
We live here now.
Alrighty.
Come on.
Jesus.
Oh, look at the outside.
We did something.
Good job.
Thank you for the plus 50.
Good fences, tempo, good shit.
Whoa!
What the fucking shit?
You're good.
I'm looking over here.
Okay.
You're not coming down yet.
You're good.
I cracked my top.
I'm fine.
I was just looking at the flies.
Yeah, you're good.
They're white armor.
You're on white?
Do we ape those fuckers for shooting us?
No.
We should not ape.
Where did we get shot?
Did I get shot from behind?
I have no shells, by the way.
Just realize that.
Oh, I have more shells.
Yeah.
I got, I got like...
Open this door.
How about a...
Hey, one point.
Nice.
Yeah, one point's fine.
That's good.
Nice.
Wait, we just chill.
Yeah, we just vibe the fuck out.
I mean, again, we just literally can't get into it.
Having these guys in your lobby until like the later rounds is just an awful experience.
So we're fine.
That's what it is.
We're doing well.
Oh, wait, wait.
I can shoot those idiots up there.
Don't get on the roof, Tempo.
You're on the roof.
Tempo, get the fuck off the roof, Tempo.
Tempo, get the fuck off the roof.
They jumped off.
We're good.
I scared them.
I'll do it in here.
Yeah, that's fine.
You're a gigantic football-sized head.
Me?
Or you or Doki?
Who's Bloodhound?
I don't know.
How do you not know who's Bloodhound?
I'm Bloodhound.
Oh, yes.
Dead.
Their horizon is killing people.
They're just going to feed everything off and we're just good.
There should be more teams than having zero points than us.
For sure.
Which is good.
What were the teams that had... who were below us?
I have no idea.
I didn't see the names.
They were like 9 and 8 and 7.
9, 8, and 7?
I don't know if I saw their names yet.
Like points.
Oh.
So if they get any amount of points, that's not good for us.
No, no, no.
I meant like... is it team 9 or team 8?
Oh, I have no idea.
Oh, okay.
I thought you meant like...
No.
I thought you meant you know their team numbers.
Because I could just look at the numbers.
What do the numbers say?
I'm not going to peek right now.
I actually don't even know where they are.
Where are you shooting from?
They're shooting at me.
Yeah, but where?
You ping them?
I can look at them.
From over here.
Oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Okay, okay.
Tempo.
Hello?
Open.
Open door, sesame.
Oh, what the fuck are you doing, Tempo?
I was trying to level up my thingy.
This man keeps going outside to scare me.
I know you're fine.
I know.
You don't have a lot of shields, dude.
You have multiple gems.
Yeah, we should have put on a gem.
Thank God.
Yeah, thank God.
It's all good though.
I mean, right now, I don't really know where the zone is going to go.
I think it's going to pull towards us personally.
But it could pull towards bean as well.
We'll find out soon.
We'll see you in a little bit.
A minute or two.
Do they have... they don't have console.
Oh.
I feel like I see a lot of teams like this way.
That's the scary part.
They have ring console.
Oh my balls.
I'm broke.
I have four cells and no bats.
And one syringe.
Wait you have one here.
I'll give you one syringe.
Yo I can get purple.
Okay how much more you have?
A thousand.
Dude.
Stop.
That's only ten shots.
I have a thousand as well.
I'm also still a thousand.
I haven't shot once.
Only ten shots.
Don't worry.
Here here.
Here's a syringe.
I dropped a syringe.
Nice.
Take that syringe big doll.
He literally told us he had one syringe.
Oh yeah.
I have a med kit though.
Hell yeah you do baby.
Yeah you do.
Get that med kit.
Yeah you do that baby boy.
This is a podcast.
Yeah it is really.
Oh wait I saw something land somewhere.
I'm gonna go kill them.
Tempo if you get knocked out I'm never hanging out with you ever again.
Wait you were hanging out with him?
I can get this killed.
You were hanging out with him off screen?
I'm gonna fucking pull.
One sec.
I should have made a recon play here.
Tempo are you shooting someone over in the building?
Oh they are.
Okay.
I'm shooting like this way.
So like I don't want to leave yet.
I'm gonna go ahead but I can't lie a really good play would be taking underneath over here late game.
Like really late.
Okay.
There's also a spot in water we could take late game.
I don't want to leave yet though.
If we go there early I just don't know what's gonna happen with my 13 squads up.
We get out angles so hard.
Alright I'm just waiting for your thing to charge me up.
Me too.
Yeah you're good.
I'm not gonna use any of my meds.
I didn't want to fight three out of a Jurassic.
If no one comes from Bean's side to fight us this is actually really good.
If anyone does come from Bean we just need to get aggressive on the slide down from the hill.
That's all we need to do.
Okay.
We're gonna try to watch your back when you're slamming like that.
If you get killed from Bean we're dead.
Like we're just gonna get sent on.
Alright who scanned us?
Who scanned us?
Okay that's not good.
This team scans us is gonna see we're a full three men by ourselves.
So just watch out for Bean right now.
Yeah I'm looking.
Yeah that's where we're all gonna look and we just gotta shoot on the cross down.
And then we just get aggressive on the slide down at all.
The door opened and I'm looking.
They're redeploying.
Okay they might just land on us.
Let's see.
I can shoot him off.
I'm gonna try to.
Oh wait where's that third?
Oh.
They're going that way.
That's so good for us.
They're gonna go towards that team that was hitting the scan on us.
Let's get gigantic.
How is this team playing top of C though and not getting shunted at all?
They're gamers.
Yeah just gamers.
They're just gamers.
What can they say?
Yeah I don't know what to say anymore.
They're just those guys power.
I don't know.
We don't have a word for you.
Do I want to throw another gen down here or no?
Um yeah I would.
We're gonna get it back.
We also have all of the cells too right?
Yeah I have 8%.
Oh they're shooting from the... yeah they're shooting from that way.
They are on bean.
This team's gonna fight us I think for sure.
Do we have no more charges?
Oh yeah we don't.
Okay.
No.
I don't really want to...
We do.
Just throwing it down now.
I'm gonna control this door and shoot these guys on top bean.
Alright.
Watch your back Timber.
Team 2 was eliminated!
Nice.
Okay good.
Good.
That's huge.
That makes me a little bit more confident that the bean team's not gonna fight us.
What the fuck?
They're shooting us from the top here.
Yeah that one.
That guy's really good bro.
Everyone's very good.
Everyone's very good at the game.
Everyone's very good at this game.
Everyone's like way ahead of me.
I'm lucky we got him.
I want these guys to leave with their horizons so I don't think they're gonna leave.
Team 17 dead alright?
We got one point off placement.
I mean we've already... originally got one point already.
Show how you're starting.
I'm like what do you mean?
Can they play the top of the hill still?
Yeah.
Yeah they can.
Just let me know what they're doing.
Someone just stared at them.
I'm staring at them.
I'm staring at my own bro.
Where do we go?
I mean there's a water spot we can play.
There's over here under the waterfall.
Yeah we could.
Yeah.
I think we might have to go there late but I don't know what these guys are gonna do.
I don't know.
They're gonna shoot our fucking Valkylty out.
Well can they... they can't go the other way.
They have to go to us.
Yeah I mean they can evac though.
Do they have an evac?
We're gonna do late game.
We're gonna jump out my side over here.
Okay?
Towards over here.
And we're gonna Valkylty over the back side on this building.
Okay?
That's what we're gonna do.
I'm just gonna wait for the charge.
I have zero damage.
Yay!
That's fine.
I mean we don't have a choice this time.
Yeah if I have the time to fucking shoot anything.
These zones have not been great to us at all.
They've not been kind.
Alright you're gonna need a gen though.
Oh they smoke us or what?
Can you see?
I'm gonna scan them.
Yeah scan them?
Nice nice nice.
That's fine.
Alright so we have two options.
I'm just gonna keep a lookout.
I'm gonna try to figure out which option is good.
Just stay on me when I'm flying okay?
Yeah yeah yeah.
They're not dropping down.
They're just... they have to go soon though.
Yeah they have to leave.
Once we see them pop their evac we need to take our Valkylties because they're gonna shoot us out.
And once we see...
They're just flying down they're flying down they're flying down!
I hit one for 80.
I hit purple 80.
Can we scan when you can?
Scan scan scan scan.
Oh no oh oh oh oh.
Why are they firing off now?
It's fine.
Oh my god I'm getting shot from behind.
It's fine it's fine.
I'm holding the door.
Okay.
I don't scan I don't scan I don't scan.
One could one one could one one could one.
I got...
I full killed I full killed.
I'm a door I'm a door I'm a door.
Okay okay.
Why are you killing us?
You're so bad at the game.
We're good.
I'm medding.
Play slow we're gonna be dead here though.
We have to kill these guys we have to kill these guys.
I'm trying to figure out where they are.
I'm gonna carry we're gonna run between these guys.
Okay okay okay I'm here I'm here I'm here.
Play slow play slow.
Play slow don't eat the Vagaldee.
They're nading us now too.
I'm...
We have to go we have to go we have to go.
Go go go go go go go go.
It's me I'm right side.
Try to get your kills.
That's different that's different.
That's a whole other squad.
What?
I'm not fighting us bro.
We got eight though.
Fucking eight.
Wait did we get any kills?
Oh we got one kill.
Where did they come from?
This might be possible.
It might be possible.
Three points.
I just cannot believe this team is fighting us bro instead of evacing.
What are you doing?
I don't think they had an evac.
That's not...
The challenges are against...
Yeah oh my god my brain hurts a little bit today.
I think yeah we should...
We definitely should have left.
We should have left.
Yeah we found their ev...
I don't think they had an evac.
I don't even know but we played that.
We actually played that correctly because we just need a valkalde late there and we just get sent on by a stupid team.
Yeah I think Rezzer was the second team hiding behind us.
I know I was the top side Seedos team.
There's no reason for them to do that either.
That makes no sense.
They died for it.
They tied the fight off.
Yeah.
I mean this is just my theory that CC is just horrible.
What do you watch party?
I mean no final round of CCs guys.
Yeah but Jesus Christ.
Too many teams out here thinking they are Aurora or fucking TSM.
Unfortunate I mean what three points?
There's a chance like a small chance.
There's a chance.
It really depends.
It sucks that team two actually died though because we needed them to go crazy and kill off the teams.
It was because they died that teams were still alive.
I mean we got eight.
We got point.
Yeah.
We'll figure it out here.
We got point.
We'll see.
Damn if we got that Valk ulti off I think we could have played that spot that I wanted to too.
It sucks.
So guys it's okay.
That means that we per- if we don't make it to the next round we purposely threw so that we could play more together.
And next week we get round three which is not that hard to be improved.
Yeah.
We get to- Yeah.
It just means that we just wanted to spend more time together as the besties so we could- Yeah we just love each other that much guys.
Yeah we just love- and we just wanted Sunday off.
We loved each other so much.
Wow.
We also did not want to stream on Sunday so that's why we purposely threw today.
Yep.
Exactly.
We didn't want to stream tomorrow.
We're so smart.
We're so smart guys.
I think if we didn't get- It's not over yet though.
I think we still could.
It's going to be really low.
I think we have to get fourth place not ninth.
I think like if we didn't get run at twice in a row that time definitely.
If we just did not get sent on two times very coincidentally by the best team in the lobby it would probably have been great for us.
The team we died to is Relax.
So they're in fourth so this is good that we died to a team that was above us.
Okay.
What about the teams alive right now?
Who's Varded?
Who's this team that I'm looking at?
Who's Varden?
Yeah, yeah.
They're team four.
Varden?
Team 10?
No, team 10 is- I don't know what that team number is.
This team just won like 30 kills so hopefully it's a really good team.
You can see when you open the set.
Let's see.
It's their tie in 10.
And 11 and 12.
Wait, what happened?
No, I'm saying we were tied with 10, 11 and 12 before going into this game.
Oh, so we're tied with 10, 11 and 12.
That's really scary.
That's scary.
Oh man.
We got 12.
We were four points away.
No!
We were four points.
If we had two games of just like two more points, we would have been fine.
We would have just died to those guys three times more.
Yeah.
Oh man, it is what it is, guys.
You know?
It is what it is.
GG's.
GG's everybody.
Team boys banned from all NA.
This guy's been a nice wig guy.
GG's.
Say it.
Type that thing.
Type it.
No, I typed it.
I typed that.
Those Forelli boy's.
They're all banned.
They're banned from all NA events now.
Oh my god!
I'm going to be a bad influence.
I don't know.
Guys, am I a bad influence?
Guys?
Oh yeah, you are.
I like you.
Alright.
GG's, guys.
You gotta go grab a bite.
Hey.
We haven't eaten anything today.
You can play next week though, actually.
Yeah, let's do it next week.
I'm in.
You practiced this week?
And then on top of that all, we figured out a comp that's good for us as well.
We'll figure that out too.
It was a feeler.
It was a feeler week.
Yeah, we were just figuring stuff out.
Exactly.
You get it.
You know what?
I'm glad I didn't have to play six hours.
I know.
I'm actually kind of glad too.
Yeah.
Don't worry.
I'll be locked in next week.
Next week I'll be locked in for six hours.
Yeah, same.
Same.
I still feel around guys.
Yeah, we're just feeling it out.
We didn't know how it was going to be.
Also, someone make my Liquipedia now because I went and...
That was an official tournament.
Liquipedia immediately.
Yeah, I want my Liquipedia now.
And the person that keeps removing it is removing my Liquipedia.
You can't remove it anymore because Challenge Circus is legit.
Yeah, exactly.
We're mad legit.
Okay guys, I gotta head out for dinner.
GG's guys.
We run it back next week.
Next week.
Is that the one on the 13th?
I think so.
13, 14...
I should be able to play 100%.
I'm 100% sure I can.
Let us know.
GG's guys.
I have a lot of time.
Bye.
Listen, don't call it a comeback because we never left guys.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We exceeded our expectations because I didn't think we were going to get past round one.
I'm with you as well.
I'm the same thing.
So we exceeded expectations.
Alright.
Well, GG's guys.
Love y'all man.
GG's everybody.
Bye bye.
Bye.
That was fun.
10 minutes chat.
Will you guys see this in 10 minutes?
You know, it's a blessing in disguise.
Because I can actually rest.
It's secretly a blessing in disguise for me.
But GG's everybody.
I honestly...
I had a...
I had a great time.
Playing with Wig and Tempo.
And we're going to see if we'll all be doing it next week.
We'll see.
But as always everybody.
Stay hydrated.
Posture check.
Get up and move around to get that blood flowing.
And if you're suffering, head to bed.
Because you deserve it.
I'll see you guys next time everybody.
Bye guys.
Bye.
I hope I do the fucking...
The delay thing always fucks me up.
I don't know how to do it properly.
Like ending this delay stuff.
But I hope I don't accidentally end it in the middle of the game.
And you guys are going to be like, what?
But we'll see.
We're going to see you in 10 minutes.
Bye.