No, you don't have to deafen.
You can all join in.
What are you doing now?
I know you're doing it now.
Yeah, hey, we're live.
We're live.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What do you mean, wait?
I don't know what you just said.
Alright, guys.
Welcome to the Toki Verde X Oversight Custom.
We're doing it live.
One million dollars.
No, it's not going to be a million dollars.
It's ten million.
Yes, funded by Nice Wig.
What the fuck?
You get the hundred thieves money.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
You were CEO for the day, Wig.
Yeah, one day.
Yeah, the one day you just made my bank account.
One day you made like nine million.
Yeah.
On that day, like one team, one tournament winnings and you took all of it.
I wish.
That's some real shit.
I would have done that by far.
Out of your mind.
Hell yeah.
Wig, are you excited?
Are you excited to get you and Greek to cast this?
Yeah, I'm pumped, dude.
Okay, Wig didn't fully read the rules.
You love making up lies.
There's nothing stronger.
There's nothing stronger than a Doki Verde lie.
I just missed every single rule.
Yeah, you missed every single rule.
We were like, Oh, do you know who the princess is?
And then he said, Oh, is it Doki?
But lies, if he read the rules, he would know that every pro player was supposed to be the princess.
Wait, wait, wait.
It says here, princess.
It doesn't say on game five.
It just says princess can use any ability.
Oh, you're reading a TLDR because you can't read.
That's what Temple made the TLDR exactly because they don't read the full rules.
Oh, I didn't read.
Yeah, I didn't read the full rules.
Okay, I didn't even know there was another one.
If you have a professional player on your team, they will be the princess.
For other teams, you decide who the princess will be.
Oh, so Doki should just be the princess.
Are you trying to say Jen's not a pro?
I'm saying you're literally the goat.
That's what I'm trying to say.
You're Hermothy.
Okay, I have a confession.
Even though I organized this custom, I haven't played Apex in like three weeks.
Yeah, you're killing it.
Did you send me that link for that VTuber thing?
Yeah, I did it in a multi-dex thing.
Oh, yeah.
Are these a lot of VTubers?
I've been playing Apex for three weeks.
Oh yeah, when was the last time you played Altair?
Oh, the rules don't apply to me.
This is really hard.
Wait, are all the people in the tab people playing this person?
No, no, it's like randomized.
You have to select your own VTuber.
You have to put it on yourself.
Okay, I don't know how to do that now.
You said you could do it!
I'm watching someone play Mario Kart.
You literally said you could do it!
I told you it wasn't me.
It was hard, it was difficult.
Jokey, you're going to be on YouTube or both?
I'm on YouTube.
Okay, I'm on yours.
That's good.
Okay, you see yourself.
You see yourself bouncing around.
Wait, I do?
Oh, that's me!
Yeah, that's me, dude.
Let's go.
That was dope.
Let me pull up to the stream.
There's so many VTubers in this thing.
I'm not complaining, I'm just saying it's hard to find out who's going to be live on YouTube.
Oh, Kewpie's playing!
Alright, Kewpie's going in the mix, obviously.
What the fuck?
Kewpie's a goat.
She wants to win so she can talk to you.
Are you excited?
She's the goat, dude.
I love Kewpie.
She's literally hilarious.
She's been working on her English, apparently.
She's getting way better.
She's going to try so hard just to be able to talk to you if she wins.
That's my dog, dude.
I hope she wins.
She also is cracked, so there's a really good chance she does take a W.
Alright, I'll make sure to message.
What about Tappy?
Tappy's really good.
One Tappy's gross.
Oh wait, there's actually some... I didn't realize.
I didn't realize!
No, I'm saying the VTubers can actually play-play.
Yeah.
He didn't even look at the list of the other people.
That's crazy.
Wow.
Is Nocturnal not considered a VTuber?
Dude, he looked at the NA people chat.
If he has his fucking cam on, no.
He just wanted to use his little handsome face in that clip.
Yeah, he's a fleshy.
Fleshy?
Yeah, that's you.
You're fleshy.
Wait, so how do I type people's names in, though?
I see the plus thing, but I can't type names.
Okay, so you go to URL and you paste the URL.
Oh my god, this is going to be so long to do.
So the opening ceremony is us teaching Wig how to use multidex right now.
Welcome to the tournament, guys.
I appreciate y'all for being here, man.
We're locked in.
Greek's supposed to be here.
I think he forgot, to be honest.
All good, though.
But he joined the server!
He joined the server, like, two hours ago, so I assume he knows.
Yeah, you're right.
I don't know where he's at, to be honest.
Wait, aren't you guys roommates anymore?
Oh, you guys still?
Yeah, you can literally just go up to him.
Yeah, I probably should, huh?
How about Discord pick, like, move in?
Yeah.
You guys are bouncing, so people will know he's talking.
I'm bouncing.
I'm jiggling.
Holy.
Did you make this website, Toki?
Don't say that.
Toki, you made that website?
It's not great.
It's good, it's just, like, it's not made for idiots, that's, like, the problem.
This is made for smart people, and I just don't really have them in me.
So you're trying to say, like, VTuber fans are smarter than the average fleshy?
Can we be honest?
Probably.
Whoa!
Not people like that.
A lot of people watch you, so.
Whoa, it's okay.
You're figuring it out now.
You can use this for later.
You can use this for next VTuber tournaments, now that you've figured it out.
Yeah, actually, it kind of helped me out here, but none of it's working, so this is great and all, but I'm really high-pressing.
Enter, and nothing's happening.
I remember I just said, NA Apex fans are very slow.
Wow.
No, it's sort of, um, I'll say, like, not NA fans, I'll say, like, NA players are very slow, and I'm an NA player.
I...
I sort of agree as an NA player.
I'm malding right now.
You're malding because of the...
Can you do something?
Can you try this?
You're smarter.
Not now, Greek!
One second!
What?
Oh shit, wait.
I'm getting messages that Designful is still not here.
Where the fuck is Designful?
Where is Design?
And saw the colorful buttons, and then I got confused.
You want me to tell Timmy to call him?
Yeah, get Designful.
Designful's not here.
They're like, where is he?
Timmy and Designful are both supposed to be playing?
Yeah.
Timmy's on, right?
Well, I don't know.
I don't see him in the voice channel.
Yeah, you can call him.
Okay, I'm gonna wake him up.
How is this link not valid?
How is the link...
Alright, but welcome to...
Welcome to the custom, everybody!
Welcome!
Customs, people are not showing up, cuz.
Don't understand what's happening right now.
Okay, let's see.
Alright, let me explain the rules real quick.
Let me swap.
Alright, guys, so...
Let's be a little bit formal here.
Let's actually have an opening ceremony, cuz we have like 15 minutes left till the game starts.
Nice, we're just letting you know.
Alright, let me go live then.
We have 15 minutes till the games are supposed to start.
Okay, so, yeah.
You start this off.
Alright, so...
I got the slides up, so you guys don't see it.
But, like, the slides are up now.
So, I'll do like a brief recap of all the slides.
So, what are you doing?
This is a VTuber slash pro tournament.
Not tournament, it's a custom.
So, every game somebody can be a winner.
And we have three prizes going out.
So, we have the $5000 first place prize with medals.
I actually have, like, a preview of the medals.
It's a work in progress right now.
But, like, it's either gonna be in gold or in color.
So, we're still deciding.
Gold?
Okay!
So, this is what the medals are gonna look like.
Maybe it's either gonna be in gold or, like, in full color, which I forgot to save the image, but you'll sort of be able to figure out.
Oh, wait, no, I do have the image.
It's right here.
This is what the medals might potentially look like.
And there's a huge shout out to GamerSups for funding, for making this for us.
And also, we're gonna have...
Everybody's gonna be sent a pin to be like, thank you for participating.
So, everybody's gonna receive this.
And... And you think game is right?
Yeah, or this one here.
We have 10 minutes before...
To be fair, we have... It starts at 6.15.
I'm going, you're locked in.
I'm so locked in.
I'm so... Anyway, we have...
Wait, why don't you help explain, too, since you clearly read the rules.
What part were you at right there?
I'm at the rules part.
What are these schemes gonna be like?
Okay, guys.
So, we got six games today.
So, we need to lock the fuck in and go over all the rules here.
Or I will start banning people in Dunkey's chat.
I do have that in mind.
You're not even married in my...
Okay, so I'm gonna get... I'm gonna get that and then we'll... Then I'm gonna start banning people.
Let's lock in six games here today.
One game... Game one, not one game.
Game one will be the normal game I'm rolling.
I'm gonna read the TLDR here because we gotta go fast, of course.
I read the whole rules, but we gotta make sure we lock in.
We have like 20 minutes.
Master and Fred can only carry one gun at a time for a game.
It's gonna be a normal game here on World's Edge, but only one gun.
Wait, how many Master Preds do you guys...
Doki, are you considered a Master?
No, shut up.
No, I am.
I'm considered a Master.
Regis, are you Master Pred?
No, he's not.
He's Diamond.
He's not.
He can use any gun.
Isn't Regis nice at games?
Boo.
You don't know that.
You don't know.
This is the first time you've met him.
You don't know that.
Game number two.
Whoa, whoa.
Game two is gonna be melee only on Storm Point.
No damaging abilities or grenades there.
So that's gonna be very interesting.
Someone's gonna get beat off in that game for sure.
Guaranteed.
Game three is gonna be charged.
Send to Lombo and Kraber only on E-District.
That's gonna be an absolute shitshow.
Can't wait to watch that one.
Master and Fred can only carry one of those guns at a time and cannot melee.
So...
Yeah, but Altair can melee.
So we can...
So I was talking about how it would be funny for teams without a master or pro player they're just gonna be in a corner waiting for a guy to roll up and they're just gonna fucking stop brawling at him in the fucking corner.
That's gonna be like 30 teams alive.
Round six, no one's gonna be dead.
Also, you can use all abilities but no grenades.
Interesting.
And then no vantage rampart and cannot fight until ring one is closed.
So if you fight before ring one is closed, I will personally remove you from the lobby.
Yeah, he's gonna do that.
He has that power.
Yes.
I don't have that.
I don't think I should.
I don't have the power but I...
You call them out on stream, right?
Yeah, sure.
Why not?
I'll do it.
Use it like the server chat and be like get the fuck out.
So game four is gonna be a hide and seek on Broken Moon and no one can damage each other.
Now, I didn't read the real rules for that one.
How does that work?
So, it's gonna be...
Our team is the seekers.
I was thinking Altera and I we're gonna compete against Jen to see who can kill the most hiders and we'll figure out the prize later.
So like...
Just punch them.
You get the punch, we get the shield.
So we're gonna be the seekers.
So we're gonna be eliminating the hiders together.
Beautiful.
Everyone will land in one corner of the map.
We love eliminating the opposition.
PoppaJenBirds in the chat.
PoppaJen, I fucking love you, man.
Love you.
Your dad taught me how to curse, by the way.
Wait, what?
Like what?
And I told him how to curse.
No, he just gets mad at me for cursing and then he cursed at me for cursing too much.
And then game five is gonna be protect the princess on E-District.
You only carry one gun at a time.
Princess can use ability slash melee only, no grenades or guns.
No vantage rampart, damn.
And when princess gets finished, the team must surrender.
That sounds crazy.
When the princess is finished, which a lot of people in this tournament will not have an idea what that means, they gotta surrender.
Everyone has to give up.
The whole team just gotta drop their guns, stop shooting, and just die.
If they get downed and rez, is that okay?
Well, yeah, if they get downed and you can rez them, it's like full knock, so they're full kill.
Then you're GG's, you're out.
I think we have a comp for that.
I have an idea.
Slay the princess.
Slay the princess!
But, Gem, do we tell our strat on stream live?
No, no, no.
All we're saying is that Tempo came into our chat and told us the game changing strat.
Not rigged, by the way.
It's not rigged.
What do you mean?
It's a strat.
I'll look away.
Yeah, yeah, look away, look away.
Of course, now and ever.
Game 6 is gonna be the normal OG on King's Canyon.
Master Pred can only carry one gun at a time.
So you guys putting Master Pred players at a handicap, which is fair, because we do have a friendly mix of Integrity going on here.
We got some Hoes, we got some Gem Burtons, we got some Dokis.
We got some Opias.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We got people that's never played Apex before, so, you know.
Yeah, we actually do.
Yesterday, they were like, this is my first time playing Apex.
That's so crazy.
That is insane.
They're gonna have either a great time.
Actually, no, but you guys did a really good job evening it out.
Yeah, we have some games that are not part of shooting, you know, so like hide and seek.
Yeah, so like hide and seek and melee.
Imagine Newcastle.
Yeah, you can't use Newcastle.
Yeah, so it's damaging.
But you can use the Q, because I thought it would be really funny if everybody throws their Q at one person and they all bloody die.
Do you guys know the Q does damage?
I literally found that out like two weeks ago.
That the Q does damage.
You didn't know that?
No, I didn't.
Like who the fuck gets hit by a mobile shield?
Real shit.
I didn't know that either.
I was just trying to play along.
That's why I was like, you can use the Q, because I think it's fucking hilarious if you die to a mobile shield.
It does 20 damage.
I feel like if you die to a mobile shield, you probably should just uninstall.
Greek, any thoughts here, Greek, on what we're watching today?
I think it's going to be pure chaos.
Are you excited?
Oh, absolutely.
Yeah, which game are you most excited for, buddy?
I think protect the princess.
You see how the pros be like pack meals for everybody?
It's going to be chaos to watch.
I think it's because the team who loses their princess has to just insta do nothing and just stand there.
That's exactly what it is.
Just let them fucking run at the team.
Just give up and just stand still.
Just eat it.
Just take it.
Just execution style.
It's like, it's over.
You failed your mission.
That's so funny.
I mean, no, I think you guys did a good job too, like kind of just wrapping the games to be fair for everybody.
I'm actually really excited.
I think it's a good idea.
It's really cool that you're working with Tempo because Tempo is the goat.
The goat of Apex.
Somebody gotta hire him.
Guys, not only is he single, but he doesn't have a job right now.
So you guys should hire him.
You guys should definitely not take the fact he's single into his resume.
If you're down to work with HR very frequently, then you might be down for that.
That's crazy work.
It's insane work.
Oh, yes.
Also, you forgot to mention in the rules, in game one, if there's a team that are way too overpowered and killed the majority of the teams, as a lobby, we get to decide how to nerf them for match six.
So it would be like a public execution under...
There you go.
Well, I mean, that's what I'm saying.
I feel like you did a really good job evening this out, and lobbies should be fair.
Yeah.
So that makes them not want to get nerfed.
What kind of handicap would you want to give teams that might be too strong?
Because of me?
Yeah.
My god, put them to your feet or some crazy shit?
Why?
Yeah, I mean, you can make whatever you want, right?
Maybe opposite influence.
Go get a controller if you're an MNK player.
Go get an MNK if you're a control player.
That'd be good.
Oh my god, that'd be funny.
They should all have a controller or an MNK.
They can use MNK.
You should have one.
What about we do a poll and let chat pick what characters they have to play?
Yeah, but then that's not really a nerf for some people.
They can, like, adapt to it.
I'd like to pick what gun they can use.
Oh.
So just singling one gun?
Yeah, like one P20.
It's OG P20 and it's on King's Canyon where the loop pool is other shit.
So it's like, you don't know if they'll be able to find that specific gun.
What about look inversion?
Like where they look left and it goes right?
Oh, hey!
That would be fun.
Those guys would get shit on.
Oh my god, that would be so fun.
One of the control players, South Pole, legacy.
That's what I'm saying.
Oh, man.
I'm trying to choose who to watch.
I gotta watch RPR for this, for one of the tabs, for sure.
And why don't you just put up YouTube?
Did you give up on the multi-view?
No, so I have to wait for people to be live in order for that to work.
This is like a horrible start for me.
Is Timmy's design awake?
I don't know.
These are the teams, guys.
That's us.
And our princess.
Oh my god, yeah, our princess is right here.
Oh, Amma's here too.
Oh shit, we got bangers in here today.
I'm locked in.
Alright, let's see.
Is everybody here?
Is everybody...
Wait, is Designful or Timmy on yet?
No.
Okay, that's a little...
I called Timmy and he didn't answer.
You're the one that's like...
Wait, are you still in Australia?
Yeah, I'm still in Aussie.
Yeah, you're in Australia and you're here.
I'm still in Aussie.
It's bloody 1pm right now.
Bloody.
Oh no.
What do you call a stovetop?
Yeah, what do you call a stovetop?
Okay.
People in the UK call it the hob.
A what?
I've never heard that in my life.
That's a made up word.
H-O-B.
Oh, I've heard that before.
That's why they're on an island.
Well, Australia's on an island too, but like...
Get that terminology out of here.
Weren't you guys deported criminals?
Woah, woah, woah.
What do you mean woah, woah, woah?
They're losers of the emu wars.
That's history.
Oh, that's true.
They did lose to the emu wars.
That's a little embarrassing for deported criminals.
Imagine the emus.
I felt like the criminal thing was just like...
Loitering or like...
Look, listen.
Back then, we had muskets, alright?
We didn't have AK-47s.
And they had feathers.
They don't even have bullets.
Like, what do you mean?
They're emus.
When you ever watch a fucking emu, bro, they're terrifying.
The fuckers are literally so scary.
They'll just peg you until you die.
Peg you?
Wow.
Woah.
I just got crazy.
Woah, that's crazy.
That's crazy.
I would not fuck with emus, bro.
Those things are scary.
Aussies go wild.
Aussies do go wild.
Dude, I have to wait for these people to go live.
I'm balding.
Just add everyone and be like, go live now.
I'm about to start going crazy in this chat.
Players, I don't even understand what I'm saying.
No, Dash is here.
Our JP translator is here.
Dash!
What's up, buddy?
I just woke up.
Here's some of the prizes, too, guys.
I'm showing it on stream.
Here's some of the prizes that Tempo took photos of.
We also have a Funko Pop, too.
Nice.
Yo, Carl, wake up!
What's he saying?
What?
Is he waking up?
I don't think so.
Why is it...
Why is it silent?
Okay, quick question.
Yeah?
Design and Timmy are both not replying.
Well, Jen's literally on call with him right now.
With Timmy.
Oh, he picked up?
Um, I don't know.
He's literally on call with him.
He's not responding, apparently.
Yeah, so those two aren't here.
And then I don't see Sykkuno in...
No, Sykkuno is red.
He said he's...
What?
Did he just woke up?
Yeah, he woke up.
How is he not...
It's 6pm.
Yeah, I don't know what their schedule is.
It's crazy.
I woke up nice and early for this tourney, bro.
Yeah!
Okay, but you're not NA.
It's 11 o'clock for us.
No, Japanese is late.
Oh, that's true.
But the matches are supposed to start at 6.15pm.
So they have time.
Yeah, we have time.
It's the gamer way.
Wake up, don't brush your teeth, no deodorant, just hop on stream and you're good to go.
Yeah, I mean, you're going to be inside anyway, so it's fine.
Totally.
It's totally not, yeah.
Did you brush your teeth?
Whoa, two times a day?
Okay.
And a tongue scraper.
A tongue scraper?
Yeah, I can't wait to do the tongue scraper.
Timmy is awake, and now we just need design and then we're good?
Yeah, we just need design.
What's this prize thing you're showing?
Oh, there's physical prizes.
So like, second place.
Second place, you get physical prizes donated by Tempo.
Apparently, so a lot of the stuff you can't buy anymore.
Yeah.
So it's like, limited edition.
I just bought a bunch of stuff.
And I figured I'd get it.
Oh, look at this shirt.
That's so cute, though.
Yeah, they're so cute.
Look at the little bloodhound.
That was when we were in Japan for Asia Festival.
Oh, you got this at the museum?
Yeah, I bought like 30 plushies.
Whoa, that thing's badass.
I love that thing.
I'm gonna give them out.
I have the golden one.
That one is a piggy bank.
Yeah, it's so cute.
I don't have this one.
It's a green ass.
Is this like, overall prizes?
Like, these are second place prizes.
So if you get second place, you get the physical prizes.
But you only get to win it once.
So like, other teams can have a chance to win it.
And then, third place, we have 45,000 apex coin packs.
Is that you as a doll?
Is that me?
God, I wish.
I wish I was cute as this.
Look at that shit.
That's so cute.
The bloodhound one?
That was Wraith.
Oh, there's like, yeah, there's a Wraith one, too, here.
Okay, that's pretty cool.
Yeah.
Oh, look, Timmy apologized.
Look at that.
Now we gotta make Designful apologize, too.
Where?
He just says, my bad.
I'll join the lobby.
Hold up, I'm coming.
Oh shit, I should join the lobby, too.
Wait, what's our comp for the first match?
Uh, I think everyone's gonna be sweating.
I ain't gonna lie, so...
What is the first match?
Give me Newcastle and Kat.
All right.
All right, what's the code?
Don't say the code out loud, everybody.
What's our team name?
Achievement Hunter?
IRS.
Yeah, we're the IRS.
Who's Achievement Hunter, bro?
I didn't think we were Achievement Hunter.
All right.
Where the fuck?
Oh, wait, yeah, Achievement Hunter's number.
Okay, I didn't look at my drop spot.
I know I made it.
I already forgot what my drop spot was.
Who's on team Gooner Gang?
Gooner Gang?
Um, IPN.
Respect.
Let me look at our landmark.
We are at...
Oh, we're at Skyhook.
Not the Trials side, the other side.
East side, motherfucker?
East side, yeah.
Skyhook East.
You guys excited?
The first match is just a normal match, though.
What do we do if no Timmy?
I mean, no Design.
I don't know.
That's a good question.
You gotta play, bro.
Jump in, bro.
Design might not wake up.
Okay, who do we know that's free right now?
Let's get Hal.
He's fucking solo ranking anyway.
He's getting off in like 20 minutes to go for dinner.
Oh my god.
I mean, that's enough for one game.
Is he on Gooner Gang?
No, he's on The Fools.
Gooner Gang is already...
Greek, this is your chance to win 3 grand.
Yeah, this is your chance.
You just gotta be there for one game.
Design might be awake by then.
Design wakes up by then.
I would be a literal detriment to a team.
I haven't played the game in two and a half weeks.
Hey, that's me too.
They don't want me on their team, bro.
Don't worry.
You'll have a great time.
Okay, who else?
Is there any pro player that's alive right now that's alone?
Let's see.
Who's alone right now?
Wait, wait.
Who is teaming with Design?
Hold on.
Are they Japanese?
No, no.
English.
Okay, okay.
Tenjin and...
Tenjin and RiruSki.
Is there anyone alone?
I'm looking at it.
No, everybody that's online that's already in our tournament and our custom.
Let's see.
We gotta drag one person in.
Tao is solo queuing right now.
Yeah, but he's leaving in like...
He's leaving in 20 minutes and we don't think he's gonna...
I mean, unless he could...
Unless he wants to play for 20 minutes.
But you can maybe ask Stunny.
I feel like he would play.
Stunny always takes opportunities to play the game.
He's great.
Is he already online?
I think he's just playing ranked.
He's on stream, just watching YouTube videos.
Oh yeah, get him in!
Yeah, yeah.
Greek, you message him.
He'll respond to you faster.
Alright, I'll ask him.
That's not even possible.
Greek's nervous to show out in front of everybody.
He just wants to make it fair.
He's just walking, stunting on them.
Greek's nice with it.
Wait, someone pinged...
Oh.
Wait, what did they ping?
Uh...
Oh, they were asking how to join the custom lobby.
Oh, you post a code.
Yeah, Mac...
MacAlberLily posted a...
Oh, how to do it?
Oh, how do we get there?
To the private match, huh?
Yeah, yeah.
I think it's one of the people that haven't played Apex before.
That's why we had to do the nerfs.
Oh, wait.
Yo, Stunny's ranking with an amigo and QT.
Oh no, they got in!
They just got in the game!
StunnyCity's down.
No, but they just got in!
Tell him to throw, tell him to throw.
He's got 8 minutes to win a rank.
True, true.
Yeah, it's true, true.
That's why I'm messaging you, so you can get him all the stuff.
Yeah, but will he be able to, like, win in 8 minutes?
Yeah.
Either win in 8 minutes or lose in 8 minutes.
We won a Pred game in 2 minutes.
Wait, really?
How?
You're the only three left.
It went by so fast.
We literally just beat him, the pie's loaded in, and we just won.
Something was wrong with the game that day.
Someone quickly, if you're in his lobby, if you're in Stunny's lobby, just stream snipe.
Someone stream snipe Stunny right now.
Just eliminate from the lobby, so he can get into our lobby.
For TOS purposes, that's a joke.
Yeah, that's a joke, guys.
We would never include stream sniping.
That is illegal in the TOS.
It's like a little party here.
Wait, you know, someone was making that where, I can't remember if it was a game, if it was COD or something, they were gonna start banning people who were doing that?
What?
Stream sniping?
Ban them as much as they were banning cheaters and stuff?
Yeah.
I can't remember what game it was, but one of the popular games was posted on Twitter that they said they were gonna start doing that as well.
I won't be surprised if it's Valorant.
Riot's really anal about stuff like that.
Actually, yeah, I think it was Val.
Yeah, I was gonna say, I feel like Valorant is one of the games that would be super anal about stream sniping.
I would have so much fun just watching streams and being like, oh, this person's stream sniping, and then ban them and give them a message saying, oh, it looks like you can't queue anymore.
LOL.
That's why Riot games people are so toxic.
Tempo is tired of bullshit too.
Do you guys know he has a blacklist?
Wait, is that public knowledge?
Wait, Tempo has a blacklist?
Who?
I love that.
This is the IRS explain.
That's amazing.
You deserve that.
Enlighten me, please.
I don't even know who the fuck's on it.
I support it regardless.
There's a list of teams that sign up and show up.
There's a list of players that are continuously late.
That includes pros and content creators.
There's a list of people that are flaky.
Wait, you have multiple lists?
I thought it was one list.
Oh, no, no.
Is that individual one shit?
They're individual lists so that if I don't want to deal with certain problems then I just delete all of the players all of those players from the invite list.
Good for you.
Actually good for you.
Good explanation right there.
Yeah, you deserve that though.
Yeah.
I've seen that discord, man.
You deserve that.
You deal with a lot, brother.
You deal with a lot.
That's why you'd be a good teacher.
I mean, he was a teacher.
What's easier, teaching children or handling Apex players?
Children.
Because at least I could scare them.
The blacklist is not scary enough?
Apparently not.
They don't give a fuck about it.
How would you scare these children?
What was the tactic for that?
Psychologically.
How old were these children?
Yeah, I was going to say, you were allowed to do that?
Junior high, high school?
They already have trauma.
You just make them if they start lying to you and shit and acting up then you just give them a psychological treatment where they feel like the most crappiest that they've ever felt Oh my god!
and then you keep putting them more and more into that hole and then you're like, that's right, you should have listened to me.
Regrestia is playing.
I can't lie to you I had a teacher I fucking hated in high school that did that to me You're definitely sticking with something that's in children's minds, bro.
No, I was a fucking terrible student after that anyway dropped out of community college and fucking did nothing.
And then my boss yelled at me because kids went home crying and then they told their parents and then my parents told my boss and I was like, well, that is unfortunate.
That is unfortunate.
That is unfortunate that your kid is stupid.
Oh my god!
In my defense I don't think you're gonna be hired as a teacher again It didn't matter if the kid was stupid or smart, the only thing that mattered is if they were willing to learn Yeah So even if they weren't the smartest if they really tried to learn then I would,
I love helping those kids But then it's like the ones that come with an attitude and are actually stupid but they think they're the smartest thing in the world I just gotta, and then they have no manners and I just gotta put them in their place Yeah Yeah I was with you on the list part I got a question Yeah?
Where are me and Wig gonna be when these games start?
Is there like a separate channel for us?
Yeah, they can look above you We're not gonna hear it, I get it We have, Wig apparently we have perms though to join any of the channels and just listen to any comms we want Oh, can I influence RPR to be tilted or is that not a thing?
Yeah, you can whisper sweet whispers into his ear It's like the most intense fight and then like join a channel and like fuck it up for them That's exactly right I'll just start screaming on top of my lungs You can throw my mic and just Wig, if you wanna troll Japanese people then get me in I'll bring you I'll bring you I'll bring you You translate it for me,
that's all we need That's it, easy Hop into those channels and start making gun sounds and go pew pew pew Oh my god, Sunny Hurry up, he's dead, but he's like Wait, oh my god, he's gonna get timed out Sunny's gonna get timed out and then he can leave Wait,
what?
What is going on?
You can't, even if you get timed out because they can craft you, you can't leave What?
You can't, that happens to me every single time in solo queue and I hate it I don't know what they mean Wait, no, oh my god, he just found out about it too He was like, what the fuck?
But you don't get that penalty So you know when it was only the support characters that could craft?
If you didn't have a support character on your team, you could leave Oh, yeah they have a support character But now anyone can craft You can never leave So you're stuck there In solo queue, I'm stuck in hell Oh my god Yo, 59 plus people waiting for the Sunny's rank Sunny,
please It would be funny if Designful woke up at that time I still can't believe that he is oversleeping in an 8pm tournament
What was he doing?
I don't wanna know That's what I'm saying, how is he oversleeping?
It's incredible Gamers really make no sense He must have been up to 1pm, he must have stayed up all night right?
He has to I mean, how the fuck Yeah, but he knew he had a custom today That's what I'm saying Alright, he's in Alright guys What a trooper There is a world where we have to restart Wait, why?
I actually don't know if he left Oh no He might definitely get the bug where he doesn't get in the game Yeah, because he has an abandoned penalty Oh, I see I think more than likely that might happen In game, then in customs it still kicks you out Alright Oh Alright,
we'll see then Let's see what happens I totally will not be back in this channel later at all For sure guys, good luck Alright, I'll see you guys later Catch ya Enjoy, enjoy Enjoy the custom Goon the gang That's what I'm saying Goon the gang I look like a goon at the start of the name That's the gooner org You're the gooner org,
alright We are almost about to start Oh, we're starting, let's go Okay, so it's Catalyst, Newcastle and Lifeline Okay, I'm Lifeline Oh wait, don't wait No, Altair's on Gibby then We're not doing Newcastle?
Oh shit, we're doing Newcastle, Gibby?
Not Lifeline?
Okay, I'll do Gibby then No, I can do Gibby, I can be big boy Okay It's up to you, you can play Lifeline too It's fine I can do Gibby, I think we need Gibby and stuff Oh, starting server How long does it take to start the server?
I took those big balls to my face Huh?
Huh?
You wanted to say that, why?
Why did you say that, Jen?
Yeah, Jen, go ahead What the fuck?
Dude, I didn't know you could change your voice like that Oh my god, you went like I didn't know you could turn off your accent like that That's pretty
Oh, you know what I found out, Jen?
I found out that You know what Tempo told me?
When he asked you to join the custom You said no No, I never said that I'm going back in DMs And then I told Tempo Tell Jen Bird and he'll be on my team And then you instantly said yes After
Why is he exposing me like that?
Dude You gotta set things straight, first of all Yeah, set things straight Right at the beginning Are you with us or are you not?
Can't believe you said no at first Okay, listen, listen I have a reason why I don't Japanese tournaments, they usually take forever To start So I didn't want to play But with Doki, it's different, you know?
What do you mean?
We're taking forever still It feels like it didn't start instantly We're like 3 minutes late Because we're yapping all the time We're just talking I just passed by even faster That's right Also, is it the bug?
Is that why we're not starting?
Is it the stunny bug?
Why game No start Stunny dude Stunny no
Oh my god Stunny Oh no It's been stuck in starting servers Still Oh my god Is it the bug?
Wait, Jen, is this the bug that he was talking about?
Yeah, it's the bug, it takes forever It takes like 50 minutes Wait, what?
No I'm joking 5 minutes maybe So we blame, this is Stunny's fault I'm gonna say it Yeah, Stunny's lagging the server Maybe we should remove him and get him back in I don't know, maybe that'll fix it
Takes 5 minutes to load
Okay, that's fine It'll be fine, guys High priority server, by the way Because it's so high priority It takes a bit to load Yo, we need to do this customs real quick They're like, okay They're kicking everybody out Right now from the public servers So we get all the bandwidth Is that it?
What's the hertz of these servers?
Like 12?
Yeah, yeah, yeah So if you're playing rank right now You're gonna lose your RP Because we're kicking you out of your server That's right We're gonna prioritize The pro players Like always Oh, man It's gonna be fun though Wait, wait, wait Since we can use one gun,
you know What are you thinking?
Because I'm thinking Like we should be using the T-Take Because that's like a little shotgun up close And at long range, it can blast someone Okay, but like Are we gonna find enough energy ammo?
Yeah, we only need like 120 for the whole game 120, that's true Oh, that's true, that's true Yeah, we can just keep shooting it Okay, but like But like, what if I miss?
You won't miss, Doki No, you won't miss You won't miss We can't have that kind of attitude on our team, Doki But I haven't used it You will never miss You're a master spread player You've never ever missed a day in your life Oh yeah, you're not gonna miss today You're not gonna miss today's custom Yes,
today it's your customs You're gonna show up Wait, Jen's chat, count the amount of shots he missed And then report it back to me at the end It said okay They left him
They will report to you They're writing it down Now for real though, you can use whatever gun you want Alright, you're gonna use the triple take?
Alright, maybe I'll use the triple take too We'll try first match with triple take And see how it goes I don't know, Nemesis is good too, but like I don't know, in a bubble fight I mean, it's like a short shotgun, right?
Yeah, well, the Nemesis, no Oh wait, you're saying Nemesis Yeah, that's true Yeah, in a bubble fight will be a bit scary That's what we have Altair for Altair can do the bubble fight for us I'm a sword, just tell me what to do and I'll do it, okay?
I don't know too much about the game Alright, you're gonna have to You don't know this game, Regis?
I don't know a little bit of it, but I'm not the best He's like, he's diamond So like, I don't know what that is for you That's solid, that's solid That's like, what's that for pros?
Like, what do you see diamonds as?
Diamonds as Like, the best players in the world At least I see that Really?
Because when I run into them, diamond players in ranked, they're like the best They're the best players I swear to god They have aimbot, bro We're sticking to my chat like, hey, I'm reporting my friend Yuris for bringing in the three Red team Regis, I'm sorry They all have one gun,
though Regis, if they do too well Regis, we will nerf them, we promise you that Regis, I'm coming for your ass Like the good old times in Apex South, brother We're the three red team Okay, maybe we shouldn't have a target there We're the three bronze team We're the three,
yeah, we're just bronze players Please don't hurt us We're three diamond players, right?
We're the three diamond players So that means we can both have two guns We can all have two guns Yay Oh my god Five minutes have passed Five minutes have passed What happened?
Any second Maybe it's calculated, ten minutes Ten minutes?!
Tempo!
Why are you screaming at me?
I don't have information!
We should be screaming at Stunny, though The guy that subbed in last minute The guy that decided to join in at the last second
He's gonna leave again
Don't worry I fix it by Blaming another person
It's just that easy It's just that easy You're playing Newcastle I'm playing Gibby Okay, but where's Gibby Okay, there he is I didn't know where he was It's been a while The two big boys We're in Are we landing at SkyEast?
Yeah, SkyEast, it's auto So we auto land there Because we have the actual Scrim codes Would you like me to grab a sniper or no?
Or are we going short range?
Do whatever the fuck you want, Altair You get two guns!
As long as you run a shotgun Yeah, look at that Oh my gosh, I forgot to Blaster opponents, use it Yeah, yeah, you get the privilege You get literally the two gun privilege I'll land over here You wanna land bloody train station?
Alright, I get the I wanna be in the middle, yes Okay, I'll get the middle Alright, if I die, I die Because I think the Pred team is I think one of the three Pred team is on the other side Don't tell me that, please No, no, no, no Wait, I think it's Hakus' team Yeah,
Hakus' team is on the other side Oh, hell no Maybe we don't mess with that I'm pretty sure I'll cook him, Kaz, don't worry Yeah, because you're in Australia And he's in EU You have the better ping because we're on Oregon This is not Oregon, brother I'm on 280 ping I'm on 280 I should be on 180 Oh,
wait Wait a minute, why are we not on Oregon?
Wait, I'm on 100 I'm on 280 ping right now What the fuck?
This is like East Coast New York City, bro We're playing this sewage rat fucking server There's no way Would anybody like a peacekeeper?
Yeah, I would Wait This is not Oregon server Why are we at East Coast?
This is crazy, dude Wait, that's good There's Hakus' team Only Hakus They're gonna have lower ping No, but they're in JP So like They're also 280 with you They're slumming it up with you Yeah, let's go Epicenter I have a vault I got my T-Tech Ping another triple take for me,
I have a vault I don't have a sniper But I'll get one Okay, it's been a while But does tripper's take use a sniper stock?
I don't remember Jen, does the triple You're holding it right now Oh shit, nice Use a sniper stock, yeah I got you Somebody yell at Tempo that we are not in We are not in Oregon We are not in Oregon I am at an extreme disadvantage right now It's okay A lot of other players Are also extremely Disadvantaged,
like the good teams Because the JP teams are slumming it up With you, so you're fine The JP teams are the really good ones Get your fat asses over here Come on my way We're here Wait, there's a team right over here Yeah, just fly into monument Wait, how are you blue armor?
Don't worry Actually, I don't know He's cheating There's a team right there That would be funny I need like shield cells and loot I have 20 cells Yeah, I never found a cell I want to get this ring console Alright Is that a team here?
I don't know, I am like so fucking poor right now Someone's close to me I'm going high There's a team on the ring console, okay?
I'm going the height of this building Okay, we're coming over I saw a new castle over there If I die, I die I have zero shield cells by the way So you guys should...
I got that shield cell though We can play the bottom floor too You know what I mean?
If you want I've never been here Can you give me some shield cells?
I dropped you the level right there You can bubble him Calm down Calm down to me You're super safe on me Get over here, you're fine You're so healthy You are not healthy I totally am Sorry, I've never been here before
Guys, um Remember I said I haven't shot the triple take yet?
I haven't shot a triple take in a long time It definitely shows
I might have missed I might have missed On the ground right here There's a bubble in front of us Stabilize underneath Maybe I'll be better without a scope on It really shows I think you should take the scope It's a 1x Do you need a 2x?
Do you need a 2x?
I just picked the first scope What do you mean?
I blame Chen for giving me the triple take idea If I had the vault, I would have been beaming If I had the vault, it would have been okay I can't with you You like that?
I thought you zoomed into their souls Like an egg timer or something No, I had the 1x I picked the first scope I could find It's fine, we're so safe with our white armor I think we're in zone, on guard Many teams around us The zone predictor Are you the zone guy?
To be honest, I guessed, but thank you Wait, wait!
Akaz's team is down!
They're doing their shit!
We're gonna do it!
Akaz's team is out!
And that's the only obstacle in our way Well, no, we still have like two more pred team
I thought you managed this shit, man Two more!
Look, they all have one gun They all have one gun It's technically managed We have white armor We have one guy with two guns But we have Altair who has two guns That's practically a pred player Are they still above us?
Wait I can hear Jen has blue armor It'll be fine Can I have multiple castle walls up?
No, only one Only one It's okay, we're just chillin We're chillin We're chillin This is just the chatting time Before the great collide Before all the teams just start fighting Yeah, exactly What?
See, it's manageable Look, we're not last Look how manageable it's been Has there been other loot at all?
There's a spitfire I could use a spitfire You're right A spitfire could pop off a flatline I could just run I'll give you my energy Honestly, for you probably don't care Probably the spitfire or the flatline Really?
Do we have enough ammo though?
That's the thing There's a bunch in this I don't think there's enough ammo There's more here, 50 right there Oh, okay, yeah, maybe I'll do the flatline There's all three There's not enough attachments for it though I'll try the light mag here I'll do the carbine then I'll do the light mag Oh,
this is fun There's a light mag I have no heavy That's fine, I'll run carbine See, look at that We're chilling now We're so chilling I want to get this juicer but it's so on them Do it, we'll res you Yeah, we'll res you Are we letting him free?
Off his leash
I have to stop and stare at him I'm like, wait, are you the whole team?
What do you want us to do?
You didn't tell us what to do I was waiting for orders Look where the juicer is It's on the building Oh, I'm looking Oh, you're looking?
I trust you I'm looking for you too I don't hear anyone I can probably get it I heard a sniper above us Are you sure that's a good idea?
Somewhere northeast We have wide armor Yeah, yeah Are you sure that's a good idea?
I believe in you I believe What's the worst that could happen?
Just hang around here The worst thing is princess goes down Yeah, yeah Don't worry, he'll be fine Long live the princess He'll be so healthy He'll be so healthy Wouldn't it be funny if a team just drops on us right here?
Look at that!
We're still wide armor Wait What?
You have to do like 100 damage Yeah, I did like 99 You did 99 already?
Yeah, I did 99 damage
It's a visual bug It's a visual bug though Yeah, yeah, yeah Yeah, Altair, you did 99 damage too, right?
Yeah, I hit him in the head Yeah He like wore a helmet so it did 99 There's a purple light mag Oh shit, I need that Wait, is that team above us still?
I don't hear them We can probably hit the console in a second I mean, yeah, I can bubble you I'll watch behind Oh, they're still there Oh, they're ratting Wait, we can kill them If they're ratting, we kill them No, actually don't, I don't think we should Jen,
no, I don't think Hold on, I'm just gonna make them move They're definitely up there What the fuck did they have in there?
They have a Newcastle shield and shit They're just ratting, ratting, dude That's disgusting Wait, I have so many nades Maybe I'll hit somebody No, I didn't I wanna hit this console, Loki Oh, look at this ring prediction I don't think we're actually in the zone No,
we're not It's gonna pull like out here We can move to the new location if you want Oh wait, they reset Wait, the bin's all reset, nice Come, come Alright, sorry, I got a little greedy Yeah, I opened the package Cause I didn't listen to you Yeah, and it paid off,
I got blue army Alright, come, come Get ready to bubble just in case we get shot Okay, set up a wall like in here Set up a wall here Towards the east There's a blue helmet here Yeah, we're good, we're good Here, here I dropped some sails for you Thank you Wait,
what do I put?
Do I put fast shot?
Oh, we move faster Okay, I'll do increase Yeah, I don't have a shotgun On me is good Wait a minute, wait, there's a team Right, the wall's not the best On me is like the safest, Loki Oh, good, good Do you have ultic sail?
You should pop it I don't think we had time to fucking loot an ultic sail Where the fuck did they shot us from?
Yeah, from the car, careful This angle and left The left's gonna be out soon, all good It'll be fine, we'll be so healthy Exactly I can watch south Yeah, what's the worst that could happen to us?
Oh Hit one for 60 Good shot there, okay One more of that, one more 60 And you get that blowout, my boy Get that blowout, my boy Yeah, yeah, because you hit You just need to hit one more shot because you were at 99 damage earlier And you get to do more damage than Doki And she's a master Whoa,
actually stop shooting now It's safest on me as well There's a team crossing from the zone We can shoot them when they cross Like on me Oh, they're right here, right here, right here From the bridge, it's a Newcastle Shoot these fuckers I got one, go ahead Nice shot there,
Doki First lady?
Newcastle, Newcastle on the left side Newcastle down, Newcastle down They're all down No, I didn't get the kill I think they res'd him That's fine, kills don't matter, remember Kills don't matter They don't?
It's placements Just winning the game Still team on the south We're still in on this Triple T Okay, that is true I shouldn't have listened We have to play underneath them, okay?
You have wall again, Altair?
Yes Okay, you put your wall Towards the left, okay?
Like on this Ready?
Yeah, you can just put it there now There's like a team right there to my left Whoa, okay Okay There's shots You can play behind this I'll put this Nice, nice, nice Oh I'm looking at this team behind, I don't know what they're doing There's a team literally in front of us Okay Oh I'm good,
I'm good Oh, I'm not good Oh, I'm not good Can you rez her?
Oh Oh Oh Wait, they are running Triple T They have your strat You're good, you're good I'm not good, I don't feel good Altair, I'm right behind you Oh You're fine, what do you mean?
I'm so fine You're so good We're fine, we're fine as fuck We've never been more fine in our life You're so fine, Jen Jen, Jen, Jen, you're so fine, they're running at you I'm so good, oh my god Who was it?
Nice try, nice try Oh my god Wait, whose team is this?
Oh my god I got crossed by so many people It's the other Pred team That is insane It's okay, we can, if they do too well We could, wait, we were their only kills No, we weren't, thank god We were?
I think we were their only kills, no?
No, we weren't, thank god That's five kills It's okay, you died to Taffy Oh my god, yeah, yeah, yeah See, you died to Taffy Like, that's a good death Taffy's a good player Wait, this is a pro team, no?
It's a full pro team?
No, it's not, it's two Preds Okay, okay, I was gonna say Yeah That's fine, if they do too well We can, we can Wait, Taffy's What, what about Taffy?
I saw a little mask of Afri on him, I thought Nevermind No, he has like one gun on him Yeah, yeah, it's okay What's it called, uh, for next time, Mr. Alton?
Just put it like towards, like hug it towards the wall I don't think there's gonna be a next time Because that was our one match That was one last time?
Now we're just gonna punch only or what?
I think next match is melee only Yeah What's the strat for that?
Yeah, we just punch people No, no, no, we're playing Lifeline for sure And we need to have Newcastle so we can, like They can't punch the thing when you're rezzing Yeah, yeah, we're playing Newcastle again Should I have a go on Newcastle?
Low key And what's the third character though?
What should our third character be?
Can we hook people or no?
We could!
We could get Pathfinder and then No, it doesn't We can grapple them into us Wait, let me see, hold up Russo No grenades allowed, right?
No grenades, no Pathfinder can cook Yeah, we can grapple people into us Wait, Wattson, you can't use Wattson either Yeah, yeah, cause, uh No, Wattson does do damage, but there's no point in I mean, we just don't use fences Yeah, we just can't use fences Oh,
they're in a rough position Oh, oh, oh, wait, wait Tappi's team might die Holy
Wait, actually No, they lost the team Okay, so, so what's our third then?
Do we do Newcastle, Lifeline, and Uh And Pathfinder Holy shit, what the fuck is this end zone?
What?
Tappi Wait, Tappi ditched his team Wait, they're in a good spot, low key Wait, they are though, yeah Wait, they just, they just grappled What is a random grenade though?
They just let them do that?
They just let them just grapple?
I swear to god, they zipped across the zone Not even one bullet fired at them, dude Yeah, that's what I'm saying It was in the middle of the fucking area They just let them do that?
Streamer luck What was our streamer luck?
We got shot by three different teams I don't even know what can cook Next game Newcastle 100% Lifeline?
I don't know I think Lifeline would be good for the rez and the Q The Q for it, and the ult too Oh my god, there's gonna be like 200 Fucking Lifeline ults If you think about it Yeah Oh You can just keep healing it You can just outheal the punches
Oh my god, the rat strat Wait There's just one left Just one man left
Oh my god Oh my god, he's crazy What is he gonna do?
Is he gonna rez?
You should Oh my god, he's fucking crazy Oh, he doesn't I guess he went in the shield Yeah, but he has to 1v3 I guess he could get second or third, yeah?
Oh my god There's a fucking giant fight below him And he's not even looking at it Jen, what's their third player?
What's their third character?
People are saying Octane or Mirage Octane and And Mirage?
But with the Why Octane?
Oh, I guess you can put jump pads You put jump pads at people And um You like jump pad at people and also just put it in the endzone Everyone just jumps in together Yeah, yeah, yeah, you throw the jump pad at the endzone And then send everybody flying out Does it actually work?
Yeah, we can Oh my god, this fuck is crazy This guy This guy fucking is crazy He wanted that red so bad Oh my god Wait, they got third though Wait, which team is this?
What is this team?
Oh, this is Ditto's team Okay, Ditto's team is getting hard nerfed Wait, who's team is this?
Yeah, Yuris, Ditto, and Amatsuki That's crazy They're gonna get They're gonna get their Their legs chopped off now The lobby shall decide What to do with them
We got second We did Oh yeah, totally us We got both We're about to win that, that was us right there Yeah, that was us Alright Oh my god, Sekuro's team got second
Ditto's Wait, let's see, who was Oh yeah, Ditto's team getting Ditto's Alright, which team shall get nerfed?
Which team shall get Definitely Banzai's team, right?
Yuris' team Shall we nerf Ditto's team?
The lobby decides Alright, it's interview time Wait, where is Wig?
Where the fuck did Wig go?
Wig just disappeared Wig disappeared in the PC Alright, I'm gonna go to the caster interview, I'll be right back guys Alrighty Alright, you guys ready for an interview?
Are we chopping?
Are we nerfing Ditto's team?
I mean, that's up to you, right?
I mean, what the lobby decides The lobby decides if they come to I mean, they have nine kills Oh, that's true, that's way too many kills That's Our team got ten, ten kills It was ninth place though Yeah, but then they got greedy You wanna nerf them?
You wanna nerf them too?
Come to the casters for interview We don't have to nerf RPR's team But do you want to?
I want to Yeah, of course you want to RPR's already mad at me, he said that I was talking very mean about him before the game started, so He still had to be nice to him So I'm voting no nerf on RPR For like nerf Ditto Ditto's so good Yeah, yeah, I know She got prayed.
Oh shit, we're fucking starting?
We're not even going into the interview?
Wait No interview, gg's Tell them I said gg's I guess no interview We'll never buy the interview after After this game Deal, deal, deal, we'll do interviews maybe every two games After this game, yeah, yeah My tempo runs a tight show My god Such a fucking...
What happened?
We're in already?
It's crazy Zain is still asleep He's still asleep?
Alright, I'll see you guys later Alright, love you, love you, bye, bye, bye Okay Tempo fucking was just like Just instant starts The next game I know, you didn't even get to Did you even get to interview?
No, we just got That's a tempo, welcome to Tempo's life Bro, I swear to god Yeah, yeah I was just like What the fuck, Tempo Be like, at Tempo We're gonna do two interviews After this game Oh my god It's like no It's no yapping time, we go straight in So just grab heals,
yeah?
Yeah, heals, yeah, yeah Wait, what are you gonna do with the I guess like heal shields Can we just keep punching people?
And then they're gonna run out of heals What if What if they also play Oh wait, no nades, what if they also play No Watson It's just gonna be an infinite shield heal Infinite shield heal, yeah And you're lifeline so you can heal So it's actually not bad Oh and I have mobile res beacon Oh my god,
I keep picking up nades And stuff Yeah, yeah, yeah, just in case Alright Alright This is anybody Wait, are cars back?
Yes sir We gotta get a car Are we running it back?
Yeah, we got the worst PR I'm fucking running it Guys, I'm gonna run to get this one car We got the worst PR Wait, the car's not clean The car's not clean Should I just fly to it, bro?
Yeah, yeah, do it, do it You can res me Yeah, yeah, yeah Don't use your craft though Just go, just go, book it We must get that car before they figure it out We believe in you I'm going for a darn Yeah, there's no way There's no way they're smart enough about the car Just keep looking for me,
keep looking We're not looking Wait, is it claimed?
No, it's not, it's not, it's still there It's not, it's not It's not, it's not, it's still there, just keep grabbing it They don't know They don't know the car's track Go, go, go, go Go, go, go, go King Princess We did it, our passenger princess Oh my god,
guys, I got it
I'm getting this Evo too Yeah, there's a mobile here I'm just gonna make sure if there's any more heals around us Alright, I have a lot of shield cells Alright, we're fine Teammates revive faster Increase time before Okay, increase the time before it runs out of fuel Yeah,
we should get that Alright, we're coming over Alright,
now we can chill We should try and get a second car, is there another car that's unclaimed?
Oh, no You're crazy for that, for real We'll just stay in the car, I'll punch you out of the car But we can all have a car We can push people out of the zone of the car Oh, no, there's only two left here Where do we play?
I feel like at the back, somewhere here I'm down for this little house We should just explore, does it really matter?
It doesn't really matter to be honest We have a car, we can literally drive by Hello, anyone here?
Is anyone?
Nope Wait, somebody already knocked How did that noose castle kill an octane?
Wait, get this juicer We'll just get purple I'm just gonna drive around and get purple How is this?
Newcastle killed the rev too We probably should get red armor That's what I mean, we should just get red armor Yeah, we should actually, that's actually a good plan We just drive by Yeah, yeah, yeah, just get red armor And we're good Poor armors Where did the care package go?
It could be a juicer
Got it?
They should give you a brick You're gonna be hella brick Oh my god, where is it?
Oh, it's the hemlock There we go, let's go We're eating good tonight There's one at the back here We're eating good Do we all have enough heals?
I think I have like one medkit though, that's the worst part What's my heal?
There's six cells, I'm looking good What about you Altair, are you good on heals?
I have three meds, six cells, four cells I think the car is way worth it Yeah, no, the car is so good I'm Watson anyway, I can just gen Oh true, you can gen on the car, right?
Reduce tactical cooldown, increase distance I'm gonna reduce tactical cooldown Where are they?
Where are all these other players?
Where are the humans at?
Wait, it sounds like bloodhound They're gonna scan people Bro, that Newcastle team is like Whoever they are They're so aggressive Look at them Oh my god, this Newcastle Three kills They're just meleeing Oh, purple, thank you Yeah, we got purple I'm gonna get unlimited ult Alright,
we gotta go over here Wait They want blood Gen, can you honk a little bit?
I'm bored Thank you Yeah, tell everybody we're here Beep beep Beep beep I like how I'm opening the doors, guys Beep beep, Altair is letting you do that That's crazy Altair is the passenger princess He's definitely the princess here All he does is just sit in the backseat and let us Oh wait,
there's a team here Oh yeah, give me a goat sound Can you guys punch them in the car?
Yeah, we can Wait, they're punching us They did like two damage We do more Yeah, yeah, yeah They're gonna come Get them Wait, get them Get them, Altair Get him, get him They're running, they know Get him, get him I'm punching Get the fuck out
I'm getting him Oh my god Oh my god I'm doing more damage Get his ass
Keep going for it Just keep
Altair, just keep punching There's no punching Just keep punching One sec, one sec I'm putting a generator You're gonna glitch What if they steal our car?
I'm in, I'm in Get back in, get back in Just keep punching Drive through the wall Where are they?
Get this fucking guy Punch him, punch him Get away Fly, Jen, fly Fuck this guy, I hate him He's so annoying Where's his team?
They left the guy, bro That's crazy The cavalry is here That's what I'm saying Let's go, baby There's two cars Yo, what's up, cuz?
We'll just do two damage to each other In the car Guys, you guys need red armor though, too Yeah, I'm gonna try to get it now Okay There's a juicer here Wait, how much more do you guys need for red?
It's gonna be 1100 I don't think we can get it This is like jousting, yeah We're medieval I'm gonna go get this one Alright We got a little distracted in our mission to get armor That was too fun We got a little distracted No, he's greasing us Whoa, whoa,
whoa It's not bumper cars, bro Don't get in your plane The IRS is here, you gotta pay your taxes Time to pay your taxes Somebody didn't pay their taxes I'm 674 to Evo Fuck, did Artemis die so much?
Sorry What's your guys' heals, by the way?
I'm like poor I have a lot
Come, come It's fine, it's fine We still have our drivers, so they can't steal the car Three bats, six cells, four syringes We can grab some heals here In those bins In the bins?
It's time to raid the bins I'll grab this I'll be close Is there another one close to us?
There's not We gotta melee somebody Someone's gonna grab these heals Quick, quick, quick There's someone close to us Look over here Oh, helmet though No heals, no heals We're punching, we're not shooting bullets What do you mean helmet?
There's only ammo
I'll protect my head If they punch my head, it'll be fine Doki, go to this right building Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay Oh my god, we're on a mission right now There it is Oh, I got shield cells Is there anything else?
You have six cells and one phoenix I have four, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, fifteen cells We can craft bats I guess Yeah, we could, yeah We might as well all three of us just keep crafting bats Everybody is like...
Ever since that one team started brawling they stopped, they got scared Whoa Where'd you learn that?
What a trick, yeah, how did you do that?
I have a lot of tricks up my sleeve Yeah, like what?
You'll see, this game Wouldn't it be funny if someone just drove by and took our car?
Just ran
I died for this car basically Can I get over this man, come on Come on, show us some of your tricks, Jen Okay Look at this maneuvering Alright, I'll stay in the car just in case I'm like paranoid somebody is actually going to run over and take her Okay,
got a bat too I'm good I think we're good Yeah, I think we're good in the heal department The zone is closing Okay, this is controller driving, sorry guys Where's my other crafter?
Crafts?
I think we have enough, there's no way I'm going to craft another one, you stay Yeah, yeah, I'm staying My car is drifting slowly back
It's an incline Is that another crafter?
It's lining up for us right now It's another crafter, yeah, people are Someone died here, wait, rest in peace brother Oh, that poor guy, I think that was Armus Oh my god, where are the individuals?
They're all hiding!
The no car people are all hiding Yeah
Bro, this is great We all have our little little jump pad Oh
Wait, wait, do it again We might be able to hit them Wait, I'm trying to boop them off so I can take the spot Big brain, you know?
Yeah, big brain, that's big brain Boost in 5 seconds, hold up Look at him, look at me I'm punching, I'm punching I'm punching, I'm punching too He's punching us, yo, chill bro What's your problem G?
What's your problem G?
He wanted his jump pad back That was his Bro, what's going on?
Ow, ow, ow You're fine, we have the Watson Okay, hold up, wait bro Please move, beep, beep, beep Motherfucker, move Get out of here please, move, move Move your ass, get out I'm punching, I'm punching We're punching Oh guys, I don't know They're going crazy They're wild I don't think they want us to have their spot I like how all the non-car people are like just chilling in the buildings away from the cars
Every car has been taken Holy fuck You know what, can someone else drive?
Yeah, yeah, yeah I'm gonna get red armor Okay, okay, I'll get armor Okay, it's fine I'm on M and K I'll just keep punching Wait, where did he go?
Okay, you gotta punch a solo, you gotta punch like a team that's not in the car I'll do a drive-by to pick you up if you need it What the fuck?
Oh, he punched Yeah, by the car behind us Honk at them How do I honk?
Stay near me, stay near me That team, that team over there I challenged them You challenged them?
Yeah, yeah, I believe in you, Jen Challenge that mountain, king of the hill Oh, he's gonna grapple me with the frog No, wait, wait This guy's crazy You're scared, Jen?
Jen, you're scared?
Go, go Don't be scared Don't be a pussy
Just one hit Come on, Jen That's another one Hold up, hold up, I'm popping off Bro, he's in mountain He's coming, he's coming Jen, did you have fun?
What the fuck, man?
They all dropped down for your ass They all dropped down for your ass, bro Another person from different angles He's gonna grapple me Bro, you'll be fine, we're literally right behind you Come on, Jen Come on, Jen, you got this We're up to land champion Get him,
get him, get him Get the fuck out, get the fuck out Get the fuck out, get the fuck out I think we might need another shield Yeah, we need to put another alternate That is crazy activity, I can't lie Holy fuck, bro I don't think they like you They really hate me,
bro What the fuck?
I'll never replace the Jen Alright, alright, alright, I'll find us a safe spot Fly, Doki, fly I'll find it here, here, this is safe Nobody's down here Okay, I'm jumping out, just stay in the car Over here, over here What the fuck?
Okay, they did not want us to have it Get back in, get back in Jen, Jen I can't I'm so laggy, so laggy Oh my god, playing from the moon We all died because of you Okay, alright, that's fine, that's fine We'll find another safe spot Oh my god, all these cars Bro,
this car won't fuck up We gotta go, we gotta go on this side Go on this side, Doki Okay, this is safe Put your shield They don't know, they don't know What?
That makes no sense, I can't make it I need to get a gun That's against the rules No, I'm just gonna shoot I'm gonna shoot I'm dropping the gun, Doki They don't know They don't know, they don't know Wait, what's back there?
What happened to us?
Play this side, play this corner What if they resolve this shit?
You can put nukes What is this ramming shit?
Oh my god, this is Wait, I wanna put a shield on Yeah, yeah, put a shield on We can have a little ramming Wait, this guy is like Go, go, go, go No, they are Jen, Jen, where are you?
Okay Play this corner, Doki Okay, why the fuck is he Maybe this, maybe this Go there, go there I'm upping, I'm upping See right underneath them Oh my god, look Oh wait, there's this one guy Look at these guys up there Look at these guys up there We have high ground We're not in zone though We gotta go to the left We're in now,
right?
Here?
Yeah, yeah, here Dude, just up in the hill I'm gonna put a shield up, okay?
Jen, fight them Jen, it'll be so fun if you climb this Behind us, behind us Oh my god, there's a guy literally behind us That's fine, we're fine I'll start punching, I swear to god I'll start throwing hands like Mike Tyson, bro Chill out Do you want to fight,
bro?
You wanna go?
Yeah, come on, Jen, do it Oh, he flew away like a pussy He saw your aura He did Wait, he's coming to punch me This thing is crazy You can get him Wait, did he fly away?
That little bitch Okay, somebody else has to drive because I need to heal real quick Okay Wait, somebody What the fuck is going on to our right?
What the fuck?
Oh shit, they're pushing me They're pushing me out Jen Wait, I think we should swap seats Okay, okay I'm swapping I'll drive Give me the sock I'm giving you the sock Can you suck me?
I don't think you can Okay, here you go It's fine, it's me It's fine, we're okay Everything is okay Wait, we can drive back to that team There's one team Push those guys into zone I'm so dizzy I'm gonna go into zone Wait, what?
Why?
Ramming speed I can do it now Oh no We took damage They're putting the pads out They're putting the pads out This is fine We're so safe I don't think I can Yeah I'm punching Oh wait, I can't Okay, we did it We're fine This end zone is gonna be fucking crazy Oh my god,
they have the rocks Who the fuck played Loba in here?
Bro, they have red armor?
Bro, they were traveling I'm fucking meleeing Is this so many cars?
Nobody wants to fight Everyone is so scared There's a jump pad We're fine I have Q I have Q I got you guys Oh my god Oh my god We're getting bullied It's fine I don't know what's going on But we're alive Wait, somebody died to ring This is crazy Get to that jump pad to win No Oh my god,
are we fine?
I don't feel okay How do we get pushed into the ring?
How do we get pushed into the ring?
We can live Are we sure?
Everything is teleporting on my screen It's okay As long as we don't get pushed out It's lagging all over the place What's going on?
I don't know, I'm scared
I'm getting the fuck out Get out No, I'm just fine I don't know I'm dying Oh my god Oh my god It's not fine It's not fine Someone put a jump pad below us But we have 9 kills
I just kept swinging I got 9 kills The screen was just doki Oh my god What?
We got 6 but who won?
Who won then?
Oh my god Holy
Neko Punch Who's that?
Neko Punch Jackie Chan won What?
Jackie Chan?
Jackie Chan Oh my god That shit was crazy Everybody just died All at once That's insane Oh my god Okay, now we're definitely doing An interview Okay, I'll be right back guys Alright, are you guys ready for the real interview?
We do, yeah, yeah Ditto's team and then Neko Punch Did you guys enjoy watching?
That was crazy I can't believe what I just watched The cars?
The car is illegal No, that's the most fun part That was absolutely ridiculous Was that Restio's team that won?
No, Restio's team was in 18th place No, 19th place No, it was Neko Punch Alright, so we're gonna get Ditto in here Girard's team had to watch that whole game Just go down They died so early at 20th So early What happened to them?
I don't even know They got chased down And immediately were just about that action They just fought immediately They just fucking fought Alright, let's get Okay, now come in for an interview Alright, what's that?
What's match three?
Match three we got Charged sent a Lombo Oh, it's Sniper only time Did you see the Restio POV?
What did I just watch?
What did you watch?
What happened?
Wait, he just got absolutely clobbered, bro Are you kidding me?
Wait, I gotta watch that again That was insane How so?
Hey guys I just watched that Restio POV Dude, that is insane That was crazy, bro Wait, what happened to Restio?
He just flew I'll translate for Amatsuki-san Congratulations on first place in the first game Congratulations Thank you Arigato gozaimasu Wait, what do you want to ask them?
You're the interviewer Wait, what?
You're lucky I'm a professional You're the caster Oh, okay What was the mindset going in game 1?
You got a teammate like Ditto who obviously can perform at a high level What was your thought process there?
Just take it as a normal game You got better players on your team Not having to deal with RPR, making bad calls What was the thought process?
I like those I like that I was thinking the landmark we got was landslide And since The tournament is more so based on placement When you get first Not more so the kills So we're thinking If we play Rampart, Loba, Newcastle We can easily find a spot And then Do something with it And then we just got lucky with the zone The zone was literally right beside our POI So I'm like Okay,
we have Rampart and we have Newcastle We can easily protect that hill And yeah, we just got lucky We just protected the hill And we got the win pretty much Are you guys excited for your nerf?
Yeah We're all aware you're getting nerfed Okay Yeah, I mean What's the nerf?
How are you guys gonna nerf them?
Oh man I mean, what could we do?
That's like the actual question Is there limits to this?
It's up to you guys You're the casters The lobby decided on a nerf for them They want them to be nerfed Oh no, should we leave it a chat?
Can you do a vote in your chat?
Are polls existing on YouTube?
Let me tell Amatsuki-san That they're gonna get nerfed Go for it Amatsuki-san You won your first game And you got 9 kills So You're gonna get nerfed No way!
What?
Oh my god What?
So You're gonna get nerfed
You're gonna decide on a nerf Oh my god, we should put one of them on controller Oh god What about no comps for one game?
No comps?
Match 6 though, they only have one nerf And it's gonna be on match 6 You didn't read the rules!
I did, I did, I did Sorry, I forgot No comps?
They have to be triple deafened for it?
Triple deafened I feel bad It's fair They're good at the lobby These guys are so good Yeah, but we should add one more just in case We should handicap them one more time Wait, let's let Greek decide Greek, you're the other caster, what kind of nerf would you like to see?
Uh, how about They have to play on 70 FOV
I like that one better than no audio That's good That's good, actually We should translate that Yeah, let me know what they think Yeah, game 6
Did it?
What was the nerf?
70 FOV
Is this selective or are you going to choose it?
For what?
Wait, no, it's Greek's choice He was the one that suggested it Oh, okay, then it's going to be 70 FOV only The whole team is a 70 FOV We can talk Yeah, we can talk, right?
Yeah, let them talk to 70 FOV He got to talk to 70 FOV
He got to put in
That's fair enough Yeah, see, isn't that fun?
Have a good time, guys Remember, it was Greek's idea I see, I see But you guys won, though!
Congratulations
Congratulations Alright, congratulations Go back to your channel, we're going to talk to the other team Bye, love you guys Bye, thank you One more interview Does every winner get nerfed?
No, no, it was just the first match They had like 9 kills Yeah, they had 9 kills and it was like a normal match True Yeah, yeah, yeah 70 FOV gives you motion sickness a little bit If you play 70 FOV to see how big your monitor is You'll actually get a little sick You'll get a little sick after like 10 minutes I feel like you're playing virtually You're so close to the screen to see 100%,
you get a little dizzy and everything, brother Hey, congratulations on winning!
Arigatou gozaimasu Arigatou gozaimasu Arigatou gozaimasu How did you do it?
I actually don't know because we were all like 250 ping and teleporting So what happened was like Everybody had cars, right?
But you weren't a car person?
We didn't have a car No, we didn't have a car We were like watching everyone like Using their car and actually we were getting hit a lot So we were like How are we going to do this?
Actually Because I was hit by a car And I got hit out of the ring So I started using the medkit early And I think that's why I survived until the end That's the only thing It's like luck, I guess Oh my god, a non-car person won That's crazy We didn't have a car Actually we were super jealous because everybody was like driving around And we really wanted one as well So we kept standing around getting hit by the car That shit looked fun It didn't feel like a melee only mode It was like Mario Kart Bumper cars Yeah,
bumper cars That's true Alright well For game 3 You guys are going to use charge rifle, sendo, longbow And kraber only on e-district What's the game plan here?
What gun are you guys going to be running mainly?
Out of those options Okay Let me translate for them So our team I speak English but Nachan here, she speaks Japanese And the other person speaks Chinese So we're We're bilingual Yeah we're a bilingual team here So I need to translate a little bit So they're asking Which sniper rifle are we going to play?
Shaobing Sentinel Jack said sentinel He's going to play sentinel Nachan All of us are playing sentinel That's a good choice We don't like the longbow?
And we're going to miss everything No, we're going to hit every shot But if you guys are going to longbow, then you might win The longbow get buffed That's what I'm saying, longbow guys Yeah, longbow got buffed too Yeah I heard charge rifle Charge rifle can break doors now too No don't run charge rifle Why?
Are you scared?
No, no, no No, no, no I'm not scared It's just not a great gun It's just not a great gun That's all I'm saying No, of course not I'm not nervous at all That's why you need to have tempo on your team I'll look for you specifically Doki, don't worry I love it dude Thank you guys so much for coming in Congratulations again for the win Congratulations Thank you Okay,
bye bye Bye Well, I'll see you guys In sniper only Doki, question for you Yeah?
Are you running a charge rifle in honor of tempo?
No, of course not We are not here to encourage him So only that squad is getting nerfed Yeah, only that squad is getting nerfed Because that's a normal match And the other matches are not Doesn't really matter There's no skill involved Well, sniper is skilled But you know The whole tournament nerfed They're the only team for the rest of the tournament Only match 6 Only match 6 Because the other games are more luck based So it's like They don't really have a chance to actually win I mean they do But everybody has a chance to win Alright I'll see you guys in match 3 then Good luck dude Bye Make sure to play along,
bro.
Alright, what's...
In punching...
In punching in walls...
Calm down, calm down.
Punching... nah, not really that.
Guys, I found out the team that won the melee did not even have a car.
Our car was... you know, Doki, you know our car was the only car in that zone?
Wait, really?
Yes, our car was the one in the end zone.
Like, we were chilling.
You were the only car that made it through?
I had to get up because I was 1 HP, but you guys stayed in the car, right?
Yeah, I stayed... no, I stayed alive until somebody put a jump pad underneath the car.
Yeah, the jump pad ruined me.
Yeah, they put a jump pad underneath the car and then I got fucked.
I was underneath the car.
I was underneath the car and then it, like, booped me, dude.
Cause I could have lived.
I could have lived if I didn't have the car, the jump pad.
What's the comp?
What's the comp we're playing?
No Ramparts.
We cannot play Ramparts.
He's playing Newcastle and you wanna play Lifeline?
Yeah, I can do Lifeline.
Yeah, do Lifeline.
Let's go.
Wait, Fun put the jump pad and killed me?
Oh, God.
Dude, I knew someone was gonna play Octane.
It's actually smart.
I can't believe it.
He fucking used the one that put the jump pad.
That fucker.
I'm gonna get a cough drop real quick.
I'll be right back, guys.
Vantage is not allowed, chat.
And Rampart is not.
Oops.
I'm back.
Why are we landing?
What is this POI?
What are these POIs we're getting?
What do you mean?
It's so shit.
It's randomised.
I hate this.
He's griefing our team.
Our POIs are so bad.
Except for Zeus.
Zeus was actually good.
Oh, my God.
You cannot blame me.
It was decided by AI.
Fuck the AI.
For real.
Okay.
I just want a sniper.
I don't even care what sniper we get.
Oh, yeah.
Tempo's gotta remind people not to shoot until first ring closes.
Yeah, I'm gonna get the console and shit.
Yeah, we can't shoot because we all have to find a sniper.
He wrote it.
I'm gonna write it for him.
Where is the sniper?
I found a sniper.
Oh, my God.
You can have two snipers.
Repeater counts as a sniper, no?
No.
It has to use sniper ammo.
I got sniper.
And then it can't be a wingman, too.
It's all snipers except for wingman and then Kraber.
Maybe you can get a Kraber.
We should get a Kraber.
I found a sniper.
We should be fine.
Can you get this juicer next to us?
Yep, I got it.
I haven't found a sniper yet.
I'm running around naked.
Oh, that's fine.
We still have one ring.
We still have a ring.
I'm gonna go for this juicer.
You guys can get this one over here.
Okay, yeah.
Altair and I are heading over now.
Maybe we'll find a sniper.
Yeah, maybe we'll find another sniper for you.
I haven't found one yet.
I'm not shooting.
I prefer longbow, though.
It's raining here.
Uh-oh, you know what that means?
Internet's going to shit.
Oh, no.
It's okay.
It can't be that bad.
I'm gonna be going...
Wait, if you're teleporting, then they'll teleport, too.
Then they'll see you teleporting.
It's okay.
They can't do anything to us.
Because the ring hasn't been closed yet.
True.
We can literally do a drive-by.
I'm gonna walk over because they can't do anything to me.
I'm coming over to you.
Yeah, what are you gonna do?
Shoot me?
I can tell Tambo to kick them out if they shoot me.
Okay.
I'm grabbing the harvester.
Oh, another wingman.
Oh, shit.
No, they can't punch.
They can't punch until the ring 1 closes, guys.
It's fine.
They killed one.
They killed someone.
What?
Wait, what?
Get him out.
Ban him.
Nice wig.
Who was it?
Tell them to stop.
How could you do this to us?
We trusted you.
What do you mean?
I had everything.
They didn't read the rules.
Or the NA.
Get them out.
The NA.
They gotta be fucking fish spine.
We got a rule breaker.
A rule breaker.
No, wig knows.
Do not fight until ring 1.
Wait, let them res.
We got a rule breaker.
They should let them res.
I don't have a sniper.
I'm running around.
Wait, you still don't have a sniper?
I don't have a sniper.
What?
I'm actually cursed.
Oh, this is bad.
I found three wingmen.
I have 50 bullets here.
Wait, wingmen count.
No, it doesn't.
It's sniper.
It doesn't read the rules.
Give me the wingmen.
No, we are not getting banned from my own custom.
I did not take it out of my integrity.
Don't want to ban you because you're the host.
I'm the host.
Tempo's the host.
Do you think Tempo's gonna let me get away with it?
You know he doesn't let you guys get away with anything.
He has a fucking blacklist, Jen.
He'll let you on the list.
I'm gonna get on his list, Jen.
You'll get on his blacklist?
And you'll get on the blacklist too.
A hundred thieves will be screaming for like a whole year.
Oh, here you go.
There's a charge rifle.
The worst sniper.
Another wingman.
At least I can fight them off now.
Give me that ammo.
That's four wingmen.
Come out, I'll tell ya.
Where do we go?
We're gonna go into zone... I think it's ending...
I think we should get this building.
If we can't, then maybe like this one of these...
We still don't have a sniper.
Rule breakers should get an extra nerf.
If you break the rules, you get an extra nerf.
I'm down to cook something up for that if you're being serious.
Wait, really?
Who was it?
Who broke the rules?
Apparently it was Mel's team.
They said in the chat...
Who shot him?
I don't know who on Mel's team, but it was one tappy who got killed.
But they res'd him though, right?
Yeah, I think they're good now.
Mel said in the chat, we goofed.
I'm so sorry.
Voice actor bloodlust.
If you know who exactly shot him, the one that killed Tappy...
The one that killed Tappy should get the nerf.
You can bring him in for an interview after and assess them a punishment.
That's true!
We can do that!
That's cool.
That's execution style.
Give him a one game punishment for shooting.
Just only the person who shot.
We should do it and protect the princess.
Yeah, bring him in and literally interrogate him.
Be like, alright, so who was it?
Who fired the shot?
Who took the shot?
We told you to take that shot.
Madness just took responsibility for it.
He said he was sorry and he did it.
But we're still gonna nerf him.
Oh yeah, perfect.
We're still gonna bring him down.
It's fine.
I'll set up your wall.
Yeah, you and Wink decide to cook something.
Towards this way.
This one works for sure.
I still have a sniper.
I have a longbow with no scope.
I have no sniper.
We have no sniper out there?
I've been saying it like 4 times already.
Oh my god, we gotta loot.
I literally told you guys 3 times.
4 times.
Go into that building and loot.
I'm holding the line.
Oh no, the zone closed.
The zone's closed.
Be careful.
Where are you gonna shoot us?
There's no way.
Fight on.
That is crazy.
You're like the guy that can carry 2 snipers.
This is bad.
I'm getting shot at.
Wait, where?
West.
Can you guys get up?
I'm gonna heal first.
I can get up.
They're flying on me, I think.
They are?
Oh my god, they fucking beat the shit out of one of them.
I'm going up.
Jump off.
Come to me, puppy.
I got you, don't worry.
We got you.
Run at us, there's snipers.
I'm blocking.
I got you.
Come to us.
I'm ulting.
Nice, good ult.
Thank you.
We're so good.
Stay in here.
Stay here.
They changed their ult.
Yeah, they do.
I lowkey wanna swap with you.
You want the charge?
No, that's fine.
Fine, fine, use the longbow.
It's fine, I'm with charge.
You're a pro player.
I have to be good at every weapon.
Yes, exactly.
Look at them.
You have your fist, so that's fine.
I have lots of ammo, if you guys need ammo.
Yeah, you can be our ammo guy.
Yeah, I have attachments too.
You're a princess.
You're our temporary princess.
That's fine.
I'm getting pushed.
How are they gonna push them?
They're all snipers.
I'll push them.
Bro, there's one team that literally fucking punched a bunch of people down.
Do you guys have any batteries, by the way?
I have one.
You might as well just give it to me, you get double heal.
Oh, that's true.
Here's two.
Someone take that one.
I have two.
I feel like we gotta loot more.
We gotta loot for more stuff, I feel like.
Somebody wasn't looting that well.
I found five wingmen!
That's all I'm gonna say.
Crossing over to the building.
I can't believe our sniper, our guy that's well known for being a sniper does not have a sniper.
I think someone was like five wingmen and no maidens.
So sad.
I thought you guys were looting on guard.
I was!
I was the one that got the sniper!
I looted so much.
Maybe I can loot this for you.
Yeah, you go loot.
You'll be safe, right?
I'm gonna drop my sniper, hold up.
I'll be back.
There's like a... I'll take your sniper.
I'll take your sniper attachment, because there's a Lobo team.
Oh yeah, true.
Take him, please.
If they take my sniper, we're doomed.
We all share one sniper.
We all share this longbow together.
My team, my team, my team!
Yeah, each of us take one shot and then we just share it.
Nah, there's nothing.
Are you serious?
There's nothing?
That's crazy.
Is this the newest King's Canyon?
Are we back to OG King's Canyon?
Oh shit, I should not have peeked that.
I'm pretty sure this guy has a 4x8.
It's fine, we're just gonna walk across.
Alright, we can just walk now, actually.
The zone's closing anyway.
Do you have the sniper?
It's still there.
Yeah, I dropped your stock, right?
You definitely need it on your charge rifle.
Alright, put your next wall up here, Altair.
Okay.
Like, just here.
Yeah, there's a team right here on that building.
Just facing east, east side.
I'm gonna check under if there's any boxes.
Oh my god, what?
Alright, if I die, I die.
I'm just scared of the team coming behind us.
By the way, I had the best sniper so you guys had to come back to grab my sniper, at least.
I'm heading over.
I'm heading over here for loot.
There's names.
There's ammo.
There's just ammo.
There's nothing.
They fucking took everything.
Can you low bow up, please?
We should've had a low bow.
Is that a rifle?
Possibly a low bow.
I thought we were gonna get snipers, though.
Oh no, I have like...
I have two shield cells left.
I can't hit a shot with this charge rifle right now.
I hit a shot.
Oh, that guy has one HP.
That guy is so low.
I hit him, too.
Look at him.
I need to suck.
Is he being on us?
They're fighting us.
There's no way they're fighting us.
They're snipers.
Where are they?
They're above us.
They're right above us?
I cracked one.
I cracked another one.
I'm going up.
Cracked two.
I'm getting sniped by the others.
I have the shield.
Go, Jango!
I'm doing so much damage.
They're getting bombed.
Chill on the staircase.
I hit 98.
They bubbled, though.
I'm punching.
Don't you go in there.
They went left.
They're getting shot.
I'm nading them.
Look at these nades.
Drop your nades.
My bad.
I jumped off.
We're fine.
They're gone, guys.
Don't worry.
Nothing happened.
They're going to bash your knees.
They're going to do some madness.
My bad.
They're going to cut your knees off like madness.
I can get a floor in this shit.
I don't have shields.
I have 13 souls.
I have zero.
I peaked too much.
We have...
How the fuck did you find all these shields?
We're going to go underneath.
I'm ready.
We can go to their spot.
Come follow me.
Can you bubble me?
Bubble?
Wait a minute.
Walk here.
You mean by bubble?
Here's a suck though.
Put the wall down this way.
West.
Put it down.
We're inside though.
That's fine.
You still have us.
Come to us.
Yeah.
They can't do anything.
They're going to break it.
They can do something.
We can play on here actually.
I'm going to go there now.
Come to me.
He's not peaking anymore.
You go first.
I'm okay.
I think we're going to run out.
We should have had a low bar.
We're going to run out.
I have ammo.
I'm dropping ammo.
We're fine.
We're so safe.
I feel so safe.
I'm hiding in a corner.
Maybe we can get to the last zone.
When we get to the last zone, you can start brawling at people.
It's my time.
Maybe the last zone will be people who are all snipers.
We can get low ground on this building.
There's a death box.
I'm going to ult.
Are you ready?
Come.
Follow me.
There's someone going in there now.
No way.
They're fighting.
Come.
Follow me.
On us.
It's time.
This is it.
It's time to start meleeing.
Chill.
I found one.
I killed one.
I got one.
It's time to start meleeing.
You can res me.
No.
This is it.
Just live.
I'm safe.
I'm safe right here in the corner.
I'm safer.
You can res me.
I'm so safe.
I can't get over there.
Don't come back.
It's dangerous.
Never come back.
I'm scared.
I'm punching.
No.
There's so many people here.
Why didn't I get a single sniper?
Five wingmen.
I'm fine.
If I had a better sniper, I ain't gonna lie.
Oh my god.
I'm gonna take that 85 damage to my grave.
That's an 85 melee.
That's actually crazy.
I fought a hard fight.
I went down fighting.
If they don't take all my guns, I'll take their lives.
I got two weapons right here.
All I'm saying is the moment you got a sniper, it was over.
You should've stuck with your fists.
You should've...
Oh my god.
We got killed by the Gooner gang.
It counts.
Five wingmen.
It's sniper, dude.
Jen, you died to the Gooner gang.
I did.
We died to the Gooner gang.
Altair didn't.
Altair didn't die to the Gooner gang, at least.
I died to some random pathfinder in the other building, I think.
What?
Do they know we...
No, nobody caught your nade mistake.
Nobody caught it.
So you're safe.
Nobody's watching.
Yeah, nobody was watching you.
Nobody watched.
It's okay, I'll turn my aimbot on.
I realized I didn't have that.
Oh my god.
And nobody watched you.
Nah, for real though, we would've been chilling.
I swear to god, we would've been chilling.
How so?
We would've won this zone, I swear to god.
If we lived there, we'd actually win.
If we lived there and if Altair had two guns.
If Altair had two guns.
Just give me a sliver of hope, please.
There's no way we looted from stadium to Blossom Drive on Neon and we didn't get a sniper.
Oh man.
That is insane.
We should've had Loba.
Look at this.
Look at the Gooner gang with the Kraber.
The Gooner gang got the Kraber.
That could've been us.
To be fair, there's only like two Loba teams.
Really?
How do you know?
Because I'm not seeing Lobalt.
Oh.
This team I'm watching is Kat.
I don't know, Loba's good, but I thought we'd get a sniper.
Yeah, you know with all the houses there.
I looted like five and I got one last second.
It was a charge rifle.
That is insane.
That's crazy.
I actually killed the other team that landed on us.
I killed them if I had the longbow.
And I killed this team underneath if I had the longbow.
Oh, I'm so sad.
That's insane.
Oh my god, I hope the Gooner gang wins.
We're gonna see the end zone though.
What is the end zone?
Oh my god.
Look at the sniper.
Bro, look at the sniper.
Eww.
Stinky.
Oh my god, the cost of life.
Oh my god, they just got bombed.
They got bombed.
They got fucking bombed.
It's a massacre.
The end zone is going crazy right now.
Oh my god, look at all these.
Oh my god.
What is going on?
It's all just snipers.
Oh my god.
My friend is literally just trying to live.
All the snipers in the...
The Gooner gang down.
Who won?
Valk team.
Who's playing Valk?
Who the fuck is playing Valk?
Valk, Gibraltar, Newcastle.
Goons out.
The Gooners got GFP.
Maybe the next game will be better.
Who was it?
There's no way.
Oh Goon.
Hibernation.
The hibernation team won.
It is...
Matou, Kahaku, Yumyumeriku, and Exphysic.
Yumyumeriku, and Exphysic.
Zizuzu.
Where did you get the extra Z in?
Yeah, where did you get the Z in?
Who the fuck?
Oh my god.
Our PR team got 16 kills.
Holy...
You guys should be nerfed.
Give them the worst possible punishment.
Oh my god.
Alright.
Gotta go to the interview stage.
I'll see you guys soon.
What are we playing now?
Protect the Princess.
Oh, it's Hide and Seek.
It's Hide and Seek.
We're gonna be seekers.
Alright.
I'll see you guys soon.
I'm down as well.
We came up with a punishment.
Okay, do we talk to the winners first or do we fucking bring madness in?
Winners first.
Hibernation.
Okay, I'll let them know.
Holy shit, she's actually won that.
Holy shit.
That was crazy.
Sniping in such a tiny ass zone.
Dash, do you know from the winning team, do you know if any of them stream on Twitch?
Let's see.
Wait, does Azuzu stream on Twitch?
She does stream on Twitch.
Yeah.
Can you?
I wanna go watch the VOD of how they won that game.
Yeah, that was crazy.
Because the RPS team almost won.
They got 16 kills.
You wanna hear the punishment we're gonna give Madness?
What is it?
70 FOV as well.
And then his shooting button on his mouse and his aiming button have to be reversed in the settings.
So hold or toggle, you mean?
No, like most people click the left button to shoot.
Left click would be shooting, but he's gonna be right click shoot.
Alright, let's get it.
Is hibernation in yet?
Yeah.
Yeah, it can join.
Wait, why is Wig deafened?
What he's fucking trying to do.
What?
Wait, what's Wig doing?
I don't know.
You think I know?
Wait, wait, wait.
They're like roommates with him.
He doesn't even answer my text messages.
Have you tried knocking the door?
There we go, there we go.
My bad, I was watching.
Hello.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Arigatou gozaimasu.
I have a question for you, Kawaku.
I have a question.
Was that finisher intentional in that last circle?
Or was that an alpha move?
Did you miss click?
What was the situation there?
Wait, you did a finisher?
In the middle of the endgame.
With 37 people alive.
The finisher got popped.
Wait, they won?
Yes.
So was that the game plan or was that a miss click for you?
Oh yeah, for sure.
That's totally intentional.
Yeah.
Was that your strats or what?
Okay, to be honest I was trying to get onto the evac tower, but I accidentally clicked onto somebody.
Are you aware that your Gibraltar ultimate did 700 damage in that late game?
Really?
Yeah, 700.
I did hear a bunch of crack, crack, crack, but I didn't think it was 700.
That was a lot.
That's a lot of damage.
You guys did a great job.
That was fire.
That was such a fun ending to watch.
It would be so funny if I actually finished the finisher though.
I know, I wish you committed to be honest.
It was full commitment towards it.
That was so good.
What's the game plan for game 5 now?
We're going to protect the princess.
Hide and seek for game 4, my bad.
What's the game plan here?
Any character comps you guys are going to run for game 4?
And run away from Doki?
We have Shizu-san as our IGL, so I'm going to let him explain.
Yes, go for it.
Shizu-san, please explain the game plan.
The game plan for game 5.
IGL, please explain it.
Well, I'm going to take the middle of the map and if I just keep going, I'll be in the middle of the map.
Alright.
So, he's planning to just sit in the middle of the zone and just tank with a Newcastle Q and a Gibby Q.
That's it.
That's his plan.
Okay, so thanks for telling me about that.
Because...
I didn't think about that, my bad.
I wouldn't jump me.
That's my fault.
We gotta change our plan now.
That was actually a fake plan.
Fake plan.
I see, I see.
But we'll go to the middle just in case, yeah?
Yeah, yeah.
Very smart.
That's so good.
I forgot the organizer of the tournament was literally in this call.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That was my question right there.
Listen, I'm not a professional.
I'm trying my best.
Dude, congratulations to those guys.
That was actually such a fun game to watch.
One of the best ones of the night so far for sure.
Yeah, no worries.
Good luck in game four and stay away from Doki.
She's scary.
Alright, we'll make sure one of us will be in the middle just to see if it was fake.
Okay.
Meet you in the middle.
See you guys in the middle, guys.
Bye-bye.
Thank you.
Arigato gozaimasu.
Alright, now are we bringing madness?
Yeah, we're bringing madness.
It's execution style.
Okay, madness is in...
Okay, at madness...
Who's gonna lay the hammer?
You are.
You have the plan, right?
I think you should too.
You've been really excited about the punishment.
I think this might be...
I mean, you've been the one really discussing about what he should be facing as a punishment.
So I think this should be...
What's...
Yo, what's enemy highlight?
What do you mean?
When the recon character, ADS, that highlights his show up, like the Bloodhound's gun.
Well, you guys can't play...
Yeah.
I won't play Vantage.
So you won't get that scanned, right?
Alright, madness is here.
Madness is here.
I'm here for my punishment.
Madness, how you doing?
I've been better.
Daddy's about to drop the hammer on you.
Dude, the ADS instinct just turned on.
I just went free kill, free kill.
I'm like telling my team.
Ah.
Unfortunately...
Unfortunately, actions have punishments.
Yes.
It was voted on here by the council.
That was just you.
It wasn't just me.
Majority agree.
This is for game 6, by the way.
Game 6 punishment.
For the last game, game number 6, you will be sentenced to 70 FOV and you have to switch your left click, which is your shooting button and your right click, which is your aiming button.
You have to reverse them.
So you're going to be shooting with the right button on your mouse and aiming in with the left.
Who cooked that up?
Who do you think?
I mean, it was a share, yeah.
If you want to punch us, we just have a controller.
Do you have a controller?
Wait, why did I say that?
Do you actually have one?
I have a...
No, you know, the first idea is fine.
The first idea is fine.
70 FOV and switch the buttons.
And let's just say the person who cooked that one up, their name rhymes with Loki.
Oh my god, Roki?
Game 6, by the way.
Only game 6.
So you have two more games before we get there.
I gotta write down these.
Good luck, good luck, madness.
And I was like, God already made me 5'4", and now I'm getting punished even more.
What is happening?
Welcome to a Doki Bird tournament.
I hope you enjoy yourself.
It's not my fault!
Hello?
Get in the comms with Doki and she's salivating from the mouth and handing you a punishment.
What do you want me to do?
Is this true?
No, that's not true.
I was like, if you want to, it's really up to you.
This might be a VOD checker.
Alright, well, good luck, buddy.
So you're good, I believe in you.
Love you.
Love you too.
Alright, Tempo.
There's another setting for you that you have to turn off enemy highlights.
Apparently, it's not just recon.
If you get close enough, everyone has it.
Okay, yeah, I can turn it off.
Yeah, that's no problem.
Alright, I'll go back to IRS.
I'll see you guys later.
Wait, before you go, where are you guys landing?
How is this working?
You guys can land wherever?
No, it's still ALGS mode.
Yeah, so like, we all get random PIs, so whoever's next to us...
That's kind of...
Well...
Nobody in game has any idea where your team is landing.
No one knows where anyone is.
Yeah, we can pretend to be hiders too.
We can just walk up to them, see if they'll do anything.
Don't have your guns out and just run over to someone as if you're hiding.
Just pull out a gun and just load them up.
That's what I'm planning on doing.
Wait, wait, wait.
Yuris is asking, is crypto a role for hiders?
I think we said no for...
I feel like we should ban crypto for hiders.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, I don't know.
Should we?
Yeah, I feel like we should.
Dash, can you ban crypto for hiders?
I almost forgot about the invis thing.
I don't think you should lock crypto.
Alright, I'll see you guys in the next game.
Alright, good luck.
Alright, bye.
Alright.
Hey guys.
Alright, so let's have a little competition between Altera and I versus Jen.
And I feel like...
Where's the enemy highlight?
Oh, there it is.
I got it.
So, basically...
Wait, can we not?
We cannot play recon.
I call ballistic.
Ballistic, who the heck is that?
Ballistic, I have unlimited ammo so I don't wanna...
I got octane.
I dibs octane.
We're working together.
Pathfinder.
Oh, no, we can't play pathfinder.
We can't use pathfinder.
No, we can't.
Fuck.
Altera, what do we play?
Jen, okay, let's work together.
Jen, what should Altera...
No, no, no, no.
Jen, come on!
He's a baby!
He's a fucking baby!
Jen, listen.
She turns her back on everyone, okay?
You and me, we can make out a deal.
Yeah, I'm down for that, Altera.
I'm down.
Oversight said crypto is okay.
Okay, I'm good.
Crypto not okay.
I overrule him.
Didn't he recon?
No, but he's saying hi.
Hi, there.
Altera, what are you going to do?
Wait, Altera, if you're second pick...
Wait, so we are banning crypto?
Yeah, we're banning crypto because he can go invisible.
And that would be a little fucked up for us.
Altera, if you get picked first, you should take octane from Jen.
No!
No, you should not do that!
Don't do that!
Alright, there's a big fight over here.
How much can either of you offer?
Altera, we're working together against Jen!
We're literally working together!
I need more than that.
Altera, if we win, we'll get something special.
I don't know what it is yet, but we'll get something.
That's crazy.
They're teaming up on me, guys.
If we win, I'll give you $500.
If it's a charity, and that's a deal.
Okay, yeah, 100%.
Jen, if you win, you get nothing.
You get the pleasure of winning against two VTubers.
That's insane.
Because I'm a pro player?
Nah, dude.
Don't you guys just love being competitive?
I'll tell you a secret, okay?
Listen.
I don't think I ever made it to plat, okay?
I thought you made it to...
You said you got to diamond!
You told us you're a diamond player!
It was plat.
You're a plat player?
I've never touched diamond in this game.
Wait, that's perfect.
Wait, what?
What do you mean, perfect?
What's that supposed to mean?
That's perfect, because then he has the perfect rank points.
Please give me first pick.
My god, please don't give him first pick.
Please don't give him.
No!
First pick!
Wait, where are you going to pick?
Where are you going to pick?
You have no more choices.
Oh, you TP'd to people.
TP to them, snare them.
And I get unlimited ammo.
Tempo told you guys to turn off enemy highlights, right?
Yeah, we got it off.
Can I just double check if I have that off?
Yeah, I do.
You guys ought to remind me to put it back on, though.
Imagine playing Scrim without it.
What if we don't?
He's going to Scrim without it.
Good luck, have fun, guys.
Yay!
It's kind of not that bad.
Wait, hiders can't shoot you, right?
No, they can't.
They can't do anything.
They just gotta hide.
Okay.
Fuck off, Doki.
These are my bins.
No, I'm fucking going there.
No, no, no.
I get inside.
That's fine.
We have one gun.
It's self.
Keep doing it, Doki.
Sabotage.
I feel like we don't need to do one gun here, right?
I feel like...
as a hider...
I don't know.
Actually, maybe I'll do...
Okay, okay.
Jen and I will have one gun, but...
I have Altair on my team who can have two guns.
Woohoo!
Woo!
Wait, what?
What?
We found someone in the bag!
That's one in the bag!
I'm coming over.
Jen, you're fucking already killing people?
We haven't found anybody yet.
That's so fucked, Jen.
Let them play, Jen!
Come on, you're a pro.
Come on!
Would a pro really do this to us?
Just for fun.
Oh my god!
They're calling you out!
You wouldn't hate charity, right?
Yeah, yeah.
If you win, you basically are saying fuck charity.
How about...
I leave the last guy alive, you know?
Wow!
What an honor!
The last guy!
Wow!
You shouldn't have.
Okay, Altair, I'm running on the other side of the map.
I'm running on the other side.
I'll see you on the other side.
I'm gonna go here.
I can't believe it.
I need a car.
Oh my god, you don't get cars here.
There's no cars in fucking...
Why aren't you admiring this?
There's no cars in Broken Moon!
Give me a car!
Oh my god.
Where the fuck could they be hiding?
Jen is already hunting people down.
He's already hunting.
I'm already.
I think there's someone up here.
I smell them.
They smell like dog shit up here.
I'm running, I'm running, I'm running!
I'm zip gliding!
Altair, we have zero kills!
Why were you trying?
There's gotta be someone here.
I see someone.
Come on.
I see someone shoot them.
What are you doing?
Wait, Altair, you're doing it.
They're running away, they're running away.
They're running away?
That's illegal.
It's not though.
It's not, they can't run.
Oh my god.
Aha!
They're running!
Come here, bitch.
I'm chasing this motherfucker down.
Oh my god, that poor guy.
Somebody kill him.
Somebody accidentally punch him.
It would be such a shame.
Leave him for dead.
It would be such a shame if somebody just punches him.
Oh my god, it would be so funny though.
Aha, bitch!
How am I supposed to find anybody?
They're such good hiders.
That's a Mirage decoy, there's no way.
That is crazy.
Got one kill, it's still one kill.
Hello.
Who is this?
Where's this purple shield at?
I smell them.
Whistler duration in the world is tripled?
Oh my god, what do I get, chat?
Slingshot or...
Oh my god, where are they hiding?
I see them!
Wait, is that...
Is that part of the...
Wait, is that part of the world?
Ah, decoys.
There's so much...
I wish we landed on separate sides of the map.
Because everyone's gonna go away from us.
Yeah, but they don't know where...
Yeah, they do.
Where we came from, yeah.
Oh no.
So everyone knows we're coming from Breaking Wolf.
Yeah, but if we keep running, they won't know.
True.
I'm literally on the other side now.
I'm trying to find this Pathfinder, dude.
There's a fucking Mirage clone here?
Oh my god, dude.
I'm just gonna go the other side, I know where everyone is.
I definitely know where everyone is.
Okay, I'm following you.
No, don't follow me.
I'm following you.
These are all my kills.
Oh my god, I haven't found a single...
These guys are such good hiders!
What if we shot Jem?
Why don't we like...
Why don't we push him off the cliff?
Let's do it, let's kidnap him with a car.
Wait, there's no cars!
There's no cars, we can't push him out.
We'll do what we did to Axel.
Where he got stuck and couldn't...
I'll play Pathfinder.
Oh, I see someone flying.
There has to be somebody on this side, right?
I see someone flying too!
I'm getting involved!
I saw him first!
Altair, you can TP!
I'm gonna TP for another 10 seconds.
No.
No!
Why is there no one hiding in this corner?
Who's next?
Oh my god, they know you're an Octane too.
They know.
Wait, Zan can kill me.
Hold up, one sec.
Let me heal.
Don't let him heal!
Melee him into zone!
Altair, go over there and melee him into zone.
Oh my god.
Wait, he's on.
No, you don't.
What are you talking about?
Oh my god.
Altair, you even saw somebody!
I haven't seen a single person!
What?!
I haven't seen a single man!
Or woman!
There you go.
I'm scared.
Oh my god.
Doki, there's someone coming over towards your far.
Do you mind?
No, I am way too far.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
I'm gonna follow this guy.
I'm gonna see if I can trick him.
Doki!
Run!
I can't find any link!
This is the first time I found a guy!
I got leaked!
I killed another one!
I'm finishing him!
Stay shank him!
This is the first time I found a person!
I can't believe they leaked my location!
So fucked!
I literally couldn't find anybody and he leaked it.
Just when I saw one guy running towards me.
That's so fucked.
That's actually so fucked.
He doxed me, I can't believe it.
I can't believe I got doxed.
In this ring, come in faster.
I have four kills, what about you guys?
Shut the fuck up!
Shut the fuck up.
I got doxed, what do you want me to do?
I got doxed too!
The one guy!
I got one!
I'm gonna steal that kill.
So Jen, that partnership...
Wait, wait, wait.
You can't just ditch me like this.
I go in the path of the winners.
Oh, I'll tear, I'll tear.
So you hate charity too.
So what you're saying is...
I love charity.
Oh my god, you guys fucking suck.
I can't find a single...
I'm literally looking at someone.
Someone just rezzed.
I'm farming.
That doesn't count.
That doesn't add to your count.
It does, it does.
No it doesn't if you killed him already.
The guy that I just killed!
I got one, I got one, I got one.
What do you mean?
What do you mean you got one?
Are we still on the same team?
Yes, yes, yes.
That's good, that's good.
I'm happy now.
For now.
Oh my god.
This is bullshit.
This is actually bullshit.
I can't find anybody.
You don't have a kill yet?
What's going on?
There's no one here!
That is crazy right now.
I saw one guy and then I got doxxed and then he disappeared.
And then he fucking disappeared.
He literally doxxed me at the worst timing.
The worst time to ever doxx somebody.
We gotta kill people man.
Where?
We haven't killed one squad yet.
Where do I do this?
I need shotgun ammo.
I'm gonna run out.
For real.
Oh my god.
Shotgun ammo.
That's a Mirage clone.
There's someone ratting in here.
I smell him.
The door's closed.
You killed one!
You got your first kill!
Let's go!
I did it!
You did it!
I don't have heals.
I don't need heals.
I just need ammo.
This is just the beginning.
We did it!
We got our one kill.
I got my one kill.
Okay, we have two guys.
How long must I tolerate amateurs?
It's an update.
You're getting all the leaks right now.
The IRS is coming.
I pumped him.
Is this RPR?
I pumped him bad.
Oh my god.
Oh, there's no more resists.
We can't res people anymore.
They're dead dead.
Red shield.
Ain't no way.
Oh my god.
Wait, Jen, are you using two guns?
Yeah.
Someone sees one gun!
Who said that?
Automatic disqualification.
We win!
This guy has a grapple cooldown of like 10 seconds.
Bro, every match you cheat!
Do I smell an on-the-fly punishment?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
What is it?
Do I have to play Southpaw or what?
Yeah, yeah, on-the-fly punishment.
What is it?
Alright, 70 FOV.
Max brightness.
What?
Max brightness?
Bro, what the fuck is this?
I'm a magnifying glass right now.
Right here.
I can definitely see them.
I'm playing a whole different game right now.
My eyes!
Oh my god.
Wait, where are they at?
Oh my god, I'm going to zoom into their soul.
You're going to zoom into their soul?
Is that even...
Boom!
How do I not see a single person?
Hello?
Yeah!
Thank you!
Oh no!
I'm sorry!
This is the FOV I used to play on console, bro.
What is this shit?
I'm so sorry!
2004, bro.
I'm sorry, I didn't know that
was...
I found so many of them.
Wait, I'm at four kills.
Where are you at?
I found a lot of them, though.
My sense feels so weird.
If I knew, I would have let her live!
I would have let her live!
I'm sorry!
I'm getting nauseous, I ain't going to lie.
Kreek, you got to help him!
He's getting nauseous!
I'm getting a bit sick, lad.
It's fine.
80 FOV.
That's you?
What's up, dude?
How you doing?
Oh my god.
I'm five, I'm five.
How many do you have?
It's on my 30th right now.
What about you?
There's no way.
Oh my god.
There has to be somebody out there.
No way I missed that.
Well, we'll see if you get the kill.
You're shooting me right now?
That's crazy.
What am I playing?
Dude, I'm going back to PlayStation 1, man.
Fucking shit, dude.
Help me!
That's my kill!
That's mine!
No way!
No fucking way!
There's no fucking way.
Why are we all here together?
Get out!
Get out of here!
Steal the kill!
What are you doing?
I can't climb, for fuck's sake.
Badass Loba down.
I'm finishing him.
No way.
There's no way he does that.
Wait, I forgot.
I'm allowed to use nades.
I know it's my custom, but I forgot my own rules.
I actually don't know if you're allowed to use nades.
I don't remember.
I don't remember also.
We have to look up.
Look up!
There's people up top!
What's up, cuz?
A lot of people over here.
There's people!
Look up!
Nice!
No!
There's no way this guy got rezzed.
This is Timmy!
I'm chasing Timmy down.
I see Timmy!
It's my teammate!
I'm finishing him!
You know it's him!
I know it's him.
Oh my god.
I'm running out of ammo.
Come near me!
I have ult.
There's a lot of them here.
It's time.
Oh my god.
I'm gonna die to zone!
They're all so low!
I can't climb!
Oh no!
Oh my god.
I'm gonna take this out.
They're all parkouring!
Guys!
What do we do when they start parkouring?
Oh my god!
There's ults too?
Oh no.
What the fuck is this?
This is...
What am I looking at?
What?
You're like one of the rats.
There's ants in there!
There are literally ants in there!
I can't!
I'm fucking dying!
I need to save my ammo!
It's a fucking beehive!
There's a beehive here!
It's crazy!
It's an actual beehive.
Oh my god.
I can't.
They're just hiding!
How the fuck do I get up there?
I lifted the beehive!
Oh my god.
How do I get up there?
Are you serious?
Wait, I think they don't know.
They don't know I'm partying.
It's disabled!
What?
I'm disabled right now.
Wait, what's going on over there?
I'm so confused.
Wait, no!
Didn't got him.
Oh my god.
They're all rezzing.
There's too many.
Bro!
They're at the balloon!
This Valkyrie is hurting my wrists.
What the fuck?
I can't!
My boobie can't handle this no longer!
I can't do it!
Okay, we got another one.
There we go.
I got one.
I got another.
This guy is insane.
I can't get this guy!
Fuck me!
Oh my god.
Dude, I got a kill!
This is not fair!
Oh my god.
One team was left.
We did it!
I don't know.
There's so many.
I didn't even check how many kills I got.
Guys, how many kills I got?
Holy fuck, I don't know how many kills I had.
I couldn't tell!
We were...
We had non-stop unlimited ammo.
Because we kept killing people.
But we never needed ammo.
I think I had like 50.
Oh my god.
Oh, that's going on YouTube?
Holy...
They're like little roaches.
When they scat, they see us.
73?
Oh my god.
I don't know how many kills I got.
We got...
Gooner Gang.
Gooner Gang got second place.
Oh, go for them.
Yeah, this is Tappi's team.
I think.
Is it Tappi's team?
What has Greek done to me?
Oh my god.
My wrist hurts.
Put enemy highlight back on too.
Oh yeah, we should put our enemy highlight back on.
Okay.
Holy shit.
That was crazy.
Oh my god.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe...
I had 43 kills apparently.
What do I get?
Do I get the hoodie?
Wait.
We don't know if you won.
I had 43.
Oh, I got 44.
You have to watch my vote of it.
I went around this corner.
It was on the edge of zone.
Guess how many people were there in that corner.
There was 15 of them.
I shot one.
I killed one guy.
All of them were scattered like bees.
It was so funny.
Oh my god.
I'm gonna go apologize to Bao.
I killed her.
I'm gonna apologize.
I'm sorry Bao.
I'm sorry for killing your team.
I'm sorry.
I didn't realize who was...
I didn't know.
If I knew it was you, If I knew it was you, I wouldn't have done it.
I wouldn't have done it.
You thought I was a good person too.
I trusted you.
I thought that was just like a guitar in your bed.
Yeah, just to hide it.
Oh, sweet.
This nice old man just came up to me and wants to play the banjo.
Sorry.
I would have let you live.
I swear to god.
Me limping.
Me limping to the finish line with the corpses of my dead friends on my back.
I'm sorry.
Personnel kid.
It was a bit funny though.
It was a little funny though.
You caught me with my pants down too.
I was like, oh god.
I was like, don't worry.
If it makes you feel better, I did it to four other people.
It wasn't just you.
Oh, thank you.
It wasn't a special thing for you.
So I'm not even special?
No, I mean you are special.
You're the only one I felt guilty.
I felt guilt for.
I didn't feel sorry for the others.
I felt sorry for killing you.
I guess I forgive you.
I gotta do the interview now.
I'm a team genius.
Okay, get out of here.
Dookie bird.
Wait, where did Wig go?
I don't know.
What?
What do you mean you don't know?
He just left.
Wait, what?
Where did he go?
He's probably in a Discord channel with one of the teams.
No, he's not.
I'm literally looking.
Where did he go?
Where did he...
He's just gone.
Get away!
You wanna Discord jackass?
Call them!
The Onika team in there.
Yeah, where the fuck did Wig go?
Oh, he's playing in the game mode?
We could be in this call while he explains it.
How is it like watching it?
It's so entertaining.
Did you see what I did?
Did you guys see what I did to a couple of hiders?
No, I didn't.
What did you do?
I did the whole pretend to be a hider and watched them walk to me.
Oh, you got people with it?
You're a super villain.
You're a piece of shit.
You're evil, bro.
Holy shit.
I got several people.
They walked up to me and I just took my gun out.
Oh my god.
It's almost worth more than Jen Burton just having all those kills, to be honest.
We did it!
Congratulations!
The whole Japanese squad right here.
The Japanese...
The only Japanese team.
Oh, really?
I think so.
Japanese!
Yay!
Dash, can you ask how oneTappy is gonna feel being the princess next game?
Okay, okay.
He's a princess.
He's a princess, so it's natural for him to be a princess.
I see.
So, oneTappy, he's like a princess in general, so he doesn't see any difference.
He's the one princess himself.
There's no...
I have a question for you, Dash.
You're good, you're good.
No, no, go first.
I wanted to know who was the last player alive on the team and what their strategy was at the very end.
How did you survive?
I hid in the shadows so no one could see me.
You hid in the shadows?
Yes, I hid in the shadows and hid behind the knockers.
I see, I see.
So, Aoharu was the last one.
And she was like hiding behind someone's knockers.
Oh, that's smart.
Very smart.
Dash, how does Aoharu feel about protecting Wontabi?
Do they feel like they could really win the next game?
Are they confident in their abilities?
Does he feel safe?
Yes!
They're very confident.
Let's go!
Fuck yeah.
Alright, tell them I said good luck and I wish them nothing but the best.
Wait, wait, wait.
Go for it, go for it.
Lock in.
Tell him that Madness was the one that killed him and then tell him what Madness' punishment is for game 6 so he knows we got vengeance for him.
I already told him that he's going to get punishment.
How does he feel though?
Yeah, how does he feel?
How does he feel about it?
Madness got punished.
How do you feel?
He's great.
He wants more.
He wants more?
What do you want him?
We have to ask him what he wants.
The first one to go is W.
So he wants that Madness if he taps the W, he goes to the behind.
And if he taps the S, he goes to the front.
Inverted control.
Do it.
We should do it.
Alright, well how about we change the...
Okay, so he wants to add it on with the inverted aim?
Yeah.
Ah, that's a doki call.
Yeah, we should do it.
I'm down.
I'm so down.
No, no, no.
Tom, we're with him.
Tom, we agree.
I'll deliver the bad news to Madness.
Instead of C, the mouse will be inverted.
That's totally fine.
That's not bad.
Alright, let's do it.
That's too bad.
Alright.
How about we say good luck in game 6?
Or game 5?
Alright, good luck next time.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
I'm gonna go tell Madness right now.
Alright, good luck guys.
So he has to do the inverted on top of everything we just did?
Yeah.
He might as well just turn the screen off.
Perfect.
Alright, I'll see you guys in the next game.
Oh my god.
Are you ready for Princess?
What should I play?
You're just here to carry your stuff.
Should I play Crypto?
Crypto so you can hide.
You can be invisible.
I can help you guys.
But the moment you show your head, they're gonna shoot you.
Because you don't have a gun.
Okay, are you really confident that you will be okay?
I'm literally a pack mule for you guys.
Yeah, but then what if he dies?
One of us could be Loba.
I can Q out.
That's true.
But I feel like being invisible...
Let's feed you guys grenades.
And you guys can throw grenades at him.
That's true.
We could.
The Crypto, I can only EMP and that's literally it.
And give you wallhacks.
Yeah, but that's good.
So then we can get the wallhacks.
But then you're safer being invisible.
That's the thing.
The only issue is that what if they shoot your drone?
What if they shoot your drone?
I'm basically useless.
Okay, okay.
Fuse or Loba?
Wait, did we just play Lifeline in Newcastle?
Play Newcastle again?
Do we do that?
If we're going to be inside most of the time then...
Yeah, we just gotta find a house.
And give you a little house.
Is this one like Zone 1, no one fires?
No, we can fire.
But it's very dangerous if the princess dies.
We need to get into Zone.
But the thing is we don't have any ring console character.
Yeah.
I mean you can predict the zone, I believe in you, Jen.
Okay, I believe.
Harvest's team is only a duo.
Oh wait, no, they're...
He came back, he's just getting back on now.
That's why we're just waiting for that.
Are we able to buff them game 6 somehow?
Is that a...
How do we buff them?
We should buff them and Bao's team.
But how do we buff them?
How do we buff somebody in a normal Apex game?
We need Destroyer in here.
Okay, Destroyer come in, just give them walls.
Just give them aim assist.
Well, my chat's saying no princess, but do you think that's too strong?
It probably is too strong, right?
No princess at all?
No princess?
We'll just be like princesses can use guns.
We'll say like these teams...
Yeah, we can be like...
Okay, so I think it should be like...
Chibidoki's team, Bao's team, and...
Gerard's team.
I'll say that.
Okay, I'll do that.
I'll go inform Gerard's team.
Armus, Bao, and Chibi...
Is there any other team that needs help?
Or is it just those...
Okay, and FaZe Connect.
FaZe Connect, you princesses can hold guns.
And Master plus Master slash Prince can hold two guns.
We have Grand Q.
Power.
They have insane power.
Isn't that insane?
Okay, they need the buff though.
They need it.
No, they'll be fine.
FaZe can get ring console.
The thing is, three of those teams...
Only two of those teams don't have a Master Pred.
Yes.
You can use...
Your team gets...
Your team gets granted a little buff.
Courtesy of the casters.
I think we'll go FaZe, no cap.
Casters granted you a power.
It's the casters' decision.
Poor Madness.
He shouldn't have fucking killed that one Tappy.
70 FOVs.
Invert W and S key.
Invert mouse direction.
And then the rest in Japanese.
Bro, casters have no chill.
They have no chill.
He can still shoot his gun.
It's possible.
I believe.
Do you see the clip I sent you?
Show your chat.
What is this?
Scattered like roaches.
What the fuck?
Holy shit.
That's what I'm saying.
There's one guy.
Disturbing the nest.
Not one guy.
Like 20 people showed up.
20 people came to help her.
What the fuck?
I didn't think to see so many.
Oh my god.
That's fucking crazy.
Okay, we can have...
Let me see if Greek or Whig are willing to play with them.
Are you guys willing to sub in for Artemis?
For a game?
I think Tempo should be their princess.
No, they have no princess.
The princess can hold the gun.
Alright, Tempo, get in there.
Join them.
Yeah, you're shooting.
You get to shoot.
Minus Tempo.
Who will be joining Artemis?
Oh my god.
If I turn my head, I have map hacks.
What the fuck?
Alright.
Tempo's joining them.
Tempo's joining their team.
In returns.
Alright, I believe.
I believe in this team.
They have...
They literally have the host advantage.
They can't fuck it up.
There's no way.
Alright.
They literally have host advantage.
They get to look at endzone.
They can put the fucking princess at the endzone.
Oh my god.
You have to watch this, Doki.
You have to watch this.
This is from Gerard's POV.
What did you do to him?
No, no, it's so funny.
I'm gonna play Fuse, by the way.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, that's so good.
That's so good.
Okay, we're starting a server.
Oh no, is it because Tempo joined in that the server takes fucking forever?
Yeah.
Is that a thing, too?
Fuck Tempo, man.
Wait, is that true?
Kick him.
Remove his co- If there's a new person in the server, it takes a long time?
Remove the co-host from him.
This is the co-host.
This is the co-host's fault.
Oh my god.
I'm gonna be right back.
I'm gonna get a cough drop.
Okay.
Can we ban this Gooner guy?
Interesting.
Taking so long!
What are we waiting for?
Oh my gosh, my...
My, like, mouse is, like, fucking up.
Oh no.
Oh no, this is so bad.
Doki doki doki doki, hear me out.
This is so bad.
My mouse is fucking up.
What is it?
Use controller, you'll be fine.
You'll never disconnect.
Use DDR pad.
Doki, it's time to switch to controller.
Come on, come to the backside.
You're better than this.
I have integrity!
How about if I give you my free Battle Beaver controller with GenBurden, you know?
What?
Signed on it.
Do you use the controller or not?
Oh yeah, no, no.
Yeah, you can send it to me and maybe you'll see it on eBay.
Make sure you sign it too.
Oh yeah, can you sign it for me?
Oh my god, can I have your autograph on that controller as well?
I would love to have your autograph.
How much are you selling it for though?
Can I get a commission?
I'm not gonna sell it.
What are you talking about?
I don't know what you're saying.
I would never do something that fucked up.
Alright, wait, what are we playing?
I don't even know.
I'm playing Fuse-y.
You're playing Fuse-y?
What about me?
Lifeline, right?
Lifeline?
Okay.
I think I was thinking Fuse because like, I don't know, Lobo's gonna be eh.
And then we're gonna run out of loot again.
We gotta find a house.
Yeah, yeah, we gotta go into a house and chill.
You smell me?
Where would be the priority for my walls?
Priority?
It would be like a corner, like hugging the wall.
If that makes sense.
Or blocking off a doorway or something.
I'll let you know.
Where are we?
Where are we landing now?
It's good.
It should be fine.
Yeah.
I'm a princess, guys.
Princess, no.
Princess, don't remember not to carry any anything.
Any guns, princess.
You've literally broken every single rule in each map.
I've never broken a rule in my life.
You held two guns in hide and seek.
I saw it.
Hide and seek or the other one?
You broke a rule in every game.
What are you talking about?
You shot a gun in melee.
Did you not do that?
Yeah, but that's to break the gender right to talk.
Yeah, but you still shot your gun.
You still did it.
Did you not?
I did, but I didn't shoot it at people.
That wasn't in the rules.
Yeah, but you weren't supposed to carry a gun, though.
Right, Altair?
You read the rules.
We trusted you.
Oh, yeah, I know, right?
You threw a grenade.
You threw a grenade in sniper only.
They could have died to that grenade.
Yeah.
I'm just saying some rules are meant to be broken.
That's all I'm gonna say.
Not in these customs.
Especially Doki's rules.
They're supposed to be broken.
I'm trying to balance it as best I could.
I'm trying to make this as balanced as I can right now.
Okay.
Oh, my gosh.
What are you writing, Altair?
I'm writing all the grenades for you guys, by the way.
Wait, what?
Wait, what did you say, Jen?
I have all the grenades for you guys.
You're not throwing it at them.
Okay, I have light ammo.
Hold light ammo for me.
What?
Okay, fine.
You're literally the princess.
You have to.
Say pretty please.
No, you might as well just die.
You might as well just die.
I'm holding you the light ammo, then.
Fuck you.
Altair, you say it.
Pretty please.
Okay, I got you, Altair.
Good boy.
You enabled him.
I told you not to.
I told you not to enable him.
Where do we go, Jen?
Princess Jen?
Let's go here, and then we get the Rincon Sal.
Princess Jen, where do we go?
Do I have to talk like a princess, too?
Yeah, how would you talk like a princess?
Yeah, posh.
Give us posh, Jen.
Fuck, isn't that like...
Oh, they don't say that word.
Is that what you see, posh people?
Asking for fucking tea?
They drink their tea with their pinkies lifted.
Don't you know that?
Ask us to go to afternoon tea or something.
Go for it.
You guys want some afternoon tea?
You're pretty good.
You have such a good accent.
Thank you.
Appreciate that.
Oh, Princess Jen.
What is the life of Princess Jen?
What do you have to do today as a princess?
Carry.
Carry guys' fat asses.
Carry the weight of the country on your shoulders, right?
Princess, no, you can't.
Don't use that word.
Use all your strength, Princess.
You gotta rest.
No resting.
We gotta win this.
You can't hurt your dainty little hands.
Hello, guys.
Come on, where are you?
Where's my bodyguards?
Princess is gonna die so fast.
Princess, don't run away.
How are you supposed to...
I need backup support right now.
Why do you keep running away from us?
Do you hate this life so much?
Princess, please.
We're just trying to help.
Oh my god.
Help.
You have a duty to uphold.
Altair, I got purple knocked out for you.
I'll put a Q right here.
Come to me.
I just realized we're letting Rollerplayer IGL.
Wait, what does that mean?
Can you Q this, Altair?
Okay, here.
Take this.
This is good for you, I think.
It's not Q-ing.
Come, come, come.
It wasn't Q-ing.
I have to check my things.
Wait, what happened?
What did you guys miss?
Altair, take my purple knockdown.
Oh, I don't have it binded to Q.
You don't have Q bind!
What am I playing with?
That's your body, guys.
There's a team up there.
What about PR?
We're fine, right?
Climb up, guys.
I'm climbing up.
I can't climb up here.
We're so...
I'm backing up.
Don't worry, Princess.
I got a drone following you.
They're chasing us for some reason.
I think it's the three-man team.
Don't worry.
Heal up, Altair.
I got Altair.
Good shit.
Why are they chasing us, dude?
They're not.
Just run, Jen.
We're body blocking you.
Run, Princess.
Your life is so important to us.
There's a team right here.
That matters.
I saw an ability there.
Go back.
Oh my god.
They all want us.
I'm getting down.
Get down, Princess.
We're body blocking for you.
I think we're good.
We can come get this juicer.
There's a guy.
What?
I can kill him.
I'm gonna ult him.
No, he moved.
The princess moved.
I'm going left.
Fuck it.
That's fine.
We chased the princess away.
There's a princess in the corner.
Get down, Miss Princess.
I got you.
There's a...
Wait, there's no one over there.
Okay.
Why is everyone on us right now?
Our princess is so ahead.
I don't know.
I got my high heels on.
I'm running.
I'm running with my high heels.
We don't have your youthful energy.
You're gonna run into a three-man and then we just have to fucking stand and die.
Okay, Doki.
Lead on, Doki.
Go.
I'm going in.
I'll take the shot.
I got your back.
I take my shot.
You get his back.
I'll get his front.
They would not know that the princess is in the middle.
Actually, being in the front makes the most sense.
They'll be like, why the fuck is the princess in the front?
They'll be like scared.
I am the real princess.
Star Wars type stuff.
They'll assume the princess is in Newcastle or the Lifeline.
They won't think it's you.
I think the princess needs a new castle, huh?
Yeah, the princess is in Newcastle.
Oh, sorry, Mario.
Your princess is in Newcastle.
Oh my god.
Princess Peach.
Princess Peach, slow down.
Princess Peach, come back.
You're burning too fast.
Please.
Your dainty legs shouldn't be using it like that.
Help me, guys.
Someone should've come during the fight.
We're close.
I see someone.
You can shoot them.
Oh, he's so low.
He's so low.
He fucking shielded.
He was so low, though.
I'm left.
Oh my god, they're 10 damage, guys.
Oh my god, you did it, princess.
I think you used up too much energy.
You should take a break.
That's too much energy.
You gotta take a little...
You gotta rest up.
Where do we make it our home?
Where should our home be?
The home?
We're gonna go there right now.
I need my castle.
Yeah, we gotta get a castle for you.
A castle worthy for you.
Anything for you, princess.
I'm hitting the scan, guys.
Don't worry, I'm body blocking.
Thank you, thank you.
Don't worry.
It's on us!
Okay, okay.
Princess, we found your castle.
Yes, this is my castle.
Look how gorgeous it is.
Look at all these openings.
Have you seen my nail polish today?
Oh my god, what did you paint it as?
You wore gloves over it.
I'm slaying right now.
That's not a very royal color of you.
You guys like my new high heels?
Oh my god, I do.
They're 12 fucking inches.
Shit, you're compensating for something, princess.
Definitely need that.
Are you trying to say...
My height, dude.
You know what I mean?
I'm 4'10 on a good day with good lighting.
Wait, there's fighting next to us.
Shall I place our wall somewhere?
You should put your wall...
Honestly, right here.
Just put a wall down.
I feel a little like...
It's very open, princess.
Are you sure this is a good place to be?
Princess, there's a lot of open space.
I'm a little scared.
There's a team right here.
What is open?
What do you suggest?
I don't know.
I feel like zoning is going to end on us.
Okay, princess.
There's a team right here.
I can bomb them.
I'm going to open the door.
No, I'm still healing.
Princess, princess.
You're heading straight at them, princess.
Don't fight.
Come back.
Close the door.
I closed the door on you.
I'm sorry.
I admit it.
They're fighting us.
Come back to the wall.
Oh my god.
Okay.
This went really bad.
Come to me if you can.
Oh my god.
That just went really bad somehow.
I told you, princess.
I told you that was funny.
How did that happen?
Communicate to me.
That's what I said.
I thought I was the only one out there.
I closed the door behind me.
And you were out there too.
I'm sorry.
How do you fumble that?
Oh no.
Why are you out there with me?
Why are you guys opening the door?
Just close it.
What do you mean?
It's okay.
All good.
I can craft a banner.
Where's the craft?
There's no res.
I can get the banner thing.
Yeah, but how do you res?
How would you res?
You have no gun.
The body guy died.
Oh my god.
There's a team right in front of you.
You know Doki, I think we did our job.
Yeah, we died to protect our princess.
Oh jeez.
Oh man.
I didn't get mobi.
Oh, that's under support.
I don't fucking know.
There's a res beacon right next to you, but is it worth it?
Princess, the nation needs you.
Now more than ever.
The nation needs you, princess.
You must be strong.
I got you guys, don't worry.
Princess, it's all up to you.
You gotta repopulate.
I don't think there's anyone in this building.
You gotta repopulate the country.
Oh, there's people there.
They won't see you.
They won't know.
If you crouch next to it, they won't know.
Gen, you coward.
They won't know.
Just fucking crouch next to it.
What do you think this is?
Princess Gen.
The population of your country is only one.
You gotta figure out a way.
One sec, one sec.
You need a fucking shot.
There's no...
I can't crouch.
Wait, what?
What do you mean?
You're a pro player.
I know, but I'm saying maybe I can get mobi though.
Yeah man, princess, revive us.
I'm sticking, I'm sticking, I'm sticking.
Stick it, princess, repopulate the country.
The kingdom must live on.
Come this way, come this way if you can.
I'm trying to survive.
No, princess, no.
I'm alive.
Princess, I'm watching you.
Princess, no.
I'm alive, I'm alive, I'm alive.
We're here, we're here.
Oh my god, I'm alive.
Help, come to me.
I'm trying.
We have to go up this corner.
I can't, I can't.
I'm helping, I'm covering.
I'm going to sacrifice myself for you, princess.
Don't, don't, don't.
I need you alive.
I'm sacrificing myself for you.
I'm covered.
Wait, I think we can go up to a restaurant.
No, do not come to me, princess.
Come to me.
Altair, come to me.
Oh god.
They're fighting underneath us.
I killed one.
Wait, how?
Back up, back up, back up.
Back to the restaurant, back to the fucking restaurant.
I'm hiding, I'm hiding on me.
Guys, I lived.
Doki, I need you here, god damn it.
I'm fucking coming over.
Get over here.
I gave you backup.
Altair, come to me.
All of us sit in this corner, now.
I'm dropping you grenades.
Grab all my grenades.
And my heals.
I'm grabbing all my heals.
We sit in this corner.
When you get wall, Altair, you're all towards north.
Yes, princess.
I've never seen anyone die like that before.
Let's go, baby.
Yes, princess.
We understand, princess.
Good.
Oh my god.
They won't know we're here.
They don't know.
If they shoot us, Altair, just put a Q down.
And we just sit behind it.
Okay, princess.
They're right below us.
I hear them, princess.
10 seconds.
10 seconds, beautiful.
Beautiful, beautiful.
This is a military princess right here.
Just when you get it, facing this way, right here on me.
I'm Q-ing the bastards.
Put it down, put it down.
Nice, beautiful, beautiful.
You're such a handsome man.
Oh my god, I might marry you.
Don't kill me.
What the fuck?
Don't get hit too much.
You can sit behind the middle.
You're scaring me, Doki.
We're gonna win this bloody game.
Don't take too much damage, don't die.
That's it.
Wait, I can nade them.
No, no, no.
Don't throw it.
It's gone.
I saved my grenade for you.
I have four more.
Right above us, careful.
Don't worry, I have so many nades.
It's okay.
Careful, northeast.
Right on the balcony.
We're okay, we're okay.
Oh my god, what is...
Wait.
Look good on me, good on me.
I'm okay.
Holy...
We just have to rat, Loki.
It's fine, everything is fine.
I have three cells, two batteries.
I have three cells, yeah.
Four syringes.
We have suck, it's fine.
Same.
Oh my god, I hear a rampart.
I don't feel so good, I hear a fucking rampart, Gen.
I hear...
Right below us, right below us.
Shoot this guy, shoot this guy.
He's one, he's one, he's one.
Okay, I meant to punch.
Can I punch?
You can, you can, you can.
You can, oh my god, he was one.
Replace your wall, replace your wall.
When you have it, I'll tell you.
When do you have it?
I have it now.
Replace it, put it down, put it down again.
Nice, beautiful, beautiful.
Oh god.
I'm safe here.
I'm safe here, I have one shield cell left.
Oh my god.
I'm gonna fuse out this team when they have to come in.
They're breaking our wall.
That's fine, I can put Lifeline on.
We can sit in this corner, this corner is good.
How does it go?
What?
Umm...
Q, Q, Q, Q.
You have Q?
Nice.
Nice, that saves us.
They're pushing out the shields.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh my god, kill this guy, kill this guy.
He's one, he's one, he's one.
I'm ulting, I'm ulting.
It's my fire, my fire, my fire.
Fucking hellfire right there.
I have no shields, I have no shields.
Stabilize.
I have one bat, I'm dropping you my bat.
You better pop the fuck off.
What is this?
Oh my god.
Uh oh.
We're fine, we're fine, we're fine.
Are we though?
My ult's gonna run out.
When's your ult?
My ult's gone, my ult's gone.
Use it to protect us there.
We can sit in this corner too, okay?
You guys are dying to the Q.
Yeah, I know.
Can't really do anything about it.
Come to me, come to me, come to us, come to us, come to us.
He's pushing, what the fuck?
Kill the princess, kill the princess.
Kill the princess, it's the Magi, it's the Magi.
I got one of them, but that's not the princess.
The Magi, the Magi, the Magi, the Magi.
Boost inside, boost inside.
About to finish you off.
No!
I'm okay.
I'm trying, I'm trying.
Run, Jen, run!
I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine.
We failed you!
We sacrificed ourselves for you!
Survive!
For the kingdom!
I'm good, I'm good, don't worry.
For the kingdom, Jen!
For the kingdom of rats!
Man, maybe you should have kept the bat there.
Maybe I should have.
Yeah, maybe you should have given the bat to me.
You fought so valiantly, princess!
Oh my god.
Wait, does that protect you?
Bro, whoever's playing that bat, no way.
No way.
There's no way.
No way!
No!
So close!
Oh my god.
There's no way!
I died to that!
I died to ring, but I got hit.
No, you got hit by the TV.
I got hit by defensive, that's crazy.
Oh my god, it's TimmyC.
I think Timmy...
Oh my god, I won!
No!
Oh.
Oh my god, it's Timmy!
Your team killed...
Oh my god.
That actually kills?
What?
Oh my god.
Dude, that's the princess.
The princess is trying to live right now.
Look at the bat, Maggie!
I think SakuraC won!
Wait, Timmy?
Yeah!
Oh my god, the boys.
Bro, the princess lived!
The princess lived from zone!
That is crazy.
Holy shit!
I saw the princess live!
I think this was Timmy.
I think Timmy was the one that was harassing us with her drill.
With the drill the whole time...
I didn't do it.
Oh my god.
So my wall doesn't stop that drill.
No, you have to use your Q.
You have to use your Q.
Yes, I could have T1!
I got burned through it.
Oh my god.
That's crazy.
Dude, that team is pushing us like insane.
That was insane.
Alright.
Get back to the caster.
I'll see you guys in the next game.
Oh my god.
That was Saikouno.
That was Timmy's team.
Timmy's team takes the W, bro.
The princess lived from zone alone!
I don't get it.
He wins the most unorthodox games every time.
It's unreal.
He's always good at weird shit.
By the way, Doki.
Manish is getting only one nerf now.
Oh, only one?
No, no, no.
He's getting two nerfs.
He got to pick one out of the three to remove.
Oh, okay.
What does he mean?
He's only getting one now.
Wait, what?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't ask why.
It's totally not my fault.
I'm going to go pee real quick.
We're going to leave the interview to pee?
How's it going, man?
I saw your princess.
Your princess clutched it up.
Yeah, wait.
Okay, but I did so much right before that.
Did you see that part?
The one where you couldn't climb the wall?
Oh, you did see that part?
It was bugged, I swear.
There's no way I wasn't able to climb the wall.
It just doesn't make sense.
Yeah, we were like...
My entire team was spectating that.
My entire team spectated.
I was trying really hard to climb.
I was holding spacebar.
I was holding W.
I was doing everything right.
And it just didn't climb.
But it kind of worked out, you know?
It kind of...
We won.
Where's the rest of your team?
I don't know.
They were shy.
Your team doesn't want to get interviewed by Wig and Greek.
Can we forcibly drag them in?
Yeah, you can.
Yeah, forcibly drag them in here.
Sure, sure.
Is it your call?
You want us to force them into...
You're going to have the guy who literally couldn't climb a wall and didn't see anything in the final match.
They were just like, Alright guys, climb up.
We're going to go.
And then I just... I was there.
I was trying really hard.
The guns were heavy.
Yeah, I force dragged them.
As per your order, Sykudo.
Hey, welcome to the interview, guys.
They wanted to hear everything.
Congratulations.
I got to say, unfortunately, our team cheated, actually.
How so?
Because I was the actual princess.
I didn't use my gun at all.
Thank god Timmy carried somehow.
I didn't use my gun at all in that ending.
I was just there.
I was just glad to be there.
Sykudo was the princess?
Yeah, I kind of was.
No, I didn't actually cheat.
That was a joke, obviously.
It was a joke because I died and didn't shoot.
It was a valid strategy, to be honest.
They couldn't tell who it was because people didn't shoot.
I say she 5-0.
Yeah, that was crazy.
I literally saw...
Somehow everybody died around Timmy without him doing anything.
He's got the aura.
He's Timmy.
He's him, you know?
Which was pretty insane to see.
Yeah.
Sorry, I'm back.
I apologize.
I was peeing.
Hi guys.
How'd that win feel?
It was so good.
I had no idea how we won.
I have no idea how you won either.
Bro, Timmy, you were the king at winning the most unorthodox games, I swear to god.
I should be dead to rights.
That's what I'm saying.
There are just so many games where you just win that.
It's just like a clutch gene you have.
It makes no sense to me.
It's actually phenomenal.
I think it's luck.
We'll take it, dude.
Also, Sykuno, I have Elim in my living room.
Is there anything you want me to say to him right now?
Oh my god, I thought you were going to bring up the climbing the wall thing again.
Yeah, um...
I mean...
Wait, I don't know.
I'm on the spot.
I just...
Ask him why he never hung out with me while he's in LA.
Wow.
He's listening on the living room TV right now.
He's going to hear that.
Honestly, Elim is pretty fake.
Wow.
Just kidding.
That's crazy.
That is crazy work, bro.
Dang.
Alright, Elim, I hope you heard that, bro.
He probably did.
We'll see how that goes.
Maybe.
We'll tell him anyway.
Elim called me baby and then five minutes later he walked up to another person and called them baby too.
I don't know how that feels.
Damn.
You know what he missed out on?
He just won that whole thing with no weapons.
That's crazy.
Yeah, he missed out on a Game 5 winner.
Alright, what's the game plan for Game 6 for y'all, man?
We got OG Kings Canyon.
Timmy, do you have any game plan for your squad?
I mean, it's Game 6 and you know we're known for that, so...
Who's picking up a wingman?
My game plan is that there is no game plan.
Apparently some teams are asking for buffs.
The lower tier teams.
What buffs do you guys want to give them?
No, you guys just won.
How do I not qualify as a low tier?
I couldn't climb a wall.
Yeah, but you have Timmy.
He barely balanced you out.
He's that bad?
No, I'm not saying that.
Timmy is like...
Timmy is...
That is crazy.
Alright, well, I wish you guys nothing but luck in Game 6.
Timmy, do your thing, man.
Timmy, before you go, I have a question for Timmy.
Hold on.
Thoughts on Design still being asleep?
Honestly, I can't blame him.
Because the one day...
I was on my team and one day I took a nap.
I actually went into a coma and I wasn't sure if I was going to wake up.
And Jen Spam called me.
That's a good teammate to get me up.
Wow, that's great.
He just didn't return the favor and do that back to you.
No, I called him too.
But it went to this random voicemail that I've never heard in my entire life.
I think...
Yeah, he honestly might not be sleeping.
He could be somewhere else.
I'm not too sure.
That's crazy.
Let's hope he's sleeping.
Yeah, we're going to hope he's sleeping.
100%.
Alright, well, GG's y'all.
Good luck, man.
Thanks, thanks.
I'll see you guys in like 20 minutes after we win again.
Damn!
Okay, okay.
If I ever get a kill, I might not.
No, you will.
I believe you.
Now that you've said that, you're going to do it.
Just got to avoid the walls.
Avoid the walls.
No climbing, no climbing.
Alright, GG's y'all.
Good luck.
See you guys.
Yeah?
Wait, Gerard's team is only one?
What happened?
Oh, we had two people.
Two people DC'd.
What the fuck?
No, he's back.
He's back.
Rue's back.
So it's just Bullet.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
So, maybe we should...
No, we could get...
You ready to join Tempo, Dash?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is the third not coming back?
Yeah, his PC is like...
dead.
Oh my god.
Wow, right.
Tempo, you really did that to his PC, bro.
Yeah, Tempo, your presence literally...
cried his CPU.
Wait, what happened to Timmy?
Their luck is crazy.
No, Timmy, what do you mean?
Timmy's around.
Oh, I think he's just rejoining, I'm pretty sure.
Yeah, I think so.
Hey, Timmy's back.
Yeah, he's still there.
Yeah, Dash, you should join them.
Uh, okay.
Wait, let me just...
He said, I can do it alone.
I'd win.
Oh, so...
What kind of buffs do we...
They want the other teams...
One pro would like to have...
One pro slash master would have to have two guns.
Should we give them that?
Wait, what?
I'm confused.
I mean, are we trying to...
Lulu's asking for another gun.
I don't mind that.
I feel like you have to name all the teams that you're going to allow that for.
I mean, it's Lulu's team, so that's...
FaZe Connect's team.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We'll do, like, same teams from last...
We'll do...
So, like, Dash and you, Tempo, you both get to have...
Well, yeah, you both get to have two guns.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Let's go!
I was going to ask.
Tempo, obviously.
What the fuck?
The all-new Tempo can run two guns.
I think you should write a written apology to Gerard that he has to have Tempo.
Every time!
I mean, he always has fun for what it seems like.
He's just smiling this whole time and laughing, so...
He don't give a fuck what place he gets.
He's over the vibes.
He's having a great time.
Let's see.
Should we let...
Should we buff any other teams, or should it be...
Armus, Fowl, ChibiDoki, and FaZe?
I think that's fair, right?
Because everyone else really, like, plays Apex pretty consistently.
Maybe Armus' squad you could buff.
I don't know how the Monster Lover's doing.
Armus' squad?
I don't even know.
Have they been doing well?
Armus...
Fools...
ChibiDoki seems like, what if we don't have Masters pros?
What kind of buffs can we give them?
I don't know.
There's no buff you can give.
You only give nerfs to people.
I don't know how else we can do it.
Armus, Fowl, FaZe, and Melee.
What if we...
If you're a Pred, we can make the...
The bottom 5 teams.
Wait, who are the current bottom 5?
Overall, the bottom 5 are Melee, FaZe, Fowl, Armus, and Fools.
Oh, but we already nerfed Madness.
Yeah, well maybe just give him a buff then with 2 weapons.
Okay, Madness can have Madness' team can have 2 guns.
How about that?
Madness can have 2 guns.
How about Care Package weapon for only lower teams?
That'd be good.
Oh, that's true.
If only those teams can get Care Package weapon.
Okay, great.
Madness can have 2 guns, but his other nerf still applies.
Okay, there we go.
Let's deal.
And then, what were the top ranking teams sent?
But we can nerf them a bit more.
Fowl, Yakiniku, Godgamer, and Hibernation.
Godgamer, and Hibernation.
You're pro.
You're also in there.
I'm in there?
But what did we do?
We didn't win any prizes!
Okay.
Your stats are a little inflated because of the...
Do we nerf our partner?
Okay, you're a pro player.
Okay, maybe we assign a specific gun to their pro player.
Okay.
This is all Season 0 guns.
Oh.
How about no wingman for pros?
No wingman.
Okay.
No wingman for pros.
Yes, yes, yes.
Everyone.
Yeah.
These pros are going to go crazy with the wingman.
You give a pro a wingman in this scenario, they're going to 3 tap everybody.
Unless your face connects.
Luzu can't have a wingman.
Yeah, fair, fair, fair.
There you go.
Okay, we should go to the channel, but is there a charge rifle in Season 0?
Or no?
No.
Oh, that's cool.
Alright, so what teams are this?
Oh, they got the buff?
There's no buff, I guess, really.
It's just nerfs for the pros.
Yeah, yeah, that should be good, right?
Is there anything else we can adjust?
No, you can't really buff teams more than that.
Alright, that's all we can adjust.
All the pro players are just going to be like, fuck.
He's fucking washed up.
Okay, yes.
Yes, yes.
They can have a second gun.
Yeah, their team is...
Wait, Kuro's playing at 300 ping?
That's crazy.
Alright, ggs.
Good luck.
Alright.
Hello, you're back?
Hello, I'm back.
We were deciding nerfs and buffs.
We're deciding...
Wait, can we play Caustic?
We can play Caustic, right?
We can play Caustic, yes.
Okay.
Things on Caustic.
Mr. Altair.
You're on Powerpoint or Wraith?
Doki, which one do you love?
I can...
Wait, what was the comp?
It's OG Classic, right?
OG Classic, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Caustic, Path or Wraith?
Classic, Path or Wraith.
I call Wraith.
I'll play Path.
Alright, good luck, Altair.
I call Caustic.
You're on the Caustic.
Apparently, in this OG as well, Altair, the Caustic battle doesn't break.
It doesn't break at all.
Yeah, so that's why it's OP.
Can we run two guns that we have?
Or should I play Caustic?
I don't understand.
We're on Oregon's server, so how is the server like 300 ping?
That's crazy.
I've been playing 300 ping on every game.
Yeah, I know, but how is the... Is it Oregon?
Yeah, Tempo said it's Oregon.
It must be routing me back to New York or something.
Yeah, it's re-routing it.
It's just crazy.
There's no at minus Tempo fix the ping issue.
Fix the ping issue.
That sucks though, I didn't realize.
No.
No wingman.
What?
No wingman for pros.
Were you not looking at the server?
I can't use wingman?
No, you can't.
I hate you so much.
What do you mean?
I didn't decide this.
Greek decided this.
You're such a donkey, man.
Greek was the one that said no wingman for pros.
It's not my fault.
Ken's always trying to figure out how to cheat.
I'm trying to cheat, bro.
We're going to Slum Lakes.
Anand was OP.
Oh my god, this is OG.
This feels so OG.
Alright, what was our drop?
We have scan 2, W.
Wait, do you remember where our landmark is?
Slum Lakes, right?
We're IRS, we're slumming it up.
Remember the last drop?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The game had scan everywhere.
That's crazy.
Our last game.
Hey, princess.
Yeah, did you enjoy being a princess?
I'm not a princess anymore.
You lived though, princess.
I lived, but my guards have died.
We did our job protecting you.
You were the last one standing, right?
Yeah, princess, you did your job.
That's all that matters.
I did my job, I did my job.
You lived for us.
Ignore that your bodyguard threw up.
Yeah, just one of them.
I did my best.
Throwing me under the rug.
It's okay.
I get it.
One gun, right?
One gun, yeah.
Yeah.
No, no.
We don't start with shield.
Yep, welcome to OG.
The backpack space was very limited.
Welcome to OG King's Canyon.
Oh my god, slumming it up.
Here's the...
Got my wingman.
This is it.
Oh, artillery pool.
This is very, very good for us.
Wait, why?
You smell me?
Because we have a zone.
Oh, we have a zone.
Whoa, did you not shower, Jen?
I haven't showered yet.
I need to.
Probably stinky.
Nothing wrong with being stinky.
If you're a gamer, if you're a true gamer, you gotta stink.
You know what I mean?
No.
Come on.
Ain't no way you're saying this.
You're a gamer too.
Altair's a gamer too.
Yeah, I'm not stinky.
There's nothing wrong with being stinky.
It's kind of awkward.
No, there's a lot of reasons.
Even if you're stinky, we won't judge you that much.
We'll be here for you.
Outside, I'm not stinky.
But inside, you don't want to smell me.
My mom runs away from me, bro.
No, you're still stinky.
You just let the outside wind blow your stink away.
Spread it to the world.
Yeah, you spread it to the world.
I'm sorry for saying that.
Oh my god, there's an R9!
Wait, wait, wait.
R9's the best for us.
I'm not using a wingman.
No recoil.
Okay, I'm gonna use R9.
Altair, do you have a wingman on you?
Yeah, I'll be your donkeys.
Okay, I'm gonna give you my wingman.
Wingman is an incredibly strong OG.
It's like a mini-sniper.
Just think about it like that.
I only remember that.
Yeah, it's like a mini-sniper.
Okay, I'm gonna give you my wingman.
Cause like, you need it.
Right here you go.
What does that mean?
As in like, you can actually snipe.
Oh, there's a 3x.
I'm gonna get a 3x too.
Um, I need light ammo.
If you guys find any.
Okay.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
I'll make a zipline for you guys.
Come.
I can zipline for you, Altair.
We need blue armor.
Do you see any?
Sorry, thank you princess.
Oh my gosh.
Oh,
I hear shooting already.
There's a team below me.
I need attachments for this.
Oh, people were here.
Wait, unless you guys looted this.
I looted like a little bit.
I don't have a lot of ammo.
So I need to find some more stuff to loot.
I need a backpack.
You don't even have anything on you.
You have a gun on you.
Where's your gun?
It's on me.
It's not showing up on my...
Oh yeah, it's not showing up.
That's weird.
Oh yeah, I need it.
Yeah, I need that.
Light ammo here.
Oh my gosh, I forgot how much inventory space I can get.
Oh my gosh, there's a gold loot tick.
And wow, that's so dog shit.
What was that?
I'll take that.
Oh, I found like only two shield cells.
Oh, nice.
I need that.
More light ammo, that's good.
Set up in this building.
All the traps on doors and shit.
I'm going to go crazy.
Alright, here I go.
I'll tear it.
I'm not touching any doors anymore.
I'll tear, I'll tear.
What are you trying to do?
I've sworn off doors.
Oh my god.
I need a barrel stabilizer and I'm good.
Oh, I need a barrel stabilizer and a stock now though.
Anything in here?
There's a penis kit.
There is.
More light ammo.
But Mosin had free shots back then?
Oh my god.
That was a shitty gun back then.
Found a blue armor.
Okay, I'm going to bring an armor swap here.
Wait, this place is looted so I'm a little scared.
Wait, we have blue?
Yo, we're kitted.
Oh my god.
Okay.
There's people here in front of me.
Oh, oh.
This guy can aim.
Ten cells, one battery.
Four cells.
How are you finding all these cells?
I have three bats.
I don't even have a bat.
Here you go.
I'm going to loot this building.
I'll be back.
Okay.
I want to loot a little bit too.
I want to loot this area.
There's a full team on the other side.
I'm bringing the digi.
Oh yeah, that's good.
I'm just going to use the 3x.
Fuck this.
I dropped the 1x.
Yeah, dropping the digi for it.
I'll take it.
For the Bangalore team.
I saw a Bangalore team in Champions Squad, right?
Yeah.
I'm going to cook their shit.
Are you in the barrel stabilizer?
Yeah, I do.
Okay, I'll get it.
Wouldn't it be funny if Akim walks through this gate right now?
That would be so silly.
How many traps can I have at once?
Is it a three?
I think six.
Oh, it's six?
Okay.
There's a team over here against that wall.
Yeah, four.
I can put six down, I'm pretty sure.
Okay.
Oh.
I got shot from...
Where did I get shot from?
Here?
Oh.
Katnito down.
I forgot how little backpack space you get in OG.
Bro, I know.
Bring back bloody barrel stabilizer.
My Arnon has no recoil.
This is crazy activity.
I shouldn't waste my light ammo, but it's funny.
I have 300.
Okay, I have 157, so I can borrow from you.
There you go, 40.
So you're just going to keep spamming?
Go ahead.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm going to keep spamming.
It's okay, you're a big boy.
You'll be fine.
Woohoo!
Hahaha!
3 XMR died.
It's so stupid.
Oh, they have a Wattson?
Yeah, it's not worth it now.
I want to use a wingman.
What?
Huh?
So pros aren't allowed to use wingman?
Yeah, pros aren't allowed.
Oh my god.
Because then they'll just farm the lobby with wingman.
True.
That is very true.
They'll just kill everybody.
Now we wait.
Now we are waiting.
Oh, there's Wattson.
Oh, it is.
It's OG, OG rank.
Wait, why the fuck aren't we playing Wattson?
Because...
Save our heals.
Easy.
Caustic is way better.
Caustic is so good.
I thought OG was like Wattson, Wraith, Path.
But Caustic farmed as well.
Get affected by my ultimate?
Yeah, didn't we?
Isn't the OG part where we get affected by it?
Do we?
You might get slowed.
The part about it is the barrels don't break.
That's like OP.
Oh, I see.
If we make it to endzone, I'll save a couple for endgame.
What do you think I'm trying to do here, Doki?
You think I'm not trying right here?
That's crazy comms by you.
Don't trust your teammate.
No, I trust him.
I trust my teammate.
No, no, no.
Someone clip it, please.
I'm going to save it to my gallery.
I do have a vendetta against controller players.
I was never secretive about that.
Every time I boot up Apex, I'll be like those damn controller players in my lobby.
That's Doki, right?
Why did you want me on your team then?
Every time I see a roller player, I look them in the eye and I was like, I can't believe you're here.
Look at me in the eye.
Yeah, I'm looking.
Can't believe you're here in my lobby.
That's right.
I said it.
Also, are you going to send me your sign controller?
Might as well get rid of it now.
Yeah, yeah.
Send me your sign controller.
Oh my gosh, the barrels are like green.
They're like green.
Yeah, shoot them.
One shot, killed one!
Okay, we're coming over, we're coming over.
I got the first one, good.
Make a portal for me.
Oh, sure.
This is a good portal.
We're good, we're good.
This guy has one gun.
Oh, wingman.
Bit scary.
Okay, loot this shit and go back.
Yeah, white armor.
Okay, I'm going back.
You can loot it.
Okay.
Doki, I found your portal.
I found your portal!
Jesus Christ!
What is that?
I wasn't going to say anything, but Jesus Christ, what is that?
I did say it was a great portal.
What is that?
I said it was a great portal.
I told you.
I thought it was an amazing portal.
It's good bait, you know?
If they chase after you.
See, look.
I can land in it.
Look, I'm here.
Are you still here?
Oh, there you are.
They are still here.
I'm just going to drop a PK inside.
I'll be back.
If I need it later.
They killed a team in front of me.
You're getting involved a little bit, Doki.
Yeah.
No, no, you stay there.
Just hold the building.
Yep.
They're like right here because the team died there.
I have 140 life, Doki.
What about you?
I have 152.
We're kind of low.
We'll be fine.
Are you scared?
I'm shaking.
Ever since he became a princess, you've changed.
I have one kill.
Ever since he became a princess.
Just one?
What happened to JenBurden10kills?
That's it, I'm running it down.
I'm going.
Let's go.
Altair can craft us.
Go.
Come on, Jen, go.
I'm so conflicted.
Stay there, Altair.
I don't trust Jen to be alive.
One way or another.
I think they just went up.
You can't do anything about it.
Someone's rezzing right next to us.
It's fine, you'll be fine.
Just pretend you're three people.
Pretend you're three people.
Come back.
I'm coming back.
Oh my god.
I'm down.
If they fight in this tunnel again, we come.
And we try to kill them together.
And then, Altair, you stay there.
Wait, how are you getting shot?
I think they're fighting now.
Let's go back.
We'll be fine, let's go.
They have a Bangalore, so we'll be fine.
Wait, they're fighting in front of me.
I have to push up.
They're getting pinched.
I'm nading this corner.
Grenades.
I'm going against orders.
I killed one.
I'm pushing up.
I'm with you.
We should push this.
I'm zipping.
They're rezzing.
Oh, they have Wattson.
One knocked.
They're rezzing.
I'm pushing up.
Pushing up.
There's one on me, in this corner.
What the fuck?
I don't have ammo.
I need light ammo.
There's no light, they're not running light.
No one's running light.
Oh my god, no one's running light.
What the fuck is this?
Oh no, there's light here.
How much?
170.
Go back to the building.
Alright, that's fine.
This is our land.
They did not expect the...
the...
the pincher.
They're still fighting though.
I got purple now.
Wait, did they take our land?
No, we're fine.
They took our land!
It's fine, just stay in the tunnel.
If they took our land, we're good.
We're heading over.
We hold this side.
Oh my god, our land.
How much did you pay for it?
I inherited it.
They stole it from us.
Inherited?
Classy!
I inherited it, I didn't have to pay anything.
Someone res'd on the right.
I'm heading over.
Let's see where the zone's pulling.
We're at god spot.
We're going to this little house right here.
What do you think?
I'm down.
You get skull piercer, Altair?
Okay, good.
That's the best part.
That's great.
I didn't have to pay any taxes or anything.
I got a gold barrel stabilizer.
And I have a 3x too.
Same, gold easel.
I believe they took our land like that.
As if they owned it.
Are you sure they're there?
They were there, but I don't know if they're still there.
I don't see any of my barrels.
I'm zipping up, I don't hear them.
Oh, they might move.
Yeah, they moved.
I set up the traps again, Altair.
I'm looking at the tunnel.
We're in end zone.
Then why did they move?
Why didn't they move and we're in end zone?
Oh, they're moving too.
They're moving as well.
Hit one 41.
I hit one for 10.
That's so cool.
One's hit for 90.
Hit one for 656.
Gold.
Well, that's a self-res.
Does anybody have a spare battery?
I got three, here you go.
Yeah, I had two, but I can't.
This is a little quiet.
I know.
Nobody wants to do anything.
Oh, I cracked him.
It's fine.
I have enough shields.
Oh, my nose.
Listen, let's move here.
Recharging my shields.
That portal was crazy funny though.
It's bait.
It makes them want to take it and they'll die if they take it.
It's like the biggest IQ play I've ever done.
There's a guy like right here.
Altair, why is your voice so ASMR bro?
Because he's just born like that.
It sounded like a podcaster.
For real.
He was born like that.
Welcome to the IRS podcast.
The IRS podcast.
Have you filed your taxes today?
Yeah, Jen, have you?
No.
I'm done.
I'm in somebody's site.
Wherever they are.
Someone's looking at me.
Who could blame them?
Sorry, I was fucking around.
I won't do that again.
Wait, there could be a Kraber.
Doki, you need to portal for this.
You smell me?
Yeah, yeah, sure.
You trust my portals now?
No, I do not.
Let's see.
I'm judging.
Watch this.
Yeah, you see that?
Yeah, okay.
That's a good one.
Watch this.
It hasn't come down yet.
Yeah, yeah, it works.
It's coming down now.
It's like the one that...
Oh, it's an L-Star!
Portal back!
Okay, I dropped an R9.
It has everything.
Here, take it, take it.
I have everything here.
From the tunnel?
I think it's the old one.
Oh, shit.
Don't die, don't die, don't die.
They might zip over.
They might try to zip over.
We can go to this building actually.
Anyone in this?
I think there's a team there, is there?
What is that?
I don't know.
I'm checking.
Yeah, there is.
Oh my god, he's on the door.
Jesus Christ.
He's literally on the door.
Okay, just hold the top.
They had a door.
Hey, we're breaking that door.
Okay, there's a team underneath us, alright?
Okay, I cannot fight for too long though.
I have to poke with it.
They're trying to find us.
They're nading us from the far staircase.
Oh, okay.
Altair, do you have a trap?
You can put a trap in this corner.
Yep.
I'm looking.
I'm looking here.
I hear them.
I'm going to go on the other side.
I'm going to try to kill one.
Almost cracked?
I'm being aimed at.
Oh, no, no, no.
Come back.
I see them.
They're right in the corner.
Yeah, they looked at me through the stairs.
They're super safe.
They're smart.
Not that smart.
Okay, I can't shoot anymore.
I have a hundred and something bullets.
Wait, their blood is unaltered.
They might push us.
Really?
No.
They're fighting in this building.
Do you have a digi?
I can.
I can portal.
Is it behind us?
No, digi behind.
I got it.
Careful.
Oh, shit!
It's two.
It's two people.
Five squads.
We can win this.
I'm God.
I'm going to the other side.
Lots of teams are here.
Is there a team in here?
There's no team in here.
There's a team below us.
Oh, really?
I don't see them.
Wait.
It sounded like I heard someone.
Maybe it was you guys.
Your fat ass footsteps.
I'm Wraith.
Okay, my bad.
I have the smallest hitboxes here.
Set up some traps underneath here.
There's a red portal underneath.
They're making a portal.
Okay.
I'm going to look at the other side.
I can't poke for too long.
I cracked one.
Yeah, he's right here.
They all took it.
Cracked one.
Careful.
One took a back.
Yeah, they're right here.
I can't poke anymore.
I have limited ammo.
You can swap guns.
I want to keep my L-Star.
Yeah, the L-Star is really strong.
It's actually good in OG.
OG?
I don't remember.
Yeah, OG L-Star is crazy.
It's basically like an R-9, but stronger.
Oh, 20 flesh.
It's fine.
I'm going to make sure we don't get flanked.
Watch out for the team over here.
Yeah,
they're just literally right here.
I don't think they're going to push.
They're just chilling down there.
I can't really poke though.
They have 190 bullets.
What's your gun?
I have 120.
You can shoot these guys.
This is your job.
I'm going to make sure this team doesn't flank us.
Yo, chill man.
Oh, he saw the hole.
He saw the hole.
He knew it was a goal right there.
Guys, look at this.
Yeah?
I'm looking at it.
In the open.
Last two teams.
There's a team below us and a team far side.
Yeah, so there's a team right here below us.
Later on, we zip up to this high ground.
I made a zip here.
You have to save Caustico out there for a team or end zone.
Basically.
This team has to leave.
This team might shoot us.
Yeah, they have to leave as well.
They don't have Pathfinder.
They have Gibby, Wattson and Wraith.
So they don't even have height.
So we can definitely take the height.
I love OG Apex.
This is where I thrive.
I got Pred on this season.
If they don't have Wattson, I have several names.
I have two names.
We just have to survive on top.
That's basically it.
Probably play this side.
On my ping.
It looks like the most spacious.
The only issue is that they do have a Wattson.
We just have to play near their Wattson so we can use their ult.
Oh, Altair.
Don't do that.
I was just putting some gas traps.
Hey!
I will hit you off.
You are a new princess.
Wait, someone's on height?
No, they shot from below.
Make sure they don't try to flank us here.
I'll tell you when to zip.
Okay, zip now.
Come to me.
Shoot them at the bubble.
Come this side.
On me.
And when this bubble runs out, we shoot them.
I'm syringing real fast.
It's going to run soon.
Don't drop down.
Shoot this guy.
I'm going to tank this by batting.
Batting us.
I got a heal.
I have no heal.
I need bats.
The last two teams are going to fight.
I'm just tanking this.
That's the best fermite in the world.
Oh my god.
Do you guys have cells or anything?
I need heals.
I have nothing.
I have shield cells.
That's my last one.
Any bats, Altair?
Nope.
I only have medkits.
They have caustic ult.
Shoot down from here.
This is one guy.
I don't have shields anymore.
I hit him.
He's armor stopping.
Altair, just wait.
What's in there?
Another team.
Ult this way.
Ult.
Afterwards.
I didn't use it.
I need light.
I don't.
I just have my...
We just have to put another gen down.
We can caustic ult these guys.
We have to focus this team on the left.
At best, I can play...
Oh my god.
It's fine.
I'll just...
We're still in zone.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I can play Q and I'll play behind this rat.
I think I can do that.
I'm going to play behind this rat.
I'm going to zip bounce in end zone.
Okay.
The solo is going to grief them.
And you guys just go crazy on the left team.
Okay?
We have to drop.
They're still in.
I'm burning them.
Shoot the other team.
Crack.
I got one.
Last guy.
It's the wraith.
I got the armor swap.
Wait, where are they?
Behind.
Shield.
Let's go.
Oh my god.
I'm not going to lie.
Let's go.
It hit the corner.
I'm sorry.
It scares me, bro.
It goes...
It's so fast.
Oh my god.
It was so fast.
At least we get to stay on top.
That's crazy.
Oh my god.
I get to keep.
This is the season where...
The IRS never fails.
This is the season where I got top 500.
Let's go.
This is the IRS.
We'll always get you at the end.
The IRS will always get you.
We'll always get you.
Alright.
Let's get interviewed, guys.
Let's all go in.
Hey, guys.
Is this rigged?
What do you mean?
It's rigged.
This is my season.
A fairy tale ending for a princess.
I know Doki told Tempa to put the zone right there.
I heard about it.
I was like, this is where the zone is going to end, guys.
We got to stay here.
Dude, that was so fun.
The end game was perfect for y'all, man.
Actually perfect.
Regis just scared me with that costume.
I tried to be as precise as possible for my teammates.
Because I wanted to win that badly.
And yet my hubris.
My hubris and my bravado.
I'm sorry.
I threw.
You did great, Altair.
Your canisters were great.
You did fantastic, brother.
Dude, I was like, oh my god.
Save this after the bubble runs out.
I'm like, wait, what?
You literally looked across.
You're like, no, there's no way.
That's what you said.
You're like, there's no way.
The important thing is, nobody saw, right?
I didn't see that.
Don't worry.
I've never seen that.
No one's watching my shit.
You're good, bro.
No, no.
Of course not.
We should do more of this.
No cap.
Yeah, that's fun.
Definitely we learned a lot about balancing wise, too.
Regarding other teams.
Definitely learned a lot from my very first custom.
Did you guys enjoy my first custom?
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What do you mean, yeah, yeah, yeah?
I didn't know if you were asking me or your chat.
No, I'm asking you guys.
Yes, the cast is.
Have fun casting this.
Oh, absolutely.
What the fuck?
Yeah, I'd watch a thousand more of these.
Are you kidding me?
Which one was the most fun game mode, though?
Or map, in your guys' opinion?
What about for you guys, playing wise?
What do you think?
I think hide and seek was the best one.
Yeah, that's fair.
I think watching wise...
I don't know.
Mine was protect the princess.
Protect the princess was really good in the punching.
Yeah, I'm with dash.
I think the punching one was really good, for sure.
But this one was unique, in my opinion.
Yeah, it was.
Yeah, I also thought that people were not really gonna stick with the actual game plan, and they lowkey did.
I thought people were gonna 100% just not stick to the rules.
And everyone did.
It was really fun.
Good time.
Thank you.
There's definitely a lot of stuff I could improve on for it, but I do hope a lot of people have fun.
That's all I want.
Also, Wig, would you like to talk to your number one biggest fan that's in this custom right now?
I asked him to come in.
Also, Tempo, do you tell them that it's over?
Who took the W in the whole thing?
Was that counted for, or no?
No, it was more so individual games.
Gotcha.
I was curious if those were two things.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hi!
GG, guys!
GG!
RPR, how we feeling, bud?
Good, I had fun, man.
Yeah?
Had a good time?
Yeah, we got a bunch of kills all the time.
Dude, every game, y'all were low-key killing.
I couldn't believe you guys survived that last reset in the last game.
That was crazy work.
Yeah!
Dude, Tuna snapped.
That was fucking crazy.
Thank you, thank you!
Are you breakfast?
Stop it, stop it.
I'm lunch, okay?
No, no, no, no, no.
Lunch is crazy.
She's going to eat lunch.
Eat lunch.
She's gonna eat lunch.
What's for lunch?
Lunch...
Onigiri.
Oh!
Fuck!
I want that shit so bad.
I mean, you're gonna be in Japan soon.
Oh my god, wait.
You're coming, right?
Rig, of course.
He's fucking casting!
It's my first time meeting you, I think, right?
Oh my god, wait.
This is gonna be our first time meeting.
Yeah, it is.
That is crazy.
You gonna hang out with me?
Yeah, of course.
RPR, you gonna hang out with me?
I'm gonna kiss you in your big mouth.
What about me, dad?
What the fuck?
That's the team chemistry we see in BLGS, huh?
That's crazy.
Wait, what?
Excuse me?
That's the chemistry we see.
That's what his tournament is called.
His tournament is called BLGS Boy Love Global Series.
Yeah, we support that shit, obviously.
Hello?
That's the whole point of it.
Express your love with your boys.
I saw you at the Apex Asia Festival.
Wait, did you not go to that?
Nah, I couldn't.
No visa, man.
Are Quna and QP potentially going to that?
For now.
I don't think they can.
It's gonna happen.
Are QP and Tsuna going to the Sapporo tournament?
Maybe.
I want to go.
He wants to.
I do.
Watch party.
He wants to.
Watch party, okay.
We'll watch.
Yeah.
I am.
QP, do you have fun?
Potentially, when the Nice Wave streams, like B-stream or anything, Shima wants to collab or anything with it?
Yeah.
That would be cool.
Yeah, online.
Collab?
B-stream?
Yeah, B-stream collab with QP.
I'm down.
What the fuck?
I asked you for a B-stream collab.
You never gave it to me.
Oh, shit.
You are not Kaminari QP.
QP is not mean to me, bro.
Has QP ever mentioned how washed I am every 20 seconds in a ranked session?
Has QP ever called me out in front of 100,000 people?
Oh, my God.
I'm foaming a lot today, bro.
I'm getting drenched out here.
I've dug myself in so many holes tonight.
It's unbelievable, dude.
I got yelled at by the Catalyst voice actor.
I'm getting robbed out here.
Are you talking to me?
No, I don't shit talk to you ever, man.
RPR, I shit talk to you to make myself feel better.
You know what I'm saying?
You put me down so you can put yourself up?
Yeah, man.
It's because I love you.
You get it.
Yeah, you get it, bro.
Oh, man.
Do you have anything to say to your biggest fan?
No, QP, I love you, dude.
Keep doing what you're doing.
Yeah, I love you, too.
I love you, dude.
You're so fucking awesome, man.
You guys are awesome.
I want to give a huge shout out to every VTuber that we've met so far.
Specifically me, that I've interacted with.
Whether you're from Japan, like NA.
They're all so fucking cool.
VTubers are such rad people.
They're such accepting people as well.
I just wish more people had that mental.
Let people be themselves and just have a good time and pursue their dreams no matter what.
I absolutely love it, dude.
If I didn't show my face anywhere already, I'd probably be a VTuber right now.
What VTuber would you be, Wig?
I'd probably make myself a really jacked dude with some big boobies.
Wait, do you want to translate what Wig said to the girls?
I'd probably put a tail on it.
Wig, Dash, tell them what his VTuber model looks like.
I'd probably be a VTuber and...
What was it?
What kind of a big boobie?
Big boobie!
I know!
At least they're on board with it.
At least they're into it.
What's gonna attract hella people, Naswig?
I mean, listen.
Get some cat ears on there.
That's the vibe.
That's just the vibe I'd be rocking.
100%.
Greek, would you?
He's like, I'm done.
I'm back.
Greek, what would your VTuber model look like, Greek?
I'd probably make it like a Greek god.
You know what my model's gonna be?
Minecraft Steve.
Minecraft Steve!
I'm built like you.
Gigachat you, bro.
Anime Minecraft Steve.
That's crazy.
Dude, that was so fun.
Doki, thank you so much.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Thank you, everybody.
Thank y'all.
Love you guys so much.
GG's.
GG's, everyone.
The next Yakiniku is on me, bro.
Alright, deal, bro.
Yakiniku!
That's her, baby.
Deal, deal, deal.
I love y'all, man.
GG's.
GG's, everyone.
Thank you all for coming.
I really appreciate it, guys.
Thank you.
Thank you, everybody.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
Yeah, IRS gets you in the end.
Can't avoid it.
IRS always gets you.
They always get you.
Alright, GG's, guys.
Thank you again for helping out everybody.
Yeah, of course.
Thanks for having us.
We appreciate it.
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
I'm gonna talk to you in my chat.
I'll see you, guys.
Thanks, Altair, for being on my team.
And thanks, Temple, for holding the fort down while I played the game.
Okay, we're back.
Congratulations on an amazing event.
Thank you.
Heads up.
So everyone that got second was a different team.
So we're all good there.
Every team that won money was also a different team.
Okay.
We're good there.
And then we have coins for the third place teams.
Yeah.
And then I've got everyone else down for So anyone who didn't win anything will also get coins.
So that is all good to go.
I'll start sending All right.
Cool.
Yeah, no problem.
Yeah, just talk to me after the stream and then we'll discuss about everything else.
All right.
Oh, hey, Jen.
Hey, welcome back.
We were just about to call it here.
Thank you for joining my team, Jen.
Thank you.
Thank you for the invite.
You're the one that made me play.
Yeah, I know.
You were not going to join unless it was on my team.
I know.
Okay, were you going to get someone else though?
Or you heard this and then got me?
Okay.
Or did you actually want me on your team?
No, you were definitely planning.
No, no, no.
You're dodging the question.
Did you actually want me on your team or not?
No, of course.
I requested you.
Okay.
That's why I told Tempo.
Because when you said no, I told Tempo.
Because I was like, Tempo, I want Jen.
And then you were like...
You want me to say what he said?
I'll call you.
I'll say the entire chat log.
You said, I'm still in Australia.
I can't play West Coast Ping.
And I was like, doesn't he play Rank in West Coast?
And Tempo was like, yeah, that's a cop-out answer.
So I was like, tell Jen that's going to be on my team.
And then you instantly said yes after that.
I'm a bad responder.
When I saw that, I instantly responded.
Yeah, exactly.
That's fucking right.
Because last time was hella fun.
Yeah, the one melee match that we had.
You mean the one game we had?
Was it only one game?
Yeah, we had one game.
No, it was Random Royale.
And it was one game.
It was hella fun though.
It was with the girl too.
I forgot her name.
I forgot her name too.
But thanks for the invite.
I'm going to take a shower now.
Because I stink!
And we've got to dub the weapons with the prize.
Tempo is going to DM us about it.
Okay.
GG's.
Have a good day.
GG's Dash.
Thanks for translating for everybody.
I really appreciate it.
Thank you man.
GG's.
Alright guys.
That was a crazy event.
I had a lot to learn.
I definitely had a lot to learn for it because I did feel really bad for the teams that weren't super stacked.
I tried my best to steer for buffs and nerfs.
I do hope that even the teams that weren't super stacked still had a okay time.
I definitely had a lot to learn regarding it.
Definitely would improve so much.
I'm going to personally apologize to some of the teams.
I know that it might have been really tough especially on teams that might not be incredibly stacked versus others.
But I do hope that overall everybody had a lot of fun.
Everybody enjoyed it.
It was really unfortunate that the ping was really high.
Tempo said he tried to put it in Oregon.
I was confused why it was at 300 ping.
I really hoped that we could figure out that issue.
I did want it to be APAC and NA together because of ALGS and everything.
I did hope that as a first event we had a lot to learn and I hope that a lot of people still had a lot of fun watching for the first event and playing.
Thank you everybody for watching.
I'm going to have another post-event stream to explain more about the whole thing process.
I'm just glad it was over.
I had a great time playing with Altair and Jen.
I had a lot of fun time interacting with the casters, interacting with different people, VTubers and everything.
Definitely was a great experience.
I cried a lot organizing this because it was done by me, Tempo and Dash.
Us three, we worked incredibly hard putting all this together.
A huge shout out to EA for sponsoring the prize pool.
Last Minute and Gamersups for donating medals and enamel pins for all the participants.
If you want to support me, please order from the Gamersup collection because it does help us a lot.
It helps my relationship with Gamersups.
Hire Tempo for those who are part of an org.
Hire this man.
He has done so much.
He has coordinated the server while I was playing the video game.
If anybody who's part of an org is looking for a manager, he is that guy.
He's single too, I guess.
Ladies and men, he's single.
Definitely a lot to learn.
I just hope overall it was a fun event to watch overall.
I'm happy that I was able to let QP interact with Wig.
I noticed that QP was a huge fan of Wig so I asked if she really wanted to talk to him because I know that team really wanted to win to be able to talk to Wig.
I figured I'll use my interview to give QP's team a chance to interact with him.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry daddy's hunky.
Don't worry.
I'll get you food soon.
Anyway guys, I will have a post after event chatting stream in an hour.
Thank you everybody.
Actually I'll make it now.
I'll make the waiting room now.
Is there a thumbnail I could use?
To talk more about.
I need you guys to know I cried a lot.
Every day I cried trying to do this custom.
I was not joking when I said for this custom I was mostly crying trying to get all of this figured out every day.
I always had some fire to fix and it was crazy.
There was a lot of last minute changes and everything.
I just really do hope people in the end still had a decent time.
I'll talk more about it at the post event.
What do I name this?
Let me make the waiting room guys.
Thank you guys.
I really appreciate it.
I'm going to make the waiting room real quick.
I don't even remember.
Dad, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I just need to make a waiting room so I can read myself.
I can read myself.
Apex custom afterparty.
Guys, I need a thumbnail.
What do I use?
What do I use for my thumbnail?
I don't have a thumbnail.
This is...
I'll just use this.
I'll use the credit slide.
Also, a huge shout out.
I don't know if you guys noticed, but I had a new overlay.
And...
Oh my gosh.
I need to get the name.
And I want to say Artemis was the one that made the old and the new Apex overlay.
I forgot to credit her when she made the first overlay.
So Artemis did the new and old Apex overlay.
So huge shout out to her.
I think when I got the old overlay, I had to go through a lot of other stuff.
So I'm sorry.
But I did it.
I'm so sorry.
I really love it.
I love the Apex overlay.
You did.
It's okay.
It's over.
Okay.
Doki Bird Apex Oversight Custom Lots to improve on.
It's over.
What do I call it?
What do I title it, guys?
What should I title it, chat?
I don't know what to title it.
What should my title be for the after party?
I cried a lot.
Yes!
Organizing it.
There we go.
That's gonna be the title.
I cried a lot organizing it.
It's fine.
I'm free.
I'm free now.
That's my title.
Alright.
I'll put it at 1115 and I'll rate it into it.
But thank you guys.
I'll talk more about it but thank you to all the people who joined.
Thank you for my teammates.
Thank you for the casters.
The fact that Wig and Greek were willing to do it for free because usually casters are paid and I asked if they want to be paid and they're like, no, no we will do it for free and I really appreciate it.
Wig had almost backed out halfway through because he had an important hangout session today and I said, it's your choice.
I don't want to force you to do it.
He's like, no, you're my homie.
I'm gonna stick it all the way to the end and I really appreciate it for Greek and Wig for saying that.
Like I said, thank you to everybody that was part of it and I hope that I can improve it more in the future because I have a lot to learn.
Definitely a lot to learn regarding this.
I really appreciate it.
Anyway guys, I'm gonna rate into that and then we'll have more of a longer talk.
Thank you everybody for watching.
As always, everyone stay hydrated, posture check, get up and move around to get that blood flowing and if you stay up for me, head to bed cause you deserve it.
I'll see you guys next time everybody.
Bye guys!
Bye!