Hellooo everybody!
Hello, hello!
They couldn't hear you because I had Discord muted by the way, now they can.
Hello guys!
So first off...
At first, I was waiting for Gumi...
You didn't download the game!
I said at first!
You didn't let me finish the sentence!
It's okay.
Anyway, at first...
I was waiting for Gumi before I got really interrupted.
Anyway, and then...
And then I realized I didn't install the game.
I thought she would take a little longer.
So I can use that as an excuse for a bit longer.
I told you 10 minutes and I joined at 10 minutes.
No, no, no, no.
You... okay.
No, no, no.
Wait, you did.
I misremembered.
I thought you said 15 minutes.
So I thought... It doesn't matter!
I apparently needed 20 minutes.
To install 44 gigabytes, by the way.
Holy shit, why is this game 44 gigabytes?
Why is this game so fucking huge?
We literally talked about how it's 15 hours long.
Yeah, but there's some games that aren't that long that isn't 44 gigabytes.
It's a fucking long game.
It's a huge game.
But anyway, it took me 20 minutes to install and it takes 2.
We were talking earlier on.
We were talking about...
How we don't want this child.
Because in Gumi's words...
In Gumi's words...
She thinks our kid's ugly.
I never said that!
Then why don't you want this child?
What the hell?
I don't want...
You said the child's ugly!
Dude, the child who wants cereal and cereal is $8!
You didn't even know it was $8 until I told you it was $8!
You were the one who wanted the child beforehand!
You can't buy the cereal while looking at the price.
This is why we're getting a divorce.
You don't look at prices.
No, it's just I don't buy cereal.
I look at prices.
I just don't eat cereal.
Yeah, then why did you buy cereal for a child?
I'll buy it if she wants it because I'm a good parent.
But if she...
I don't want her!
Okay, all of us say a good parent wouldn't say I don't want her.
Like...
That's...
That is...
Bro...
Are you really going to say you're a good parent after that?
You're winning this case.
You can have her.
Hey, you can have her.
I mean...
No, no, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You're trying to purposely be a bad mom so the court wouldn't give you the child.
That's fucked up.
You wanted the child, not me.
Wait.
Who's playing husband?
Who's playing wife?
I'm playing husband.
Okay.
Look at us.
Who's going to be playing the husband if you let me?
It's not you.
I'm pretty sure you don't have a big dick.
I'm sending you a photo of...
I'm sending you a photo of mine too?
Hey guys.
Do you guys want to see the picture?
Hold on.
Discord.
Upload a file.
Hey guys.
Do you guys want to see the picture?
I'm going to send her.
Alright.
I'm going to need this.
I'm sending you this.
I am not sending that to chat.
But...
Wait.
I am not...
I think mine is bigger.
Mine is bigger but yours is faster.
Yours is attached.
Mine is part of the body.
It is not part of the body.
That's a rat.
Guys.
This is part of the body.
This is...
It's a fucking rat.
Don't say that about him.
He gets sensitive.
I know you are working through this.
I get sensitive.
He gets sensitive.
Don't say that.
He's going to retract.
He's going to shrivel up.
He's going to shrivel up now.
You hurt his feelings.
You're gonna hurt his feelings!
Good.
Mine is bigger than if it shrivels up.
Yours isn't real!
It's not biologic.
Biological.
Hey, if I glue it on, if I glue it on somehow, it's gonna be real.
It's not biological!
It's made of plastic!
Okay, for those of you guys who really wanna know...
Okay, Gumiho, why don't you explain what photo you sent me?
I sent her Dikachu!
Can you say that again?
Can you elaborate?
I, V.
Gumiho, sent Doki Bird Dikachu.
Can you elaborate what that is?
It is a Pikachu with a huge strap on.
Okay.
By the way, guys, this is one of her favorite pictures that she has in her folder.
I have this photo for like, seven years!
And that helps my- That does not defend you!
That literally helps my case!
She has this photo!
I've seen this photo so many times!
Because she loves it!
She loves this photo so much!
We've been friends for more than eight years now!
And I have- I've seen Dikachu for a while now!
It is so good!
It's such a good photo!
It's so good!
Alright.
Okay, apparently my sound guy was like, you gotta turn Gumi down a little bit.
Sound guy?
Okay.
How about- How about now?
Alright, anyway guys.
This is gonna be like, the true friendship test between Gumi and I.
Because we've been friends for more than eight- Gumi, you know you're not gonna be- You're gonna be screaming in like- If I turn you up right now because you talk like that, you're gonna be screaming in the next like, ten minutes.
Yeah...
Alright, so...
By the way, later on apparently- That's me!
I was not ready you son of a bitch!
That's me- It's a cutscene!
You don't have to be ready!
I love cutscenes!
No you don't!
Okay, I don't.
I was like, don't search Dikachu in Google.
Yes, if there's a dick in front of Dikachu, don't search it.
I know, I've gotta work overtime.
Well you're British?
That is you.
That is so you.
You're British too!
No I'm not!
I can't do any accents!
Oh fuck, you're right!
Oh my god, our child is- Is she okay?
What?
What is she doing?
Why is she watching us?
Dude, that was me!
That was me in fourth grade!
Did I tell you the story?
In fourth grade?
Mhm, when I was a kid.
Yeah?
I got a bad report card, so my family told me I wasn't allowed to be in a room with any working electronics so I was locked in a dark room basically.
And I played with clay.
Well not even lights?
Well the lights were allowed to be on, but like I played, like- Get out, get out, that- Wait, I can't Oh, get out.
Wait, you husband.
Anyways, I played with clay the entire summer and I think that's what like broke me mentally.
Wait, that was your breaking point?
Yeah, no, I used to be like the stereotypical like quiet girl in school.
Yeah.
But then um- There's no way you were like that.
Playing with clay and talking to clay all summer.
Did they have a name?
Does he- Does he have a name?
No, I made like different clay monsters.
I made them evolve into Pokemon.
They were my OCs, if you will.
Uh, Rose.
We know your original characters do not steal.
You know we love you.
Your mom doesn't love you, apparently.
That means that- Okay.
Um, your dad actually doesn't want you.
Neither of us wants you.
Uh, we're trying to say we're sending you away to Harry Styles.
Harry Styles?
Where the fuck is Harry Styles?
We're sending you to Harry Styles.
Yeah, but where is Harry Styles as a location?
Oh shit, you know Harry Styles?
Wait, what the fuck is that bird thing on her poster?
Who- Bro, she's so spoiled!
What bird thing?
Like that post- The dragon?
Yeah, no.
Bro, this girl is so spoiled.
This girl has a room that's like twice as big as my room.
Oh fuck!
She lives in a fucking barn?
I would- woah!
No, it's just- that's not a barn.
It's like when suburban areas have those- oh no, this is a farm.
It's a different body, this is a farm.
I saw the milk cat.
I was gonna say.
What the fuck, Dr. Hakeem?
But where did she get her British- oh, her mom.
Okay, I was gonna say, where did the girl- little girl get this British accent?
That shows I take better care of her because she took after my accent.
Yeah, because someone has to work and make money for this family!
I'm a doctor!
I'm literally a doctor!
You don't know- we don't know that.
For real.
You could be pretending- you could just- Say you're a doctor, and then like, just go out to the bar or some shit.
That seems like a goomy thing to do.
Honey, I have to go to work now.
It's 9pm.
Yeah, it was an emergency call.
Yeah, the horses need help.
I'm a horse doctor, by the way.
You said you were a chicken doctor yesterday!
Girl, I- call me Mr. Worldwide.
I'd be all over the world and fixin' everything.
Cody!
I'm trying to sleep!
Shut up!
That's us.
Does that mean we can't die now that we're dolls?
Maybe.
Yo, the little girl's pretty impressive.
How the fuck did she make a doll with like, puppet- With like, crochet and wood?
Did she like, carve that herself?
This looks handmade.
Yeah.
Oh, she's pretty talented.
That's our child.
Dude, our place is a mess.
No wonder I'm divorcing you.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It was my fault that the barn's not clean enough.
You literally say you work in the farm and at the barn.
No, no, no, no, no.
I say I work.
I didn't say I clean the barn.
What the fuck?
Can't keep your workplace clean.
Dude, this guy makes me uncomfortable.
The book of love.
Dude, he has a butt chin.
Oh my god, he does.
Oh, is that his lip?
Oh my god, you did jump.
Killing myself in game.
Oh shit, we can't die!
We can't die!
Oh my god.
He's creepy.
I would never want to talk to this guy.
Hey!
This could be our third husband.
Third?
This everyone is omen from Melon, obviously.
Wait a minute.
Third?
Plus, I promised your daughter to fix your marriage.
How the fuck do you promise our daughter anything?
Why would you try?
You've been talking to her all day.
Hey, it's Rose!
Wait.
Dude, he had a creepy ass old man flip-top on her.
Wait a minute.
Excuse me, sir.
But why are you talking to our daughter?
What?
This is me.
I'm left.
Okay, X is... we're using controller, right?
Well, let's find a way.
Alright, we gotta leave.
Okay, when you said you're left, I'm left.
So I guess it's just like...
I'm left.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think so, yeah.
Alright, we gotta turn on this lever.
Oh my god, it's like McGee.
Be a deer.
Be a deer and help me turn on this lever.
I don't think that you're talking to me, man.
Hey, man!
What's going on here?
Goomy.
How do I punch?
Turn on this lever.
Whoa.
Ooh.
Whoa, Meg.
Ew.
Meg, uh, they're alive.
What is going on here?
I have no clue.
But whatever's going on, we can't lower that staircase without those fuses.
But... those fuses?
They just... they just ran away.
I mean, did you see them with their little fuse legs?
We'll worry about that later.
Let's just bring them back.
Wait, we have to bring them back?
Then what's the point of like...
Okay, do we work... oh wait.
Oh, no.
It's just two.
We already got two of them.
That's the easiest puzzles ever.
Yep.
Last one.
This is the third one.
Yeah, but do we have to do it together?
Yeah, we don't even have to do this together.
Only one of us has to do this.
Same here.
Okay, A... okay, A, B.
Where the fuck...
Oh, it teaches us the controls.
It's like Mega Man.
Tomorrow, we'll be Mega Man.
You know what?
I don't even need to do this.
You can do this yourself.
I'll just wait here.
Okay.
I don't like the sound of that.
Girl, I literally need... look at this shit.
Oh shit, okay.
I didn't know at first.
I was like... it was like one guy.
Come on, you're strong enough for that.
You don't need me.
Come on, what happened to all the horses?
Girl, I'm not carrying them.
What happened to all the horses?
I'm just fixing them.
Yeah, but don't you have to like, you know, like...
What the fuck is that sound?
Do you hear that?
What is that?
I think it was the door.
No, there was something.
There was a little grumble sound.
Is it one of your horses?
This is why they're divorced?
Look, that's why we're trying to get divorced right now.
What the fuck?
Wait, toggle sprint.
Oh, okay.
We just gotta press that.
Oh.
Wait, how do we get there?
Oh, there's a wood... there's a wood over here.
There's a wood over here.
There's a wood over there.
Alright.
Let's do this together.
Look at that.
See?
Look at this teamwork.
And then we jump...
Wait.
Oh shit, I'm dead.
Wait, what?
Oh, okay.
This is why you're the doctor.
And I'm the farm boy.
Yeah.
This is... this is why you do all the thinking for us here.
I'm like...
Sorry.
I'm like the... Oh, what the fuck?
X?
Yeah, that's what I said.
I'm like the... I'm like the... the arm here.
I'm the muscle.
You're like the arm here?
Wait, how did you get there?
Wait, how do I...
This way.
I'm the muscle.
Whoa.
I think this powers up the soul.
What do you do?
Let's check it out.
What?
Oh, okay.
I did it.
You're welcome, sweetie.
Ew.
Hey, I think we have to do something about this.
What do you mean ew?
We're married.
What do you mean?
Not for long.
I mean, our daughter's trying to fix our relationship right now.
What, you don't want your daughter to fix her relationship?
I'll throw this shit off the cliff.
Do it.
Do it, pussy.
You won't.
Do it.
Yeah, that's fucking right.
What the fuck is that?
Do you see that shit?
What?
See what?
It's looking at us.
What is?
On top of the bucket.
Look.
Where is she?
Where?
On the bucket.
Look.
Where?
I think you're going crazy.
Just ignore the glowing eye.
I think... yeah.
Yeah, just ignore the glowing eye.
Bye-bye.
Oh, my head's too big?
Give me a sec.
Sorry.
It's where I startle all my brain.
Give me a sec.
Apparently, my head is too big.
That was a cool joke, man.
Okay.
What do you mean joke?
What do you mean joke, huh?
Okay.
There's a reason why I'm the doctor.
Oh, perfect.
Yeah.
Are you trying to say people who work in the barn are stupid?
Is that what you're trying to say?
No.
I'm just saying I'm smarter than you and my brain's bigger.
I don't know.
Look at the head size.
Well, what kind of brain can be stored in that tiny head of yours?
Girl, sometimes I'll be hearing you shake your head and it sounds like a baby rattle.
There she is.
No.
Rose, darling.
Dude, get this guy away from our kid.
Yeah, get out of the way.
I need to go and talk to my daughter.
Your daughter?
Oh, you talk like you own her.
Oh, whoa.
Whoa.
We don't own people anymore.
It's 2024.
Hey, explain Pal World.
Explain Pal World.
They're not people.
Oh, except for those people.
You can catch humans.
Yeah.
Why do I recognize your voice?
What the fuck?
What?
No.
We've never met.
Sorry.
Looks a bit like a vacuum cleaner.
Oh, yeah.
Because it is your vacuum cleaner.
Is that a vacuum cleaner?
My vacuum?
It's not my job.
Dude, imagine putting something in a vacuum.
You know, the guy who suck up all kinds of crap in your stomach.
Oh, no.
That's...
That's you.
You've ruined my bowels with all that crap.
That's your purpose, though.
What are you sucking up dust?
That was it?
Yeah.
Whoa!
No!
God!
Look, there it is!
Is that dirt?
You call that dust?
Well, I mean, you know, some of it...
That's why it broke down.
It was your fault.
It's a vacuum cleaner!
No!
Fix me!
Thank you.
Instead, you put me away from life in here!
Yup.
Look at what you fucking did!
We got consumed.
Oh god, I hate throw up.
That's a lie.
You have two emotes dedicated to it.
I should have never made that bet with you.
We got bored.
Eww!
Oh god, please just take us to the math part.
That is our strong point!
We're collabing right now!
I don't like that he's humping the air.
You saw that?
Look at him!
Wait, did he flex his hips at us?
Yeah, he did.
I think we're getting closer because of our hate of this guy.
Yeah, I think he is fixing our marriage.
Yeah, look!
It is fixable!
What if we both just go separate ways?
Do we really have to?
Yeah!
We just walk away from each other.
What if we just decide to stay dolls forever?
Yeah, yeah.
What if we just decide that?
What the fuck?
What the fuck is that music?
That's bad.
Bad water.
Hey, have you ever thought about jumping?
There's a fucking eyeball!
Have you ever thought about jumping?
Alright, I'll race you to the finish line!
Sorry, I said press G.
I'm up.
I'm already gone!
What the fuck?
How do we do this?
It's not this way.
It's not that way.
It's the other way.
Oh, wait, you have to move it!
You have to move it!
Okay.
Get inside!
You bitch!
You fucking bitch!
This is exactly why we're getting a divorce!
I hope we stay dolls forever!
I hope we stay dolls forever and get eaten by a fucking cat!
What the fuck!
That's taking right!
I said it!
I fucking said it!
What are you gonna do about it?
Oh shit, you're a dog!
I hope... what the fuck?
I hope you get shit off by a bird.
Whoa!
Hey, I'll wait for you.
Wait, why does it have a thingy over there too?
Oh nice, okay I have to...
do this.
What does that do?
I don't know.
Alright!
The current has reversed!
Oh, it reversed!
So you have to...
So you have to do the thing on the other side.
Okay, no.
Like, on the other side, you pick it up.
And then... yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then you put it up.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, see?
You're gonna let me tell you what to do.
Man moment.
See, I don't miss the hole.
Cause I'm not a man.
It was one time!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That was kinda fun actually.
Oh shit, what the fuck is this?
Get in.
You bitch!
My hand slipped!
You fucker!
Oh, oh, oh!
Woah!
I'm gonna punch you!
Alright, you're good.
Don't worry, I'll help you.
Woah, woah, woah!
No!
What the fuck is this?
Do it.
Just press the button!
There you go.
See?
Look at that.
I sac- Go to the next one, you bitch!
Oh, whoops.
Sorry.
Husband moment.
Go to the next one!
I'm trying!
I am!
I did the thing!
Alright.
Look at me go.
This is why I'm first.
How long is this freaking vacuum?
I don't know.
It's pretty long.
Woah!
Wait, am I gonna make it?
I think I made it.
I made it.
See, look, I didn't miss the hole.
I didn't miss the hole this time.
Yeah, everyone gets lucky once in a while.
This is why we only have one kid.
Thank god.
It happens.
Thank god we only traumatized one child.
It's alright.
Only one kid will have to pay for therapy.
I'm not paying for it.
She's gonna pay for it herself.
What the fuck?
Okay, I'm dead.
What happened to you?
I don't know.
Someone was trying to jump and I thought she was doing the right thing.
Oh!
Oh, wow.
You couldn't even make that jump.
I made it, man.
You know you gotta grip onto the side to make it.
That's not making a jump.
If you barely made it, it's not making a jump.
What the fuck?
Why did you fucking...
Okay, no, no, no.
I fucked up.
I didn't realize...
I can't grip on this.
Alright, now pull.
Yes, okay, now keep...
Now keep spinning it.
There you go.
Good.
Does that mean I can leave you now?
What the fuck?
Well, I'm not the one with the third husband.
Hey, no need to be jealous of Omen, man.
Oh, I accidentally jumped off it.
You know what they say about marriage?
Death do us part.
What?
You don't know it.
What does that mean?
No, no, no.
You fucking whore!
You know,
I think you know why we're getting a divorce now.
How the fuck do you do this?
Get in there!
You get in there!
No!
Why me?
You fucking bitch!
I'm not even doing anything!
That's just you!
Swap it!
I swapped!
There you go!
God!
I have to go non-verbal.
You have to go non-verbal?
Oh no, we have to do this too?
Okay.
Goomy, remember all the good times we've had?
Goomy, remember all the good- You missed that jump!
How do we tie him up?
It's so cute.
It's cause I don't trust you that I'm double jumping.
What do we do here?
Oh, what the... get on the Roombas.
There we go.
Okay, let's go.
We're such good friends.
Friends?
We have to stay friends after divorce!
For a child!
I only do that to exes I like.
Alright.
Wait.
Where's the other end of this though?
Wait, but where do we- do I just like go here?
No.
It doesn't make sense.
Where does the end of that vacuum go?
Oh!
I get sucked in here!
Goomy, you could have said something!
Hey, listen.
Everyday's a school day.
You learn more and more everyday.
You could have said something.
Alright, here you go.
What's this?
I turned off the light.
I don't know what it does.
Why didn't you turn it back on?
What, you don't trust my judge?
We're trying to save electricity here.
Girl.
I'm trying to take every cent of your money.
Woah!
Uh huh.
I thought we signed a prenup!
No.
Wait, you didn't sign the prenup?
I wrote down Kaz's name instead.
That's fucked up.
That is fucked up.
That is actually illegal.
Wait.
Did you just admit that you committed fraud on my stream?
No, hey.
No.
Hey, I think one of us had to press the- You know what to do.
You know what to do.
Goomy, you know what to do.
Come on.
You don't trust me?
Okay, that's on you.
I didn't trust you.
Go, go.
Okay, I'm going.
There, see?
Oh, you don't trust me.
Wow.
How do I do this?
I'm sending over a platform, man.
How is that a platform?
It's this!
This was a platform!
Oh, okay.
I see it now.
I'm a little special.
You like that.
Fucking whore.
Hey.
You bitch.
Oh, get on that.
No, you get on it.
You get on it.
You're pissing me off.
Goomy, grab the pipe!
Grab the pipe!
I'll do it this time.
Sorry, I didn't know where to go.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't know where to go.
You didn't tell me where to go.
I need someone to tell me what to do.
You didn't aim it high enough!
Maybe you should do this.
Yay.
But clearly I'm not good at aiming.
You should know in the bathroom.
I should have known.
You should have known in the bathroom.
What are you doing?
Oh, you go up!
Yeah, I'm kind of smart or something.
What do we do from here?
Oh, oh, I go inside!
We need to get it down!
Wait, where are you?
Where did you go?
Where are you?
Oh, aim that thingy!
Like this?
Yeah, aim at the hole!
I'm doing it, I'm doing it.
Well, you have to aim too.
What do you mean I have to aim?
I'm sending it to you!
I'm doing it!
I think I'm doing it!
Am I doing it?
I don't think I'm doing...
Oh, am I?
I'm doing it!
It's getting full!
I can aim!
Oh, I'm making it a little bit dirty.
You're gonna have to clean that up later.
What the fuck?
I'm the perfect husband.
Oh, then we push.
Oh, talk about dead weight!
Yeah.
That's you, right?
What?
I don't even have a death counter.
Uh oh.
Is that first boss fight?
It's ugly!
You bought that vacuum!
I didn't think it had fucking googly eyes!
No, I glued that on because I thought it looked cute.
Oh my gosh, she just liked me for real.
I can fix you!
That's why you married me!
Oh, I'm an engineer.
Oh!
You're an engineer doctor?
Yeah.
And you settled for me?
Yeah, worst mistake of my life.
Damn.
That's harsh, man.
You're replaceable.
That's why she's trying to replace me with a better husband.
What?
I'm out of here!
See you later!
I'll show you who's the best, sucker!
How the fuck do we defeat him?
I don't see your fire blood here!
I thought we had to throw it back or some shit!
I'm literally doing my job!
I'm out of here!
Girl, what is that aim?
What do you mean?
That's a hit!
That's a fucking hit!
Ow.
Okay.
Look, if you can't do this, you can't platform.
Girl, did you get hit earlier?
No.
No?
Are you aimed then?
If you're so good!
I'm sucking it!
It's still it?
I'm going to!
Look!
See?
I hit him!
This is the fucking easiest platform game ever.
What the fuck?
Just run!
You can't fucking throw forever!
See?
Oh shit.
I think you can go forever.
No, no.
It's fine.
No, you can't.
See?
Look.
You got tired.
Alright, I'll be at the bottom.
Okay?
I'll let you do the work at the top.
Ow.
I got hit.
Um, I fucked up.
Look, I'm sucking!
There you go!
It's coming in!
Look at that.
So easy.
Bro, we can't...
How are we supposed to get a speedrun if they're fucking making us do all this other shit?
I'm pretty sure there's got to be an exploit or something, right?
There has to be.
This is the slowest boss battle ever.
I'm pretty sure there's got to be an exploit or something, right?
What are you mean?
It spawned next to me!
Okay, I can't suck anymore.
I can't suck anymore.
It's my limit.
Oh, shit.
I'm okay.
Oh, I don't know.
Why didn't you care about me getting hurt?
And the fucker you're inting my run.
Suck it!
I'm sucking!
Yeah.
Yeah, I kinda did all that damage.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Hey, I'm back.
Oh, hey, look.
Your husband was gone, but you didn't care.
Did you die?
Oh, wow!
Wow!
You didn't even think about it.
Did you even notice?
Wow!
She's already moved on so fast!
I was focused on living, man.
Time to finish this.
How do we finish this?
Oh, no!
Eyeballs!
Oh, that is so fucked up!
Do you think this is too much?
Kind of.
But he tried to kill us.
Oh, my God!
Bro!
What is wrong with you?
Oh!
He's gonna eat his eye!
That's fucked up.
Oh, my God!
Imagine dying like that.
Bro, this was your idea.
No.
We both did it.
I was peer pressured.
Watch it.
Why did she make them look like us?
Because you're never home.
Why didn't you tell me about them?
I'm never home?
I'm the one that knew about it!
Well, come on.
Let's find her.
Where are we?
That's fucked up.
Yeah, you were never home.
Use this place.
Get away from me.
I'm getting closer.
Ow.
Hey, your husband drowned.
Yeah, not a new.
Whoa!
Yeah, you need my help.
You can't...
I have to be here.
Unfortunately.
Dude, why the fuck is she still in here playing on her own?
Rose!
Rose, you have no other toys.
You can look at her.
That's crazy.
This is her only toy.
What the fuck is that?
Who said that?
What the hell is that?
Ew!
Is that a hammer?
Yeah, it is!
What is that?
That's my tool, friends.
We used to be important and taken care of, but that human locked us up in her toolbox and left.
Yeah, that human.
Her daughter?
No, you!
I heard that heartless woman found a new job in town and doesn't have time for her hobbies anymore.
Who cares about hobbies?
You know how painful it is to die from rust?
Yeah, you heartless woman!
Slowly!
What the fuck?
I don't like his eyes.
You just don't like eyes in general.
Ew.
Oh.
I don't even think I want to touch him.
I wonder if he can poke his eyes out.
Okay, what is going on there?
How is he on my back?
Woah!
Oh!
You're like that guy from Guardians of the Galaxy.
Yeah!
I have the whistle power.
Yeah.
Oh, nice.
I bet you can't whistle.
That's me.
I did that.
That was me.
Do you like my whistle?
Stop!
What are you doing?
Why are you having me?
I can't do anything.
Stop!
Go ahead, then.
Get away.
Of course, I'm the one that aims.
What are we supposed to do?
Oh, like this?
Okay.
Wait, what are you doing?
I think you have to jump down.
On the other side.
No.
Go on the other side!
You said jump down!
Oh!
Okay, okay, I figured it out, Gumi.
Okay, so you do that.
I'll keep doing that.
Gumi, I figured it out.
I figured it out.
I know how to solve this puzzle.
And that's how you do it.
You're welcome!
This is why I'm the brains.
Thank you!
You're welcome!
Your savior is here now.
Ready now?
What the fuck?
You're fine.
But how do I get across?
Can I just swing from this?
Can you throw your nail here?
Oh, okay.
What the fuck?
Okay.
You suck at this game.
What do you mean me?
You suck at the game too!
Why didn't you make them jump already?
Why do you need so much prep time?
Why do you need so much prep time, huh?
It's called momentum!
If you were an engineer, you would know that!
But I'm not.
You're the one that's stuck.
You said it with a farm boy!
Throw the fucking nail!
Where?
Oh, there.
Sorry, I'm blind.
Dude, do I have to wait for it to load a bit?
I don't know.
I think I have to wait for the wheel to complete.
The wheel?
No.
Yeah, it has a small wheel on it.
Oh!
Here, have a second nail.
I got two nails!
Okay.
Nice.
Look, see we're working together like a good couple.
Why is this?
Why do we do this here?
Oh, wait, maybe...
Oh, wait, what?
Oh, you have to hammer that.
Throw it in the hole!
No, you have to come back here.
No, you have to come here.
Okay.
Throw it in the hole.
Okay, so what I think is that I have to throw it into a hole after you do that.
See, that's what you do.
So when you hammer...
Yeah, so when you hammer it, I throw it into the hole.
You're lucky I was here to help you.
I think I'm lucky to have you here.
Yeah, you're so lucky.
You son of a bitch!
You come down here!
How was I supposed to know you didn't come down here?
I didn't make it!
Look at the other screen!
Why would I look at the other screen?
This is your business!
Like...
Nice.
Thank you.
Whoa!
Oh my god!
I hate him.
There are no relationships without challenges.
Challenges make you grow!
What is it with you?
Can't you just leave us alone?
Yeah, leave us alone!
We're trying to fix our marriage!
And it's going really well.
Right?
So, when you hear this sound...
Following it, keep following it, and you will find the challenge you seek!
Oh, that's kind of cute.
And you will find the challenge you seek!
Do we have to do the challenge?
We're not completionists.
Yeah!
I don't know.
Welcome to your first couple challenge!
I think we have to.
Win or lose, you must do it together!
You must do it together!
Huh?
Well, I guess we're gonna have to.
All right, you wanna give it a try?
We haven't got time for this.
Oh, you afraid of losing?
Me?
No way!
Bring it on!
Oh, I'm gonna bring it.
This isn't a competition, Gumi.
Score it by staying up and...
Wait.
Go ahead and ready up!
I'm ready!
No, wait a minute.
Go ahead and ready up!
Wait a minute!
Go ahead!
Ready up!
Oh, no.
I don't know.
I mean, we don't have to.
What?
No, no, no.
You know?
Hey, ready up.
I'm ready.
Look, I'm shaking my hips on the screen.
No, come on.
Gumi, we've been...
Yeah, go ahead.
We've been such good friends for...
I'm winning.
You need to warm up for this.
I'm gonna go get some ice cream.
Where am I gonna go?
Oh, no.
Hey.
You're pretty bad at this.
You're not even gaining points either!
I'm not gonna lie.
Neither one of us is getting any points.
Why are we not getting any points?
Because you're not staying up.
I don't have to.
Ow.
I think I went from fault.
Like, how do I gain points?
I don't understand.
You gave me points.
Did you not read the rules?
Sorry.
Don't go.
That's not fair!
I can't stay up for life!
Yeah, because I'm a god gamer.
It's not fair!
The game is actually rigged!
Like, this game is actually rigged!
This is not fair.
This is like not fair.
This game is so rigged.
This is not fair.
This is fucked up.
This is so fucked up!
Oh, you got a point!
How?
How did I get a point?
There should be like a cooldown.
What the fuck?
How did I even get this point?
I don't know.
Oh my god.
Give me another point!
I hate this.
I got one!
Oh, I got another!
No!
This is fucked up.
This is like so geared up towards the hammer.
There's no way.
There's no fucking way.
There's nothing better!
What did he say?
Can you throw your nail somewhere?
I don't think so.
Oh, I can.
Here, I can.
Yeah.
There you go.
You're welcome.
Huh?
Okay, here you go.
It's time for you to do your job.
Hey, why put my other nail?
Did you not grab it back?
No, I don't think I get it back.
I think I have to like...
take it and then like do it really fast.
Yeah, I have to do that.
Oh wait, you don't even need me.
Yeah, I don't.
You have to do over there.
Uh...
Come now.
Oh, here, here, here.
Oh, wait.
What?
No.
What do I do?
Stay here?
Oh, okay.
Don't worry.
I figured it out.
You're welcome.
And then...
Oops.
Oh, I got two nails!
Oh.
Alright.
And then...
She left it way back where she pulled it out of the platform early.
I think you're supposed to have three nails.
I'm supposed to have three nails?
Yeah, I think you're supposed to have three nails.
No, no, no.
I have two nails.
Oh, you have it now?
Oh, okay.
And then I do it here.
Yeah, I'm good.
Um...
Oh, okay.
I thought I was going to be stuck forever.
I thought I actually soft-locked myself.
Oh, what's this?
Oh, we have to go here.
Oh, it's a game for us.
Yeah, what is that?
Flip the switch?
What do I do here?
Shoot at...
Use your hammers on a target to score.
Oh!
Wait, where's the target though?
This is not fair.
Like...
You just have to hammer.
I have to aim.
Oh, God.
Yeah!
FPS, bitch!
That's what you're like.
That's fucking right.
I have to aim with a controller.
I'm not a controller player.
I have to run.
I have to aim.
What happened to your aim?
You don't have to aim with a...
You don't have to aim with a hammer.
Oh, my God.
You have to aim at that.
You have to aim at it, okay?
Yeah!
You have to aim.
Cody, don't screw this up.
Are you gonna...
Yeah, yeah.
Just get the jump.
There you go.
You're welcome.
Pull it back.
There you go.
You're welcome.
Yeah.
Oh, you're not patient.
You have to be patient.
There you go.
See?
You have to be patient there.
You trust me?
You didn't say yes or no.
You didn't answer back.
Nice one!
You pissed me off.
Why?
I asked you if you trusted me.
You didn't say anything.
How was I supposed to do?
Oh, what the fuck?
You have to like...
I have to aim it so that you...
I don't think you can make that actually.
You have to go through another cycle.
The more I got you.
You trust me?
I didn't realize.
You have to...
Wait, how do you get hit over there?
You have to land up here?
Oh!
Oh, what?
Wait, what?
I have to jump early.
I have to go early.
Oh, okay.
So it wasn't my fault.
Oh, but...
Okay.
Oh, whoops.
Wait, where are you...
Oh, it's here.
Alright, I'm here now.
Oh, here you go.
Three nails.
What the fuck?
How do I...
Oh, I got three nails.
Nice.
I fell down.
How do I get out of here?
Is there anything on your side?
How do I get out of this?
Oh, I can jump?
Oh my god!
Yeah, I needed the boost.
I got it.
Nice.
I'm here.
Okay.
Oh, this is easy.
Alright.
I'm here.
And then...
Oh, okay.
And then I do this jump jump.
No, no, you have to do this... No, you have to do the other one.
Oh.
Because I have to wall jump.
Yeah.
Okay, so like what I figured out is that I have to do...
And then...
Yeah, and then I do that.
And then I put this back here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, and then I do that.
Nice.
And then...
Look at that.
God, I'm so good at this game.
Nice.
And then...
Bam.
Nice.
I'm so smart.
Damn, she just liked me for real.
Look, we have good teamwork.
I don't know about that.
The book said so.
You want to trust that book?
Yeah.
Okay.
I mean...
I mean, he complimented me.
Unlike some people.
You get it when you deserve it.
Oh!
What did I deserve?
Oh, what the fuck?
What the fuck?
That's his friend.
That's his best friend.
It doesn't look like your friend's happy.
Oh.
We have a...
Wow.
Whoa!
Wait, he's shooting at us!
Oh, we have to run forward!
We have to run forward!
It's parkour!
Stop playing hard to catch!
Um...
I'm still alive?
You got this!
Do this for us!
Do this for our child!
You have to be here!
I believe in you!
Alright, I'm here now.
What do we do?
Oh, I have to go here.
Hahaha!
I'm on the other side!
What do I do from here?
Oh, I have to do this.
Wait, but what about you?
Will you ever be able to come back?
Is there something you can stick here?
I don't know.
I guess I'll just...
Do I just wait here for you?
Oh, I think I should have helped you.
No!
Yes!
See?
You don't need me!
Hahaha!
Oh!
You didn't need me!
I'm dead.
I'm coming back!
Oh my god!
I have to run all the way back!
Give me a sec!
I'm coming back!
I'm coming over!
Don't worry, honey!
Hahaha!
There you go!
You're welcome!
There, see?
I did it!
I'm doing it!
Alright, we need to hammer this.
Oh!
Hahaha!
That's my bad.
I pressed the wrong input!
Hahaha!
Don't die like me!
I never died.
You have to put a nail in it, Doki!
You have to hammer it first!
You have to put a nail in it from far!
No, it's fine.
See?
You still made it!
Look, you're just making this harder for us.
What about our speedrun?
I'm speedrunning!
I'm running!
Push out!
Put a nail in it!
I'm trying!
You're not making it!
Hahaha!
Now I know why we're getting a divorce.
I know why.
I've been knowing why.
Now I know why.
Do this transformer!
Bro, I thought he liked his friends!
Yeah!
I think this guy...
Oh!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
I think this guy lied.
Ow!
Okay.
I'll put a nail in it!
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
I did everything I can!
Bro, I don't think this guy wants him to be friends with him anymore.
Oh, what's he gonna do?
Smash you with the shovel?
Oh, he flipped you off!
Oh, we can't suck the eyes off him.
Whoa!
Wait, why isn't that tool...
Why doesn't that tool have eyes?
He's cutting holes in the floor.
Oh, I don't like that.
Where the fuck is the...
Can I just like...
Ow!
Okay, don't worry, I can do this.
I was caught by surprise.
Wait, do I have to like...
Oh, he's coming!
He's swiping!
Oh!
I'm throwing!
Your fucking thick head blocked my nails!
Okay, here we go.
We're good, we're good, we're good.
Keep hammering, keep hammering!
You did it!
He doesn't have an arm anymore!
Oh!
Oh, shit!
Holy...
Oh my god, you're so flexible!
What the fuck?
I know, I can do this quick!
Because yoga lessons paid off!
Oh!
Oh, he angie!
He angie now!
Oh, what the hell?
Oh, he's very angie!
How do I...
Um...
Don't worry, I dodged it!
Dodged!
I'm gaming!
Oh, he's on you!
I just sat near.
Oh, shit!
Oh, it's on you.
Oh, no, no, no, it would have passed that.
You're the...
Oh!
I was trying to hammer!
Hammer, hammer, hammer!
Get on him!
Break the contract!
That's why I married you!
You!
You're the one that's supposed to yell the contact clues.
Hammer, hammer, hammer!
Get on!
Get off me!
Jim, you suck!
You didn't tell me the contact clues.
That's what marriage is about!
I don't need to know what marriage is about!
You're supposed to tell me the contact clue.
Look at the camera!
Look, this is not my fault.
Marriage is like a teamwork.
And there is no I in team Gumi.
Really?
There's no I.
I have to do quite a bit of communication here.
I don't know.
I don't feel like I understood the context clues in...
Don't die.
Where was my context clues again?
Don't die!
No!
Hammer!
There you go.
Are you happy?
Are you happy now?
I got two.
I skipped that thing.
Oh my god!
Our floor!
It's okay.
It won't cut everything.
Right?
Um...
See?
I told you!
It can't cut everything!
Okay.
That's on you.
I swear to god.
Don't die!
Where's my fucking wife?
There you go.
Easy.
Nice.
You see?
We did it.
Teamwork.
Why do the other tools not have eyes?
Like...
Eww!
Oh god!
Oh god.
Oh!
I don't like that.
I don't like that at all.
Oh.
Look at me!
I'm whole!
You saved us from that Rust in Toolbox!
They're all blind.
Thank you, Mei!
You are a true hero!
Oh...
Thank you, Mei.
Yeah, I'm a true hero.
Wait, what about me?
I did all the work.
What did you do?
Did you see that explosion?
Anyway, we still have to get to Rose.
Oh of course, of course!
We did all the work together.
Can you help us?
They have to get to the other side.
Ew!
Ew.
Yeah,
it does not feel safe at all.
I don't think that's how physics works.
Rose, look down!
Gamers, look down!
What the fuck, asshole?
What the fuck?
Bro!
The moment we turn into human form, we burn the book.
For real?
And we never buy books for a child again.
Oh, wait, pause.
Learning was a mistake.
Okay, that's why I'm the engineer.
They turn into dolls and now she questions the science?
That's true.
Oh, we can skate now!
I'm a skater boy.
Oh, jump.
I fucked up.
How far is this fucking thing?
I'm pretty good at this.
Me too.
Woo!
It's like Tony Hawk.
Skater boy.
Yeah!
Oh, my God, how long is this?
There's another one.
There's another one?
Oh, my God, I'm almost there.
I almost caught up to you.
Oh, my God, I have to wait for you.
Don't worry, here I am.
Okay, stay right there.
Stay right there.
Hello.
I'm with you.
There you go, you're welcome.
I turned it on.
Wait.
You...
You wait right here.
Okay, you wait right here.
This one's the shorter path, okay?
You turn not off when I get over there.
Okay.
Okay?
Okay!
Go over there!
I'm heading over!
Boom!
You're welcome.
Okay, how about you wait...
How about you wait next to the start?
How about you go back?
I'm going!
I'm here!
I fell down.
We did!
Yay!
I pressed it.
Woah!
We're so close!
We're coordinated!
Look at us!
This is why we're a couple!
I died.
We... I need you back here!
It stopped!
We...
Oh, hey, thank you.
I don't...
Wait, I can just let you do everything and I can just respawn next to you.
What?
Yeah?
Do you need me to come over?
Thank you for that!
Do you need me?
I think I need you.
Okay, I'm here now.
I'm here.
Gumi, Gumi carry!
Gumi and Doki carry.
Oh!
Oh, more eyes!
This game has a weird obsession with eyes.
It does.
Same.
You are... nothing escapes my lenses.
Look!
Wait, in here?
Alright, okay.
Let's see.
That's a human!
Is he...
That's him!
That's me?
Am I dead?
You're not dead!
What's going on?
Yeah, what's going on?
Where's she?
Where are you?
You're streaming.
I'm taking a little nappy.
What's the matter with us?
Take your little nappy.
Me, me, me, me, me, me.
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me.
And she's just sitting there with her dolls.
And then you two came alive.
Also, like, it's weird ... that's a little creepy that there's a binoculars up here.
Like, who's looking at us?
What happened?
Bird watching me.
Huh!
She was crying.
Oh my god...
Who hurt her?
Can't be us.
We're good parents.
Yeah.
I bought her $8.00 cereal.
That's me!
Oh my god.
Oh my god!
That's me!
She always wanted, every day she gets a new doll.
What the f*** is that?
What am I doing?
No...
We could be having a nightmare right now.
I knew it!
Magic was real!
You didn't believe in me, Goomy!
Na na na na na na na na na na na, my little pony!
I'm a virtual wizard!
I'm still a wizard?!
How do we get a kid?
That's the laugh he did.
So you settled for me?
You are an engineer and you married me?
Sometimes you date and you marry someone because they're funny.
Am I funny?
Wait, I'm funny?
What the fuck?
Creep?
How does she know where exactly our daughter is at all times?
I mean, whose binoculars are these two?
That's facing our house!
We're outside!
We're gonna touch grass!
Did you watch?
It was pretty cool, right?
What the fuck?
Eww!
Lock distance initiatives do work!
Bro, I just wanna punch it.
Yeah.
Oh, we got rope powers!
I had it outburst and I had to say it.
Alright, let's swing across!
Oh, that's easy!
That tree is huge!
Don't worry about it!
The ropes will take us to Rose in an instant!
Sorry, I was looking at the ladybugs.
Yeah, I was looking at the ants.
Okay, we don't jump that way, by the way.
We don't jump the left side.
It's the right side.
It's the other side.
It's the side I didn't look at.
Oh, there's a plane!
Look at this!
Where?
Right here!
Oh, throw it!
Throw it!
Where do I throw it?
Oh, no, wherever you want!
Okay.
Weeeeee!
Where is it going?
We'll never know.
Um, did you build a treehouse for Rose?
No.
Why do you ask?
There are windows.
There's windows?
Yeah.
Oh.
Who lives there?
I don't know.
Tree people, I guess.
They exist?
I mean, if magic exists, tree people exist too, right?
Why are you not waiting up for me?
I'm right behind you!
You told me to throw the paper airplane!
No, no, no.
It took 50 years.
It's a heavy... Look, it's a heavy airplane, okay?
I'm not as jacked as I was before when you married me.
Okay.
I'm not going to throw it.
Yeah, that's because all you do is do your farm work and then eat them goddamn potato chips.
Yeah, but we get fresh potato chips because of meat.
Those are your favorite potato chips.
I actually don't like chips.
So you lied.
So you lied to my face.
I don't like chips at all.
You lied...
I don't like chips.
You're welcome.
I grew those.
I'm going to put them on.
All I need are rice crackers.
You see how far away it is?
I think lying isn't good for a marriage, you know?
I'm going to put them on.
I'm going to eat..
What's inside there?
You're so lucky I had only one cracker left on my table.
Oh, a table.
That was perfect timing.
What the fuck?
Oh my god, it's a fucking rat.
Dude, I think that's a squirrel.
No, it's a fucking rat.
Squirrels are just tree rats.
What the fuck?
Where did he get the jar?
You know what happens when wearing a jar?
No, no, no.
Please elaborate what happens.
Rainbow Dash.
What is the context of that?
What is that?
Why is there white goop in here?
Glue?
Isn't that glue?
Look, it's like arts and crafts.
Why do you have glue in here?
It's like arts and crafts.
Oh my god, she's talking to you.
I just wanted to tell you something.
It's important.
Have you heard of this book by Dr. Hakim?
He says that it's important to forgive each other.
This is so fucked up.
We've become friends.
Imagine like you're a daughter talking to your dad about something important.
He's just sitting there ignoring your ass.
Oh, that is... that's trauma.
It's okay.
She's already gonna get therapy anyway.
This is just gonna be...
It's okay.
You're busy.
Sorry.
It's okay.
She's already getting therapy anyway.
It's a two-for-one deal.
Oh.
Yeah, she might as well.
Like the extra trauma doesn't matter.
What the fuck?
We're getting interrogated.
Are you in with the wasps?
The wasps versus tree rats?
What?
Kill you?
No.
We're not working for any wasps.
We'll see you, Sigeron.
Pull the switch.
You got it, chief.
Oh my god, what?
They're gonna kill us.
Get away!
Oh!
We're unkillable.
That's crazy.
They're just watching the shit.
Yeah, I know.
That's another issue here.
They wanted us to die.
Why would we help them after they tried to kill us multiple times?
Let's find out.
I'll only do it for money.
What?
That was terrible.
Horrendous.
Is this Alvin and the Chick Monks?
There's three of them!
There's Alvin, Theodore, and the other one.
Oh, right!
Dude, this gotta be Alvin!
That has to be Alvin!
He looks like an Alvin.
Wait, where did the chairs go?
Does it disappear with us?
I think the fucking wasp got sucked up in it.
Why the fuck was he holding his pod?
Oh, did you see he has a machete?
Yeah, it's not like they could have guns.
It must be like a broken knife or some shit.
Oh, it's like... look at that tiny knife!
Awwww!
Look, it's Simon!
Oh my god!
Simon, Theodore, and Alvin!
Fucking rats.
And look, Theodore!
What the fuck?
They made shrines out of them.
Oh, she's...
Oh!
What's your Oshie mark in this?
Is that my Oshie mark?
The nail, of course.
Oh!
Mine is glasses.
Yeah!
Tree...
Wait, they have a TV?
Dude, they stole our TV!
Bro, what the fuck?
How smart are these tree rats?
The wasps have invaded our tree and wiped out most of our tribe.
Oh!
That's a pocket knife that he has.
What?
We can't kill those crazy creatures.
You nuts!
I did not realize there was like a actual war going on.
Like, this game had something to do with like war between squirrels and wasps.
What?
Does this mean it's gonna get Call of Duty?
Oh my god!
It's gonna get Call of Duty!
Of course, I get the gun.
Oh!
I get the fucking bazooka, bitch!
You get that?
Hehehehehe!
We sent in an undercover agent who would operate our mean robot.
As planned, the wasps believed the robot was their real queen.
But instead of wiping out the wasps, our agent was seduced by its power and switched sides.
Aaaaah!
So, kill the wasps...
Oh my god!
The agent...
went rogue.
Yeah, sure, but The wasps cannot take our nuts.
There's no way this game takes 15 hours.
There's no way.
We're like speedrunning this shit.
Yeah, I feel like we're already like 30% way through.
How much have we finished in this game, guys?
We got through two bosses already?
The vacuum and the toolbox?
Yeah, in within an hour and 30 minutes.
We're not even at 10% of the game.
You never take anything I do seriously!
Yeah!
Me too!
The divorce happened early.
Look at that!
They answered our prayers.
Apparently we just completed chapter one.
That was actually chapter one.
Okay, how does this work?
That's not fair.
Why do you get the cool zone?
Poor Emma.
What the hell?
Are you not here yet?
Oh.
I was testing out my gun.
Oh!
My thing is like fuel!
Okay, shoot it at the pile of sticks over there.
See, this is why we're good together.
Here are the context clues.
I'll just watch you fire that shit away!
Here are the context clues!
What do you mean?
Over here!
You give me the clues!
What is this?
Oh, it's the practice.
We don't need practice.
We're good.
We're good at this.
We don't need practice.
I already got it down.
See, look.
There, see?
Look at that.
No practice needed.
Umm...
Do I have to go there too?
Wait, what?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure you have to go through.
Yeah.
Yeah, I didn't know if there was something I had to do over there.
Then I can...
put this down.
See, look.
I did it.
The muscle can think sometimes.
Oh!
I don't think we needed to do that, but okay.
Oh, wait, we do!
We have to launch... Oh, wait, it's up here!
It's up here.
Yeah, I didn't need to do that.
Yeah, and then you have to blast the target.
Yay!
Progress!
This is like just very... This tree must be dying because it's so empty on the inside.
Yeah.
I mean, they're at war right now, so...
The grass?
Look, I was getting there.
I was getting there.
I don't need it!
I was about to... I was about to shoot it!
You just had to be patient!
Okay, and then I think you have to destroy it.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't worry, I got you.
Okay.
Uh...
Oh, it's over there!
You just had to hit it!
Hit what?
Isn't that?
Yeah, I've been hitting that.
Oh, uh...
Wait, lower it again.
Stupid.
Fuck you, man.
I thought about the answer myself with no help whatsoever.
Wait, hey!
Every day is a school day!
Right?
You're learning!
Yeah!
Yay!
I lowered this.
Wait, it doesn't go through.
Yeah, the sap isn't sticking.
What's this?
Where are you?
I think you need to weigh this down.
Up here.
Good thinking, brains.
I think you have to blow it up on your end.
I think you have to weigh it down a little.
No, I think you have to blow it up on your end.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
See?
Look at that.
You need me.
Okay.
What?
I think you climb to it and then I turn you.
Okay.
Not even...
Oh, I can grip it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Nice.
Okay, and then I... jump on it?
Yeah.
And then what?
Oh, and then we go through the door.
Yeah.
What the fuck is this?
What is this?
That's an acorn.
I'm experimenting on an acorn.
They really are nuts.
Ha!
I don't think that's it.
No, we have to wait like this.
Look at that.
You go...
You jump on and then I push you up.
Yeah, you jump on one of them.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Can you grip this?
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I'm pretty...
Can you grip this?
And then you do a wall jump and stuff.
Can you grip that?
Okay, sorry.
That's too far.
Yeah.
All right.
Can you grip this?
Alright.
Yeah, see?
God, I'm so smart.
You're dead.
Yeah.
It didn't stick you for too long.
Okay, don't worry.
I got this.
It didn't let me on the wall.
Okay.
This ain't it, apparently.
Then what is it?
Oh, there's more here.
Oh, you go from here.
Oh!
Okay, blow that up.
Get on there.
Okay, I figured it out.
And then you jump on that.
And now I'm gonna make this heavy.
Yeah, and then you jump on that.
And then I'm gonna make this heavy.
Okay, and then I'll do this.
Okay,
and then I'll do this.
I'm running out of ammo.
It's getting a little too heavy.
Blow up the one below you.
Blow up that one below you.
I can't.
I can't blow up.
Blow it up.
It doesn't let me scoop in.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Don't worry.
I got this.
I figured it out.
I'll just keep overloading it.
I'll overload it and then...
Okay, I got an idea.
I got an idea.
Okay, you go back on the other side.
Then you blow it up.
I can't.
You want me to go all the way home?
Yeah, no, no.
Go over here.
You can't go from here.
This side of the wall.
No, I can't.
I can't shoot while I'm on this.
Oh, okay.
It's okay.
I will spill so much goo that it will have to go down.
There's no way.
There's gonna be so much goo on this.
I'm gonna overload this with the goo.
Hey, you're doing it.
I'm doing it.
There's so much goo going on.
Don't worry.
Do not worry.
It's extra goo.
Okay.
Okay, now you can blow it.
What do I do from here?
Oh, I see.
Oh!
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm on it.
Why is she supposed to shoot it?
I don't know.
This is your side.
I was like, why would I know?
I'm looking.
Hello?
My gun's kind of weak.
What the fuck?
So weak.
There you go.
Look at that.
Goo.
Now I understand why I'm the goo.
What does that mean?
Only husbands know.
Oh!
Hey, I wonder what these buttons do?
What the hell?
Oh my god, they have a torture chamber.
Yeah, they do.
What is this?
What happens?
Oh shit.
What about this?
Oops.
Wrong button.
Oh, you're an acorn!
How did they turn you into an acorn?
Where did you go?
The expected distance.
Close.
There you go.
You're welcome.
Wait, what?
Oh, I got you out.
Dude, they have a fucking torture chamber for the wasps.
I know.
Yeah!
Wait, you can just turn them into acorns forever.
So you eat them.
Oh.
Wait, do we go this way?
This lid doesn't look so stable.
Hang on, those are interesting calculations.
Over here!
Corrosive.
Chain reaction.
Wait, what?
Do I just put this?
What's it do?
Oh!
The latches.
They're opening.
I got it!
You gotta wait.
I made a circle.
You like it?
It's my artwork.
Wait, this one...
You missed that one.
Okay, wait.
Sorry, I'm not good at...
I need more practice.
Let me go to the bathroom real quick.
What?
Oh no.
It's...
Oh no, give me a sec.
Whoa!
Looks like something was kept in here.
Oh.
Whatever it was, it's gone now.
Oh, it could be like the queen wasp.
What do we do for this?
It's ready.
Oh!
It's pulling it over.
Okay, and then you...
Yeah, I was gonna say you get rid of that, and then you get rid of that.
And then...
You get rid of that.
Not to get rid of any of these?
Well, you do have to start because it weighs it down.
Oh!
See, look at that.
It weighs the branches down and it pulls it down.
I see.
Uh oh.
It's okay!
Oh, I'm weighing them down!
Yeah!
Is that it?
No, there's more!
There's more!
It's okay.
I'm quickscoping.
Easy.
Easiest fucking fight of my life.
Bam.
Look at that!
There's nothing!
Yeah!
Okay, simmer down, Simon.
Yeah, Simon.
It's not the weapon.
It's how we use it.
How do we do this?
There's some acorns over here.
Do those acorns matter?
Oh, I know!
I know!
We light it!
Yeah!
Yeah, and then you blow it up.
I think you go up there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then...
Oh!
I get it!
I got it!
You have to blow this and the other one.
Give me a sec.
I'll let you know when to blow it up.
Look, we're working together, Gumi!
Maybe this marriage is salvageable!
Okay, you blow this up.
And then...
Blow this up first.
The first one.
And then the second one.
And then...
I leave you for another woman.
And then I guess I just go fuck myself.
Yeah.
I think there's a bridge here!
Let's knock it down then!
There is?
Ow.
Here?
Oh!
Okay, okay, okay!
I figured it out!
Go!
Throw it!
Blow it!
Yeah!
I did it!
See?
I'll never leave you!
There we go!
I told you I'll never leave you!
What?
I thought we were getting divorced.
You're literally leaving through divorce.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, you have to shoot that.
You shoot through that?
Yeah.
Look, you asked for the divorce!
No, you did!
No, you asked for it!
I disagreed!
What the fuck just happened to me?
I came like, live.
Yeah, you lied.
I saw that.
What the fuck?
Wait, what's this?
Oh, it's a tug of war!
I got the fastest fingers in the West.
Oh.
I'm on the right side.
I'm green.
Alright, I'm ready.
Alright, I'm looking forward to this.
I'm ready.
I played Mario Party.
What the fuck?
What?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This'll be a piece of cake.
Back to Mario Party.
Like, my fingers are tired today.
What?
How are you so good at this?
Yeah, I played Mario Party.
You better than that!
You wanna go?
No, that's okay.
You just really go with your fingers apparently.
Yeah.
Yeah, sorry about that.
Rose and I used to play with it all the time.
Just another thing this spring.
That was a great time.
Oh, man.
My legs hurt.
Dude, what the fuck?
Why can't they make this a cutscene or anything?
I know!
Why do we have to do this?
They're like, look at how beautiful this is.
Yeah, just give us the cutscene.
You don't know that!
We'll get to it!
What the fuck do we...
Oh my god, I'm getting like...
I'm getting on to all the ops.
How did I not hit that?
Oh, here you go.
It's okay.
I'm coming back.
Don't worry.
I'm here.
If you were worried, I'm here.
Oh, what?
You weren't hit the entire time?
I'm here.
Don't worry.
You don't have to worry.
Gumi, I'm here.
Gumi.
Don't worry.
Huh?
I'm like right behind you.
Say something.
What?
Oh, someone died.
Okay, that's bullshit!
You fucking activated it!
Where am I?
Oh my god.
I'm getting lost.
I didn't activate shit!
I'm getting lost because of you.
Oh my god.
Okay, we're fine.
We're fine.
Maybe I should just keep dying because apparently when I die, I just respond to wherever you are.
Like...
This has to be a boss fight.
Nah, this is gonna be a mini fight.
Too early for the boss fight.
That's true.
It looks like a mini fight.
May the acorn be with you, they said.
Alright, let's see.
Oh!
We just turn it.
Yeah.
There's nothing wrong with that.
We just turn.
Oh!
And then the wasps come in while we turn.
Um... Okay.
They're all down.
It's up to you.
Is there anymore?
They're down.
Keep turning!
I'm still turning!
Oh!
Shield!
Shield wasps!
This one looks tougher than the others.
Oh, this is...
My sap isn't sticking to its shield!
Yeah, my sap isn't sticking!
Shoot at his butt!
How?!
I'm fucking... Oh, okay.
I'm shooting the butt.
I'm shooting the ass.
I'm shooting the ass!
Shoot it!
The ass has been stuck!
He's aiming at me!
It's okay!
I'm pulling!
Shoot the ass!
There, see?
That wasn't so hard.
Okay.
Okay, shoot the ass!
Shoot the ass!
Oh!
I got shot in the ass!
I did!
His ass is stuck!
His ass is gone!
Okay, I need you to shoot that!
I need you to shoot this goop!
Okay, while you do this, I'm gonna shoot the goop here.
Oh, shit!
Okay.
Got it!
I'm shooting the goop!
Dodged!
Ash is shot!
One more!
Nice!
He's distracted!
He's good!
We did it!
We got him!
Nice!
Easy!
So easy!
Easy clap!
We're so good at Ash shots!
Backshot!
We did it!
No care!
No need to envisioned.
I'm right!
You want me to shoot this goop now?
I thought wasps... for the ants, I know when the ant queen needs babies, they start birthing male soldiers.
And then the moment the queen ant is pregnant, they kick them out.
I thought those were bees.
No, it's for ants too.
Isn't our wasps...
Oh, some wasps have male drones?
Drones?
I thought all bugs were like that.
Like all colony bugs are like that.
What the bug?
Yeah, someone's like they mate with a drone and then the drone dies.
That's their purpose.
Yeah.
They were... because like every...
As they should.
Whoa.
I didn't know... yeah, porn to love.
Porn to love not to work.
Okay, then...
Listen, the bees are onto something, dude.
Like why would they eat the food they mate?
Porn to love not to work.
Holy shit.
Someone's like I'm fine with that.
It's like Snoo Snoo.
Like that Futurama episode.
Death by Snoo Snoo.
Uh oh.
Ew, kill the babies!
Kill the babies!
Bro, why don't we just like shoot the... shoot the big... the honeycomb.
Ow!
You shot me!
Shoot the baby in birthing area!
I did.
There you go, the baby birthing area.
There's more!
There's more crawling!
There's more?
Oh shit.
I was trying to look at the cookbook.
Stop shooting me!
Stop getting so close!
Stop!
I was trying to run past them!
Alright.
Clearly I have to fucking back out after.
Alright, here I am.
I shot... I did the honeycomb.
I did the honeycomb.
Oh shit!
Okay, I did the honeycomb again.
The honeycomb...
There's a baby on me!
Shoot the baby!
I can't hear you goofed up!
I did!
I goofed all over the baby!
Okay, I shouldn't say that out loud.
It's like, dumb.
Oh god.
Oh my god!
There's so many!
Alright, there you go.
The babies are goofed.
What?
Not by me.
I did it.
I need to clarify.
Apparently.
There's so many goofed babies!
That wasn't done by me!
Oh god.
Okay.
Oh god!
I have the hardest job here.
I have the hardest job here, man.
Oh.
Hey, you got it!
I did it.
Yay!
What do we do here?
Hey, what's this?
What puzzle is this?
Okay, I clearly can't do anything about it.
Uhhhh...
Oh wait, there's a wall here!
Nope.
Never mind.
Oh, there's a bottle?
And a hole?
I think we have to...
Drop the bottle into a hole?
Yeah, make sure we drop the bottle into the hole.
No, no, there's like...
grass on it.
On the side.
There is?
Oh, there is!
Okay.
I'm on the opposite side.
Let me walk over.
I did it.
Oh, I see!
Okay, I'll goof the other one.
Oh, the bees are happy.
Bees not happy.
Bees are easy.
They're not the...
Oh wait, there's bees on you.
There's bees on you.
Oh, there's two bees on us!
Oh, that's a boss!
That's a boss.
I got the other...
I got the small ones!
The boss is on me!
I got the small ones though!
I goofed it!
There's so much goof on it!
I kept goofing!
I'm getting fucking poisoned!
Just keep shooting!
I'm dodging!
I shot him again!
Keep shooting!
Never stop!
Where did he go?
Oh shit!
Bro, she's so goofed up.
Bro, she's so goofed up!
Alright, I'm okay.
I'm okay.
Shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot!
Shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot!
Oh fuck!
Okay.
Okay, I'm dead.
I'm dead.
Don't die.
There you go.
Shoot her!
She's full!
How the fuck do you flick with the controller?
She's full again!
EDF!
We have EDF at home, guys.
We have...
This is Helldivers.
Oh, I have to put this on here.
Nice.
Alright, and then we gotta jump here.
Because I made this for us.
Okay.
Yeah!
Happy anniversary!
This is my gift.
Oh!
Bindi picture!
Oh my god.
Nice.
Can you like get closer?
To the camera?
Can you...
What do you mean can I get closer to the camera?
Can you get closer to the camera?
Okay.
And then... No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Get closer.
Can you turn around?
Yeah, that's good.
Okay, can you move up a little bit?
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Move a little bit more left to left.
Let me see...
Back up, back up.
Oh, yeah.
Nice.
Okay, there you go.
That's all I wanted.
Oh, look!
They're fighting it!
It's like a...
It's like a history lesson.
Oh, there's a timer!
Is that us?
Look at us.
That's us!
Oh, wait!
Is this...
Is this a puzzle?
No, I think this is just for fun, man.
Oh, okay.
Oh my god!
This is our best photo yet!
Wait, let me see.
What the fuck?
What the hell?
I know, I know.
I'm a great photographer.
I think we gotta go.
What about my photo?
Okay, okay.
Let me go.
How do you want me to pose?
It's beautiful.
What the hell?
Look at this.
Look at that.
That's pretty good.
I know, it is.
That's a really good photo.
Oh, these are like all the photos she must have...
Wait, who took these photos?
Wait a minute.
The squirrels did, man.
Hey, this looks like a boss battle area.
Oh, that definitely looks like...
Yeah, it's time to go down.
There's a lot of creep shots of us, though.
Ducky?
Yeah?
Oh.
Oh my god!
Oh, it is a hammer!
Oh, god.
Oh,
god.
Where's the HP?
Okay.
Oh, god.
There's so many.
Okay.
They're full of honey.
Oh, god.
I'm dead!
I'm okay.
You can die now.
But not really.
Not really.
Oh, god.
It's fine.
We're good.
Ah!
Whoa!
There's so many bees!
There's more!
How is there more?
Oh, god.
Are we supposed to like...
Wait.
Wait a minute.
I don't think so.
I think we were.
We were supposed to.
I don't think so.
Oh.
Okay.
Donkey, go for it!
Go for it!
Okay.
Nice.
Look, I don't want to get dehydrated.
Okay.
I got the first box.
There.
Okay.
I got the first box.
There.
Alright.
Where is it?
Where was it?
I don't know!
Look, there you go.
How?
What?
You stupid son of a bitch.
I'm coming over.
Stop.
Why me?
There was an area that I could have avoided it in.
Okay.
Alright.
Wall.
The walls.
The walls!
Okay.
Nice.
It's already gooped!
Okay.
Jesus Christ.
How many fucking bees are we killing?
In front of me?
Okay.
I'm just gonna jump.
You know, we don't even need to goop this.
We can just jump.
By the way.
I just noticed.
Well, we need to goop this one.
Um.
What do you think I'm doing?
What?
Why?
Why did you die?
What do you mean?
How did I die?
Why the fuck did you die?
Why did you die?
I wonder how.
Come on!
We're going by boat!
Help me out!
Help me out?
This is a boat?
Here we go.
Now there's water.
Now it's the water level.
Everybody's favorite.
Everybody loves water levels.
I love the water level music.
Don't we need like oars or something?
We don't need oars, Cody.
We've got an engine.
We do?
Oh, the gulp!
No!
Engineer time!
What?
This is you and your engineer brain.
The physics!
He's a nun!
Not just your wooden face, Mei!
You have a beautiful wooden face.
Okay.
Our thing has a health bar, Doki.
Do you trust me?
Trust me...
Wait,
it doesn't even do damage if I hit it.
You have to make sure we don't land in the mines.
I can't see that one!
All I'm saying is that you have to make sure we don't land in the mines.
Don't hit the trees so I can see the mines, please!
It's not my fault there!
Oh, this is easy.
It doesn't matter if we hit the side.
It matters for my eyesight.
Oh, that's a lot.
That's a lot of bugs coming in.
That's a lot of bugs coming in!
In front of us!
Turn to your left!
Right in front of you!
Where are you?
I'm aiming in front of us!
Not my front!
Girl, I don't know what your front is.
Why aren't you looking at my screen?
I'm not a screen peeker!
Hello?
Our game crashed.
What?
Do we have to do that again?
Do we?
Hello?
Can you hear me?
I... Yeah, I hear you.
Okay, okay.
Oh no.
This server died.
I'm not saying...
Oh, what?
No!
Do we have to do that again?
No, I think we only have to do the ship part.
Oh, thank god.
Okay, I said to an invite.
I sent you an invite.
Okay, proceed.
All right, don't worry.
This tap... Please don't tell me.
Oh my god, we have to do this again.
All right, here we go.
Hey!
Oh!
It's our ships full HP though.
It's like nothing bad ever happened.
In front of you.
My front.
I don't know what your front is.
I don't know.
Screen's fake!
It's okay, it's okay!
It's like we never lost HP so I never did anything wrong.
Yeah, look at that!
I'm gaming!
We lost HP.
Because you keep hitting it!
You keep hitting it!
How was I supposed to know this flimsy ass wood would lose HP?
How?
Oh shit.
Our HP!
I don't know where I am!
I'm lost!
Don't critic me!
Turn right!
I am!
Look, see?
I'm a good driver.
Look, I wouldn't be able to drive if you didn't yell at me.
Is that why our car's all banged up?
Uh oh.
Oh no.
It's okay, what is he gonna do?
Kill us?
We're fine, see?
They're not gonna do anything to us.
It's like a tornado.
We're fine!
Oh, oh wait, that's a tornado.
Not... Oh, I have to drive past it.
Okay, don't worry, do you trust me?
Hey, it's all up to you, dog.
Do you trust me?
Anyways, I'm tabbing out.
Wait, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
This is not fair.
Oh my god.
No, don't go away!
Where's the boat?
Go through the eye of the storm!
The eye of the storm!
What are you on about?
I'm on the boat!
Wait, how did you get... Where are you?
Where are you?
How did you get there?
Oh god, idiot!
How do I get there?
I'm drowning!
At the top!
I'm here, guys.
I'm here.
I did it.
Wait, I think it's easier if we go into the storm.
It's easier if...
No, because our boat's gonna freaking die.
I think it might be easier.
Goofy, I think... I think it's gonna be easier if we're in the tornado, Goofy.
You're pissing me off.
I think it's gonna be easier.
Stop crashing us!
We didn't lose HP!
We did it.
In front of you, in front of you, in front of you.
My front, my front, my front.
Look, see, we made it through.
We made it through.
Don't crash into that wall.
I mean, we don't have to have a wall if somebody hits the target.
Well, I have to be close enough to get the target.
Yeah!
We did it!
I, like, ripped onto my controller so fucking tightly...
...that my hand hurt.
Bro, you gotta relax, Goomy.
You gotta relax.
Hey, jellyfish.
Poke it.
Poke the jellyfish.
Okay.
I poked it.
You sure did.
I did.
For some reason, I thought it was that, like, Fighting Nemo DS game from the early 2000s.
Oh, yeah, yeah!
Then you could jump on the jellyfish.
You remember when you jumped on jellyfish?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then there was the mini games and the shark tank.
Mm-hmm.
Dude, I kinda missed those movie games.
I actually own that.
Yeah.
The good ones.
Not before they started, like...
Oh, that's a wall.
Okay.
Not before they... It's like, cash out.
They used to make actual good...
Actual good movie games.
What does that do?
I'll lift it up.
Oh!
Oh, look!
It's Nemo!
It's Fighting Nemo!
Nemo!
It's Nemo time!
Just keep swimming.
Oh, this is easy.
This is like platformers for...
I even cried while watching, uh, Fighting Dory.
Oh, you did?
Wait, what made you cry?
I don't remember why.
It's been so long.
Your turn.
Oh, it's this way.
I wonder if we like... If we didn't like that, would we be able to find it?
Would we be able to just go forward?
Oh, no!
Maybe speedrunners do that shit.
Oh, hey!
It's... It's like...
It's like... It's like caveman squirrels.
Wait, there's big Nemo squirrel.
Dude, giant squirrel.
Oh my god!
There it is!
There's a dead squirrel!
Holy shit!
That's a giant big squirrel.
And then... Oh, that's us!
I think they think we're good people.
I don't think so.
Look how angry our machine looks.
Wait... Is that us?
Yeah, look!
There's us!
That's me.
You can tell from my big...
Whoa!
What?
Hey, look!
Someone did not like that.
They love toilet paper!
They do?
Where?
Oh, they do!
They love toilet paper!
Yeah!
They love toilet paper and... and like all our other stuff.
And stealing from my stuff!
Yeah!
They love to steal.
So why are we helping them again?
Um... So we can get home or something.
Wait, what?
What are these?
Oh, can you light it?
No?
I think we can go down though.
Whee!
What the fuck is that?
Can I goop it?
Oh, what?
Magic is real!
Wow!
Woo!
Bam!
Ba-na-na!
Ba-na-na-na-na-na-na-na!
Oh!
I couldn't make it!
You have to like shoot yourself at it.
Yeah!
Nice.
I can aim.
Wait, I overshot it.
You have to hit that one.
I did.
Yay, cause I'm a gamer.
Huh?
Where's the next one though?
Oh, it's over here.
The next one flies.
Where does this take me?
Oh, I have to go in the... go in the hole.
Go in the hole.
See, I didn't miss the hole.
I'm literally right behind you.
I didn't miss the hole.
Are you not proud of me?
Oh my god, there's a fish!
The hole is pretty darn big, I'll be honest.
It's the... the sea turtle.
What the... That's not a turtle.
It's like the sea turtle.
It's like Crash.
It's like catfish.
Oh!
It's like Crash.
No, it's like the stingray.
It's like the stingray that takes you to school.
We're going to go to school.
No, aren't catfish... don't catfish like eat everything?
Yeah, they do.
They're bottomless.
And they have taste buds all around their body.
Wait, so like they're tasting my feet right now?
Yeah, it is.
This is why we're getting divorced.
What?
I'm just showing you...what?
I'm sorry, that was my breaking... that is my lie.
That was the last straw.
That was the last straw!
Oh, it's like on its back now.
Wait, did you die?
Oh...
It did a flip.
Oh my god, look, it's showing us all these cool tricks that he can do.
Wait, look!
There's more!
There is more!
Do I have to jump on them?
No, I think it's just decoration.
Dude, this is cool and all, but like, stop making me move on this.
This could have been a cutscene.
Oh my god, he's dead!
Fuck you, Cody!
Why are you blaming on me?
What did I do?
When we get divorced, you can't blame anything on me anymore.
You have to blame it on yourself.
Yeah, that's the point of my divorce, man.
You have to finally take responsibility.
Oh my god, I'm calling him.
Are you calling me fat?
Oh my god, man!
I let myself go because of you!
Because of me?!
Wait, where?
Oh, a shooting range.
Wait, what?
What are you gonna do?
Oh, it's over on the other side!
I'm just big boned, okay?
This is a dad bod right here.
People love dad bods.
Okay.
Un-charge.
Wait, what?
Oh!
Oh,
I see!
Bro, the aim is so weird though.
For this.
Oh, it's the right stick!
Yeah, no.
I kinda don't like this.
Me too.
Oh no.
What do you mean there's like bullet fall off?
What the fuck?
I don't like this.
Oh my god.
Aiming with this is so hard.
It's so difficult to aim with this.
I think I'm giving up.
Yeah!
FBS!
This is it.
This is where the...
Gamer of the year.
Gamer of the year right here.
You're a controller player?
Is that it?
No, it doesn't matter what input I use.
I'm just gonna... I'm naturally gifted.
Dirty controller player.
Apex Legends get her.
I'm gonna put you on the left side now on my screen.
That doesn't matter.
I'm just naturally talented.
Explain the Mario Party game.
That's not...
That doesn't require aim.
That's why.
Explain the hammer game.
That looks like an elevator over there.
We have to cross over.
That's a deep pit.
It's okay.
We don't die.
What are you afraid of?
We don't even die.
Where are we supposed to...
Here?
Oh, okay.
How did I get here before you?
I was looking around.
Where are we going?
Only one way out.
Oh, look out.
These are here.
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh, okay.
Okay, I figured it out.
So, like, we have to avoid the bees on the wood platform.
We didn't know.
Yeah.
I think I figured that out a bit earlier.
I'll be honest.
We have sort of time where they're...
see where they're gonna be arriving.
Yeah.
Oh.
Bro, this game is for babies.
Look at this.
This is a baby game.
We're so good.
I don't think it's a baby game since they're talking about divorce.
No, babies need to learn early on.
We can't shelter these babies.
You know, you're right.
Yeah, babies don't need to be sheltered.
Oh, poop time!
Poop time!
There you go.
Nothing spawns behind us, right?
No, we're fine.
We're fine.
Yeah.
They only spawn in front of us because they're not that smart.
Okay.
How far are we going?
Going up.
To the top, baby!
To the moon!
Oh, fuck.
We're in a coliseum.
Oh, okay.
I think there's a boss fight here.
Ehh.
What is this place?
I don't know, but...
They look pretty angry.
Yeah, they do.
Wait, that's a beetle!
Oh, beetle!
Oh my god!
Oh, he's so cute!
Oh, are you ready for this?
I'm not sure.
He's so cute!
What's he gonna do to us?
He's so cute though.
Okay, I'm gooping.
Uh, the goop isn't showing up.
Oh, I'm fucking dead.
This guy one-shots.
This guy one-shots!
Oh, I think I know!
I think I know!
We gotta lead him here!
Um...
I think you were supposed to...
Why didn't you do all the floors first?
I'm dead.
He has to be right on top.
Okay, alright.
I'm gooping out here.
I'm gooping here.
He's running at you?
Alright, I'm gonna stand here and then like you make sure to shoot it the moment he runs at us.
You make sure to shoot it!
You make sure to shoot it the moment he runs over.
Okay, yes!
Nice!
That's it!
That's all we have to do!
His shell is too strong!
Oh shit, he can fly now!
Okay, don't worry.
Nice!
I'm bait!
Okay, it doesn't go up yet.
Oh, he's doing a double jump.
He's doing a triple jump.
Oh baby, a triple!
Oh!
It hit on me!
I told you he won't shoot!
He flipped over!
Okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
I gooped.
I'm bait!
There!
Nice!
Please, please, please, please, please.
Alright, here we go.
Oh no, you're bait now.
You're bait.
Yeah, yeah, it's fine.
We can wait for him to walk.
He's charging!
He wants to charge!
You're ready!
Yeah!
We did it!
Nice!
We're gaming!
Oh!
I'm just a beetle!
Sounds like Seth Rogan.
Worms!
Slugs?
Larvae?
No!
I'm a vegetarian!
And gluten free!
Oh!
Okay.
Well, uh...
You know the queen?
She has all the nectar.
So if you help us take her down, you can have as much nectar as you want.
Shake my head, not loyal.
Gaslighter!
Yummy!
What are we waiting for?
Come on!
Jump on!
Oh!
We got him!
We're on a ride now!
Nice!
Shake my head, not loyal though.
Wait, how do we...
Oh!
You shoot!
You're the aimer!
You have to shoot!
You have to shoot too!
No!
I move!
I move and jump!
You shoot!
Where's the shoot?
Stop backseat shooting!
Yeah!
Whoa!
Okay.
I jump.
Let me go.
Just remember to shoot.
You know what's crazy?
You were moving the exact same way I was moving.
Wait, really?
That's...
I thought I was moving.
Someone wasn't reading.
This does not have to do with reading!
It just...
It's called...
reflexes.
See?
I jumped.
You could have shot that.
No, I couldn't have.
You jumped into the barrels.
You could have shot that.
What are we talking about?
Shoot!
It's shooting time!
Alright, nice.
And then I...
jump!
Look at me go.
I'm a good driver.
Better don't get us killed if you won't die.
I have a driver's license.
Um, okay.
I have a drive-thru.
No!
Still go!
Yeah!
Nice one, Mae!
Pew!
Wait, would it matter?
Would it just fall on us?
Maybe.
Like a bomb?
Let me go.
That's when you know I'm a good driver.
Pew!
Meow.
What did you do?
You crushed!
You didn't shoot!
You didn't!
That wasn't odd that you fucking crushed into that!
Our perfect run!
Nailed it.
Um...
Well, you could have flew all along.
You could have just flown all along for us.
Um...
I think he regrets working for us.
What the fuck!
He's on fire!
And now he can fly.
Oh!
That's fucked up.
We Yoshi'd him.
We'll just grab another beetle later.
Damn, that's crazy.
If Mario can do it and have a billion dollar company, we can too.
We know you're not the real queen.
There's a squirrel in there.
100%.
They said that in the lore, man.
I gooped it!
Slowly tip it away!
I had left.
I did the button!
What are you doing?
Where's the...
Why did you leave?
I don't wanna get hurt.
What do you mean I gooped the fucking button?
Okay, now we go on it.
Okay, let's see.
Easy.
How do we...
Where's the...
Oh!
Wait, wait, wait!
Oh, wait, no?
Where's the...
Wait, but where's the... where's the funnel?
Where's the funnel now?
Where's the funnel?
I can't find it.
Do we do backshots?
I think we do backshots.
I'm trying to find the funnel.
Wait, where did you shoot?
It's wherever the X is!
Backshots!
It's okay.
There's an X right here.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Oh, how did I fail?
I don't understand!
Don't worry I'm coming back.
Oh yeah, okay.
I'm gooping.
I'm gooping wherever the X is.
But he's looking at me.
I can't!
Oh the bees are looking at me.
I shot the coochie.
You shot the coochie?
There's two X's on the back.
Actual backshots!
I can't do it.
There's bees blocking!
You guys shoot the bees!
I did!
Okay.
Okay, okay.
I'm going back, back.
I'm going back in the back.
She's looking at me but I got the...
I got the edX.
Coochie down!
Ass time!
Oh, the airstrike.
Oh my god!
Ow!
What?
How was I supposed to...
I died because I was off screen!
That's fucked up.
That's fucked up, man.
Oh my god.
Okay, we're okay.
Spread out, you heard her.
Spread out.
Where do they go after the bomb?
I can just stand still and just jump from here.
I don't have to move.
Okay.
Alright.
Come with me, come with me, come with me.
It's the backshot time.
Backshot, backshot, backshot.
I got the back.
It's looking at me.
Well, that sucks.
Okay, I got the back.
I got it.
Where am I?
I was off screen!
That's what I said!
This is fucked up.
This is bullshit.
This is so bullshit.
We're good.
I can stand still.
Oh.
Don't stand still, by the way.
Don't stand still.
You gotta keep moving.
I've learned that you gotta keep moving.
Hey, look at my health bar.
It's okay.
It's a good thing that your Fuki is hiding the health bar.
So they won't know if you got hit or not.
I didn't die, by the way, guys.
I didn't get hit.
My full HP.
You're at half HP.
No, I'm full HP.
I'm shooting the back.
Backshot, backshot, backshot.
Back is goop.
I have gooped the back successfully.
Backshot, backshot, backshot.
I'm gooping the...
There's too many bees.
You gotta keep shooting the bees.
I have to reload sometime.
That's a you problem.
I have backshot, backshot.
I'm trying to goop, but they won't let me.
They're protecting the queen.
We have to split.
You go the other side.
Okay, it's looking at me.
I don't know what to do.
Oh, I got it, I got it, I got it.
It's literally attacking me.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Okay,
okay, I'm going back up.
I'm going back up.
I'm doing it.
I got the back.
It's your turn.
It's fully backed.
Backshot!
Yeah!
What the fuck?
Where am I?
Wait, where do we shoot?
Oh, here, here, here.
Yeah, yeah.
It's the wire.
I know, I know.
Try.
What?
I didn't see it.
Don't get me.
You're welcome.
Okay, okay.
The bees, the bees, the bees.
What do we do about the bees?
I'm gonna shoot the bees.
Ow!
You gotta shoot the bees.
I can't aim at the things because of the bees.
I am!
Okay, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
You gotta keep aiming the bees.
You gotta keep aiming at the bees.
Oh, I got it, I got it.
I don't got it, I don't got it, I don't got it.
I got it, I don't got it, I don't got it.
Oh god, oh god.
I need to reload.
I'm getting dehydrated.
Oh, I got it, I got it!
There you go.
There you go!
Okay, bees, bees, bees!
Bees, bees, bees!
It's good, it's good!
Last shot, last shot!
We got it!
Where's the squirrel?
Wait, it was a bee!
That's not...
It is a bee!
She's a fake!
Wait, then how do they get more wasps?
Oh, shit!
But like, how do they make the bee wasp make more wasps?
Where did the baby go?
Where did the larvae come from?
What?
Oh!
Oh my god!
Cool guys don't look at explosions.
Yeah.
We're so cool.
That's so cool.
You see those TikTok videos where they put gasoline over a wasp hive?
That shit's so...
No.
We've never seen that TikTok!
There's like a pro tip...
I've seen a guy that vacuums wasps.
What the...
What the fuck?
I saw one where you get like a...
Like a bucket of gasoline.
And you put it on top of a wasp nest or whatever.
Like the wasp nest...
All the wasps in the wasp nest will just fall into it.
And die.
You are one of the noblest pollinators in nature.
I... I am?
Yeah, of course.
Bees pollinate crops that feed...
Dick Rider!
What the fuck?!
How did these bees fucking booty dodge all those bullets?esty
That fucking aim though.
Okay you're driving, I'm shooting.
Oh there's my underwear.
The little sweets, that's cute.
The fucking machine gun man.
Code not!
Oh no Alvin's angry.
Alvin's angry.
Don't worry I can fly.
What happens if I go...
Girl!
I didn't know.
Hello?
I'm gonna go pee.
I didn't know that was gonna happen.
I didn't...
It was not intentional.
It was an accident.
I swear.
It was just a little teehee accident.
You guys believe me right?
I didn't mean it.
I think...
Guys I think I'm doing really well chat.
I think I'm a great husband.
Don't you guys think so?
I...
Don't you guys think I'm an absolutely perfect husband?
Like...
The reason why we're getting a divorce is not because it was my fault.
I feel like clearly, I tried to...
I tried so hard to make it work I tried so hard to make it work And clearly, It wasn't a me issue for this.
Like...
Clearly...
Sure, see?
Father of the year!
Okay, I'm gonna make a pull.
Who's the reason for this?
All I'm saying is that I think I'm perfect husband material.
Okay.
Like, anyone would want me as the husband.
I'm a perfect dad and a perfect husband.
There we go.
See?
No crashes!
No crashes.
Oh, I can rev!
I can rev!
I can go fast.
You guys gotta make sure you clear the way.
You guys gotta make sure.
Shoot the thing!
Okay, here we go.
We're good.
Puppet!
I'm trying!
There's a cooldown!
I can't just pump whenever you tell me to pump!
Well, you're gonna have to pump it here!
Threatenita!
Woah!
My god!
Squirrel gliders!
Shoot down the squirrels!
They're not people anyway!
That's fucked up!
They shot us first!
They shot first.
Why am I taking damage?
Why am I...
Because they're shooting, you stupid bitch!
Yeah, but if you killed them before then, I wouldn't get shot.
That's why I'm swapping to mouse and keyboard.
It's worse!
It's worse somehow!
The DPI is so low!
That fucking changed your DPI!
I can't be ashamed!
Don't worry.
Because the talented controller input can do this.
That's why you need me.
We got more trouble ahead!
I'm gifted in any input.
Woah!
Pick one!
I destroyed all three, so...
Okay, I couldn't tell because they were still there.
There's something behind us?
There's fucking things behind us!
They're so fucking slow!
Oh god.
I hope you're shooting them.
There's still planes behind us, by the way!
It's escalating quickly!
What?
There's some things behind us!
They're slowly occurring!
That's a U problem!
Oh god.
Why did you pause?
I didn't get the pause button!
Why is it...
Is it better now?
No, I still haven't fixed my DPI.
I have to aim with my arm instead of my wrist.
It's okay, we're out.
We're out.
I think it's over.
Are you gonna fight the squirrel?!
Oh my god, its Alvin.
Oh shit!
Shit!
Oh my god, fight, fight!
What am I supposed to do?
Am I just...
Oh, I'm just gonna make sure.
This is a fighting game now.
What the fuck?
It's time for Tekken!
Beat him up!
Kick his ass!
Oh my god, he's not doing it!
He's talking!
He went super fast!
Oh shit!
Oh my god, KO!
What the fuck?
Oh, that squirrel is dead dead.
There is no way.
Wow!
I do love you!
Oh my god.
Oh, we have to balance this.
Yeah.
Yeah, we have to be fully balanced!
What are you doing?!
Okay, I'll be right side!
I'll be right side!
Okay.
I should have been left.
I was left.
You should have gone left.
What do you mean?
When we're my... Okay, I'll stay... When we're balanced, I'll be left.
Okay?
When we're balanced.
Okay.
Alright?
Okay, okay, okay.
Mm-mm, alright.
We're gonna be good sometime.
All I'm saying is that I stay on the left side.
I know where my place is.
Okay.
Look at that.
Yeah, Gumi?
Yeah?
I like to go to the left side too.
Why don't we just stay in the center?
We don't wanna go anywhere.
We stay in the center.
Okay.
I think that's just easier for us.
Wow, wait.
Look at what happened.
Maybe... we just have to stay in the center.
How about you stay in the center and I steer?
Maybe that's just better.
Yeah.
Okay, but I'm getting scared.
I'm getting scared.
Maybe there's just too many cooks in the kitchen.
You know?
Too many cooks.
We don't want too many cooks in the kitchen.
You're scaring...
What am I doing?
I am doing everything I can to save this marriage.
Yeah?
Okay, here we go.
Well, they shouldn't have stolen from us in the last episode.
Alright, nice.
I think we should go right.
I think... and then we should go left.
We should go left.
No!
Please, not the beginning.
Oh, thank God.
We're not the beginning.
You think the squirrels will be mad about the plane?
We'll be fine.
They shouldn't have stolen from us in the last episode.
I'll never look at a squirrel the same way again.
Um...
No!
Gooby, we can make it through, right?
Maybe we stay in the center?
We think the squirrels will be mad about the plane?
Don't worry.
Well, they shouldn't have stolen from us in the past episode!
Maybe... Maybe...
I'll never look at a squirrel the same way again!
What?
Oh!
Oh, it still works.
It still works.
Left!
Nice.
Right.
Center.
He didn't do that.
Apex callouts!
He's won!
He's one!
He has a purple armor seal!
Crack!
I'm shielding!
Shielding!
Cover me!
I'm reloading.
Where's Rose's room?
Where is that?
Oh!
Is there?
Shit!
I was like, where the fuck are we supposed to go?
Right!
I'm not gonna wait!
Okay.
Alright, we're good.
See?
Nice.
We did it.
That's you sleeping.
Sleeping on the job.
Oh my gosh, she's gonna talk to me.
She's like, Mom?
Hey, do you remember Mr. Baboon?
Mom's sleeping!
This is mom's sleeping hour.
I'm sleeping!
Dude, she's about to run away from home at this point.
Yeah, she's gonna fucking inside out it.
Oh my god.
Damn.
Mommy has two jobs, leave her alone.
Yeah, you talk to dad?
Bro, what?
That's his life.
You're lying?
You're making shit up.
I just want you to know.
Someone's like, I think we need to call CPS on them.
We're not terrible parents!
We have to make all of them.
We are tired from making so much money for our kid.
Our kid has to fucking...
Dude, just because I'm fucking napping doesn't mean you have to call CPS.
Yeah!
Wow!
Look at her room!
Tell us we're not providing!
I'm providing!
She has a TV in her own fucking room.
Like, what the fuck?
I'm
flying by the seat of your pants!
Oh, haha.
You're real comedic, you know that?
Thank you.
Look, there she is.
Oh, I miss her.
Do you think she's okay?
She looks fine.
I mean, she's playing like nothing happened.
Yeah, see?
She's playing like nothing happened.
She looks like she's happy.
Just like me when I had to play in my room.
She's not disassociating.
We've turned into a couple of dolls, remember?
Of course I remember.
Whoa!
Oh!
Are you ready to talk to Rose?
Why not?
She's our daughter.
Well, can you talk to her without fighting each other?
Of course we can.
Of course we're like... one minute is all we need.
You see?
I don't think you are ready!
Wait, is he trying to stop us?
I think that he is.
And are we gonna let him?
No!
Yeah!
Finally, we don't have to listen to this guy.
Wait.
What if we can't make Rose cry?
We have to.
We'll be stuck like this for a while.
We're gonna make our child cry.
What the fuck is...
We got a sniper on us.
We have a creep on us.
Dude, they're breathing so heavily!
Oh!
There's a lot of pillows.
A dream catcher?
Oh!
There's like a pillow for it.
Yeah.
Yeah, well, you haven't played here lately.
Hank Brothers?
Oh!
Rose calls it mommy space.
The mommy space.
Aw, she has mommy-ish.
She has mommy-ish shoes.
Don't we all?
Alright, let's see.
How do we do this?
Oh, yeah!
The tank one!
Wait, how do I...
Oh!
I figured it out!
Why are you getting closer?
I don't like how close you are.
You're in the corner.
We hit each other.
I just need that one hit.
And then we're good.
Wait, where did...
Yes!
I would have hit a save a little second earlier!
I'm a gamer.
Wait, it says I'm two and you're one.
No, it says that I'm four and you're one.
Well, it says two and one for me.
It says four and one for me.
I love stars!
This is my way.
What the fuck?
That's right.
Get distracted by that.
I get a head start now.
Wait, what is this?
What's a flashlight for?
Maybe flashlight on is better.
Does it really matter?
Why is there a car truck?
Wait, there's something in the car.
What's happening here?
What is this?
Is this an Easter egg?
Oh, it's the brothers!
It's the brothers!
There's an Easter egg from their other game that they made.
It's the...
I've never played that game.
Me too.
I've never played it either.
But it's like the streamer game.
It's like if you want to play a co-op or something, it's either this or the other one.
Alright, let's play the other one next.
What's this?
Oh, it's just like Easter eggs.
Wait, what?
Enter password?
Hacking?
Like this?
Oh, you're on the other side.
Oh, alright.
Oh.
Oh!
But what do we do here?
I'm green?
I am red.
I think... are we stupid?
Are we...
Look at that!
Oh!
Whoa!
It's okay.
We're figuring it out.
No, no.
We have to make this guy angry.
Right?
You make him smile!
I thought it was eyelashes.
Oh, why?
Why?
Look,
I thought they were eyelashes.
Okay?
Uh-huh.
Whoa!
Oh!
Because I brought you in the Space Museum!
Liar!
Rose had picked me at the Space Museum and commissioned me for a special mission.
I am the only one who can protect Rose from the dark side of the universe!
Well, we're also assigned to protect Rose as her parents...
Stop lying!
Your mission is to make her cry!
Damn!
That's a fucked up mission.
The bigger the better.
They can be happy tears, Moonbaboon!
People can cry out of happiness!
Take him out, Spacebaboon!
Dude, Spacebaboon is CPS.
Eww!
Who caught CPS on us?
Who was it?
I'm having a panic attack.
What should we do?
It Takes Two has the most accurate portrayal of panic attacks.
Have you seen that meme where people were like...
were like talking about which movies had the best portrayal...
which animated movies had the best portrayal of panic attacks?
Did you see that?
I've seen people say... you know that movie...
the Pixar movie with the motions or whatever?
Yeah, Inside Out.
Yeah.
Yeah, I've heard people say...
that anxiety looks fuckable or...
What?!
It works!
Inflation!
Cosmic inflation!
Oh my god, inflation!
If you wanna know...
Wait, what does anxiety look like from Inside Out?
Basically, she looks like the...
Cosmic inflation!
She's like the orange one.
Do you know they release the new emotions?
It's like anxiety, envy...
Dude, anxiety does not look fuckable!
It's like anxiety, envy, boredom...
and I don't remember the fourth one.
Woo!
Haha!
How come you get all the cool gadgets?
Because I'm cooler than you, Cody.
Yeah, how come you get the cool one?
I forgot what the fourth emotion they introduced.
Let's find a way out of here.
Bro.
Can you not buy Rose, you cruiser space monkey, please?
Well, she was the one who picked him out.
Yeah, and you paid for him.
What do I do?
It's terrifying.
Oh, wait, what?
You would be upset.
Like you would be upset.
Someone threatened to hurt Rose.
Yeah, well, we're not hurting Rose.
Wait, how do you get up there?
She needs her tears so she can have her parents back.
Uh, I have moon shoes.
Now let's move on.
Oh, I get... I know, I know.
I don't know.
Wait, the moon...
Where are you?
Where did you... How did you do that?
I'm trying to get there.
How did you do that?
I have moon shoes, man.
Stop!
Oh.
Wait, how do...
What did I do as a big boy?
Oh!
Wait.
Actually, no.
Where are my context clues?
Oh, I figured it out!
I figured it out!
I go smart.
And then I do this.
Wait, do I do this in?
Mm-hmm.
I did it!
You know...
I'm pretty smart.
Wait, don't you...
You can let go right now.
Yeah.
I know, I was just watching.
I was watching you scream.
You were just watching?
Mm-hmm.
That's fucked up.
We're supposed to be a team.
There's a control room at the very top.
If we can get up there, I think we can make it out of here.
What's this?
Oh.
Oh, there's no battery.
You have to go in there.
Oh, okay.
See, this is why we're a team.
You're my context clues.
Okay, I'm pushing it in.
It's I.
You know, I think sometimes I just stop and I just watch.
What?
Because of how smart I am, right?
I just want to see how your mind works.
Yeah, because it's like a genius.
Maybe it takes us out of here.
I'm a genius.
You're just like so impressed with how this mind works.
What the fuck?
Wait, what the fuck is this?
Wait, I'm in somewhere else.
That was intense.
Oh, no.
I'm with you.
Wait, no, I'm here.
Oh, it's another game!
This is another game?
Spacewalk?
Okay...
Oh, we play this.
Land on platforms to clean...
Oh, it's like that crab game!
Oh no, this is platform.
What the fuck?
It's so slow!
Okay.
Oh, oh, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Come on!
Give me more!
No, I fell!
No!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Yes!
Mine!
Wait, that's fucked up.
That's fucked up.
I can do that too.
Yes!
I took yours!
Another point for Doki!
I didn't realize I could take yours until later.
Doki!
Yeah!
What the fuck was that?
It's called being a Winnie.
What is this?
I think I started like a supernova.
What the fuck?
Can we like shoot the stars into this?
I think we can go into the...
There's the world.
Oh, there is.
Yeah.
Alright.
Purple world.
What's this?
Can I step on it too?
Oh, we can?
Oh, it's like the monkey ball game.
Monkey ball?
Yeah.
Oh, I...
I think you have to push it.
Yeah.
Wait, how do I push it?
Why don't you try becoming big first?
Oh, I have to be big.
Big.
Big time.
Okay.
I'm pushing.
Yeah, it is!
It's like that stupid...
The monkey ball!
Bro, I push so fucking slow.
Beeeeee.
Okay.
Don't worry.
I'm pushing.
Jesus Christ.
I wish I go faster.
I'm so slow though.
Can I actually go faster?
I can't.
Even if you dash?
No.
It won't let me.
I have to push as slow as possible.
Alright, here you go.
Alright.
I'm watching.
I'm watching you.
Now what do you do?
I don't know.
What do I do?
Do I just stay here?
Oh!
I smell it!
Oh, you crushed me.
Okay.
That's a little fucked up.
But that's okay.
I knew what I signed up for when I said I do.
Wait, what?
Okay, yeah.
I'm ready.
Go slow.
Push it.
Alright.
Oh!
Can I push up?
Oh, maybe.
Oh!
You have to push back up.
You stay small.
I can't keep staying small when I'm excited.
What?
I'm pushing it in.
Push it in!
I'm not done!
Oh, at least it teleports us, which is nice.
We don't have to walk back.
Alright, we got it.
I missed the back shots.
We got it.
Go to red.
Red portal.
Because I'm red.
How are you red?
I'm red!
Look!
Look at my shirt!
And tell me that's not red.
That's orange.
That's red!
You just don't understand.
Do we both need to be here?
Oh, it went all the way up.
Red?
Oh, it's this way.
You have to jump on the planets.
And then...
The planet made me slide off.
That was fucked up.
Don't worry, you'll get there eventually.
I'm here now!
I believe in you, Gumi!
I believe!
Boom.
Why are you saying these things?
What do I do for this?
Goddamn.
How do you do for this?
Oh!
Maybe like...
Get on it!
You have to get on it!
And then I like...
Wait, what?
Oh, wait, you're already on there.
Okay.
And then you hit me that way.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then I hit you to the front.
Bam!
Slap!
Okay.
Me
up there?
Yeah, how do you get me up there?
Uh, go to the drawers.
The drawers?
There's the drawers.
To your lab?
The drawers?
Oh, I see, I see!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm in.
Got it.
I fucked up, I fucked up, I fucked up, I fucked up, I fucked up.
You gotta restart.
I fucked up.
Yeah, sometimes husbands make mistakes.
You can't be perfect.
Oh.
Because being perfect is very... More often than not.
Being perfect makes the relationship very toxic.
You gotta be able to make mistakes to show that you're human.
Oh!
Hello?
There, I'm good.
I'm in.
Okay, I'm tiny.
Tiny man.
Tiny man!
Oh, shit.
Tiny man dropped off.
Tiny man is still walking up.
It's okay.
I'm gonna check on the left side.
That's me.
Hey, I got this.
Alright, I'm pressing it in 3, 2, 1.
Yeah!
He happy now!
I'm the short king.
Alright, last portal.
I'm surprised we're not at the school yet.
We're not at the math problem.
I told you, there was... The only thing I remember from watching people play this game...
...is the one where there was math problems.
No, I know what you're talking about.
Yeah, that's the only... That's like apparently the only like...
...clippable thing people clip from that game.
Cause like, I...
I don't know... I did not know all of these other things existed.
That's for sure.
I didn't know all these other things existed in this fucking game.
Nice.
Did we just jump?
I assume we just jumped.
Oh!
I jumped a little too forward.
Me too.
Alright, we can do this.
What?!
It's okay, I believe in you.
You live for me.
Live on for me!
I'm about to die on purpose.
Yay!
I did it!
Oh my god, look!
It's like the android symbol!
Oh yeah, it is!
I assume like...
Oh, I assume I do this.
Yeah.
And then...
Oh.
Oh, I do small...
I'm small.
Okay.
Big time.
Wait, I have to launch you.
Maybe?
Or do you launch... Oh yeah, I do launch you.
Oh, we flip!
Our brain is expanding so much from this game.
Dude.
Wait.
Can I do something here?
What do I do?
Big?
Big.
Yeah.
Where am I?
You have to wind it.
Oh.
So I get down there.
No, no, wind it back.
Cause it's a spring.
Okay.
And then it launches me.
I figured it out.
It was the other way.
Hey!
I did it.
My god.
Sometimes I wonder how I... how my brain works sometimes.
Oh, relax.
How will people know I'm the world's greatest dad?
It's okay.
I don't think they need to know any lies.
This is why there's no world's greatest mom.
Whoa.
After all I've done for our house?
Like what?
What have you done?
You need to get closer.
You need to get closer, bitch.
What have you done?
What have you done for this house?
I work jobs to pay our bills!
While you sit there and make potato chips!
Yeah.
But you're eating them.
No one eats.
Oh!
You ate one!
No, that was a homemade rice cracker.
That's not what you said last night.
Son of a bitch.
What?
Now swing.
Oh, I have to put that there.
Alright.
Oh, we're like a pendulum!
Wee!
A pendulum?
A pendulum.
Yay!
Wow!
Okay!
Wait, which way is up?
You're alright, Mae.
Look, I'm up here!
I mean, that way.
We're gonna swing!
Wee!
Yeah.
This doesn't seem to be working okay.
I mean, we're alive.
So I think it's good progress.
Oh!
Here I go.
Small.
BB.
Don't worry, I'm heading over.
I'm very slow.
This is fucked up.
I can't see your screen anymore.
I'm here.
We do it?
We did it!
We opened it!
That should be all of them, right?
I think so.
Good teamwork.
See?
Even the game thinks we have good teamwork.
Look at that!
Oh, it's open.
I'll go on the other side.
Which way do I turn?
This way?
This room is this way.
Am I turning the right way?
I am!
Oh, here we go again!
Gumi is carrying this- What do you mean?
You need a fun dad!
Every relationship always has a fun dad.
And that's me.
I'm the good cop.
I wouldn't know.
The reason you fell in love with this beautiful man is because I was just so fun.
Put your feet away.
Collaboration.
Blah blah blah blah blah.
Oh, blah blah blah blah blah.
Huh?
Oh, you're pissing him off.
Blah blah blah blah.
Blah blah blah?
Collaboration.
We collabed!
We've collabed for like three hours now!
Don't worry.
Oh, wait, is that a game?
There's a game!
I've left.
I left too.
You gotta pick where I'm going.
I wait for you here in game town.
You fucking bitch.
Oh my god, it's tennis!
Check it out, man!
See, I'm so fun!
I let you experience fun things, Gumi.
My hand hurts.
I'm the fun dad!
We get to play!
We get to play games!
I need a nappy.
Gumi!
Fun dad!
Let's see what this is about.
Alright.
Hello?
Dodge the lasers?
Dodge the lasers.
Where's that?
Oh!
Oh, I see.
I see now.
Oh, I know where you're gonna throw the lasers.
Watch this.
Bam!
Dodged!
Oh, wait.
Oh, now.
Oh, no.
Now it starts.
Okay.
Oh, god.
Wait, this is not fun anymore.
This is...
Wait.
Oh, god.
Woo!
Fuck that!
Lock the fucking...
I'm trying!
No!
No, no, no!
I'm still up!
Oh, no.
Oh, the fun dad!
I'm still the fun dad.
You can't take this away from me.
Oh, no.
Why are you so good at this?
Yeah, I play a lot of...
Oh, my god!
Why are you so good at this?
I didn't get hit once.
You're so good at this one.
I think I'm better at reaction time.
You're better at the aiming thing.
Holy fuck.
That shit was intense.
Okay, which one?
Oh, wait.
There's multiple new ones, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's go to the beach.
Beach?
Wait.
Did we go to the beach?
Did we go on the wrong one?
I don't think so.
Oh, no.
We got the right one.
Okay.
You were so focused.
Oh, I have a door.
A little door.
I can't do anything.
Oh, my god!
I'm a pinball!
Get the pinball me!
No, no, no, no, no.
Right, right, right, right, right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here, here, here.
Oh, wait.
I can move.
Okay.
Don't worry.
I got this.
That's why I'm the fun guy.
I have to talk.
I actually have to watch your screen now.
What?
Who messed up now, huh?
Okay, fine.
That was on me!
I'll be honest.
I just wanted to see if you would die.
What the fuck?
I did it on purpose.
I'll be honest.
What the fuck?
We have to do this again.
I just wanted to see you die.
I was preying on your downfall.
That is so messed up.
You fucker.
You fucker!
Fucker.
After all you put me through today, it's well deserved.
What do you mean?
This is a team game!
We don't progress if you don't do it.
Hey, I'm having fun.
I'm having fun.
You bitch.
Don't worry.
Imagine if you missed.
That would be so messed up if I missed it.
Oh my god, I still get blown up.
That was the most painful game of pinball I have ever played.
We do what we have to, Cody.
I still fucking died.
That's so fucked up.
What is this?
I don't know, but you gotta climb it.
What the fuck is that?
What are you doing over there?
I hip thrusted a rocket.
You need to stop hip thrusting, man.
Stop.
I can never stop.
Why don't we have a second child yet?
That's on you.
What the fuck does that do?
I don't know.
What is this?
Oh, what the hell?
There it is.
It's over there.
You need to turn it off.
You need to turn it off!
Oh.
What was that?
I can't stop.
How was I supposed to know that I died?
You need to turn something on, clearly.
Do I do this?
Yeah.
Then I can do this.
Boop, boop.
I fucking...
I can feel you wanted to turn that on.
I thought about it.
You thought about it.
I can see your brain thinking about it there.
Okay.
I'm pressing it in now.
It's in.
I don't know if you noticed.
Hold on, what?
It's in?
Is it in yet?
I've said that before.
We were making our first child.
And that is why we only have one kid.
Wait, which color did you go into?
I went to the one on the left of what we just finished.
Which color?
Is this orange?
Oh, it's orange.
I was looking at your screen and not mine.
Cool.
Don't let anyone tell you otherwise.
Alright, I heal you.
Boop.
You can't find me.
Where do I go?
Do I go up here?
No, you're supposed to go straight forward.
I'm here.
Don't worry.
The husband is here.
Oh, I can hip-thresh this.
Watch this.
Ugh.
I have a lot of pent-up aggression right now.
No!
I'm dead!
Don't worry, I'm coming back.
There you go.
You wanna watch this?
Look at me go.
I'm a beautiful butterfly.
That was not beautiful.
Go big.
There you go.
Ew, the noise he made.
What the fuck do you mean?
He went, errrr.
I went big.
How do I get over to you?
Go big again, I think.
I'm checking.
I'm big.
Can you not jump on?
Jump where?
I can't jump anywhere.
Can I?
Because I lower it.
I don't think I can.
Oh, go tiny.
Go tiny.
Real quick.
Yeah?
No.
Wait, you go...
Oh, I know.
Wait, hold on.
Go on the other side.
Other side.
Okay.
Yeah, and then I jump down.
Oh!
And then you go big.
And then I go big.
Yeah.
And then I go small.
I go mega small.
Oh my god, we're doing it.
We're using our... We're putting our two brains together.
To make one full brain.
Hmm...
Um, I would say...
I have about 75%.
What?
What happened to the other percent of that brain then?
You're at a 25%.
Okay, nice.
Yes!
Whoops.
I still died.
You have to win for me!
I still died!
Okay, you have to go first.
Okay, I got it.
You have to go first!
You didn't win for me to go first!
No, I wasn't looking!
I can't use my eyes!
I'm blind!
I need my context clues!
Okay, see?
If we work as a team, things will get easier.
I don't know if you know that.
You're pissing me off.
Look, we can do this together.
Like a team.
I'm already here.
I let you... ladies first!
Ladies first!
Alright, I'm pushing it in.
Alright.
Playing a little music.
Ooh!
Nice.
In we go.
Stop fighting your tier and chat apart.
Oh!
Whoa, whoa!
What's this?
Oh, look at the boxes!
Big time!
Big!
Oh!
I went big.
Oh wait, you have to get below.
On the other side?
Because, like, look below me.
What do we have to do here?
Wait, there's something.
I see it, I see it.
There's like stuff here too.
What's over here?
Oh, do we have to grab all these little things?
Yeah.
Ow!
Okay, I figured it out.
We have to grab all these tiny things.
I'm heading higher.
Higher before anybody else.
Oh!
Boop!
Can I get big?
Grow up, get this out.
I can't get big though.
What do I do from here?
A feed time?
Oh, I can!
I'm glad.
I did it!
I got one!
Nice!
I got the second one.
Okay, and then...
Do I need to put this closer?
There you go.
I got one.
And then the next one is yours here.
That's the last one, I think?
Unless there's more?
No, there's one more.
Oh, the last one's like above here.
How do we do this?
Oh.
Oh, there's a tiny one here.
Oh!
I need you for the last one.
I'm gonna figure out what to do for this one.
Because it's inside this.
There's like boxes to your left.
Yeah, no, that...
I already got that one.
Oh.
I'm confused.
Oh!
I have to stop at the button!
That's what the button's for!
Oh.
Big!
Okay, and then...
There we go.
I already forgot about the button.
Yeah, I didn't see anything on my side.
Can you put it on the pillow?
Alright, now we have to do this one.
The final one up here.
Alright, I need you to take me to the other side.
I'm shrunk now.
I'm baby.
Baby!
Baby time!
Okay.
I'm going up.
Where is it gonna take me?
I'll never know.
Oh!
Oh, I almost dropped off.
I got the last one!
I did it!
I'm a hero, Gumi!
I'm a hero!
Obviously, we need to put this one over here.
Are you making them further apart?
Yeah.
Wait, I can help!
Okay.
And then...
Here.
And...
I'm gonna put this here.
Are we missing one?
No, right?
We got all of them, right?
Maybe we are missing one.
Oh, they said we can...
Oh, I know!
I got an idea!
We slanted.
Like here.
Oh, I got it!
I got an idea!
You need to reach this all the way up.
Wait, I think we can.
Yeah, and then we...
Yeah!
I'm so smart!
Look at my brain!
I told you!
This is exactly why you married me!
Look at that!
I told you.
I told you, Gumi.
I can be smart too.
This is true!
It's so true.
Look at that.
This is why I'm a catch.
This is exactly why I'm the catch here.
I'm the one that's 10 out of 10.
I'll press this.
I'll do the one here.
I turned everything.
Yeah!
Computer!
Defenses?
What does he mean?
Hold on, I'm waiting for you.
Oh, you didn't wait for me?
I'm here now.
What do we do here?
Wait for you for what?
I don't know.
Just make sure I'm here.
Wait, hold on.
We gotta swap it.
Oh, yeah.
There we go.
And then we swap this.
How do you swap?
Oh, from here!
Okay, give me a sec.
Wait.
Wait, I can't swap this.
Oh!
No, no, no.
Come here.
Come here, come here.
No, no, no.
Go stand on the one to the left.
No.
I'm thinking.
So you're gonna lock it.
Oh my god!
We're so smart!
Nice!
I knew I could figure it out.
We did it!
Together!
Alright, Dr. Hachine.
I see the current isn't making it through.
Can you go tiny and then wall jump up?
Yeah.
I'm doing it.
Boom, boom, boom.
And then I'm plugging it in.
It's in.
Overall happiness?
Happy, neutral, sad?
What?
Freak!
This guy's a freak.
Why is she monitoring our child?
Like...
Daily mood change.
She could be going through puberty!
You don't know that!
Puberty makes boys and girls do crazy things.
She could be a tween.
Yeah.
Yeah, still super creepy.
Hey, what does this do?
I agree.
Super fucking creepy.
The laugh tracker!
Dude, ours would be awesome.
I would be out of the fucking tracker, man.
I could break the chart.
Oh my god!
She's just like us for real.
Yeah, he's not a licensed therapist.
Exactly.
Where's his degree?
Oh?
Where is that taking us?
Oh, this is a gladiator.
I think it's a bus fight.
Yeah, this is a stadium.
This is a gladiator stadium.
Okay, how do we do this?
Oh, there's like red buttons here.
That's on you.
I'm trying!
I need you to grab this!
Nice.
See?
I did it.
I did something.
And we just jump.
We don't have to go anywhere.
The point...
Hey, Goomy, I don't think you should just stand still, Goomy.
I'm just saying.
Yeah.
You were like, I don't think we have to go anywhere.
So I was like, okay, I'm gonna zone out for a second.
I need help!
Get down!
And it broke towards me!
I am coming!
I'm coming!
We
did it!
So easy.
Come on.
Make this a little more difficult.
This is so easy.
Yes, aim at Goomy and not me.
Look at that dodge.
Ow.
It's okay, I have regen.
It's on you!
Where is the...
But it's over here!
On me!
You have to jump!
You have to...
I have to walk up a wall, man, not jump!
This is it!
Come over here!
We've got to get rid of that laser!
I'm doing it!
What am I doing?
You get the laser!
Don't touch things down there!
Nice, we did it.
See?
That was so hard.
Wait, if I was tiny...
If I'm mega tiny, they can't kill me.
Where am I?
I'm dead.
Don't die yet!
I figured out that you should not be tiny!
Don't be tiny!
What the fuck?
Oh my gosh.
Don't worry it.
How do we do this?
You dodged!
You dodged the fucking rocket, man!
Oh my gosh, it didn't work!
What is that?
I can't...
It's so hard.
It's so difficult.
I can't dodge.
I'm too stupid.
I didn't dodge!
Okay, you ride the rocket and then you try...
I'm doing my best.
I figured it out!
Look, look, look!
Look!
We did it!
Yay!
Wait, get in the ship!
Get in the ship!
Right here, go tiny!
I'm tiny, I'm tiny!
I'm in!
No more games!
What do I do?
Oh no, man.
Computer, computer, remove all limiters!
Oh my god, he's removing all limiters!
Don't worry!
Stop it!
Don't die, please don't die!
How did you die?
I wasn't patient!
Is that what you want me to say?
Doki!
I have so much I have to dodge!
It's okay!
It's okay, I'm not dying!
It's okay, I'm not dying this time!
I'm there!
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here!
What's this?
I'm here!
Just keep dodging!
Look, I'm here!
I can't look!
I'm almost there!
Don't die, don't die, I'm dying!
You're so good at that though!
You're so good at that!
It's the whole pomo party, did you say?
I thought you were really good at it!
I am really good!
That's why I've been lasting so long!
I've died three times!
I was confused!
He makes broken bikes on the path, Doki!
I was so confused!
DOKI!
I'm running out of space!
I'm almost there!
Don't worry!
Don't worry, Gumi!
I'm almost there, Gumi!
I'm almost there!
You got this, Gumi!
You got this!
I'm so good at this!
You fucking bitch!
I'm going to save you!
What about the pinball?
Trust me.
Yes, trust me, Gumi.
We keep trusting me.
I'm the shooter!
Where is he?
I thought you don't believe in screen peeking.
This game happened.
Where is he?
Oh there he is.
Oh wait.
No I didn't!
Wait what?
How did I miss?
Okay.
One last one.
Oh he's so close this time!
We did it!
We're such a good team!
How do we get back to Rose?
I can't let you harm her.
I'm her best friend!
Awwww.
We're an asshole!
I'm not an asshole!
I just know what's good for our daughter.
I'm gonna close my blinds.
The sun's in my eye.
I can ask Rose to play with you again.
But you have to help us get back to her.
Okay.
I'm back.
Is the monkey dead yet?
No man.
You won't make her cry.
Yeah yeah yeah.
We promise.
Of course we will never do that again.
Dude you're such a ghastly!
I like how... Oh my god so it's Deadpool super chat was like it's like Harambe all over again.
No!
There she is!
Rose!
Sweetie!
Darling!
Look!
This might look strange but it's us!
It's mom and dad!
Rose!
We need your help!
Look!
Rose it's us!
Oh my god why is she running?
Is she running her I'm running away letter?
She can't see us!
Oh my god this is like inside out.
We need to talk!
What the fuck you're hitting her!
CPS!
Darling!
Wait I can't do a British accent.
I was just saying if I talk in a British accent I can't do it.
Oh I can move like items!
Dude imagine she fucking thinks she's haunted now.
Oh shit!
Oh my god we're getting closer to math.
Oh she's gonna believe in ghosts now.
Let's Let's destroy something Rose loves to make her cry.
Whoa!
Goomy!
Rose loves her elephants.
It's her best friend.
You're gonna kill the elephant?
We make Rose cry.
Hey my bad.
I'll buy her a new one I promise.
Great idea!
You're enabling me!
Okay I'm an enabler.
Yeah I would admit.
I'm an enabler.
But you had the idea.
But you had the idea first.
Oh shit you clayface.
Oh!
My nose is itching.
Yeah that's the dust.
You must remember to clean under her bed.
Yeah.
Noted.
Alright here we go.
She has so many toys.
Oh my god look at all her socks.
Yeah exactly.
One less would be a good thing.
Wait there's a game here.
Where?
We have to buy a replacement.
Right?
No.
Wait look at this.
It's time for a new frame.
It's my favorite number.
8888.
Lately she's gotten attached to it again.
I don't know why.
Oh!
Wait was there an easter egg over on the left then?
I don't know I'll watch.
Alright give me a sec.
Oh look a little car!
Drive the car!
Oh there is!
There is a little car.
Oh.
I think I have to push you.
Yeah but is there like...
Do we have to do any of this?
There's a rodeo!
Wait come back!
Yeah just...
Oh I have to take you back.
Hold 8!
Yeah I'm coming back.
I'm coming back.
Oh the game was like behind us.
That was the main area.
Alright hold 8.
Oh!
Sorry I sneezed.
What?
There you go.
So you made it!
Oh!
Did you crash?
I'm stuck here.
I did it every time.
Every time.
I did it every fucking time.
Don't worry I'm getting you in right now.
I'm getting you in.
You're in.
What?
I crashed again!
Oh my god!
Okay.
You're in again.
Alright.
Okay we're good.
Okay.
We're good now.
I'm in.
Okay.
That means we're close.
Yeah we're closer to the sea.
Alright let's go to the rodeo.
One less would be a good thing.
Wait I'm getting the car first.
I think the car progressed it.
Doesn't it?
Yeah we'll just get a replacement.
Yeah yeah it like progressed it.
I think you should.
Okay
let's just find it.
Okay let's just find it.
I'm ready for the rodeo.
I can't get out.
I literally mean it.
What is wrong with your game?
What do you mean?
Why do you keep crashing me?
You couldn't get out!
You left the session!
I was able to keep honking it!
You exploded on my screen!
What do you mean?
I literally saw you explode on my screen!
Oh my god.
Let's go to the fucking radio.
Yay!
The rodeo!
Why don't we stop?
Stay on the bull as long as you can.
How do you do that?
I don't know.
Oh!
It's just a rhythm game.
So I assume it gets worse right?
Look at me go.
Oh my god.
So fucking easy.
Is that not B?
Why do I keep crashing?
Why?
Did you crash again?
Why does it keep happening?
In one last program!
Okay let's just not do the rodeo.
Let's not do the rodeo.
Let's just do the rodeo.
Let's just progress the game.
It's the server!
Oh my god!
It won't even let me connect to the server anymore!
Excuse me.
I think this was a good point to stop.
I think...
Goofy.
I think this is a good time...
It's not my PC issue!
It's connection!
It's not...
It's not even the PC issue.
You know...
It's okay.
We can finish it another time.
It's a server issue.
I think this is a good time though, Goofy.
I think our marriage has been quite solid so far.
Yeah, I know.
That was pretty cool.
It's pretty solid.
Did you have a great time?
I think I had a great time.
Yeah, I had an awesome time.
If you had to rate it out of 10...
Oh yeah, definitely an 8.
An 8?
Why isn't it a 9 at least?
What did I do that doesn't make it a 9?
I don't know.
Name one thing.
I remember you standing next to a button...
I don't remember that.
While I was fighting for my life against a moon baboon.
No, I don't remember that.
You don't remember that?
No, I don't know what you're talking about.
There.
But anyway...
That was fun!
What?
Did your chat know how far we are in the game?
How far are we, guys?
How far are we in this game, chat?
You guys know?
Out of how many?
We're at chapter 5!
We're 50%!
Hold on, I see that you have a poll up.
Who's the reason for the divorce?
71% Doki.
No, I don't.
We're at 50%!
Next week we're beating it.
We're beating it next week.
Give me a day.
No, next week.
We'll figure it out.
Okay, but I will say...
I'm not...
Actually...
No, I am here next week.
Alright, yeah.
Next week we'll finish it.
Yeah.
We can do it.
We're like speedrunning this.
It's so easy.
Yeah, it's so easy.
I think if we...
cut out all the times...
and we like...
clearly were just messing about...
We would have been...
We might be like...
We would have been 70% done...
if we didn't fuck around too much.
If we, as a team, together...
didn't fuck around that much...
I think we would have been like 70% done.
Yeah, I think if we...
both completed the challenges...
as fast as we could...
But we were just messing around.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We, as a team, were messing around...
together.
Together.
Anyway...
We're gonna call it here, guys.
Thank you all for coming.
I don't know if you're gonna call it here, Gumi.
I think you're gonna keep playing Minecraft.
I'm gonna call it here.
I'll see you next time, Gumi.
I'll message you after this.
Yeah, yeah.
Bye-bye, Gumi.
Bye-bye.
Bye -bye.
Alright, everybody.
I think I did really well!
I think I'm perfect husband material.
Don't you guys think so?
Yeah!
I honestly...
I honestly... like, I did not realize...
this game was like... had so many...
things in it.
The only thing I knew...
about this game was like...
the math part.
And I didn't realize how much more complicated...
this game was beyond math.
I was like, holy shit!
There's more to this game than just...
the math portion.
There's so much...
more!
There's...
bees and rats!
Tree rats.
Anyway, guys.
I'm gonna call it here everybody.
And take a rest day...
Take tomorrow as a rest day.
I'm gonna rest today.
Um...
I feel very, very tired.
Today was a very, very...
busy week for me.
So I'm...
going to... You know, I actually was tempted...
to like actually reschedule one of my...
streams.
Like, I think I was like...
thinking about rescheduling the...
steam stream.
Because I was feeling really, really tired.
But I was like, no!
No!
The happiest I feel is when I'm streaming.
And I know when I stream, I will feel so much better.
So like, I like push forward.
Because every time I was like, oh my gosh, I'm so tired.
I'm so tired and exhausted.
But I was like, no!
Doki.
You're happiest when you're streaming and you'll feel...
so much better you do the stream.
And I did!
I felt so much better.
Yeah, it does help.
I love streaming.
Um, and I always love streaming...
for you guys.
So it does help.
So I'm glad I did stream...
yesterday.
Um, but yeah.
I'm gonna take a rest now.
I'm sorry I can't do a little...
We haven't done like a little end of stream...
Zastadons in a while.
Or like do like super chat...
readings at the end.
Um, I'm still trying...
to like slowly... not slowly...
like fast adjust right now.
To everything going on.
There's so many like...
behind the scenes stuff that I always have to do everyday.
Um, so that's why there...
hasn't been much like Zastadons at the end yet.
When I finally stabilize...
we will have our... we will bring back...
a little chat together at the end...
of the streams and a little... the super chat...
readings at the end of the stream.
But yes!
Thank you everybody!
As always everyone...
stay hydrated, posture check, get up and...
move around.
Uh, to get that blood flowing.
And if you stay up for me, head to bed.
Cause you deserve it!
I'll see you guys next time everybody.
Bye guys!
Bye!