Hellooo!
Hello everybody!
Let me get my lo-fi in.
Give me a sec.
Now it's actual late night radio.
Hello everyone.
I hope the music isn't too loud though.
I'll turn it down a little bit just in case.
Oh, so this is gonna be... Hello!
Hello, hello guys!
So for those who are new here, what is Goodnight Dragoons?
Um... Goodnight Dragoons is just gonna be like... I think I'm gonna... I want to do this like...
I'm gonna try and do this like once every week.
Um, maybe like every Saturday or Friday.
Um, and it's basically like a chill late night session.
Because I always see a lot of Vtubers that do like morning radio shows or like morning streams.
And it'll be like... like, like you know, like, like mor... like, oh hey!
This is the first thing you listen to in the morning!
Um, I'm not a moron.
I'm a morning person.
As we all know, I'm not a morning person at all.
Uh, I'm most like... I'm mostly a night person.
A night owl.
So, uh, I was like, you know what would be better than a good morning radio show?
A good night radio show.
Because at least I'll be awake.
Uh, so usually I'll just do this like before I sleep.
Or like, you know, most likely, I don't know.
Sometimes I might be going to bed after the stream.
Maybe not because I do have a lot of work to do.
I've been procrastinating.
Not procrastinating, but like, um, I've been like taking a lot more naps than usual.
Uh, and because of that, I'm so behind on a lot of things.
I'm so, I'm so behind.
I have like so many things to do behind the scenes at the moment.
And I'm like, uh oh.
Uh oh.
Um, but that's basically it.
It's basically just like a late night, uh, like I guess you can call it like a late night podcast.
Oh my gosh, speaking of that.
Okay, this is a little already off topic.
But like, I don't know if you guys, there's been like a new trend at the moment.
Where, um, also I guess like the stream is also good for those who are on the other side of the world.
And you guys don't have to wake up super early for me anymore.
Um, well, for not, not anymore.
But like at least once a week, you guys have this afternoon slash a little bit of a stream.
I'm gonna set up the morning radio show for you guys on the other side of the world.
Um, so it's not that bad.
Cause like I usually rarely stream at these type of hours.
But I wanna do this, like I wanna try and be like super consistent.
I'm not gonna do this every day.
Cause, um, I don't have the stamina for that.
And like I, I, I...
I...
Guys, I, I need time to do other stuff too.
So...
So, this is just gonna be like maybe I'll try to do this like every Saturday.
Um, every Saturday at the same time.
Like 9pm PSTNList or something.
That's happening on Saturday.
I'm gonna try to make this like super consistent on having this every Saturday.
Um, and I chose Saturday because, um...
I see it as like, you know, the weekend type deal.
For people in NA.
So like, cause I know like, you know, 9...
It's, it's 1am... what is it?
It's like midnight for the Easties over there.
It's midnight for the Easties over there.
So like you have an excuse to stay up for like, you know, like...
For a little bit longer.
You stay up for a little bit longer for the stream.
And, um...
And, ah...
And it's also like not too early for those on the other side of the world.
And not too...
Cause I want it to be like the perfect balance.
Well, it's not perfect.
But like a good balance between like, you know, uh...
People in NA and people on the other side of the world.
And I'm very sorry to the EU goons though.
People in SA too.
I'm really sorry for the EU goons.
Because like, um...
EU goons ain't fucking faring so well lately.
I'm so sorry for the EU goons.
I'll try my best.
Um...
You guys still have your 12.30pm streams though.
So...
At least...
At least you got that.
It's always so hard though.
Um...
I always want to have like...
At least one stream.
For some...
Like for people around the world.
Um...
Always just one stream for you.
Like at least...
Not one.
But like at least one stream where...
Where people can catch my streams.
You know, like...
Just at least one of them.
So...
So I try my best to balance as best...
As much as I can.
Uh...
Mehdi!
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Doki's very own late night talk show.
The next Jimmy Fallon.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Jesus.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Oh my god.
As someone in NA who's maintained aircraft on the mid shift.
This is great for me.
I'm so glad you're making this a thing.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Oh my god.
Jesus.
You have your own very...
Own plane.
Oh yes.
I forgot.
Doki Airlines.
You reincarnated into a plane.
Thank you Jesus.
Uh...
Crow.
Doki.
Go to bed.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
I actually...
Okay.
I think it's just because I've been like working a lot lately.
But...
Um...
I've actually...
Uh...
I've been like taking a lot of naps lately.
So...
Um...
The past like...
I think the past like...
Three plus days I've been like napping more.
Um...
I think it's because like I've been working a lot lately.
So...
My energy level has been like a lot lower than usual.
Um...
And...
Like...
Oh my gosh.
I felt really bad because...
During that collab...
Uh...
With Juna, Bri, and Kai...
My brain was so fucking fried.
Because I just woke up from a nap.
And I don't know why I do this.
I always be like...
I was like...
Okay...
Doki...
Uh...
What...
This nap won't fuck you up too badly.
Every time.
I don't...
Oh my god.
Every time.
I don't...
I need to learn to not nap before stream.
Because like...
I'm like...
My brain was like...
Trying to wake up before...
Before like...
Uh...
Before the stream.
And then like...
They were all like talking a lot.
In the...
In the call.
And I was just like...
Yeah...
I felt...
I felt so awkward before the stream.
Because I was still waking up.
So my brain was just like...
Oh...
Because like they all know each other.
I didn't...
I didn't really...
I was like the new person in the group.
Um...
So I was just like...
Oh gosh.
I feel awkward.
Oh my gosh.
My brain isn't...
Wired yet to be...
To like...
Interact with people.
My intro...
Introvert self is like...
Slowly waking up.
I felt less clever...
During the collab.
I felt like...
Oh my gosh.
I was rewatching the collab.
And I was like...
Oh my god.
If I was more awake...
I would have said this instead.
I would have been...
I would have been like...
Oh...
I would have like...
Role played more.
If I...
If I was more awake...
I would have been like...
You know...
We were making the jokes about the elderly.
I would have been like...
Sud...
Why don't you visit me in the retirement?
I would have said...
Shit like that.
I was like...
Oh my god.
Doki...
If you were more awake...
You would have been so much more clever in this collab.
You would have said more funny things.
I was like...
Doki...
Why are you just being reactive?
You would have been so clever if you were more awake.
Doki...
Lord Karosus...
Thank you for the akasupa.
Thank you.
I learned that taking naps are worthless.
I woke up one day in middle school.
And I was like...
I've been exhausted ever since.
Thank you for the akasupa.
Thank you.
I let my clippers down.
What would they clip from me now?
I'm glad you guys still like the collab.
I always want to try it.
I always want to improve myself in content creation.
So I was just like...
Oh my god.
I could have said this.
I could have said that.
But yes.
I do rewatch my VODs.
Just to be like...
Okay.
What can...
Not like...
Not like critique myself.
I rewatch my commentary skills.
I'm not going to critique my commentary.
But it's just like...
Technical wise.
I rewatch my VODs.
For technical wise.
And also like...
Sometimes I'm like...
Whoa.
I'm actually really funny.
I rewatch my VODs.
I was like...
Wow.
I'm actually really funny.
I'll be like...
I can't believe I came up with that.
Like...
But like...
I don't know.
Like today...
I rewatched the collab VODs.
I was like...
Oh my god.
I could have been funnier.
Like...
Oh my god.
Today I was like...
Today I actually was like...
Oh my god.
If I said that...
It would have been so fucking funny.
Why didn't I say that?
Because like...
You know how it's like...
I was a demon.
And we were joking about the bachelor party.
I could have been like...
Wow.
Who ordered a number 15?
Boutchika.
Wow.
I could have said that.
I was like...
Oh my god.
I set up the perfect joke.
I was like...
You were such a good chemicals...
And I didn't go full sugar.
A wig Dokie would have went full sugar.
I had done perfect donation.
Dokie.
You had done perfect thing.
You could have run.
Because I kept...
Like...
I was the demon.
I kept doing that attack where you're basically the bachelor party type deal.
I was like, I can't believe it.
I set up the perfect joke for this and I didn't.
There was no payoff.
I threw.
I fucking threw.
It would have been so good.
Anyway, yeah, my brain actually, my brain was like not awake.
It like slowly booted up.
The comedy sector of my brain was not fucking on at that time.
I need to remind myself to not take naps.
Not like, okay, to not take naps before a stream.
Because I swear to God, I feel like, I feel like...
I'm just like not... I realize I'm not as funny if I taking naps before the stream.
I was like, I was like, oh my God, I'm definitely funnier if I just don't take naps before the stream.
I definitely, I need to remind myself not to do it.
I need to remind myself not to nap before streams.
Because my brain just doesn't have enough time to boot up, boot up and be active.
And actually like, and actually create content.
Because I'm like still, still like legarthic and stuff like that.
Anyway, also, oh yeah, I got distracted a little bit, but I was also inspired.
I was also like inspired by...
It's the newest trend right now.
It's like a newest trend in content creating.
Where content creators are making these like new channels.
New channels where they edit their VODs in a way, they make compilation.
And they edit the VODs in a way where it's like videos you put before you start...
Like videos you put before you sleep type deal.
Like white noise.
Have you guys seen that lately?
I've been like, okay, wait.
There's this channel I've been like play...
It showed up on my recommended recently.
And it's been like...
So, oh my gosh, let me see if I can find it.
It's been showing up in my recommended.
I've been like watching it regularly.
Like whenever I before...
Like when I'm like heading to bed, I just put it on on my phone.
And just play in the background.
Just to like help me sleep because it's like white noise.
I'm trying to figure out...
Remember like what channel it was.
It was like showing up in my recommended a lot.
Yeah, sleep channels.
So, it's basically like a lot of like content creators now recently are making channels dedicated to like...
Giving me like editing the VODs in a way where you can play in the background.
And they basically like mute and lower all the loud sounds on those videos.
And then they like mute and like lower the sounds and remove all the screams and everything.
And so like you can put it...
It's like the same vid.
It's almost the same video.
Just like you can put it in a background and you wouldn't like wake up to it.
Like stuff like that.
I'm trying to remember what channel it was that kept playing.
I kept getting recommended of...
That's basically...
Oh, it's fine.
Also...
Thank you for the magenta soup.
Thank you.
Finish watching your stream tips video.
Here's the tuition I can spare.
Just wondering though.
Should there be a personal Twitch to watch others and a work Twitch to stream as?
Thank you for the content.
No, because...
Why?
There's no point in having separate Twitch channels unless you want to be like incognito.
I don't have separate Twitch channels.
I usually just use one.
So...
So honestly like there's no need to unless you want to be like secret about who you want.
But even then you just get like BTTV.
I think that's that is it.
Yeah.
If you get BTTV, you can...
There's like anonymous mode where it logs you out of the Twitch chat.
It logs you out of the Twitch chat.
So like they can't...
People can't track where you're...
Who you're watching.
But obviously it's only available on...
It's only available on like PC.
It's not...
It doesn't exist on mobile.
So like I usually never watch streams on my phone anymore.
Because like...
I've noticed...
I've noticed people have been like stalking who I watch.
And then people would like at me in the chat.
And would be like, Whoa, Doki's here.
So...
So I just...
I just watch on PC.
Because...
I just watch on my PC because I have the...
I have the plugin that like puts me in anonymous mode.
So like people can't like look in the chat.
Like I'm like, Oh, I have to go to the chat list to find me.
Yeah.
There's like...
I was like, Oh, that's awkward.
Sean, thank you.
Thank you.
That sounds like a scam.
The brainwash viewers...
Thank you.
I'm trying to remember that channel.
Okay.
I'm gonna like...
I'm gonna be like PNG for like one second.
Give me a sec.
Guys, this is important.
Like, now I'm dedicated.
I need to know.
I need to know what...
Because like, I always like, I put that channel in the background, but I can't remember it on top of my head now.
Now it's like, in my... now I'm like, you know like those moments where you're like, oh my god, what is it?
That's me right now.
That's me.
What do you mean?
Okay, there.
Oh, okay.
Was it Cat... Catty... Caris?
Catty... Caris?
I think that's... is that his name?
Was that the... he has a sleep channel, right?
Catty... Caris... Sleep.
Oh yeah, yeah!
Catty Sleeps!
Yeah.
This... this guy's video... this guy's like, videos...
has been like, in my recommended... for so long.
And it really helps.
I don't know what the fuck...
Okay, not gonna lie...
Okay.
Not gonna lie, I'll say this... I... I have no idea what his videos are.
Like, every time I put... I just put it in the background for actual white noise.
I have... I have no idea what his content is.
I literally forget what his content is.
I just put it on it because it was just really good white noise.
I just put it on as a background... ooh, something fell.
What fell?
Okay, not important.
I... I put it in the background and then he's like...
And I'm like...
So... I just... this is... like, I got a lot... there's also like, did you know... did you know gaming also has one too?
Did you know gaming?
Sleep.
I think it's... yeah, what was it?
Okay, did you know...
Video game facts to sleep?
Sleep too.
Yeah, this one.
I also have... I also do this one too.
Miku!
Thank you for the super chat!
Thank you, thank you!
Hi Dokie!
Just came from your Holokitty stream.
Sad I wasn't able to catch you live.
But so happy to know you, Sam.
Your Oshis are my Oshis too!
Tsudamono's too cute!
Thank you for the super chat!
Thank you, thank you!
That's fucking right.
You never forget your first... never forget.
I talked... I told this story before.
But for those who don't know about my history with Sanrio stuff...
So like... also I hope that... is the music okay at an okay volume chat?
Is the music at an okay volume by the way?
But yes, anyway...
As I was saying, when I was like, growing up...
It wasn't just... I never had like a favorite Sanrio character.
Until... until... I... until I saw Tsudamono.
Wait, there's music?
Okay, I'll turn it up a little bit.
I'll turn it up a little bit.
Alright, so I never had a... I've never had a favorite Sanrio character until Tsudamono came into...
Came into the picture.
And the thing is...
Before then, it was... there used to be... I don't know if it's still around.
I don't know if it's still around.
But there was this other... it was a Korean... I think it was Korean store.
It was like, Goodnight Bear.
I think that's what... is that what he's called?
Goodnight Bear... no, that's not him.
It's that blue bear.
Blue bear... is it Korean?
Oh, it's literally Blue Bear!
Oh my god!
His name is... his name is literally Blue Bear!
Okay, so...
Um...
So... basically...
There was this... there was these stores going around.
I don't know if they're still... I don't think they're popular anymore.
I honestly don't think they're popular anymore.
Um...
In NA.
I knew they were like... they were super fucking popular back then when I was growing up.
But I think the company was called like Morning Glory.
And um... I used to... like my mom used to buy me a lot of like...
Um... like the mascot characters.
From... um...
From the... the comp... like from the store.
Uh... and I used to be like obsessed with Morning Glory.
There was this other one.
I saw someone... like I retweeted it too.
The R.
There's like the Korean bunny.
I'm trying to remember the Korean bunny.
Like...
Uh...
Like he's like... not... not... I'm not talking about Molang.
I'm talking about the... the... the OG Korean bunny.
Hehehehehehehehehehehehe.
Does anyone remember?
I retweeted the... someone... you remember?
The... someone artwork of it.
Like a parody.
The... Oh... No.
Not Molang.
That's like... that's like current Korean bunny.
But there was like the OG Hehehehehehehehe.
Is it Mashi?
Oh yes!
Yes!
It's Mashimato!
Okay!
I was fucking obsessed with uh...
Mashimato and a blue bear.
Hehehehehehehehehehehehe.
That's the... That was the original.
It's the original Korean bunny.
Now everybody knows about Mulan, but Mashimaro was the OG.
The OG Korean bunny.
Thank you for the akasupa.
Thank you, thank you.
Since you're a person who sleeps 17 out of 24 hours, I need advice on how to sleep quickly when my brain doesn't want to stop.
Thank you.
Okay, thank you for the akasupa.
Thank you, thank you.
Straight up, put white noise.
This is how I fall asleep.
I just put white noise of any YouTube video.
Usually the best ones are like podcasts or like someone, you know, it's just non-stop yapping.
So I'll just like...
Just play like any YouTube video or like Twitch streams or anything.
You can do music as well.
Music doesn't work as well for me when I sleep.
So I just put like podcasts or like commentary videos.
Or I used to sleep to Apex streams back then.
Now I just put on like random long videos.
It has to be super long too.
Like maybe like 20 plus minutes.
I choose a video between 20 plus to an hour.
So like, you know, if I...
Wake up, the video will still be going.
And it really helps a lot with falling asleep.
And like I can't really...
And also like when you're putting these videos, they're talking a lot too.
They're talking a lot.
So like your brain doesn't think about like, you know, anything else in your thoughts.
You're just thinking about like you're just...
Your brain is just focused on the white noise that's playing around.
That's playing on your phone.
And honestly, like I have no idea what any of the videos talk about.
Like I have zero memory of any of the videos that play when I go to sleep.
It just like my brain just deletes all of that information afterwards.
But that's basically how it helps me go to sleep too.
But yeah, anyway, as I was saying, the old...
Before Sanrio, I...
My mom would buy me a lot of those like from the Morning Glory company.
Like the stores.
There used to be so many of the stores where I used to live.
And I would have like...
I don't think they're like as popular anymore.
I think they got replaced by a lot like similar stores.
But it's not Morning Glory anymore.
But I used to have like a lot of stationery.
A lot of like pencils.
Oh, you know like those lead pencils?
Where...
Oh my gosh.
Okay.
Okay, it's like...
I don't know if people still use these.
But as a kid, instead of lead pencils, it's like...
They're like little capsules.
Wait, I'm gonna get a picture.
I can show the picture on screen.
I wish I know what it was called.
But they're like little capsules.
And then you...
After you finish using them, you plug it out.
And then you put it on the top.
And then like, you know, another capsule will come out.
Does anyone remember those?
They used to be so popular for children.
Yeah, they used to...
Yeah, they used to be like incredibly popular for kids.
I don't think people use them anymore because they realized it was so...
What's the word?
It was very environmentally unfriendly.
It was incredibly wasteful.
I'm pretty sure.
Because like, you know, after you finish using them, you know...
You can't do anything anymore.
So I'm pretty sure.
Also a choking hazard.
You're right.
It was most definitely a choking hazard.
But kids loved it.
But I honestly, I don't know what it was called.
I just remember I would...
There was like...
I used to use those because like that's what my mom bought for me before I went...
Before I started using lead pencil.
They were like...
They were pretty fun though.
More balls.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
I drew the artwork of you.
Of you.
Mashimoto version.
I didn't know you would know this.
Of course.
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
KR bunny.
And also thank you so much for the retweet.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Of course.
It's the OG Korean bunny.
Yeah, it's like a little dart Lego.
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure like because it was definitely like a choking hazard.
And also not very good for the environment that it definitely quickly died out like...
It's definitely definitely people realize like oh that is not very safe for kids.
We should we should stop.
We should stop making them stacking up pencils.
Okay, let me see.
Yes.
That's what they are.
And then I would...
Okay, wait.
Blue bear.
Is that the blue bear version?
No!
Where the fuck is that blue bear?
Okay, blue bear.
Blue bear stationary.
Okay, let's see.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, I'm like looking at all the...
Oh my I had like so many of these things.
Oh, I had this before.
Wait, no, that's bootleg.
Nevermind.
I did not have this before.
I...
Wait, did I?
Okay, I had this but it was the not bootleg version.
Like...
Also, Pat said thank you for the 20 gifted chips.
Thank you.
Oh my gosh.
My mom would like...
I remember my mom would buy...
Would buy these types of...
Would buy like these types of stationery for me because it was like, you know, a fucking bargain.
Like all in one special, you know, like that type of deal.
But, also, like the non...
The non-bootleg version.
Just so you know.
Oh my gosh.
I'm looking at the morning...
Oh my gosh, I love how like the Morning Glory store just puts us in a model now.
Just it's just Sanrio products now.
No!
You have your own.
Morning Glory.
Why are you selling your own?
I'm so sad.
My childhood is getting absorbed by all the other monopolies.
Oh my god.
My childhood.
They're getting absorbed by all the other monopolies.
Oh, back in my day.
Fox, I don't know if you guys know this, but back in my day, Fox channel, like, the Fox channel used to be its own network.
I know.
It's so crazy.
I know it's insane.
You mean Disney didn't own like 80% of the media?
No fucking way!
Prop, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Goodnight, Doki Bird.
Sleep tight and plenty and keep on smiling for next day and next day and next and so on.
T, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
I would not be surprised if Disney just absorbs like 10% more of the media around us.
What else is next?
Okay, ABC is also Disney.
Um...
Fox is now Disney.
HBO... I don't know.
I don't know if...
I don't know if Disney can actually buy HBO.
Who owns HBO?
Anyway, who owns HBO?
Let's see.
Who owns...
Who owns HBO?
HBO.
Casey Bloys.
Who are you?
Oh yeah, Warner.
Honestly?
With the rate Warner Brothers is going?
Alright.
Somebody quote me on this in 10 years.
I bet you in 10 years, Disney is gonna buy Warner Brothers.
I bet you guys.
This is what's gonna happen.
In 10 years, Disney is gonna own Warner Brothers because I fucking...
I don't care.
I don't care if this guy watches me because like...
And if he does, I say that's an honor that the Warner Brothers CEO watches this stupid dumb VTuber.
But like I fucking hate the Warner Brothers CEO.
He's like the worst CEO that we've ever seen.
He's like the worst CEO that we've ever had for Warner Brothers.
And with the rate he's going, like all he fucking cares about is like meeting the...
Like finance... like meeting the fucking financial line.
And I bet you... I bet you I would not be surprised if Disney offers that guy like a lot of fucking money.
He'd take it.
100%.
He does anything for tax breaks.
I bet you he would fucking take... he would take the money.
Anyway.
Please don't copy strike me on any games I play from Warner Brothers.
Please.
I really... I really like the Batman games.
Please let me continue playing the Batman games.
I would really appreciate it.
Please.
You'll get nothing from copyright striking me.
Like I get like... like it'll be like pennies.
Please.
Don't tell...
Oh my gosh.
By the way, I got hit by limited ads.
I got hit by limited ads on my collab.
I must have swore... did I swear in the beginning?
Someone pull up my collab stream right now and tell me how long did it take to hear the first swear word.
I submitted an appeal already.
But like somebody pull up the stream right now and tell me how long it took for me to swear.
I need to... I need to find the sweet spot.
I need to figure out what is the sweet spot of like the amount of time I can like basically like...
So you know it's like oh you cannot swear in the first like X amount of minutes.
And then I need to figure out... I need to tie myself.
I need to wait until like 10 to 15 minutes until I swear.
First 10 minutes.
Okay guys.
Maybe I play the intro for 10 minutes.
I'm getting straight.
Maybe I just... I just play the intro for...
And was that 3 minutes and 50?
Bro!
We didn't even last one... like less... we didn't even last 2 minutes.
Oh my god.
We didn't even last 2 minutes before we went into swear mode.
That's so fucked up.
That's so fucked up man.
Peter, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Current Warner Bros.
CEO is speed running bankruptcy.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Gladstone, thank you for the super chat.
Just gotta learn to say frick instead of the other F word.
Okay I swear to god if I get like limited for the stream...
Guys, did I swear?
I don't remember.
Did I swear in the first 10 minutes?
Today.
For this stream right now.
Did I swear in the first 10 minutes?
Cause I don't fucking know.
Yes but it's already after 10 minutes.
I can... it's already like...
It's already like...
What?
Oh my gosh.
How long have I been streaming?
It's already been like 30... 38 minutes?
Has it already... oh my gosh.
I fucking don't stop yapping.
It's already been like 38 minutes and like...
Time flies by so fast.
Um...
But yeah.
I learned that...
I don't... it must be a new rule.
Cause I was... I would never get hit in the past.
And I like... swore so much.
I used to never get hit by the limited ad shit.
Um... in the past.
So they must have recently changed the algorithm or something.
I just hate that.
I hate it because obviously I don't get the ad revenue.
Um... I don't get the ad revenue for like the first couple of hours.
Uh... because they hit me with the limited ads.
And because of that...
Um... because...
And like people usually watch the VOD.
You know like...
After the stream ends, people would watch the VOD instantly.
So it's like...
Nooooo!
YouTube!
Yeah the most important hours!
Nooooo!
Um...
But...
It was there before...
No that's the thing!
Um... on my previous channel...
I rarely if ever get hit with limited ads.
It only happens when...
Uh... I usually only get strike by like music stuff.
And it was...
I would never get strike for...
This is like...
It's been the first time.
It's been the first time I've been like getting strike for profanity.
Uh... which has been very surprising.
D2H!
Thank you for the AKASUPA!
Thank you!
Honestly I could figure out what to say.
It was bouncing between a genuine question or a DN joke.
But I can't do that to my Kamiyoshi.
Just answer me this.
Any thoughts on playing Metro?
Thank you for the AKASUPA!
Thank you!
Um...
Depends on like which Metro series.
Uh...
I might try Metro at a later time.
I think like I stopped because like...
I think I...
I don't know why I stopped.
I think it's because like there was too long...
It was too long of a break in between.
So like I just stopped playing it.
Um...
I think I'm gonna try and find a Metro game.
I might start on a Metro game that was considered more the popular one.
Because I don't think I actually...
I don't think I like enjoyed the one I played.
I don't even remember which one I played on stream.
I actually...
I actually don't remember!
I don't think I enjoyed that one.
Um...
As much as I would have liked it.
I mean as much as...
I...
I don't think I enjoyed it as much as I would have liked.
So I feel like I should try to find...
I should try and start one that I...
That was considered like...
Um...
Like universal appeal.
A lot of...
A lot of people are asking me because I talked about Fallout.
Um...
It's really good.
I highly recommend checking out the Fall...
I feel...
Fallout show.
I feel like we're in a generation where like gamers are now making the shows for like video game adaptations.
Um...
And I feel like we're at a point where we have people who actually play games.
And they play video games making good adaptations of...
Of...
Video...
Like...
Of like...
Um...
Like of video games.
And...
Um...
Okay.
The Halo series.
We don't mention the Halo series because the Halo series was literally made by a group of creators who don't even...
Who don't even like play video games.
They literally don't care about Halo.
The writers basically...
Never played Halo.
The only exception...
The only... I think the only exception for that was like Last of Us.
Because the creator... I think the creators of Last of Us...
The creators of Last of Us actually played the game.
But they told the actors to not play the game.
But the... the creators and the writers and the producers, they know the story of Last of Us and they actually play the game.
But...
They told the actors, they're like, no, do not play the game.
We want you to act without any of the knowledge of what's going on in the video game.
And...
But they were still pretty faithful to the Last of Us game.
But yeah, I think like the Halo...
The people in Halo, they did not know what the fuck was going on.
Twisted meta?
Okay, twisted meta?
Like...
There's no...
Not gonna lie...
I don't... I don't think the video game...
Has much lore.
Like...
It was...
The game was just about like people in cars, like beating each other up in cars.
So like...
I... I feel like the game itself didn't really have a lot of lore to build off of.
So...
I was so surprised that...
I was...
I was so surprised that the show...
Actually...
Like...
Did something.
What do you mean as what?
What's the lore?
I feel like...
Okay...
Like...
Like I meant like more...
I've only played one twisted meta game.
But also I was like super fucking young.
And I feel like...
I feel like...
The people...
Like okay, if you look at the other games...
The really successful adaptations...
A lot of the game...
A lot of them had like...
A lot of people like know about the lore of these games.
Like Fallout has an extensive lore.
Last of Us has an extensive lore and story.
But like...
Twisted Metal...
All I remember about Twisted Metal was that clown and then cars.
And then cars.
And then they made a whole entire story.
Based off of like...
A car.
I was like okay.
But yeah, anyway.
I highly recommend...
Like I feel like a meme about like oh video game...
Video game adaptations is like almost non-existent anymore.
Because there's been more...
There's been more like home runs than there is duds in general.
And I honestly feel like...
I honestly feel like we're at a time where people actually know how to make good video game adaptations.
Because they're running out of sequels to do.
People are tired of fucking superhero films.
And people are tired of superhero films.
And people are tired of sequels.
Video game adaptations is the next niche.
We're at an era of video game adaptations now.
Honestly, it's true.
It's true.
It's not about superheroes anymore.
It's all about video game adaptations now.
We're at the new stage.
A new era.
What's that word called?
You know, like the next peak of cinema?
Fuck, what's that word?
What's that word called?
I forgot what it's called.
My English is deteriorating.
The next mainstream thing.
It's the next mainstream act!
And we're getting Warhammer 2!
The next era!
We have the next meta.
Yes, it's the next meta!
No more superhero meta!
We're in the video game meta now!
I think it's also because we have the graphics.
We have the ability to do CGI now.
Of like actual video game CGI.
So, I mean, okay, here are like...
Alright, the good ones.
There was Fallout.
There's Last of Us.
The Witcher.
Until like they fired half the writing crew.
The writers.
Yeah, until they fired some of the writing crew.
And also Henry Cavill.
Arcane.
What else?
There's so many.
Sonic was pretty good too.
Sonic.
Mario.
Umm...
The Witcher was good until it wasn't!
Alright guys?
You can't blame them!
Cyberpunk.
Umm...
There's been so many like actual decent ones.
Okay, Detective Pikachu was pretty fun.
Yes.
Detective Pikachu was pretty fun.
Only because of Ryan Reynolds.
If it wasn't for Ryan Reynolds, I think the movie would have been...
Pretty shit.
Not gonna lie.
Ryan Reynolds is the only reason why Detective Pikachu was as good as it is.
Because if you take Ryan Reynolds out, the other actors were so bad.
No offense to the other actors.
But they were not as memorable or as good.
Umm...
Deadpool.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
We're currently at the end of the video.
Finally in the Dune era.
But next year, video games will rise like the...
What?
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Who's that?
I'm scared of saying their name because I don't know who they are.
Oh, it's from Dune!
Okay.
I was like...
I'm scared.
I don't want to get baited into saying something.
Yeah, I haven't seen Dune by the way, guys.
I haven't seen Dune.
I was just worried.
Worried I'm getting baited.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Leah, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
I haven't watched Dune yet.
The only thing I know about Dune is that the...
The only thing I know about Dune is the...
It's the movie theater...
Cup holder for Dune.
Have you guys seen it?
Oh!
Have you guys seen that?
Oh, is it a popcorn bucket?
Have you guys seen it?
Don't worry guys.
I can show this on stream.
I think...
Because it's a popcorn bucket!
Guys, look at this.
This is the only thing I know about...
Dude... the fucking... the fucking... it's a popcorn bucket!
You stick your hand in it!
Your hand!
You stick your hand!
The only appendage that should go in there to grab the popcorn.
And then eat the popcorn.
Oh yeah, that's the only thing I know about Dune.
It's just this.
That's literally my only knowledge.
But...
But yeah, that's like...
Everything I know.
Anyway, as I was saying, I feel like...
It's gonna be interesting what...
What the new... what is it?
The Warhammer movie is gonna be because it's gonna start... it's gonna be like...
Oh, is it gonna continue the trend of actual decent video game adaptations?
But oh also, also, also I was gonna say... yeah, but yeah, check out...
You gotta... you guys gotta check out Fallout.
I think if you really like the games... if you really like the games...
if you really like the lore, if you just like Fallout in general... even if you don't like Fallout.
I think it's like really interesting to watch.
It's actually really decent I'm only on the first two episodes The first episode was so good That I had to click next.
Like I was like, I want to watch the next one But you guys can get tell me all the spoilers because I already read a lot already... guys I already read the wiki I already read the wiki I got into the rabbit hole of... you know how like when you click one article and then you click on the next article and then you click on the next article?
So like, I was like, oh man, Vault 33, Vault 32, and Vault 31.
That's so interesting.
Because like, I love the lore behind Fallout because I thought it was like... it's just very interesting to read.
And like, if you guys don't know the lore of like the Vaults, each Vault...
Each Vault has like a different experiment going on.
So I was curious.
I was like, oh, what is this Vault's like science experiment?
So they'll like do like a social experiment with each Vault.
Like with each Vault.
And the Vault is where like they put all the people in there and stuff like that.
And then I was like, oh, okay, I want to know what the Vault... what their social experiment is.
Or like the science experiment is going on in that Vault.
Like in the Vault we're looking at.
And then so...
I got into a whole fucking rabbit hole of...
Of the show.
So I sort of know how it... I sort of know how the show ends.
But like I'm on episode two.
Um...
There's like... so like if you guys don't know about the Vault lore.
There's one Vault where it's just filled with clones named Gary.
And all they say is Gary.
Uh...
And... and um...
There's another Vault.
There's a... there...
Oh, I know you guys are curious about this Vault.
You must be like, what's in Vault 69?
It's... they basically in Vault 69 is one guy and then all women.
That's what's in Vault 69.
Real... this is actually real lore by the way.
I'm not making this shit up.
Like that's actually what's in Vault 69.
Um...
They knew, of course, they know every fucking gamer is a ten-year-old inside.
Okay.
No, not ten-year-old.
That's the wrong age.
Puberty 14.
Okay.
Every gamer game developer is a fourteen-year-old.
Has a fourteen-year-old inside.
Sorry.
I just think about what age do people hit puberty.
And I was like ten is not the right age for puberty.
Right age!
14 is much better!
The inner 14 year old.
But yes, and then I think those were the most ridiculous ones for me.
I think there was one where...
I can't remember, there was like another vault...
where...
I can't remember.
There was like one vault where it was like one guy...
and then it's all puppets.
So they want to see like how insane...
like will they be able to function as a human being...
with no socialization except for the puppets?
And obviously the answer is no.
Yeah, no.
That person was not okay.
The puppet man.
Yeah, the puppet man.
Wait, did Penny Arcade actually write that one?
Wait, Penny Arcade?
Oh my God, that's a name I...
I fucking...
That's a name I haven't heard in so long.
Are they still like...
Is it still alive?
How?
Holy shit!
The creators of Penny Arcade is almost in his 50s.
That's... Oh my God!
I think a lot of people feel so old right now.
Oh my God!
He's in his... He's almost in his 50s.
They're 46 and 48.
They were like the OG gamer comics.
You're better off being a ghoul than him most of this world.
Guys, okay.
We'll see other...
Oh God, Cyanide and Happiness.
Bro, I'm so sad.
Cyanide and Happiness.
They still make really good games.
They still make really good content.
But because they're like super old now, people don't watch Cyanide and Happiness anymore.
I still like...
I still like watch it ever so often.
Like there'd be like a gaps in between before I like watch Cyanide and Happiness again.
And the creators of Cyanide and Happiness, he's 30...
Okay, not as old.
Not as old.
So not as old.
36.
That's pretty good.
36 to 39.
That's decent.
That's pretty good.
It makes you feel less old now.
Bro, I used to love Cyanide.
I actually owned...
I owned several hard copy books of Cyanide and Happiness.
I have like...
I actually...
I kickstarted a bunch of their game like board games as well.
Because like I honestly I just love their content.
And don't say 30.
Look, 36 is pretty decent.
Not as bad as 48.
I can't believe Penny Arcade.
Like the creators are like 48.
Oh my god.
They're like the OGs too.
Okay.
Um...
Oh my god.
This is like blast from the past.
But does anyone remember that fucking Cartoon Network comic of...
Oh my god.
Does anyone remember?
Because it was like...
Okay, these were the comics that people used to read back then.
It was...
Um...
It was Penny Arcade.
I think Grim Tales.
I think that was how it was like Cartoon Network.
But what if they're like super fucking edgy?
And it was like super fucking edgy.
So it was like people would read...
Um...
Penny Arcade.
Grim Tales.
Uh...
Cyanide and Happiness.
And...
Snafu.
Yeah, Snafu comics.
And...
Uh...
What else?
There was like...
Oh my god.
Fusion Fall.
I remember Fusion Fall.
I never got a chance to play Fusion Fall.
I don't know why.
I think I was just too stupid on the internet to know how to play Fusion Fall.
Mega Tokyo.
Bro, Mega Tokyo.
Mega Tokyo?
Can I say that?
It was a scam.
They don't...
Do they still exist?
Oh, they do.
Okay.
Wait, not Mega Tokyo.
What was it?
Not Mega Tokyo.
The Tokyo Pop?
No.
Not Mega Tokyo.
What was it?
Is it Tokyo?
It was like some...
Well, not...
Was it...
Uh...
The publication.
Was it not?
It was not...
I'm not talking about Mega Tokyo.
It was...
It was like a book publication.
The comic books before, who were like...
I'm not talking about Mega Tokyo.
I'm talking about like...
Is it Tokyo Pop?
Oh, yeah.
I don't know if they are better now.
But, like, I heard Tokyo Pop used to have like really bad illustrator contracts.
I think...
I don't know if they are better now.
But like I remember there was several...
Like the publisher.
Yeah.
The publisher.
I remember back then the publisher had like really bad like contracts and everything for like artists and translators back then.
Like people were making not twitlongers but...
I guess Twitter?
Sorry, not Twitter.
Twitter was not a thing yet.
So people were making like the DeviantArt and Tumblr equivalent of twitlongers about Tokyo Pop.
And then... and then yeah the angry bloggers.
They live... there was like live journals and Tumblr posts and DeviantArt journal blog posts about Tokyo Pop.
Because apparently they paid really little in terms of translations and it wasn't like super accurate.
But the thing is...
They had so much...
They had so many licenses and I think at one point they went bankrupt.
So like it took off like majority of the English...
The English translations of Tokyo Pop mangas.
So like majority of like... because like they own... they had... they almost had a monopoly for like manga.
And I think they went bankrupt and at one point and they had to like...
They had to like take down...
They had to like take down like the majority of like you know they went bankrupt.
So they had to... basically a lot of manga was like taken out because of it.
And I... and apparently they're still around.
So they must have got better.
They must have got better.
I remember people were like...
Yeah.
They almost killed the whole scene.
Because they literally had the monopoly.
They had the monopoly of manga.
For like the NA side.
Because like it was the only way to read like NA manga.
Like English manga.
And then it like... they almost went bankrupt.
Oh my gosh.
And then there was... there was... there was...
Does anyone remember the...
Okay.
There was this like thing back then.
Where it was like... I wish they bring it back man.
The OC contest.
Oh my god.
So...
I used to love Endling.
Endling stuff.
Ever after.
Oh my god.
I love reading his comics.
And then he like... he stopped.
Because I guess he got a real job.
Silas, thank you for the five gift chips.
Thank you.
But back then there was like original character tournaments.
And it was so fucking cool.
Because...
Because like...
There was this thing where...
People would make up these like tournaments and stuff.
And then there was like a whole lore around it.
There was like a whole lore and everything around it.
And then it was like people would like...
Enter with like original characters and stuff.
And then there would be like battles.
Yeah, OC battles.
So like they'll draw comics, animations, stuff like that for like OC battles.
And the most famous...
The most famous one was...
The Ever After tournament with Enling hosting it.
And...
Oh, with the climber.
I used to love the...
Like I was so obsessed with the climber.
The climber was my K-pop stat.
The climber was my BTS.
All the women love the climber.
Was it...
Was it clamber?
You must not...
Wait, maybe I'm thinking of it wrong.
What was his actual name?
Is his name actually climber?
I might be remembering it wrong too.
Enling tournament.
Ever...
Ever After tournament.
Okay.
Was it Ever After?
Okay, Enling.
Oh my god, it's so long.
What did he climb...
I was... No, you don't understand!
It was... Oh my god, it's so old that like... Oh my god.
Was it... What was his... Oh my god.
Okay, end zone.
Okay, it was called the end zone.
Okay, who was...
Who had competitors?
Was he actually called... Yes, he was!
He was called the climber!
Okay, I was getting paranoid.
I was like, am I forgetting it wrong?
Because all the animation was made in Flash.
Okay, but that shit, I love the lore!
I'm so sad!
The guy, the creator of...
The creator of Climber, he fucking disappeared because he got a real job too.
So... God damn it!
Why do they all keep getting real jobs?
But...
But that shit was so good!
Oh my gosh, I was like obsessed with like the lore behind this, the climber and like the ad... Okay, like you might think watch re-watching me because I re-watched the animations recently because it's on Flash.
Like it was on Flash, but somebody saved the animation... saved the animations and stuff on YouTube and I was re-watching it and I was like, oh the voice acting was not as good as I remembered it.
I had... I had those rose tinted glasses on.
It was not as... it was not as like pretty as I remember.
The fight scenes though!
The fight scenes were still pretty fucking good!
I have to admit, like the fight scenes were actually pretty fucking insane though.
Even if like, um...
Even if like the voice acting wasn't as good.
I think back then, because a lot of them were also like Newgrounds creators, I would say like Newgrounds creators are incredibly good at fight scenes and fight choreographies.
Uh, Mouse, thank you for the... or Mouse, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Hey Doki, any game recommendations to play when you're bored but won't get you too worked up?
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
That is so difficult.
I haven't been like actually playing any um... um games off stream.
Um, because I feel like we're in like...
low-key a gaming rut.
Not gonna lie.
Um, because like a lot of people would like recommend like a lot of like... what are those called?
Like those crafting games with like crafting and stuff like that or... I would just say like... ah my gosh.
I honestly feel like... for me, I feel like we're in a low-key gaming rut for me because like a lot of the games I like are not meta anymore.
Um, there's... but like honestly if you don't want to get too worked up and want to pass the time, just play some open world survival games.
Yeah, that's what I was gonna say, open world survival crafting games.
Those are like the easiest um games that are like the most chill type deal.
Uh, I would say like... I haven't tried it out yet but a lot of people have been playing Planet Crafter recently.
A lot of people saying like, Planet Crafter has been pretty good.
Uh, but yeah, Oh my gosh, I... oh my god.
And there was... what's his name?
Carl?
Oh my god, bro.
I used to love those creators so much.
Carl and the Climber.
They were my BTS, man.
They were so... I would draw fan art of them in my sketchbook all the time.
It was pretty shitty fan art.
But like I used to be so fucking obsessed with Carl and the Climber from... from like the end...
like from the... what was it?
The Law of Talos.
The Law of Talos tournament and also the... the end zone.
Oh my gosh, if you guys... I highly recommend checking out at least... I'm pretty sure the... the com...
The creator still... oh my god, he's alive?
Oh my... I'm gonna follow that.
He was my hero.
That guy was my hero.
No, you don't understand.
He was my fucking hero.
I used to love that.
I would like read all... I would like read like the lore and like absorb his lore... the lore of the Climber.
Oh my god, his animations was like fucking sick.
What's his Twitter, guys?
Oh my god, bro.
The last time he posted was in 2012, guys.
Of course I would... he still...
Oh my god, Photobucket.
Bro, fucking Photobucket, man.
Okay, guys.
What is... what is his Twitter?
I need to stalk him.
I need...
I need... I need to stalk this man.
Alright, check his likes.
What?
Oh no.
Don't say it, please.
Don't ruin...
You know when they say don't meet your heroes?
Don't ruin this for me.
Please.
I... I hope his likes would not be deal breakers.
Do not ruin this creator for me.
Mon!
What's his Twitter?
I need to know!
Please, I need to follow him.
I need to follow all my favorite creators that were my role models.
Oh my gosh, I should not say role models.
Because now I'm scared of him.
I'm so scared about what his likes are.
I'm so...
Now I'm scared.
I can't say role model.
Because what if I shouldn't role model him?
Like...
No.
No, don't ruin this.
Like, I love this shit, bro.
Don't fucking ruin this for me.
But yes.
Also, like... Oh, there was another creator.
Really... I... Oh my gosh!
It was like... Oh my god.
I used to admire so many artists back then too.
So it's like crazy going back memory lane and like how... how much... how much like...
What's the word?
How much they've like grown as an artist and stuff.
I don't want to expose my shi...
There was... There was this other artist that I used to like... I really like their art of.
But like I'm worried that like... I'm like honestly worried about what... what they are now.
Because... Oh my god.
Okay.
Because I know what happened to one of the creators and like what pathway they went to.
So I... So I'm so embarrassed.
But there was this artist that was known...
Okay.
It's gonna be... Okay.
It's so fucked.
Oh my god.
Like when I read like... Like as I got older...
And then... As I... As I got older...
And then like I realized like... You know, they got older too.
And then... Okay.
I won't name anybody.
I won't name names.
But back then on DemonArt...
Um... This was for Pokemon Mystery Dungeon.
Um... Yes.
Okay.
Some people are like... know where it's gonna go.
So like... There used to be like really popular things with like Animal Crossing and Mystery Dungeon.
And like Pokemon... Pokemon and Pokemon Mystery Dungeon and stuff like that.
And there would be like roleplay groups.
So like people would draw comics and stuff with like OCs.
So a really famous one was the Pokemon Mystery Dungeon roleplay group.
And... Let's just say...
Um... The main creator of the roleplay group...
Definitely went a different direction afterwards.
I remember... It used to be so cute.
It used to be like so cute.
And the lore was so interesting.
But then...
Money talks...
No... It's not Pokemon anymore.
Let's just... Let's just say...
Um... Money definitely talks.
And... Um...
It's definitely...
Uh...
It's not about cute Pokemon Mystery Dungeon.
It's about...
It's not about cute Pokemon Mystery Dungeon missions anymore.
And...
And I just remembered...
Because I used to follow this artist.
Because I really liked their art.
Because it was so cute.
And the story was so interesting.
And then it went a different direction.
I won't say the name.
But for anyone that ever followed the DeviantArt Pokemon Mystery Dungeon roleplay groups.
Like the most famous one.
Would know exactly who I'm talking about.
Like they...
They...
They would know.
Because they were like one of the...
They were the most famous Pokemon Mystery Dungeon like artist back then.
And...
And it went a different direction half...
A couple of years later.
I can't believe it.
Like name it.
I guess like they still do...
They still make content.
So I can't say anything.
It's just...
You know.
When people get older.
I guess they...
They...
You know.
They got bills to pay.
And everything.
I understand.
They get...
They have bills to pay.
And there's a market for it.
But like...
Oh my god.
Little me was not ready for that.
Little me.
Just liked cute art.
And...
I was just like...
You know what they say, don't meet your heroes.
That's why I'm so afraid.
I'm so afraid.
Like someone was like, don't check this person's likes.
And now I'm scared.
Now I'm scared.
Because like, I've had that moment before where like I used to admire...
I mean, they had really good art.
You know?
They got older.
I'm scared.
Delta, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
And I'm scared.
Because usually... usually... you know... when people get older...
I don't know.
I'm scared.
Just... I don't know what they're doing now.
I don't know.
I'm worried.
My childhood.
I don't want my childhood to be like this.
I don't want my childhood to be...
I don't want my childhood to be gone again.
Oh my gosh.
Also like...
Similar with like Newground animators.
There's like... there's like some Newground animators that I've like...
super admired and like was like really into their arts and animation.
And I was like, what are they up to these days?
And then...
Porn.
Straight up.
I was like...
I checked their Twitter.
I was like, oh!
That's a dick.
I was like...
I was like, whoa!
Alright.
That takes me back.
Got a pill in my...
Yeah.
Um...
I only have someone...
Literally every Newground animator I knew back in like 2012.
Porn.
All of them.
Every single one!
Thank you for the super chat.
He wasn't even super chat.
I was like, oh...
Okay.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
It's either like... that direction or they're... or they're... you know...
Or they're making... making like...
Or they went viral for like a video game or a TV show.
It's one or the other.
Either a show...
Either a cartoon show...
Or you know...
Drawing porn.
Genki, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
I meant check his likes to see if he was still active.
Didn't mean the other way.
Oh!
Oh thank god.
Okay.
I like Genki.
Like I misinterpreted that and it started to...
It started a whole thing.
It started a whole fucking tangent on its own.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
But yeah.
Blast from the past.
Hanta, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Everyone was too young back then.
But then they realized this dark side of money.
For me, I am just stuck with...
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Also, the more I talk about this...
The more I realize I was way too young to be like reading or watching any of these things.
By the way, I should have never been allowed on the internet.
The thing is, I didn't even start on the internet really young.
I wasn't allowed to be on the internet for a long time until like I was...
I wasn't allowed to be on the internet until like really, really late.
So like I didn't even have...
Like I wasn't even allowed to have...
Like I didn't even have like a Facebook account when like people were...
People... everybody made Facebook accounts.
And like...
One of my friends had to make a Facebook account for me.
Because I had no idea about Facebook.
And then all I did...
I think when I was finally allowed to be on the internet...
All I did was play Neopets.
All I did...
I was just like...
Yay!
Like I just played Neopets instead.
Instead of doing anything.
But yeah, anyway.
That was like usually...
And then like later on when I found out what the internet was really like.
When I found out what the internet was really like.
I sort of like...
I went all in.
So like...
I like explored the internet a lot.
I read a lot of internet comics.
Fanfiction.net Before they...
Okay.
I did something a little illegal.
I definitely should not have been reading some of the fanfics.
I definitely should not have been reading the lemon one.
Fanfiction.net
And then also...
Also, you know...
I...
I found out about Newgrounds and artwork and stuff like that.
And...
The what?
Let's say lemon and limes.
Lemon and limes.
Nova, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Sup, Dokiho.
Your night's been going well.
I think it's been going pretty well.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Welcome to the internet.
Ba-da-na-na-na.
Ba-da-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na.
If you know, you know.
I was an internet connoisseur.
Oh my god.
And then the live journal role-playing groups.
Okay.
Back then.
I should not...
You know how they're like, you gotta be 18 and over to read this?
Read this.
I was 18 for a very long time.
I was 18 for a while.
So there was like this...
There was like this...
There was this famous live journal role-play groups where...
Who wasn't reading Lemons when we really should and have been.
Thank you for the super chat, Nexi.
Thank you, thank you.
Okay, so...
I'm gonna go back to the chat.
Um...
If you know, you know.
There was like, there were these famous live journal...
For those who don't know what live journal is, it was like...
A lot of like old people would use...
I'm sorry.
A lot of the older generations would use it.
I was...
Definitely was not...
I should not have been allowed on live journal.
I was way too young for live journal.
I should not have been on that.
But I've been 15...
I've been 18 for a very long time.
Um...
I mean...
I...
It was like pre-tumblr.
It was basically pre-tumblr.
And um...
And there was like a lot of like anime communities on there.
I would use live journal to like...
Uh...
Take the icons for like anime shows.
Like some of my favorite anime shows.
Oh my god.
I was part of the Glee live journal community.
I...
Okay.
I would admit.
I would take some of the animated icons from the Oran High School Host Club live journal community.
And the Glee one to put on my MSN icons.
And please don't not Glee.
Anyway.
Um...
As I was saying.
There was like this live journal roleplay community.
Where like people will roleplay as like different characters.
From...
Different...
Uh...
From different fandoms.
So like it was like a fucking mix mash of like...
It would be like the Team Fortress 2 sniper meeting.
I don't know.
Meeting Hikaru from Oran High School Host Club.
And it would be like the most insane roleplay session ever.
Like there would be like so much lore in it.
And then it was all public.
So then I would like read the roleplay sessions of like random fucking characters.
Talking to each other.
And...
I don't...
Bro I don't remember what it was.
It was just like...
It was...
It was either like super hinged or...
Or...
Like...
Or it would just be like super casual.
Like okay.
Guys.
Not everything was a lemon.
Not everything was lemons.
Sometimes it was just general interactions.
Like what if the Team Fortress 2 sniper...
Met up with this random anime character.
There was like this really popular one with a Persona character.
Like she was the one that was like wearing the detective one.
Not the Persona 4.
No wait.
What Persona are we on in now?
Like...
It was before Persona...
Not 4.
It was Persona 4.
Okay that detective character from Persona 4.
It was so famous.
Like they actually were like...
They became famous in the LiveJournal community.
And like the detective character from Persona 4.
And like this person was like...
I don't remember who the fuck was she like...
What were they coupled with.
But like I followed that person's LiveJournal post a lot.
Because they...
I followed that person's LiveJournal post so much.
Because they were a really good writer.
They were a really good writer.
And like I was like so immersed.
I was so immersed in the lore.
Hahaha.
Like this lore.
And then oh my god.
I remember like at one point this...
They met Pinkie Pie from Final Point.
There was a roleplay session with Pinkie Pie from Final...
It was so serious.
I wish I remembered...
I wish I remembered like...
I remembered what it was called.
It was so popular.
Um...
It was so funny.
It was just so funny.
Um...
It was actual lore.
Because like at one point there was a murder mystery.
With a bunch of random anime characters and cartoon...
Anime, cartoon and game characters.
It got to a murder mystery at one point.
That they were trying to figure out a murder with a bunch of anime characters.
Slash cartoon characters.
Slash game characters.
And I was so obsessed with what the fuck was going on.
And it was all roleplay.
Hahaha.
It was...
Um...
Thank you for the Akasupa.
Thank you.
Appreciation Superchat to feed the overworked mods that provide links for every single topic that Doki has been yapping about.
Thank you for the Akasupa.
Thank you.
I love crossovers.
Who was the...
I don't fucking know.
I barely remembered what it was about.
I just remembered like the general...
Generalness of it all.
Oh my god.
Um...
But yeah, anyway.
That was like my internet history.
That was literally my internet history.
Growing up.
It was a wild internet history.
I should have never...
I should have not been...
Hahaha.
On those sites with how young I was.
I should have 100% not been on any of those sites.
For sure.
Hahaha.
I need you guys to know.
When I started out my internet history.
I was like playing Neopets, right?
I even had to...
I was so naive.
I didn't lie about my age when I started on Neopets.
To the point where like my parents had to fax the Neopets headquarters.
Proof that I had parental permission to access the more restricted areas of Neopets.
Hahaha.
And you guys were like the restricted areas of Neopets?
What are those?
It was basically the forums.
Like um...
The Neoboards.
Because like I didn't lie about my age.
So I wasn't allowed to talk to anybody online.
Or like use the Neomail.
Or anything.
So they had to like...
They're like oh if you're underage and you want to access the Neoboards.
You have to fax...
Um...
You have to fax in your parents.
Parental permission.
Hahaha.
Like a permission slip.
So you can like access the Neoboards and talk to the adults.
So...
So I had to get that happen.
Because I wanted to like...
I would be like I want to talk to strangers on the internet.
Hahaha.
It's like man I want to talk to the stranger.
Okay I didn't tell her.
They didn't know.
It ended up being I talked to random strangers on the internet.
But like...
Because like it was just like...
They just like access to things.
So they didn't realize at that time.
It basically led to me knowing more about the internet.
Because you know...
I started talking to fucking adults on the internet.
Hahaha.
I definitely should not have been.
Because like...
Because like you guys didn't know back then.
Neopets was like um...
Was mostly for adults.
And for college students.
Like and I was definitely neither of them.
Hahaha.
So there was a lot of like...
Like it was like...
I remember I talked about the story before.
But like there was a help section.
There was a help section.
And um...
And like in the neoboard.
And I was like really scared.
Because I was like oh my god.
I'm gonna um...
I don't know.
I think I was like oh my gosh.
I'm gonna go to middle school.
For the first time.
And I'm really scared.
And I was like I don't know what is middle school gonna be like.
I'm so scared.
And then some...
Some adult was like...
The help section is for like...
Is for neopets related issues.
But don't worry.
Sixth grade is not that difficult.
Hahaha.
You're like...
This is not the right board.
To talk about this.
This is for like neopets related help issues.
Like reporting bugs.
Or like needing help regarding neopet issues.
Hahaha.
I like my dumb ass was like...
Please help.
I'm really scared about sixth grade.
But should I explain?
I'm scared.
Hahaha.
No.
It was just one person.
There were several people.
And they were like...
Oh do not worry about middle school.
It's high school.
You have to worry about...
Hahaha.
Oh my god.
It was so embarrassing thinking back to it.
Oh...
They're like...
No trauma dumping child.
This is neopets man.
Hahaha.
I told this story in the ROPLOX stream.
But like I also...
There was a roleplay board on neopets.
And because I wasn't a high schooler.
I would like join...
Okay.
It's funny.
Because I swear to god.
I'm pretty sure majority of the people.
That were in the high school roleplay.
Has never been to high school before.
Hahaha.
Because I was just some fucking...
Middle schooler.
Roleplaying as a high school student.
Like in those high school boards.
Where like...
I was like...
Oh I'm in like 10th.
I'm a sophomore.
And I...
Hahaha.
Because they're like...
Imagine what high school could be for us.
Hahaha.
Just faking it.
So like...
There'll be like roleplay boards.
Where you're pretending you're high school students.
And then there's like multiple versions of it.
It's like high school.
But like what if we're like...
We all have powers.
So like mutants.
Like X-Men high school roleplay.
Or like...
Magical school high school roleplay.
Or...
Superhero high school roleplay.
Hahaha.
And then I would have like...
Word documents.
Like word documents I made on Microsoft Word.
Of like...
Character sheets.
Of like all these different high schoolers.
Plus warrior cats by the way.
I would have high schoolers and warrior cats.
With like established character sheets.
And um...
Hahaha.
Powers.
And I would be like...
And then I would have like my intro pre-written.
And everything.
So I could just copy and paste it as a...
Like to start the story of my character.
And it would be like...
Hahaha.
I wish I still have it.
So I could like cringe at it.
I really... It was... Oh my god.
I really do wish...
I still... I still have it.
It's so fucking cringe.
Thinking back.
Oh my god.
I did not get online.
I was way too young for Gaia online.
So like Neopets was like the baby version of that.
Um...
Hahaha.
The cringe is overwhelming.
I was way too young to use Gaia online.
So like there was a baby...
Baby version.
For me.
Hahaha.
This is giving me emotional damage.
That I wasn't prepared for.
Oh and now I'm illiterate.
I feel like...
I hit my peak.
Um...
I definitely hit my peak.
In terms of intelligence.
And writing.
Um during that stage of Neopets.
And then everything else was downhill from there.
Like...
I...
I wrote a lot.
For Neopets roleplay.
And then as I got older.
I realized I...
I definitely got more and more stupid and illiterate.
The older I got.
Hahaha.
Oh my god.
Holy shit.
I've been yapping for so long already.
Oh was there already...
An hour and thirty minutes?
Oh my god.
What did I miss?
You missed cringe doki internet history.
It was...
It was pretty fucking cringe back then.
But who else wasn't like cringe?
But everybody was cringe back then.
Um...
Everybody was like super cringe back then.
Cause we didn't know better.
I definitely should not have been talking to adults for sure.
But like um...
At the age I was.
I'm...
We did not know what was safe for kids.
Hahaha.
People back then.
Did not realize.
That it was sort of a bad idea.
That we had like little doki.
Talking to fucking college students.
Hahaha.
Oh my god.
I'm just thinking about that.
Why did they talk to me?
Hahaha.
Oh my god.
Um...
Um... but yeah.
But it's from Neopets.
Because of the boards.
On the Neopet boards.
It led to me discovering DeviantArt.
And then from DeviantArt.
It led to me discovering like other stuff on the internet.
Like from DeviantArt.
To fanfiction.net.
To Tumblr.
And to LiveJournal.
It was all downhill.
The moment.
The moment my parents faxed that parental permission slip.
It was over for me.
It was so over.
I sped run my internet cloud.
Like I'm not in TickleCloud.
I sped run my internet like um intake.
Like...
I learned things on the internet.
At an exponential rate.
At because of that.
All because my parents faxed in that parental permission slip.
And it went downhill.
In the pipeline.
Neopets to Newgrounds.
That was not the way it should go.
But...
But it did.
It fucking did.
Oh my god.
I also had like...
Wait let me see if I can...
Find it.
I also had like...
I started liking videos.
To like...
As for like...
Not intel.
What's the word?
For like...
I guess like topics and stuff in the future.
So if I find something funny and interesting.
Oh my god.
Did you guys see the...
That fucking Furby video?
Of like...
To a couple.
This couple made a Furby...
Not like a Furby robot.
Did you guys see that?
That shit was so fucking...
With the like...
Boston robots.
They fucking took the Boston robots.
Dog robot.
And then turned it into a freak of nature.
You guys haven't...
Okay.
I'm gonna fucking show you.
I'm gonna...
Show you this.
Look at this.
Look at this abomination.
No not that music.
Okay the full video was so...
It was like...
This is like basically a...
Super cut of that video.
I think the messed up part was...
When they were...
They wore the fucking mask.
Oh my god.
When they wore the fucking...
Mask and everything.
I think that was the worst part.
We say...
Progress.
If Furby was released in 2030...
Instead of 1998...
The...
He's broke.
Technology.
That's what it was.
Chat you wouldn't understand.
We're progressing forward.
Not backwards guys.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Um...
Anyway.
Oh my gosh.
It's been...
Super fucking fun.
I'm really enjoying...
I'm definitely...
Really enjoying...
These night time gaps.
I hope you guys have been enjoying it too.
I've been enjoying just listening to me talk about...
Random things...
Tonight.
And I hope that...
I hope that I didn't ruin your sleep by sending that video.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
I hope...
I hope I haven't been ruining your sleep.
Because I ended up sending the Furby video.
And like...
Doki no.
We were gonna be like...
Okay.
We were heading the right direction Doki.
Now we're 50 steps behind now.
I'm never gonna sleep.
I'm sorry.
But like...
Okay.
I just wanna say...
Like one of my favorite videos...
Okay.
No I'm definitely gonna get copyright strike if I played it on stream.
So I...
I'm already getting like limited ads.
I don't want more.
But oh my god.
Wait I'm gonna show you guys.
This is like one of my favorite songs.
That I'm gonna show you guys.
Okay.
I'm not gonna say it out loud.
This is one of my favorite songs.
And I'm gonna show you guys this.
Where is it?
Okay.
I'm trying not to say it out loud to spoil it.
This one.
Okay.
I'm gonna pause my lo-fi thing real fast.
And I'm gonna mute this.
I'm gonna listen to it now.
Guys this is one of my favorite.
Please play.
Too late I'm doom and it's midnight here.
Oh George thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
I love this.
This is one of my favorites.
Honestly.
Instead of ending the night with...
Um...
I don't know.
Instead of ending the night with Furby.
I'm gonna end the night with Crash Bandicoot.
I'll sing along to it too.
For you guys.
People are gonna be so confused.
For not watching the video.
I got so obsessed with this song.
That I would like.
I kept like whining.
I would like.
It just like hit me.
I'd be like.
Whao whao whao whao.
Whao.
Whao whao.
Whao whao whao whao.
Whao.
Sweet.
Thanks for the morning Doki.
I'm off to work.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Whao whao whao whao.
When I first watched this video.
I just kept wowing.
Like I'd just be like.
Whao.
I was like so obsessed.
I don't know why.
I think I'm so special.
I think.
There's something wrong with me.
Whao.
I would quote this too.
I would quote this video a lot.
You're like.
But Doki what is there to quote?
Exactly.
I was definitely very special.
I don't know why I was quoting this video.
But I was quoting this video for some reason.
Whao.
Anyway.
Anyway guys.
I'm gonna call it here.
I hope you guys have a good night everybody.
I hope you guys sleep well.
And good morning to everybody on the other side of the world.
As always everyone.
Stay hydrated.
Posture check.
Get up and move around to get that blood flowing.
And if you stay up for me.
Head to bed.
Cause you deserve it.
I'll see you guys next time everybody.
Bye guys.
Bye.