When the games begin, place your bets at 10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, GO!
Mondays.
You need more training, dragoon!
Hello, everybody.
Wow, can't believe it.
I can't believe you dragoons couldn't even win.
Win the race.
Hello, everybody.
So, did you like the dragoon race test chat?
It was dope.
I did all of this in one go.
All of the race tests were done in one go.
I did not.
I also thought you guys could win it.
Well, I guess you guys need more training.
So, what is this, might you ask?
So, if you guys didn't notice, this is actually a customized, do-it-your-own horse race test.
But instead of horse race test, it is the dragoon race test.
Yes, so if you guys didn't know about this game, it is a little miniature game, a little miniature simulation.
So, this isn't the announcement, by the way.
The announcement is later.
The announcement.
To get the announcement, you dragoons have to beat Doki Field.
And clearly, you guys did not beat Doki Field in our last race.
So, we're going to have to do more training.
So, in order to get your announcement, your very special announcement, you have to beat Doki Field.
So, let me give a huge shout-out to the original creator of this mod.
Or not mod.
The original creator of this game is by Stop Signal.
They created their own version of the horse race test.
So, like, you guys aren't, like, you know, Twitter brain-rotted like me.
It was an internet trend back then by Blake Andrews.
And his Twitter account is Snake Andrews.
And he made a little, like, internet thing where they put all these...
It was, like, basically a horse race test simulation.
And he...
Like, everybody was, like, rooting for these horses.
And then things got, like, super deep, the lore-wise and everything.
And I believe it's still going on now.
He brought it back.
But there is, like, more content towards it.
And then Stop Signal made his very own...
Him and his team made his very own do-it-yourself horse race test.
And then I did...
I was...
Okay, I have to say...
It was, like, a little game jam moment for me and my team.
Because I got this idea two weeks ago, I think.
A little bit, almost two weeks ago.
Maybe a week and a half.
I got this idea, like, a week and a half ago.
And to do my special announcement.
Because I was like, Ah, Doki, I miss when you were so creative back then.
And I want to go back to these creative things.
Doing creative stuff again.
Having these creative ideas.
Because...
And then Inspiration struck me a week and a half ago.
And...
And we did a little bit of, like, a little game jam session.
So, huge shout-out to the team.
For creating all of this.
Modding all of this.
So, this was done on the original game.
And they basically modded everything.
To make it more Doki Bird Dragoon themed.
And so, huge shout-out to that team for doing this.
Um, I'll say they're, uh, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Let's see.
Uh...
Oh, wait.
Wait, they're...
Oh!
Oh, there's an extra secret Doki, apparently.
I was just told that they did have a secret Doki from the Doki-verse in here.
That I didn't know of.
But huge shout-out to Lou, Kano, and Frel.
Uh, there was a team of three that modded and did the artwork of all of this, too.
So, huge shout-out to them.
And Ichio page will be linked, uh, linked whenever the dev, uh, whenever the dev gives me the link.
I will post the Ichio link for you guys.
So, you can customize your racetracks and everything.
So, let me show you guys real quick.
Um, so, you can see the dirt here.
I can customize this and everything.
This was originally in the original game.
But we also, like, um...
Redid some of the textures.
So, this used to be a house.
And now it's just a extra chonky dragoon.
I...
They're like, what should we replace this obstacle with?
And I wanna be like, I want an extra fat dragoon.
An absolute unit.
So, you can put this anywhere you want.
Not on the dirt.
And then there's also, like, punchers here.
And then there's mines and everything.
So, you can customize it fully.
And then, obviously, here are...
Here are...
Here's all of them.
They all have their little sound effects.
Pearl did the dragoons.
So, and then I did, obviously...
I voiced the tomato.
I voiced all the doki's from the doki-verse.
And then I even got dad to bark on the mic for me.
And then there's tomato goon.
So, let me put all of them in here.
So, and then we press start race.
And then...
There they go.
I don't know if they can get out.
I think I locked them in.
So, this is all...
This is all fully customizable.
There will be an itch.io link that I'll send to you guys.
And you too can, um...
You can, like, edit your tracks.
Make your own tracks.
Play around with it yourself.
Maybe even customize your own map.
Like, maps.
Add more doki's if you want to.
So, yeah.
I thought it was really fun.
Anyway, so clearly we gotta do...
We gotta train you guys more.
Because you can't be...
I feel like you guys are struggling...
To beat any of the doki's from the doki-verse.
Because I mean the tomato.
Tomato one, dragoons.
Oh, is the game loud?
I'm sorry.
I'll turn it down a little.
But all I'm saying is that you guys seem to be struggling...
Beating any of the dragoons...
Any of the doki's from the doki-verse.
Hmm.
Guess we got...
Guess you're not gonna get your announcement until...
Guess you can't get your announcement...
Until you beat a doki.
Alright.
So, here is the link.
If you want to play with it yourself.
Here is the link to the itch.io.
I will do...
Give the link...
I'll pin the link...
Um...
Pin the link for it...
At the end of the announcement...
So those who want to download it...
Can download it...
Experience it yourself.
Let me show the image real quick...
Too for it.
Huge shout out to my editor...
Uh...
Hebe.
She's also the thumbnail maker.
She helped me put together the video...
All the videos...
Um...
Itself.
So...
Um...
Last minute as well.
Because I was like...
I...
You know...
The idea came to me.
And I was like...
Oh my god...
I want to have like...
A little video...
Instead of like...
Uh...
To like...
Build the lore.
So here you go.
It's a...
Do it yourself.
Horse race...
Thing.
Doki mod.
So...
We did...
Add more stuff to it.
We added...
You know...
Our own characters.
Uh...
We added like...
New features to it.
Uh...
So there's like...
Little adjustments to it...
From compared to the original...
Original game.
So...
Uh...
I hope you guys all enjoyed.
Stop Signal.
Thank you for the super chat.
Yeah!
There he is!
That's the creator!
That's the creator of the original game.
Uh...
Stop Signal here.
The dev.
Thanks for playing, Doki.
Thank you again for making such an amazing game.
And letting me mod it and everything.
I really appreciate it.
By the way...
Stop Signal actually like...
Replied back today...
To us.
So I was like...
Oh...
I was like...
Super happy and thankful.
Um...
Because we were just gonna do it on a Google Drive.
Because like...
I didn't wanna like...
Step on any toes or anything.
And then later on we were like...
Okay, maybe we put it on Itch.io for a bit.
And then like...
See if he'll reply back.
And then if it confirms and everything.
So...
I'm super happy that...
Um...
We got Stop Signal's approval.
And blessing to upload it on Itch.io and everything.
I really appreciate it.
Thank you again!
But yes, I hope you guys...
Have a lot of fun with this horse race test.
Or Dragoon race test mod.
Um...
Anyway...
Let's train you guys.
I have the perfect map to train all of you guys in.
Ha ha ha ha!
It is...
Also, you can adjust the...
You can adjust the starting line.
So like if you wanna cheat and have like...
I don't know...
Like, you know...
Let him win something.
Like right here.
I can literally put him next to it.
And...
Okay.
Ha ha ha ha!
He's not a racer guy.
He's...
He's a lover.
I tell you...
It's all RNG!
No more training for all of you.
Oh...
Let's make it.
This is hell.
It's okay.
Look, see it?
There's no way.
There's no... I don't even have to... Okay, I lowered it.
There's a better now, sound guy.
I lowered the volume.
Look, it's training.
Eventually, one of you guys will make it.
Welcome to hell.
This is hell.
Okay, I can lower it more.
Alright, here we go.
There we go.
That should be better.
I swear to God, if none of you drag booms, get it in.
The fabled five big booms.
I believe.
Surely you guys can make it.
Surely you guys can make it to the end.
This map gets five big booms.
Oh my God, Chalky!
Chalky, the bombs are literally taking you to the end goal!
You can't fuck this up!
Chalky!
Oh!
Alright, I was gonna say it.
Chalky, if you fuck this up, then that's on you.
Chalky will have merriment.
Alright.
Alright, let's clear.
Let's clear all of this.
Alright, I think there will be...
Yeah, so we can basically play around with this.
And there's, like, swapping tilesets, so, like, things look different.
So, I'll show you guys.
Like, things will each... So, the Chalky Goon will turn into, uh, into, like, trees, depending on what settings you're on.
So, I'll put some of these around for you guys so you can see how different they look and everything.
And also, there's, like, settings here.
Like, you can make them not trip.
You can, like, bump, not bump.
The horse name, uh, which would be the dragoon name.
It would be, like, ma, ma, ma.
And then resetting the level.
So, if you change the tileset, you can see that the Chalky Goons turn into trees.
We don't know how to fix that yet.
We don't really know how to fix that.
But, not yet.
Like I said, it was, like, a little game jam session.
But there are trees now.
There are also trees here as well.
So, but then, you know, when you're at the grass, they're back to Chalky.
They're just extra Chalky again.
It's their, it's their little, yeah.
Yeah, it's just the extra Chalky Goon just, like, turns into a tree somehow.
Alright.
Let's make, let's, you know, let's customize this a little bit.
And then, you know, I want to put the trophy right here.
And then, we'll see if, let's see.
Maybe, actually, no.
I'll put the trophy right here.
And then, we'll turn the dirt like that.
And then, oh, wait.
Can he make it?
Alright.
There's no, the countdown voice was edited in by Heavey.
Um, she was, she was the one that customized, uh, customized it to make it more.
I gave her, like, instructions on, like, how I wanted the video to look like.
And she did it perfectly within, like, a day.
Um, and that, like, last minute edits, like, within, like, two hours ago.
And she did it perfectly.
I was so happy that, uh, we were able to get the, the, the dumb things I wanted to do for the video.
I was, I was very happy about it.
I was, like, I was, I, I don't know.
I just, I had, like, specific instructions and, like, she was able to, like, replicate it and everything.
Um, alright, let's go.
Okay, let's put some...
Alright, here we go.
Yeah, get past the minefields first.
Dragoons, I believe.
If you can get past this, you can get past anything.
Alright.
Place your bets, dragoons!
War never changes.
Place your bets.
Who do you think will win?
We're out of hell now.
You can turn it back up.
Alright.
Out of the hell's portal.
The hell universe.
I think this is my favorite part.
They asked me, like, can you guys send, uh, uh...
Doki, can you send, like, dad photos for us?
So, like, when he falls down, we'll just Photoshop dad into...
It's my favorite!
Like, I...
He had, like, the perfect pose of him just lying on his back.
Oh my god!
This is the closest Longoon has ever been!
To, like, the trophy!
There's no way he'll fuck it up!
There's no way!
This is the closest you've ever been, Longoon!
Ha ha ha ha!
And then he's gonna, like, get out of him!
Oh my god!
And then the regular Goon from...
Nowhere!
From downtown!
Oh my...
Now the Ingoon's here!
Ha ha ha!
Longoon!
Longoon's been stuck here for the longest time!
Ha ha ha!
We've been closer!
Stop!
Oh!
Goodbye Longoon!
It was nice seeing you down there.
Goodbye!
Ha ha ha ha!
Wait, how did Krookie get down here?
Longo number uno, I believe.
Yes, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Oh my god, Longo's back!
Oh my god, the punch is putting him closer.
Oh... Poor Longo.
Please, the trophy's right here.
Oh, Krookie, come on.
You're like right there.
You're actually right there.
No!
He almost... Oh, he's back!
He's fucking back!
Krookie, Krookie, come on!
Do it for the Doki-verse!
For the Doki-verse, Krookie!
That dang Chalky-coon.
Krookie, stop joking!
Oh, goodbye, Krookie.
Krookie, go for Krookie.
Johnny, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Oh my god, I...
Please, Krookie, come on!
Oh my god, Tomato, let's do this!
Four times!
The four-time champion!
Let's go!
Another Doki-verse wins!
No way!
Where the fuck did the Tomato come from?
Oh wait, I think I'm gonna be left-side... Okay, give me a sec.
I realize I may or may have to be left-side Doki.
She's finally back, guys!
She's back from retirement!
I guess we need more training, Dragoons!
You're not getting your announcement and I'll tell you when, guys!
Not so dreadful!
Lagoon has no girth, so he has no worth.
Chunky-goon has a way to keep him great.
Thank you for the super chat!
Thank you, thank you!
Wait, what is the secret...?
I don't know what the secret Doki is!
Okay, how do I do it?
If you right-click on the Dragoon in the character creator, you will unveil...
Wait, what?
How do I do that?
Okay, wait...
The Dragoon... is it here?
Oh, wait, not here.
How do I...
Create...
How do I do it?
Okay, I need the dev to give me a step-by-step guide.
I don't...
They said...
They said we can unlock a new...
A new Doki.
I don't know how.
How do you unlock a new Doki?
What is this?
Okay.
I'll...
They'll let me know later.
The secret Doki.
Instructions unclear.
Guys, I'm too stupid for this.
I don't know.
Okay, don't worry.
Right-click.
Oh, Dragoon image?
Oh, okay.
Well, that's not it.
Don't worry.
They'll tell me later.
I'll be like...
Wait, I should mess it.
How do I unlock...
Step-by-step...
On how to unlock...
The secret Dragoon.
Please.
I know.
Understand.
Oh, like here?
No?
I can't...
I can't keep myself.
Please.
Oh.
Maybe like...
Jovey.
Oh.
Don't keep it.
Alright.
It's time.
This should...
No.
This should be the final match.
The...
This should be the...
Okay.
Let me...
Actually, let me see.
I don't want...
I don't want to...
Oh, my God.
She's too strong.
It's Jo Dharma.
Oh, my God.
Jo Ban is too strong.
She's already getting closer.
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
That was the hidden... that was a hidden secret from the team, the dev team.
Oh my god, you go Jovio Dokument!
You go!
It's too powerful!
Damn baby!
The spirit of Jovio lives on!
Guys, he's... the Chonky Goon is part of your community!
Do you not believe in him?
Do you not believe in your own god?
Just cleaning up all of mine.
Chonky Goon, lock it in!
Guys...
If Chonky Goon can win this, you guys get the announcement early.
I mean...
If Chonky Goon can win this, you get the announcement.
Oh, he moved on.
I don't know, he hasn't...
Oh!
He's left the cage!
Jovio, no!
Nice!
The impact!
Dokument!
Yes!
Let's go!
The impact sent in her back!
He's going back!
There's still one mine left for Chonky Goon.
He has to finish the job!
No!
Jovio!
What are you doing?
Oh, he just wanted to say hi.
Okay, that's...
That's fine.
Oh, nice!
He got it!
He finished the job!
He's finished the job, guys!
It's okay!
No!
Chonky Goons!
I don't know why Chonkiness can beat those kicked up cheeks!
Thank you for the super chat!
Thank you!
Jovio, Dokument 2D Model!
What?
Look at the...
They give us a super chat!
Thank you!
It's okay!
I believe!
Come on, Doki!
Don't disappoint the Dokis from the Doki-verse!
The Doki Council is watching right now!
I believe!
Come on!
Doki Field was able to single-handedly beat Chonky Goon all on her own!
Come on, Jovio!
The Doki Council is judging you right now!
Oh, nice!
Nice!
Take him back to the corner!
Take him back in there!
Chonky wins!
He'll have my respect!
That's good!
He's stuck!
He can't do anything!
No!
Jovio's stuck!
Jovio, please!
Get out of the prison!
Get out, Jovio!
Come on!
The door is stuck!
They're both stuck!
But how is Chonky stuck in a bigger hole?
Get Chonky's up for fines!
His only task is just mines!
Please, I need this!
Come on!
Come on, Jovio!
We can't give them the announcement yet!
We still need to pad more time!
We need to pad as much time as we can!
Why the hell is this so intense?
Welcome to the Dragoon Horse Race!
The Dragoon, welcome to the Dragoon Race Test!
I hope you enjoy your stay!
That was basically what Twitter was like for two weeks, guys!
This was Twitter for two fucking weeks!
I'm gonna turn it up a little bit more!
Oh my god!
You guys swap places?!
I...
How did you guys swap places?!
Get out!
You know!
Great big body, teeny tiny brain!
Thank you for the zipper chat, Ace!
Oh my god!
Now you're puffing!
Chonky-kun was like, I wanna be back in my safe space!
I want to be safe again.
Please, leave the hole!
Leave the widening of it.
He wanted to go home.
Oh my god, it's been five minutes.
Get out of here!
One of you!
It's been five.
No, not you though!
Not you!
Get back in the hole!
No!
Oh my god, they're both in... No!
Jovial!
No!
Get back in there!
Oh, thank god!
Oh, thank god, Chucky!
Thank god!
Oh, he's back home!
He's back home again.
This tough thing is, Jovial could have won this five minutes ago, but she certainly needed a bad time.
So she's stalling.
Thank you for the super chap thing.
No!
Get out!
I need a bad more time!
I didn't expect you to... No, Chucky!
Please!
No!
Go back home!
You're so close!
Yes!
Go home!
Thank you for the same time!
kneel!
Michael took out!
The thumbnail holodex Sound off the part of Dr går начинаются just says, Goon!
Goon!
Race Test!
Thank god!
He choked!
Nice!
As you should!
You didn't learn from your last race, did you Chunky Goon?
He didn't learn!
Chalk more like chalked.
The choke is real.
Yes, keep choking.
Come on, Doki.
Don't disappoint the Doki-verse.
We have such a high record of winning.
We beat all those dragons.
Your tomato, your tomato, Doki, is a four-time champion.
Chalky police.
Oh my god.
Guys, I might have designed a really fucking hard track accidentally.
I might have fucked up a little bit by making a really hard track for them.
I didn't think this would be that difficult.
I thought it'd be a little easier.
It's a bit tough.
Please.
Get out of the hole, Jovio!
Oh.
Sorry, I accidentally paused it.
I...
I was too angry.
I was too angry that I paused the game.
I...
Guys, you don't see it yet.
The Dragoon may be rigged.
Cryopan, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
There's no entitlement.
We could be here forever.
Not so deadpool.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Oh!
No!
Come on!
It's so close!
You were just there!
You were just there, Jovio!
You were literally just there!
Come on!
No!
It's in the corner!
Your cake is too big!
Yes!
Jovio!
There is the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you!
That's right, aged poorly.
Joe... Jovio is winning at making dieki crash up.
That's right, your super chat age poorly!
That's right, another one for the Doki's in the Doki-verse.
That's right, Dracoons.
You need more training.
Great.
Just, I don't know, just be better, I guess.
Just... I don't know.
I guess just...
Get good.
So, I'll even help you guys.
How about this?
I'll put in... All right.
All right, let's see.
Maybe we just need to figure out who is the best drag wound out of all of you.
Don't worry.
I have some pre-made maps that we could use.
I think you'll need it anyway.
You guys definitely need it.
Not Jovial?
I mean...
You guys were struggling so much.
I think I gotta... I think I gotta make it a little bit easier for you guys.
You guys were struggling there.
So...
Let me make it just a little bit easier for all of you guys.
All right.
Here we go.
You know what?
Here, let all you Dragoons race each other too.
He, he, he, he, he...
He, he, he, he...
Perina rules, Jovial loss.
The dragon.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
We don't need...
Look here.
Here's an easier map too, Dragoons.
Maybe...
Maybe this is more of your...
Maybe this is more for you guys.
You know, this track was...
Was made for you guys.
Guys, you know, someone can win.
At least a dragoon can win, guys.
Alright, but if the tomato goon wins, he's one of us.
I get custody of tomato goon every weekend.
And today's a weekend.
Oh my god, that would be so sad.
Guys, if the tomato goon wins...
Oh...
Long goon, you're tired of the shine.
Today's the weekend.
I get custody of tomato goon.
On the weekend.
So technically, he's part of the Jokeyverse.
That's right.
It's not rigged if you're just...
No!
You were so close!
You know what's even sad, though?
Alright, there's...
Alright, let's see.
I think...
Alright.
There's no way.
Okay.
Alright, well...
Long goon, surely...
Surely...
You can't fuck this up, right?
Here, I'll just put a couple of here.
There we go.
Alright.
Long goon, I believe.
You can't...
Surely you can win one match.
One game.
Right?
Long goon...
Can't be that bad.
I believe in you.
No, he can't win.
I...
Come on.
Just get out of there.
Five hours later.
Come on.
You can't get out of there.
Yeah, he's our scion.
The back room.
I can't even...
Get through the fucking hallway.
Come on.
Surely, look.
He's helping you.
Just get out of the hallway.
Just that...
That tiny hallway.
There's two holes.
There's two holes, Long goon.
Two fucking holes.
Surely you can make it through.
You're not chonky like the chonky dragon.
You can fit in there.
There's two holes in there.
This is horrible map.
Sounds like a long goon.
It's so much pain.
Come on.
The hole is literally right there.
It's right...
Just get out of that one hole, Long goon.
You got this.
Cyclone, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
The Robin, thank you for the super chat.
Vaughn, watch your skip three hours.
Guys, he's one of you.
Do you not believe in your own brethren?
Your own brother.
The dragon can't find the hole.
No.
Long goons.
What happened?
This is your representative.
This is your representative that you picked to send to the race.
To the dragon race test.
You picked him.
He's your tribute.
Hell no.
Anton, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Thank you for the super chat.
Oh, he's stupid.
Stupid.
Okay.
His goal is to like go through the hole at least once.
If he goes through that hole...
Any either of the holes.
Once.
Within five minutes.
We will count this as a victory.
That's all we want.
Next thing again.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
I've never been so ashamed to be along.
Oh my god.
He's doing it.
He got out.
He got out of the hole.
As long as he doesn't go back.
It's a victory.
Oh my god.
And he did it within five minutes.
Look at that.
See?
I told you.
He's special.
But like the good kind is special.
Good.
Thank you again for the super chat.
Thank you.
Kaz, look at him go, dude.
What a legend.
Sheer perseverance and determination.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Papa Smurf, thank you for the super chat.
Two weeks till I age out of being a long guy.
Thank God.
He's like, please.
Please, I want to be a real winner.
Make me chonky right now.
Spam, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
We believe it will take three hours.
Oh, he's going back to the... He's like, please, mother.
Put me back in the hole.
I feel more safe in the hole.
I... I want to go back.
No.
The hunker needs to go to Google Maps.
Come on.
It's right there.
That's the other hole you need to get to.
Bro fighting himself and losing.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Alright.
If Long Goon doesn't hit the objective within 10 minutes, I'm sorry.
He's got to be trapped in hell.
I... Yes.
He is... He will be exiled from the Dragoon race test if he can't get out of here in 10 minutes.
He's lost.
Please free him.
He's gonna get... We're gonna delete him from the game files, chat.
We have the version... Version... 5.0.
We remove Long Goon from the data.
He went back.
Chunky chat.
Thriving.
Alan, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Uh, eating, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Oh boy, this ring keeps hitting me when I step on it.
Maybe I should step on it more.
Ryan, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
I was here when Lagos got sent to hell.
Dear representative, your tribute is gonna get you to lead it from existence.
We're gonna fucking fatter snap you out of this game.
It's like, what do you mean?
We never had long goons.
There's always been four.
There's always been... There's always been regular goons, chonky goons, and egg goons.
It's always been three.
Never four.
It was never long goons in passing say.
I even, like, changed my sub badges.
Like, they just never existed.
You're fighting for your existence.
Come on!
Don't do this to me!
Unlucky, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Long goons, why did you go back to the hole?
I'm worried.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Actually, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
It's okay, Long goons.
You go when you feel like it.
It's a test!
He can't test up limited time limits, guys.
There's a time limit in tests.
He can't just go when he wants to.
Thank you.
He just really loves that screen.
Yeah, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
I'm proud of him for trying.
Oh, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
If you didn't read my message, Long goons has two brain cells and both are fighting for third place.
If Long goon ever had a thought, it died alone and afraid.
Come on, Long goon.
Come on, in four minutes, you can get out of that hole.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Why does he keep getting punched?
Is he stupid?
He's... Look, hey, hey, look.
We have... Okay, Long goons.
Long goons, defend yourself.
Why is he like this?
He's just like me.
He is.
He's me.
What do you mean?
He doesn't represent you.
He was chosen.
You picked him.
Please, Doki, don't delete Long goon.
He taught me how to love.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
TikTok, two more minutes.
Good.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Here for Long goons, public exile in less than four minutes.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
TikTok.
He's about to get deleted.
Oh my god, he like...
He like entered that hole and then he got afraid.
He got scared.
He's never been there before.
Mark, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
A long neck means it takes longer for...
He went back!
Why did you go back?
No, it's fucked up.
The second hole is actually technically bigger than the first one too.
Why...
Why does...
Why does he run?
He was too scared of the new hole.
It's over.
Put him out of his misery.
Brother, why are you like this?
He like touched it a little bit.
And then he got scared.
And he's like, never again.
Mom...
Mom, please...
Take me back home.
Guys, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Self delete, please.
If he couldn't win when he was literally right next to it, he's a lost cause.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Okay, that's...
To be fair, that is true.
He was...
We knew he was special when we put the trophy right next to him.
And then he went the opposite direction.
I...
Two...
One...
Zero...
Bye long goon.
You shall be deleted...
Out of existence now.
Your brethren shall...
Shall win the race for you.
They shall...
Tomato goon shall...
Shall be there in your place.
Alright, let's get...
Reset the level and make a...
Alright.
The final two tests, guys.
I believe in you.
Alright, let's make a new track for us.
Okay.
You know what?
We'll send like...
Some people on this side.
And then some people on the other side.
Okay, here we go.
Alright.
And then...
We'll do something like...
There we go.
Ooh.
Alright.
And then we'll put the trophy...
Right here.
We'll put another race...
We are not doing ten more minutes of that.
The coolest.
You guys like my coolest.
And then we'll put...
Punchers right...
Oh wait.
We'll put the punchers...
Right here.
And then...
Here.
Here too.
And then we'll put some mines.
Alright.
And then we'll put some oils...
Oil here.
Too.
And then...
The oil pit.
It's like the mud pit.
But...
But hotter.
Yeah.
Get out of the oil.
Alright.
Let's see.
Hey.
There we go.
Okay.
Wait.
Three should be here.
Actually, we'll put two over here.
Alright.
So my four dragoons.
There's always been four.
Four.
Um...
Drag...
Regular goon.
Chonky goon.
Tomato goon.
And egg goon.
There's always been four dragoons.
And those were our four goons.
Alright.
Place your bets, guys.
Who will be your representative?
To fight.
To race against Jovio Dokiman.
Place your bets.
Chonky goon.
Or...
Tomato...
Goon.
Alright.
Place your bets, guys.
Place your bets.
Chonky goon currently has the highest win rate out of all the goons.
But will he be able?
No.
Will he be able to win this race again and get a rematch against Jovio Dokiman.
Alright.
In three.
Two.
One.
Alright.
They're all like slipping in the oil pit.
First they have to get out of the sexy hot oil pit though.
Oh my god.
They all slipped up.
Damon.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
No.
They can't get it.
They can't make it out of it.
I believe.
Stop saying that.
To be fair.
Tomato is closer to...
Oh.
The tomato goons out.
That's my goon.
I have custody of him on the weekends.
I know that guy.
Oh wait.
No.
Don't go back.
Come on.
Come on, tomato goon.
Cause if you win technically, I win.
Look.
Tomato goons are bleeding.
It's just the juices.
Of the sweat.
He's just sweating red.
Only plays on the weekend.
Oh my.
Come on.
You're so close.
You're so close to the fish like tomato.
He's beating up the dragon.
Oh my god.
Oh.
Egg goons fucking sabotage chonky goons.
No.
Not back in the oil.
Come on.
Get out of there.
You can do this.
Come on.
Get out of the oil pit.
Get out of there.
OKAY.
It's OKAY.
The egg goon isn't in the corridor yet.
We're still fine.
Yes.
Chonky.
Slow and Steady.
How the fuck did the chonky goon make it to the other side.
Your fucking brother is on the left side still.
You know what they say.
The smaller they are, the more aerodynamic they are... Yeah, Iggoon, yeah... Dragoon just... Just noclip!
Just face through the wall!
I like how... Tomato Goon has been like... Still trapped in the oil pit.
He's just like... He's just like... I just wanna be slippery and shiny.
Yeah, it doesn't matter, they're fast.
It doesn't matter if they're... Oh my god, he's back in the fucking oil pit.
They're just faster to hit the walls, chat.
The oil pit is just too sexy.
He just wanna be a fucking... He just wanna be a fucking salad.
He's not looking too good for Chonky Goon, guys.
Chonky Goon... His whole mission is just to get rid of the bombs.
Chonky Goon... He just... That's his whole mission.
On the wall, Chonky Goon!
Chonky Goon is to be... Deserved to be sent to the power of...
Roar, Iggoon!
Let's go!
All right.
Agoon!
Chonky Goon!
Now race against...
...Doki...
...Against...
Jovio Dokiment!
A rematch of the century!
All right!
Let us...
Grab...
All right, let me grab...
...one of my favorite maps.
Give me a sec, guys.
I'm gonna grab one of my favorite maps.
That I like to use.
I think it's...
I think it was this one?
This one?
No.
Okay, it's not this one.
Oh, this one.
Yeah.
All right.
Okay.
Heh.
Here we go.
Put...
...this here.
Okay, let's get rid of seven.
And then we'll put two here.
All right.
A rematch.
Let me make the pull.
We're back here.
Where it all began.
Place...
...your...
...bets.
Jovio Dokiment...
...versus...
...Egg...
...Goon.
All right.
If Eggoon wins this...
...you get your announcement, chat.
In three...
...two...
...one.
Eggoon does have size though.
What happens if he loses?
Then we must have a rematch with all the dragoons again.
Until...
What?
Jovio's like, hey loser.
He's like, yeah.
Can't even get out of the hole.
Oh shit.
Never mind.
He taught the Eggoon how to get out of the hole.
He felt bad for him.
Jovio's taunting him.
He taunted him, but Eggoon felt so inspired.
He was like, that's it.
I won't let you win.
For the dragoons!
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
He's winning by pure spite!
Oh no.
Jovio, Doki, please.
Doki, please.
Doki, man.
Get out of the hole!
You've taunted him enough!
If he loses, he's gonna be scrambled good.
Sorry.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Avenge your brothers!
For the Longoon that's trapped in hell!
He can't even see it and he's made more progress than Longoon did in 10 minutes.
Please!
For your brother that's stuck in hell!
No!
Come on, Doki, man.
Come on, Doki.
You got this!
Doki Field was able to beat this map!
With his eyes closed!
No, please stop showing your ass!
I know it's cheeky!
I know you're kicked up!
We all do!
Each Doki has kicked up asses!
There's no Doki that doesn't have the cake!
Of course...
Of course Kroki does!
The tail feather is just hiding the cake!
Oh my god!
Get down from there!
Come on!
Just need to get down!
Come on, Doki-ville!
Come on!
Come on, Doki-man!
Enough with his hole!
I know you like the egg goon's hole, but enough!
Bro!
You're scaring me!
He's good pushing Jovial in the box!
No!
Stop gapping him!
Stop!
Stop gapping!
They really like that top of the map!
Bro, he's like playing fucking goalkeeper right now!
Oh, it's okay!
No, Jovial, please!
Jovial, downstairs!
Downstairs!
That's for tossing it!
Come on!
You're just flexing!
Come on, come on!
No!
Come on!
It's right there!
It's right there, Jovial!
Come on!
Look!
And Goon came back just to say hi!
It's your chance!
It's your time!
Toasting you for the super chat!
Thank you, thank you!
That reflects the streamer we're kicked up to!
Oh, that's good!
That's good!
He's distracted!
He's like the turtle in the hair!
He's taking a nap right now!
Fighting his time!
Come on, Jovial!
I know you got this!
For the Doki Council!
For the Doki-verse!
Every Doki in the Doki-verse is a winner!
Come on!
Yes, Jovial!
Yes!
Don't disappoint me!
He's building up speed!
No!
Go back down!
Yes!
No!
Oh
my god!
He's just following him!
Escape the hole!
Oh, we're so close!
Right there!
In there!
They're just pretending to race!
So they can have fun in the hole!
It's like a little intermission for them!
Okay, that's good!
Aguna's trapped on the left side!
He hasn't know how to enter the third hole yet!
Because some people don't know there's a third hole!
Oh, yes!
Take over his hole!
That's good, that's good!
Block him!
Now just head down!
Head down, Jovial!
Yes!
Down is up!
And then you go up!
And then you go up, Jovial!
Please!
Then you go!
Yes!
Come on, dragoons!
How can you guys not win that?
Down is up!
No!
It's okay!
I believe in you guys!
I guess I just gotta give you guys another map!
Alright!
How about...
I'll give you an easy map, guys!
Look!
I'll give you guys such...
You know what?
No!
Alright!
Oh!
Come on!
Look at how easy this map is!
There's...
Come on, guys!
You guys just need to train one more time!
And then it should be okay!
And then you'll be fine!
Oh my god!
Look at all these losers here that bet on the wrong Doki!
Look at that!
See, the trophy is literally right here!
There's no way to fuck it up, guys!
There's...
Look at that!
It's literally right there!
There's no way you guys can fuck it up!
This should be...
Oh my god!
Ikkun was like...
Look at!
What the fuck!
Oh my god!
Ikkun was like...
I want a rematch!
I...
He locked it!
He wanted...
He's like...
I heard no bell!
Alright!
We'll do an easier map!
Just cause I'm a little worried...
Wait...
I'm a little...
Worried...
For a goon!
Ha ha ha ha!
Let's see it!
We'll do...
Okay, no, not this one!
This one's called Purgatory!
This might be a little difficult for you!
Ha ha ha ha!
Hmm...
There's one good one...
Oh...
Oh this one!
Alright!
We'll swap it!
The chonky goon is here to watch too!
Heh!
Alright!
Place your bets everyone!
Start pull!
Place...
Your...
Bets...
Ig...
Goon...
Or...
Yeah!
That's where...
Long goon is!
We're not going to Purgatory!
Ha ha ha!
That's where the losers are!
Versus...
Jovio...
Doki-Mint!
Ha ha ha!
Alright!
Revenge!
The rematch of the century!
Here we go!
Ha ha ha!
Oh my god!
Jovio ready!
It fucking bumped into the egg goon!
Like it's hockey!
An egg we trust!
Look!
We even have your brothers here to watch!
They're like, If you lose this we'll fucking eat you!
Ha ha ha!
Jovio ready being aggressive!
And shank the egg on the drive-by!
The chonk...
The extra chonky goons gotta watch!
He's...
They're...
They're giving extra pressure to egg goon!
They're like, If you fuck this up for us brother...
You shall be consumed!
We're so hungry!
Ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha!
We're so hungry!
Ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha!
Come on Jovio!
I know you wanna...
You wanna like, give egg goon a false sense of security!
But I know you also wanna win!
Don't you?
You come from a line of winners!
Yes!
She took his lunch money.
But the egg will take the win!
Alan, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Oh, both Jovial and Egg Goon are on the bottom left.
Never mind.
Jovial was like, I don't like that.
Whoa!
Egg Goon!
Yeah!
No!
So that's right up here.
You know what?
No, it makes sense.
It makes sense.
Literally, he was surrounded.
He was surrounded by all the other Dragoons there.
He just didn't want to get eaten.
You know, that makes sense.
I did say, I did promise you guys, that the moment you Dragoons finally pass the test, you get your announcement.
Before I give you guys the announcement, I just want to say that you can also play the game yourself.
So here is the pin link.
The pin comment.
Sorry, my brain isn't English-ing right now.
But, if you want to play and try out the mod yourself, feel free to download the game on the itch.io page.
And you can also mess around, create your own maps, do your own embedding system, seeing what Dragoon would win.
Huge shout-out again to the team for doing this in such a short time span and being able to do, like, this mini game jam with me.
And, you know, creating something really fun for all of you guys.
I had a great time watching the progress of everything being made and seeing it all come together.
So, huge shout-out to the team again.
If you guys want to check their socials, you can see it on the itch.io page where it links to all the creators that helped me with making this.
Anyway, but Iggoon, to all the Iggoons out there, congratulations on winning, on being the chosen Dragoon representative.
To beat Jovio Dohima.
You are the peak Dragoon form.
Now, on to the announcement as your prize.
Yeah!
It's a new outfit!
Yes!
Finally, a new outfit reveal for... Sorry, my brain is not working.
I'm such like an amateur right now.
I'm so tired.
But yes, we're finally gonna have our own beach episode!
Next week, starting next week on June 20th, 5pm PSC, we will have our own beach episode!
Yes!
My very first outfit reveal!
Yay!
Since coming back as the Bounty Honor!
I'm really looking forward.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I have some fucking crazy ideas for that stream.
Well, not crazy.
I don't want to hype it up.
It's just nice to be creative again.
So, I'm super excited.
Luka, thank you for the Akasupa!
Thank you!
I really appreciate it!
Beach ball suit!
Let's go!
Next week, they give a super chat.
Thank you!
So excited for the summer outfit reveal.
See ya!
They give a super chat.
Thank you!
If Doki is a beach bird, does that mean she's a seagull now?
They give a super chat.
Thank you!
Alright!
So, a little context about this outfit.
This outfit is actually one of the charity goal outfits.
So, the winner of the auction that got to pick the theme of this outfit decided to pick summer outfit.
So, this is... your fellow dragoon actually helped design this particular outfit as well.
So, I hope you guys look forward to it.
And it is a summer theme slash beach episode.
I will post the silhouette of it later today.
As well as the dragoon race test where people want to download it on Twitter.
But yeah!
I look forward to it, guys.
It's gonna be really... it's gonna be fun to have something new.
A new skin suit.
And... it's gonna be fun to have a new skin suit.
And just to show you guys new hairstyle and everything.
It's gonna be fun in general.
But thank you guys for coming, everyone!
I did... I didn't know what to do for like...
But like... okay, I like struggled a little bit trying to think of how to do with this type of announcements.
Cause I, you know, I miss doing creative stuff for you guys.
It's been a very long time since...
Since I've done creative stuff these days.
Since I've been like super busy.
And, you know, just playing... just streaming games and stuff.
Because of how busy I was.
And there's so much stuff behind the scenes and everything.
So...
And then sometimes I get like ideas and inspirations.
So fucking last minute.
So I really appreciate the team for enabling me.
And for like putting up with like, you know, such a tight deadline.
To put all of this together.
As the announcement.
And it was...
I really appreciate them as well.
For creating all of this together with me.
So huge shout out for the team.
And it's been fun doing something creative like this again.
I always enjoy doing stuff like this.
And, you know, being able to just like...
Do more than just streaming video games.
Technically, this is a game as well.
But...
We...
I helped produce a game for you guys.
For you guys to mess around with.
Like a mod of the game.
Sorry.
We didn't make it.
We modded another game.
To make it more...
Doki slash dragon themed.
Um...
But...
It was still really fun to do.
And it was really fun to like...
Just see the progress from the beginning to now.
And everything.
And...
It was just great to do something super creative again.
Um...
And I hope I get to do more creative stuff.
In the future.
Um...
As things get...
What's the word?
As...
It gets easier to manage.
My time.
I've been delegating a lot more this time.
So...
It's slowly freeing up my time.
To...
Uh...
Use my brain for things like this.
So...
I'm glad I was able to.
Uh...
But yes.
Thank you everybody for coming.
Thank you all for the super chats.
Uh...
I'm gonna go rest now.
And sleep.
Cause I'm tired.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
I'm eepy.
Ha ha ha ha.
But...
I hope you guys enjoyed...
This little fun stream I did today.
And I'm very excited about the announcement.
Um...
So I'll see you guys...
Well...
I'll see you guys...
Like on Monday.
But...
Ha ha ha ha ha.
But I do hope...
To see you guys on...
Friday.
For the outfit reveal.
On June 20th.
5pm PST.
I'll play the trailer again for all of you guys.
But thank you all for coming.
As always everybody.
Stay hydrated.
Posture check.
Get up and move around.
To get that blood flowing.
And if you suffer me.
Head to bed.
Cause...
You deserve it.
I'll see you guys next time everybody.
You can tell my brain is lagging a lot.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
I'm just...
I'm just a little teepy.
Just a little tired.
Ha ha ha.
I'm trying not to drink caffeine today.
Uh...
Ha ha ha.
Because I know like caffeine...
I don't wanna depend on caffeine.
So like...
So my brain is lagging a little bit.
Because of the lack of caffeine.
But I'm trying my best to like...
Not rely on it.
Ha ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha.
But...
Thank you all for coming.
I'll see you guys later everyone.
Bye guys.
Bye.
I'll see you guys.