What is it in VTuber terms, hag?
I'm a hagtuber.
And then when you're 40, you're basically dead.
Oh my god, those look like ball sex.
But then your friend banned me because I called them a whore and I'm like...
Doki.
Hey, that's me.
When are you singing my song that I wrote for you?
First of all, we need to get the important things out of the way here.
Okay, that's a news drop right there out of nowhere to start off the podcast.
Yes, yes, yes.
So, yes, Lilia wrote me a song a while ago.
And I haven't done anything with it.
Oh no, don't worry.
No, no pressure.
Just so... I'm just making sure you haven't forgotten about it.
Yeah, no, I haven't.
I'm sorry.
Okay, to be fair, okay.
Okay, to be fair, I have excuses lined up.
Don't worry about this.
No, I understand.
I understand.
I just thought it would be really fun to ambush you just like out of the gate.
This is like peer pressure.
So now fans would be like, at Doki Bird, when are you going to sing your song?
It's such a good song, guys.
She's going to sound so great.
I'm just so excited for it, okay?
That's the only reason.
Yeah.
Yeah, so like she wrote me a song.
I asked Lily if she was open to writing me a song.
And her and her producer, who were also the ones that made last cup of coffee, were like super down.
And then months pass and it's still singing.
But I have an excuse, guys.
No, it's okay.
It's going to sound so good.
Yeah, it's going to sound really good.
And the production balance is going to be insane.
But yes, like it was unfortunate timing because I actually got very sick when I was about to record.
No, I get you.
Yeah, I got really sick and my throat was like not okay for the longest time.
And then because like, I don't even know, but I did like a 3D concert around like November or so.
And then during that time, I was sick before then.
For that November concert, when we were recording our songs, I literally submitted a song that was like, because I had like several songs I was doing for that concert.
And my last song I recorded for it, I submitted it two days before the concert was supposed to get me to start.
I was like, oh, shit.
Because that was how sick I was.
Because like, I got better.
And then when I had to travel to the studio to rehearse, I got sick during traveling there.
And so I came back, so my voice wasn't okay.
And then I went to Atlanta for the concert.
And then I got sick again.
You're getting sick quite often.
I think it's because of COVID.
Ever since COVID, my immune system got like really like fucked up.
I don't know.
Am I allowed to swear?
Yeah, you can swear.
Yeah.
So like during COVID, my immune system, I became like a bubble baby.
Because I was always inside a lot.
Because I always was like, I don't want to get COVID.
And because of that, ever since then.
And that was around the time.
I don't know.
You know, like COVID was around the time where the VTubing boom started.
Yes.
And then, yeah.
And then so like everyone was like staying at home mostly.
And that's where I started doing VTubing stuff.
And then because of that, I didn't really go outside anymore.
So my immune system got weaker and weaker.
And then this year, this and last year, I was traveling so much.
But my body wasn't ready for that.
So like every time I travel, I would get sick.
Because after the concert, I went to Japan.
And then I got sick again.
Do you use that?
Do you carry around three bottles of hand sanitizer for baby?
Yeah, I do.
I can't.
But the thing was like during Japan, like people were like, like I went to a land there.
It was like the very first land I went to.
And there were so many people there.
Like there was just, you couldn't avoid it.
Yeah.
I just got over being sick too.
And it was very frustrating because I couldn't use my voice properly for like two, three weeks, which was quite insane.
And it just 1000% nerfed.
Oh, I also think maybe, oh my God.
I'm such a bad podcast host.
This is Doki Bird, everyone.
Oh, by the way.
Yeah, hello.
I'm Doki Bird for this video.
Because like this is the first VTubing episode you're doing.
So you're like, who the heck is this virtual anime girl?
Poki isn't here.
So we thought it'd be really fun to do a VTube guest episode.
And I whip out my VTube model as well.
And we're both VTube models.
Yeah, so cute.
Yeah.
I heard you have like a collection of them too.
I know you've had like so many different like designs and models over the years.
I have, but it's only because like, you know, I feel like if I don't feel connected to the model, it's hard for me to use it.
This is the first model I really, really like.
I love it, which is why I'm using it so much, right?
That's true.
Yeah.
Same for me.
I know like a lot of people like my older one, the retro one with the twin tail, where the theme was thief.
But that was like, but that was like so old.
Like literally like during like COVID era time when I got that skin suit.
And then like, um, and like, yeah.
I like it.
I got that skin suit.
And then, but the, cause like it was rigged around that time too.
So like the rigging for that was very like outdated.
I did get it updated when I came back.
Um, but like still I did connect with it as much as I did during that time.
Because I felt like back then I was, when I used to stream back then during that era.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
My dog is also like that too.
He like knows whenever I end stream too.
And like every time I end stream, he's like, oh, that's when, like, he knows my tone when I'm about to end stream.
And he runs in and would be like, it's time to feed me.
Dogs are so perceptive.
Wait, continue your story.
Wait, what was I talking about?
The Phantoms.
Oh, yeah, the thief one.
Yeah, but like I said, like, back then when I used to stream back, like I started streaming back then, I also didn't play a lot of FPS games back then.
I was more of like an artist streamer.
Cause I used to like draw a lot back then.
So like it matched well with the vibe.
But now I'm more of like a gaming streamer.
So like every time I see fan art of like, when I used to see fan art, I'd be like, the thief outfit with carrying a gun.
It just, it's like, I was like, oh, it's just something off.
There's something off about it.
And so like, that's why I was like, oh man, I want like something that fits me more.
I can totally get that.
I think if it, like, if you relate to it more, you feel connected to it more, you want to, cause it's like supposed to represent you, you know?
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
It's kind of how I felt too.
I'm like, I need something simpler and just me.
And then I'm like, oh, I love this.
And like, but can you explain the, um, wait, so Phantom Thief is because, wait, why?
Oh, oh, Phantom Thief.
Oh, the Phantom Thief.
It was basically a play on my friend.
Her name is Mint Phantom.
And so like, fans started calling us because we do a lot of streams together.
Yeah.
Like me and my friend.
And, um, they started, it's like a little ship name for them.
Like the Phantom Thief.
Oh, that's cute.
Phantom Thief.
Yeah.
So it was more so since like, every time we do something together, it'd be like, oh, it's the Phantom Thief duo.
Oh, that's adorable.
I like that.
I saw, I remember seeing like the super viral clip of you.
Oh, there's so many.
Oh my God.
I need to go beat my dog.
Hold on.
Oh, Timmy.
I'm just joking.
That's a joke.
It's a bad joke.
I need to stop making that joke.
This is in Minecraft, right?
In Minecraft.
Do you like ever name a dog, Timmy?
No, it's too sad.
I get attached to my Minecraft dogs if I named them after my real dogs.
It's because dogs' lives are so short.
Yeah, but then you can, you know, like the new Minecraft update, you can feed it and then the hearts will go back up.
So you can just give it like a little, you know, a little warning hit.
I'm just scared.
Sometimes they like, the teleporting aspect of them is a little wonky.
Oh, that's true.
So sometimes they like go in the middle of nowhere and I'm like, oh, you're dead.
Yeah.
You're just like...
Enough about dogs though.
It's all about horses right now.
Am I right?
Oh, true.
The Uma Musume.
Have you played?
No, I haven't played.
Because like, for me, okay, I'm always worried about playing any games related to gacha.
That's true.
Because like...
If I ever get hooked in anything where I have to spend money, like, I have a problem.
No, I understand that.
I'm sorry.
You've never done that.
Like, I haven't played...
Like, I told my chat would be like, when are you gonna play?
And I was like, you guys gotta bribe me to play this game because I...
I'm worried.
Like, and also like, when I saw like people playing the game at first, there was so much reading.
I was like...
The horse game is on my tablet.
The horse game is called Uma Musume.
For anyone wondering, it's a really interesting anime horse game.
Anyway, and I spent $13 just to get like 10 pulls or something.
Right?
And then yesterday, I spent another $20.
So, in total, I spent $30, but that's it.
That's it.
I will not spend a single cent more.
I'm basically free to play.
If we're being honest here.
But what if they come up with new horses?
That's...
What if they come up with new horses?
Oh, man.
They're winning.
New support cars.
New horses.
New trainers.
What you gonna do?
Low-key be a really good horse girl name.
What?
With the bird at the end?
Doki Battle.
That would be so cool.
Oh, do we...
Oh my god.
Do you have ADHD?
I think I have ADHD.
Oh, I was talking about the fish.
So, Jackie.
Well, we're not gonna let you finish, but anyway.
Oh, no.
I love this so much.
I saw a clip of you going like, huh?
Like that...
That pink...
Can you do it?
Like...
Yeah, that thing!
It was so good.
I saw it and I immediately went to my record.
Soy.
I'm like, soy.
I want one too.
It was so...
I swear to you, I was like...
I didn't even realize I made that face.
Because whatever...
You saw like the full context, right?
Yeah.
Like, are you and Peter still together?
And then like that...
I was so...
I...
Because I was joking...
When that happened, I was just joking around with my chat.
Because I was like, oh, they're so like...
They're on a date right now.
And I'm just here trying to play Apex.
And then like, and then he dropped that.
And then she was like...
And then she was like, oh, no, yeah.
Yeah, we are.
And like, he's right beside me right now, playing like Minecraft.
And then, literally after that, the guy, DC's, like, disconnects from the game.
After she said that.
And then he was like, oh, and then he came back.
He was like, sorry, my internet, like, died for a little bit.
I was like, sure, buddy.
I think it was so good.
Because, like, it just felt like a very funny, like, genuine in the moment sort of thing.
Like, it was so funny.
I saw the clip and I died.
It was, it was great.
I was like, I can't believe that happened to me.
Because I wasn't, I wasn't even planning on streaming that day, too.
I was, like, literally, it was, the whole stream was just me trying to, I just got my new PC.
And, like, I just got it back.
So I was just stress testing my PC at that time.
So I was just, like, I just happened to stream and it just caught, like, it just caught that moment.
I was like, oh, my God.
The most random things go viral, I swear to God.
Yeah, that's so true.
Last night, my friend's alt Twitter tweet went viral, too.
For just, like, random reasons.
She just tweeted about a bad Uber experience, right?
Yeah.
Where she gave him a one star, because it was so bad, and then he circled around.
Wait, I saw that tweet!
Wait, you saw that?
It went in my algorithm!
That's what I mean.
It's, like, the most random tweets about, like, she, this isn't the first time a random tweet of hers got viral, too.
It's just, like, this random tweet!
Yeah, like, and, like, she didn't have, because I looked at her Twitter, too, because, like, you ever just look at, like, a viral tweet and just check someone's Twitter account?
Like, who are they as a person?
And I was like, she didn't have that many followers, too, on that alt Twitter.
Yeah.
And it just randomly blew up.
It's so random.
Sometimes, it's, um, it's funny, though, because, like, I have this, like, fear, low-key of this fear, I don't know if you have it, as a content creator, right?
You sleep, and then you wake up, and you wake up to, like, thousands and thousands of notifications.
You gotta check Twitter right now.
And I'm like, oh, my God, what did they find?
What did they do?
What did I do?
I'm sorry.
And you're like, what leaked?
What Google talkie came out this time?
What?
Like, I think I lead a pretty peaceful life, but that's, like, low-key a nightmare situation.
Yeah, like, when you're, like, when you're, like, a content creator for so long, you're, like, you've done so many things, and you're just, like...
And then, but you just, like, see, like, other content creators getting cancelled and everything, and you're just wondering, oh, my God.
Like, what did I do?
What did I do?
That's true.
Yeah.
But I feel like even when content creators get, like, quote, unquote, cancelled, and people forget about it in, like, a week.
That's so true.
It's so fast.
I think, like, every, like, a week on the internet is, like, what, 20 years online?
Yes.
It feels like forever in the moment, and then something new happens, like, five minutes later, and we're, like, okay, we're gonna move on, I guess.
Yeah, like, it's just so forgettable.
We just have such short, I think it's, we just have such short attention spans these days.
Like, we're so, like, brain-rotted from the internet.
Oh, my God.
We just, like, just, like, something else just catches.
Like, you know, like, jingle jingle.
Do you browse, like, TikTok short-form content?
Oh, I do for YouTube shorts.
Not TikTok, though.
But YouTube shorts.
Yeah, YouTube shorts.
That makes you better.
Yes, because we're on YouTube right now.
This podcast is also going to be on YouTube.
Dude, I used to think like that.
Yeah, I'm like, yeah, I don't browse TikTok.
I browse shorts.
I'm a little bit more.
Yeah.
I'm more sophisticated than I'm more cultured.
And then I went down to TikTok rabbit hole anyway.
So now I browse all three.
Oopsies.
I feel like TikTok, like TikToks are, like, more brain-rotted than YouTube shorts.
Because I remember, like, seeing...
You know, like, when a TikTok video goes viral, it, like, shows up on Twitter.
Yeah.
Like, the stuff that comes from TikTok is just even...
Like, it's at a whole new level.
Because it's, like, we're...
What is it?
Gen...
What's the newest gen?
Not Gen Z.
No, no, no.
It's Gen Alpha now, man.
Yeah, Gen Alpha.
Oh, don't tell me.
I feel so old.
I'm...
The chat calls me anti.
Like, I don't...
What is it in VTuber terms?
Hag?
Whatever the fuck.
Hag, yeah, yeah.
Dude, it's so, like...
I know it's...
It's...
Okay.
At first glance, it sounds kind of like, okay, it's a little rude.
But then, at the second class, it's a really funny meme.
Like, hag?
What a word to use.
Yeah.
Like, high hag.
And then it's like, when you hit 30, you're a hag.
You're a hag.
You're just...
You're eldritch.
You're, like, ancient.
And then when you're 40, you're basically dead.
You're dead.
Oh, my God.
That's so funny.
It does feel like, in this space, you know...
I think it's because my friends and I talk about this, right?
Because a lot of friends are my age, too.
It's like, we started off streaming.
There's nobody really, like, after us.
Us, this generation.
Yeah, I guess.
So there's nothing to look forward to, I guess.
So, if you're the oldest, obviously you're gonna be, you know, you're considered the oldest.
Which kind of sucks, but...
At the same time, you know, respect your elders and all that.
Respect your elders.
Yeah, because, like, you guys are basically, like, paving the way on, like, what to expect when you're older and everything.
I always, like...
Okay, to be fair, like...
When I always...
I was so surprised when I found out Shroud was only, like, 30.
Because he...
Because I thought...
Because he was here forever.
Forever.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But that's the thing.
30s is, like, paving the way.
Yeah, yeah.
30 is...
Which is crazy.
Is, like, the elderly.
And I was like, he's only 30?
I was so surprised.
I was like, bro, he...
To be fair, I thought he was, like, almost...
I'm sorry, but...
Yeah, I thought he was almost 40.
Oh, Shroud, don't look at this.
He's a nice guy, man.
He is.
He's a really nice guy.
But he was here forever.
He's, like, with Justin TV days, right?
Oh, my God.
I remember Justin TV.
Yeah.
And he was part of the OG CS.
Like, CS days as well.
So I never thought...
I was like, he's 30.
I was like, oh, my God.
That's a lot younger than I expected.
Well, nowadays, they're like...
Well, I was, like, seeing...
Like, you know, Jason Dewey, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The new and upcoming.
Very big streamer now.
But he's, like, 21 or something, right?
Yeah.
21.
It was so young.
And a lot of them are, like, that young.
Like, 19, 20.
You know, every time fans come up to me now.
Every time.
Every single time now.
They're like, I've been watching you since middle school.
It's so bad.
Every time.
No, it's not even, like, an isolated incident.
It used to be an isolated incident.
But now it's not.
They're in college now, Doki.
Oh.
I've been doing this way too long.
You're going to have people come and be like, I used to watch you in elementary school.
I know.
I've had that.
Like, this one girl.
She's, like, 12 years old.
She's like, I watched you since I was five years old.
And I'm like...
You have your whole life ahead of you.
You're so young.
So bright-eyed.
Also, what are you doing on twitch.tv?
Actually, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
You're supposed to be 13 and older to have an account.
No.
I feel like kids these days are so much more in tune with, like, technology.
And, you know, everyone has a fucking iPad.
iPad kids everywhere.
iPad kids.
Yeah.
Back in my day, I had flip phones.
Flip phones.
Do you remember those?
I remember those.
Back in my day, my parents would let me have a phone until I was in eighth grade.
Yeah.
And now you start young.
Oh, do you know, like, but if you are an iPad kid, technically your brain is not developed very well.
Did you read that?
That would be scary.
Like, if I were a parent and I read that, I'd have no more iPad for you.
Yeah.
I was like, what?
Because, like, you know, nobody had, like, studies for it yet.
And then now they do because iPad's been a while for a while.
They're like, oh, yeah.
Now that we, like, actually know what happens when you give kids iPads, it actually messes up brain development for children.
Dude.
I am low-key scared of that kind of study, but with other things that we are currently doing, like, for example, society's overconsumption of caffeine.
Like, I drink a lot of diet cokes and stuff.
Like, you know, all that aspartame skin.
Yeah.
That's so true.
Energy drinks, like, a lot of...
Hey, we're here for a good time, not a long time.
Remember?
That's right.
I mean, I'm already pretty much dead in my thirties.
Yeah.
You're approaching 40.
You're...
Dude, it's...
When I was in my late twenties, people would always say, yeah, you're pushing 30.
You shouldn't be doing this stuff anymore.
Now that I'm in my thirties, they say, yeah, you're pushing 40.
I'm like, it's never gonna end, is it?
It just doesn't end.
Yeah.
It's actually...
It's...
It's very interesting, like, seeing, like, what the...
Like, we're literally living, living through it now to see, like, our consequences.
Cause we're like...
Cause you're like the test subject.
You know, it's so interesting to see, like, how far VTubing has gone too.
Oh, true.
Like, so many VTubers.
Every single combination of human eggs, some kind of animal, slash mystical animal design.
Slash thing.
Slash place.
Yeah.
It's like, whoa, I'm waiting for the first refrigerator VTuber or something.
You know?
Fridge Chan.
Are you...
You're just human or a bird?
I'm a...
Well, yeah.
I'm like half bird, half human.
Cause I was like a dokey bird.
Yeah.
I would say it's very bird oriented.
You know?
Yeah.
Do you have like a...
Like a...
Like, you know how VTubers have like a lore thingy?
How they came to...
Do you have a lore?
Oh, yeah.
Like, I'm actually a tomato.
And like, I have various, like...
Skin suits.
Makes sense.
That I get into.
So...
So I have like...
I have a crow version of me.
Wait, can I see?
Oh, you wanna...
Okay, wait.
Can you show me your outfits?
Okay.
I'll show you my outfits.
So I have a crow version.
I have a Garfield version.
I have a tomato...
Or OG tomato.
And then...
And I have like a...
And I have like various outfits as well.
So wait, I can show you like...
I can take off my skin.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Change.
Changing.
Alright, let me...
Let me change real quick.
We should do like an animation here where like curtains go over her.
And the curtains come out.
Cause that'd be really funny.
Like the magical girl.
Yeah.
Where is...
Oh, there it is.
I haven't brought this out in a while.
I only bring it out for like...
Special occasions.
Oh, I'm excited.
Wait.
Okay, wait.
I'm holding a knife.
Let me take my knife off.
I don't know why, but...
I forgot.
I put a...
I had to wear a...
That is not what I expected.
Literally a tomato.
Yeah.
Um...
So like beneath every...
All my skin suit.
This is me.
I'm like...
So like...
It's like a tomato that's pilot.
Like...
Oh, get in the Mecca.
So I'm like piloting every anime girl out there.
And...
And a crow.
And a crow too.
And...
I freaking love that.
That is so funny.
Oh, wait, wait.
I have like...
Let me put...
I have a special toggle for this too.
Um...
Let me see if I can...
Oh my gosh.
I need to remember all my...
Toggle stuff.
It's been so long.
Okay.
Uh...
Oh my gosh.
There's this really good one that I like to use.
Okay, there's this one.
I don't know why, but your voice fits the tomato really well.
Oh, I know.
Yeah, I know.
I know it does.
For the audio only listeners, she does indeed have a tomato form.
It's the most janky shit I've ever seen, but it's very cute.
Why does her face...
It gets tiny and small.
Yeah.
Do you have little bites?
Like...
Oh, that's...
Her face gets really small in the tomato, which adds to the comedic effect.
I have like a hat.
Oh, the hat is so cute.
Yeah.
I can wear a hat.
And then I can have...
I can be a cowboy too.
I'd be like...
Yee-haw.
And then...
Oh!
She's a little cute little...
You know, it's the...
It's basically the pleading emoji.
Yeah.
Like...
And this one's my favorite.
Wait.
RGB tomato.
RGB on.
You know?
Oh, wait.
I don't know how to turn it off.
She doesn't act.
She's just switching colors right now.
She looks like she's having a bad trip.
I'm like, oh, take your meds.
Take your meds.
But...
My favorite definitely is...
The crow.
Because every time I put out the crow, everyone was like...
Oh my god.
Like, your voice fits perfectly on the crow.
Let me see.
Okay.
But that actually takes a while to set up though.
Really?
Okay.
Let's do it at the end then.
Yeah.
Because that one is like...
It's like a 3D model.
So I have to...
Oh, you have a 3D model.
Yeah.
The crow is like...
The crow is a 3D model.
So...
This one's recent.
This one I just...
That one is so cute.
Oh my god.
Every time I press anything, it's like I'm texting.
So I'm like, I'm gonna cancel you right now on Twitter.
Let me...
Let me type it on my phone.
Wait.
I love that one.
It's so cute.
Oh my god.
You make me want to commission more outfits and stuff.
But they're so fucking expensive, man.
Oh, that's the fun part.
That's the fun part.
So I can change it to like a tomato hoodie too.
Oh, that's so cute.
And then...
I'm gonna have like a lollipop.
Like...
Oh my god.
That's so cute.
I'm gonna stuff you in a locker.
I want more outfits now.
Oh, you should...
That's like the fun part.
Honestly.
But like...
It's so expensive though.
Like YouTubing.
Oh, that's so true.
It's so expensive.
That's so true.
Like not just like the art itself, but the rigging too.
The rig...
No, I tried rigging like one thing once.
Like the mini...
I see those like mini chibi ones.
But even that took me like two full days to like learn the tracking and everything.
Right?
And that's not like with all the cool physics and stuff, you know?
That's true.
But I have a lot more, you know, respect for people who rig models.
Yeah, yeah.
That's the most time consuming thing.
I really thought it was going to be under like my list of hobbies.
But I crossed that out really quickly because the amount of time it takes is unreal.
Oh, that is so true though.
Like have you ever seen...
Okay, so my rigger is Celia.
And she's like one of the most like well-known like VTubing rigs rigger out there.
And she recently did like...
She recently did Saba's rigging.
And she posted like her...
She posted like the file for it.
And it was crazy.
Like...
No.
I know.
It's insane.
Not only the rigging part too, but like the art.
Well, yeah.
I tried drawing the file as well.
Just making it like separating everything into layers.
Yeah.
And then they have to redraw some of the layers too to make it work.
And everything like cutting wise as well.
And then...
It's such tedious work.
Yeah.
Essentially making the 2D art look kind of 3D.
And it has to be like natural too.
Because when you turn this way, I make sure...
Everything just looks okay, right?
Yeah.
Angle wise looks like...
Looks natural and everything because it's all about...
Because if it's off a little bit like...
You look weird.
Your brain will notice it right away too.
You're like...
Like it's like an uncanny valley type...
The moment you realize something's off.
I love how much it's grown.
Like I wish 20 year old Lily had this technology.
I remember using fucking PNGs.
Like 2 PNGs.
True with Fugi's and stuff too.
Well, I still love Fugi's though.
I think Fugi's are just so gif.
For those who don't know, it's like...
Still PNG and then active...
Like a talking PNG when you talk essentially.
Like voice acting.
It can be animated too.
It can be like a gif and stuff.
And it's like more immersive.
Yeah.
And like you actually know who's talking.
Like...
I draw one for like everyone I'm in call with.
Yeah.
Because it just...
It just makes it so much cuter in my opinion.
Yeah, yeah.
Like there's just more like...
Like it's just more animated and more like...
I guess personal wise.
Like for the community and for yourself to look at.
I love you too.
Oh yeah, but...
Oh wait, I forgot to show you my last outfit.
This one...
This one I got for...
It's like my summer outfit.
But this was the other outfit I have.
Oh my god!
I'm like on a beach.
And then I...
I love that.
And then I didn't realize this, but...
Okay, I'm gonna unlock it.
And like...
So I have...
Oh my god!
Those look like ball sex!
Yeah, I do!
They look like ball sex!
You've been told this, right?
You have been told this!
Okay, but look at the physics though.
Okay, the physics is phenomenal.
Like truck nuts.
Like it's just really good.
Okay, so...
I didn't realize how...
Sus...
It was.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's perfect.
The audio only was there.
She's in like a...
Like a Hawaii teacher sort of thing.
Yeah, yeah.
And there's three...
Tomato...
Looking water balloons.
Water balloons.
Yes, hanging from her...
Side bag.
But when she bounces up and down, it does look like ball sex.
The physics of it.
So you should check out...
Check out the video on YouTube.
Check out the video.
There are a lot of audio only listeners.
So I try to like tell them...
Wait, I really like this.
It gives like a...
What's the androgynous feel to it?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
So I'm like...
The...
The cool ass.
Yeah, you're the cool fucking...
The cool ass at the beach.
When I did the summer...
Cause like for this one, it was actually like...
I did a charity auction for this outfit.
Uh huh.
So like I was like, okay, whoever wins the auction gets to design the new outfit.
Wait, that's so sick.
Yeah.
So like it was like a fan that designed this outfit too.
You're so cool.
That's such a good idea.
Wow.
So yeah, it's like, you know, something good for charity and also like something the fan won.
Yeah.
Honestly, they designed it really cute.
I really like it.
Uh, but yeah, that's like the parts.
Cause like for this one, they also wanted a tail too.
So you can sort of see...
Wait.
I see the tail.
Yeah.
Cause they were like, we wanted, we want you to be more bird-like.
So they like, uh, gave me a tail.
To be like, okay, now you're definitely Doki bird.
Wow.
So cool.
I love seeing different like...
Dude.
Oh my gosh.
Show you my one outfit.
Yeah.
Ready?
Yeah, I'm ready.
Um, sorry.
That's it.
That's the...
Okay.
But not only that way.
That's not it.
It's okay.
I have one too.
That's it.
Okay, glasses do this though.
And then the...
And then the color changed.
But that's really all I ordered because I'm like...
I think before I tried too much at once and it overwhelmed me.
So I...
This time I'm taking it like...
Simple.
Tiny bit at a time.
Yeah.
To be fair, like...
For like the toggles and stuff, like...
You normally don't even really use it on stream.
That's what I learned.
Like, my first YouTube models, I commissioned like seven toggles and I'm like, why the fuck did I do that?
It only cost more money and I end up just using the simplest one anyway.
Like this...
What is it?
Oh, yeah.
I just asked for like a disappointed toggle because I'm disappointed in my chat or something.
Are you always disappointed in them?
No, they're disappointed in me, especially when I boot up Valorant.
They tell me to end stream.
Oh!
No, I don't blame them.
Oh, God.
I'm so bad at FPS.
Yeah, I'm really bad at Valorant.
That's like...
People are always surprised when I tell them like, I'm so bad at like, tactical shooters.
Cause you're like, you play...
You're like an FPS like, VTuber.
How are you bad at like, tactical shooters?
But like, I'm so like, I always tell people I don't have ADHD, but it seems like I do.
But like, I just, I think it's just being brain rotted.
It's not ADHD.
It's just, I'm just so brain rotted.
Oh, no.
We gotta fix this.
But basically like, when I play tactical shooters like Valorant, you know, like the thing is, you have, you can't move when you're shooting.
Yes.
And like, I, I, that's just goes against everything I want to do.
Oh, that's true.
Yeah.
Apex are moving like constantly.
Cause if you're like, I play for me, I play mostly play movement shooters.
So I play like Apex, Overwatch, Marvel Rivals.
And they're all about, you have to move.
You have to move.
Yeah.
If you move, if you don't move, you die.
And if you move in Valorant or any of you shooting your fucking ass.
And Chad is like, why the fuck are you moving?
You have to stop and shoot.
And then, and then you always have to have your cross.
You always have to have your crosshair at their head at the whole time.
I know.
But if you play movement shooter, like if you play Apex, my, cause I played, spent so many years on Apex.
And for Apex, your crosshair has to be at the body, not the head.
So it's like, it like fucks with me when I have to play Valorant.
Yo, that's completely different.
Yeah.
Completely different.
The muscle, like memory, like with my hand, it just fucks with me.
So I could never get into, I never could get into tactical shooter.
It's just so slow for me.
What kind of other games, what other games do you play nowadays?
Well, I usually, I just play like Rivals on the side.
Rivals.
Yeah.
And like for me, like, people would be like, oh, what single player games do you play off stream?
But like, I don't like, cause I'm like, if I'm going to play single player, I'll just stream it.
You know?
Yeah, that makes sense.
That's how I feel too.
I'm like, I might as well stream this.
Yeah.
Like I'm like, cause also like, oh my gosh.
Okay.
So you, I always say this joke to my chat, but one of the reasons why I love streaming like single player games is so I could be like, you know, it's like at chat GP, like at Grok, like, how is this real?
So I could be, I always be like at chat.
What do I do next?
Like, I'm like, I love, I actually love backseating because like, I, I, I like, I, you know, I was like, I don't know what to do next.
So I could be like, chat, where do I go?
No, but sometimes chat gives you wrong information.
Yeah.
But that would be like, I've had that happen.
But then I like, cause like I was playing this game, the new FNAF game.
I don't remember what it's called, but the, the secret, I remember there was, there's a new FNAF game that came out and they were like making me, like, I had to go to this store and I need to get password, but I missed the clue to get the password, but I didn't want to go back.
So I was like, okay, chat, tell me, just tell me the password.
Cause I'm not going to go back.
And then, and then they kept like, we're like, you know, they'll be like type boob, you know, like eight years.
And I was like, no, it's not boob.
And then I was like, I'll be like, guys, I know one of you will crack.
And I was like, guys, I know like some of you guys here want me to get this achievement.
Like to unlock the secret ending.
And if I don't get the answer in five minutes, I will leave.
Cause I don't care as much as you guys.
Like for the secret ending.
Do you ever get like one guide?
Oh, lots of times.
And then I, and then when I do get one guide.
You banned them.
Okay.
I have, if they me over, I have, I have like given them a one day ban if they me over.
But like, whenever I get one guy, it's not even one guy.
It's like three guys.
Oh no.
Three guys would give me the wrong answer.
And then they're like, I can't believe you got three guides.
Three guides is crazy.
That would happen to me.
But yeah.
Oh my gosh.
The amount of times I get one guide.
It's, it's looking crazy.
Yeah.
I feel like sometimes all the chats gonna, chats like great, right?
And then one person says something.
And for some reason you single that person out and that person, you just listen to them.
And then it's wrong.
And then.
Yeah.
And just.
It'll never happen again.
If you ever got like the chatter that would spam the wrong answer multiple times.
So you think everyone's saying that answer, but it's just him.
It's just him.
Dude.
My favorite part about Twitch is, um, you can click on their name and see their chat history.
Right?
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
It's awesome.
Once I was, um, you know, the share chat feature when you collab with other streamers.
Yeah.
Um, one chatter in my friend's chat was like, yeah, I got banned in Lily's chat for saying she should do this.
I was just trying to help.
And I'm like, okay.
Okay.
Let's see.
So I pull up his chat.
The receipts.
He was saying some very inappropriate stuff.
Let's just say that.
And I'm like, I can't believe you would just lie about that.
Like, I can see your history, bro.
Like, wow.
Lying on the internet.
I like how they go to your friend's chat too.
And I'm like, you think I'm not gonna pull up your chat box.
I'm just like, Lily's not here.
I can do this.
We had a shared chat.
Also, my friend ended up banning them too.
I know.
Yeah.
I found out recently, but like, apparently if you do a shared chat, you ban someone and time someone out in like your own chat.
Oh, it carries over.
Yeah.
It carries over too.
Oh.
Yeah.
I just found out.
I don't know if that's like an old feature or a new feature.
I kind of like that.
Yeah.
Nicole, I'm sorry.
No, no, you go first.
No, no, no.
I was just gonna say, yeah.
Cause like, then you don't have to like, you know, tell your friend to be like, oh, remember ban this guy.
Be sure.
Watch out for this guy.
Yeah.
A lot of times people, sometimes they'll come over from my friend's chat and they're like, yeah, um, your friend banned me because I called them a whore.
And I'm like, what do you want me to do, man?
Like what?
Why?
It's like, it's like, you can't, I don't get the logic.
I really don't like, you think you're gonna get favors?
Like a teacher.
Like I called your friend a slut and she banned me and I'm like, you're not a good person.
Yeah.
You're like, yeah, I can't, I can't believe she would do that.
Oh, so funny.
Crazy.
That's actually crazy.
Wow.
I'm hungry.
Thankfully, today's sponsor is Factor.
You guys know the drill.
Trying to eat well, something specific like keto is a huge amount of work.
I've tried to stick to keto so many times and who wrote this?
Who wrote this?
That is true though.
I did try keto so many times.
With Factor, it's just, it's literally right there.
It arrives fresh, ready to eat, straight to your door.
No cooking, zero meal prep.
You just put it in the microwave or oven and they're ready to eat in minutes.
It's perfect for any active lifestyle or inactive like me where I sit in front of my computer and stream.
My current favorite meal is the Roasted Garlic Butter Salmon.
It's really good.
It fulfills my protein obligations because I don't work out but I still like protein because it makes me feel healthy even though I don't work out.
But I should work out because I'm getting old and my body's breaking down.
The variety is incredible.
You have 45 weekly menu options.
You can pick any meal that fits your summer gains or goals, whatever they are.
So, if you want to enjoy more this summer and get all the flavor with none of the fuss, I recommend Factor.
Get started at factormeals.com slash sweetandsour50off and use code sweetandsour50off to get 50% off plus free shipping on your first box.
That's code sweet and the letter N, sour50off at factormeals.com slash sweetandsour50off for 50% off plus free shipping.
Thanks for watching and supporting Sweet and Sour.
Bye.
But yeah, but you've been on YouTube.
You had a YouTube partnership, right?
Yes.
Yeah.
Like two years ago now, right?
Oh my God.
Was it really two years ago?
Dude, time goes by so fast now.
Yeah, it's so good.
I remember seeing that trailer when it came out that you got signed over to YouTube.
That was two years ago.
Oh my God.
Got my bag.
Got your bag.
At the time it was like, oh, I can't believe I was even considering like not taking it.
It's so fucking stupid because when I think about it, like no one would say no to that amount of money.
Right?
Like it's life changing money.
I think anyone in my position would have taken it.
Yeah.
And I'm really glad I did.
You could like, obviously you always come, obviously you can come back.
Yeah.
And you come back and you still do whatever you want to do.
And then, but then there's like less pressure, you know?
Because you know you already...
Way less pressure.
You have like the money for the future type deal.
It's already set for life type stuff.
It's like, um, yeah.
Like I stream because like I want to, because I have fun with it.
And it's, I've been having more fun recently.
Yeah.
And it's like, it doesn't feel like bad.
Like I used to sometimes.
I'm having fun.
Yeah.
Because you're not about like really chasing numbers or anything or like doing what's best for like growth.
You just do what's fun.
If I want to play horse girl anime game for three hours, they're going to watch me play Uma Musume, you know?
And you're like, I, this is what I enjoy.
You support me.
Yeah.
I'm going to play this anime horse girl game.
I remember when it came out, like Skara, Skara is the one who started playing it.
Right?
Yeah.
And we're at the, like, we're all hanging out and he's trying to show us.
No, you don't understand guys.
They're like horse girls, but they're anime.
And we all give him the side eye.
Okay.
We're like Skara.
Please.
Okay.
Not in front of other people.
Is that weird though?
There's so many weird gacha games out there.
I know.
To be fair, that seems very tame for the other ones.
It is.
He's like, we can try to describe it.
Yeah.
So they're horses, but they're anime girls and they're racing like it.
Anyway.
So you're like racing women.
I must apologize to him.
Because now I'm in more, I'm in very deep.
Every time I go on a stream.
He's streaming right now.
He's playing the horse girl game right now.
That's insane.
They get you.
Yeah.
Because it's super popular in Japan for like years now.
It just came over to the United States.
Yeah.
Global release.
But I remember when my child was like telling me about it.
And I was like, I am not surprised that it got really popular in like US or like NA.
Because I was like, bro, Americans will race anything.
Like it's like a primal nature to see who's the fastest, you know?
And I was like saying like, this is basically like legal gambling because like, I don't even know this, but like horse racing in the States is like getting more and more banned or like restricted now.
Because of like, you know, like animal rights and stuff because like horse mistreatment in some places.
I didn't know that.
Yeah.
So a lot of places that does horse racing in the States are like closing down because of it.
So then like, this is like, they're fixed here.
Like racing anime girls legally.
Without the worry of like...
It also makes me happy because like, you know how like they're based off of real horses in Japan.
And like, you know, like one of the horses, you know, Haru Udara, she got like...
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, you can donate like rye grass to her.
And people are memeing it because people are donating so much to her.
They're drawing her like under tons.
I think she got donated tons of rye grass.
Yeah, and then like, they took a picture of it and you see her like looking at the grass be like, oh.
Yeah.
It looked like an eye spark.
I was like, oh, I don't know why I'm getting so much grass, but yippee.
I think people like it because like, um, because she's, first of all, she's a cute pink haired anime girl in the game.
And in real life, apparently she like never won a single game.
Yeah, yeah.
Like, um, the lore, like I was saying like, the lore between the actual horses is like so much more interesting.
It is.
Than the, the, the horse anime girls.
Yeah.
Cause like, you know, like Gold Ship, the shit that comes out from Gold Ship.
Like they said, like, he actually has an IQ of a seven year old.
Um, yeah.
Cause like the average IQ for horses is like four year old.
Uh huh.
And Gold Ship was like one of the rare horses that like has the IQ of a seven year old.
And he was like super, super fucking smart.
So like some, if he wants to win, he'll win, but sometimes he just doesn't want it.
Yeah.
It costs like 12 billion yen or something in one race.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
And then apparently every horse that has like made a, like every horse that's like a child of Gold Ship was like considered like real, like a winner basically.
Cause you need to pay 2 million yen to breed Gold Ship.
What the fuck?
Yeah.
That's kind of nice.
And then apparently he has like a, every horse that has like bred with Gold Ship is like 100% like there's a baby.
Like.
So everyone's like, yeah, he like, he's like guaranteed.
Wow.
What a funny horse.
Cause like in the game.
Yeah, he's a silly horse.
Gold Ship is like very, what's the word?
Molatile.
Cause it kind of makes sense.
Yeah.
But some of the lore is kind of sad.
Like one of the horses that I got first, the anime girl horse.
Rice Shower, right?
She's super cute.
And I'm like, oh, I was telling Chad, I love Rice Shower.
And everyone's like, oh, she doesn't know.
She doesn't know the lore.
The Rice Shower lore.
That Rice Shower got euthanized when they were like six years old because they broke a leg or something.
I'm like, that's fucking sad.
That's just sad.
What?
I didn't know that.
So sad.
Oh my God.
That's so sad.
The dark underbelly of horse racing.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Cause they're like based off the real horses and everything.
Yeah.
I'm okay with the anime girls.
He's like, you know what?
I just want to know about the anime girls.
I just want to be happy.
I...
No.
Doki Bird is a great horse name by the...
I think Doki Bird is a good horse name.
There it goes.
There goes Doki Bird.
And she's catching up.
Doki Bird.
I don't know if you're saying it like that.
Oh my God.
I've seen like...
People were like, I can't wait when they add these new horses.
And then one of the...
Like these American horses.
There was one that was like...
Like his name was literally Fortnite.
Fortnite.
Right?
There's...
Fortnite?
There's also Skibbidi Riz now.
Oh yeah.
Skibbidi Riz.
I want to see Skibbidi Riz and Umamu.
I don't know how they're going to say it, but it's going to be really funny.
Skibbidi Riz though.
Yeah.
And you know like when...
When they add like foreigners into like a Japanese anime game.
Yeah.
Oh, that kind of English?
That would be really fun.
Yeah.
I love horse game.
I kind of like it.
It kind of makes me happy when I see a lot of like...
Streamers or whoever, right?
You get unified with like one game.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Like Ludwig had that Umamu Summit tournament recently.
Mm-hmm.
Just stuff like this is fun to see, you know?
Like more games.
Yeah, yeah.
It's like, you know, all these people who like normally don't interact with each other.
Yeah.
But like the horse game was different.
It's kind of like, um, gosh, I still remember the summer of 2016 when Pokemon Go unified the world.
Do you remember that?
The era of peace.
The era of peace where everyone was like actually going outside.
Yeah.
Everyone was outside.
And everyone was on her phone.
You could tell like, like event was happening.
Yeah.
Everyone was just around that certain area too.
And strangers were so nice to each other.
They're like, oh, bro, there's an aerodactyl over there.
If you keep going.
Thanks, bro.
Like, you know, just four times.
And then COVID ruined it all.
I do think COVID did mess up some things.
Oh my God, I found out recently, like, apparently, like, if you ever get COVID, like, like, you actually get dumber or something.
Because did you see that article?
I was like...
No, I saw it.
A lot of people got brain fog.
They can't remember things.
No, I saw it.
And I'm like...
Fuck.
See, the thing is for me, I don't know if it's COVID or I'm just getting old.
That's true.
Because like, I had brain fog recently.
But that was just because I was like, so fucking stressed out.
And didn't like...
Because I was like, planning for...
Because I had my birthday this month.
And I had my...
Another concert.
And also like, birthday preparations.
Mm-hmm.
Because every day I was just so fucking busy.
And then I was having brain fog.
So it's like, is it because I'm getting old or because I'm stressed out?
Like...
Oh no.
Or COVID.
I think it's just like, a mix of everything, really.
That's true.
We're like, patient zero.
But you do a lot of like, concerts.
Well, it was mostly for...
Like, I only done two.
So I've done one for November.
And then the other one was, you know, for...
It was for my birthday for Anime Expo.
Uh-huh.
Because I got invited to Anime Expo.
And like, the concert thing was like, my own idea.
So I was like, oh, you know, like...
Because like, there's like, people who don't know who I am.
So I figured like, oh, 3D concert is a great way to advertise yourself.
Can I ask about that?
I was always curious.
Yeah.
When VTubers do like, 3D concerts and stuff.
Like, how does that...
Are you like, singing live?
Is it recorded?
Like, are you there?
Like, how is it going?
Oh, okay.
So it depends on like, depends really on the VTubers and how the concert venue is.
But like, so sometimes you can tell if it's like, pre-recorded with like, the singing and stuff.
Usually, the go-to would be like, pre-recorded singing, and then the dances could be live.
Or like, both of them are pre-recorded, or you do them, and you do the MC live.
So...
Or like, the entire thing is pre-recorded.
So it really depends.
Like, there's a...
It depends...
It is a mix and match between like, the time availability, and like, budget and everything.
Because like, doing a lot...
Everything live is so risky.
No, I understand.
Especially because you have to like, set up all the things beforehand.
Yeah.
I did a concert, like, in person a few years ago.
And it was the most terrifying thing.
I have bad stage fright.
Performance anxiety.
So I look at...
And then afterwards, I learned that people do V2 concerts.
Yeah.
And I started watching them.
And I'm like, wait, that's so fucking sick.
Yeah.
Like, the motion capture and everything.
And then you have different camera angles and stuff you can do.
And because like...
That's why it's very hard to tell when something's like, live or pre-recorded.
Because you can do like, different camera angles while it's live.
So...
But like...
And...
Yeah.
But usually, singing is done pre-recorded.
Just because it's very hard to...
No, I understand that too.
I think it's so cool though.
Like...
Wow, technology has come so far.
Do you need a 3D model to do the concert?
Um...
Well...
Yeah.
I mean, it is a 3D concert.
But like, you can do it with 2D.
But like, you know, if you have a guest that doesn't have a 3D model.
You can like, you know, get the 2D model in as well.
And then they just...
On a screen or something.
And you sing with them while they're on the screen.
Or they're like, you know, the 2D model itself.
And you just move around it with the 2D model.
Uh-huh.
But it is possible.
It is possible.
But it is...
Oh my gosh.
Have you ever been in a mocap suit?
No, but it sounds really fun.
Oh my god.
There's like...
There's so much stuff you have to put on.
And we like sit there for like, I think like 30 minutes.
Just having them put everything on.
And then like...
But it's so cool.
Like seeing yourself on the screen with the 3D model and moving yourself with it.
It's just such a cool experience.
Oh my, that's so sick.
In general.
Yeah.
And then I know like technology has evolved so much.
Because I saw...
Have you ever saw that video of someone like motion capturing a horse?
What?
Yeah, you never saw it.
No.
I don't remember which game it was.
But...
They like motion captured a horse.
And you see the horse wearing the little 3D outfit with the hat too.
Like the little...
That's really cute actually.
Yeah, it's so cute.
Because you know how...
You know Stray?
The game Stray?
Yeah, the cat.
Yeah, they motion capture the cat for that.
Oh my god.
No wonder the cat looks so good.
Yeah, yeah.
So there's like videos of the motion capture of the cat.
And like them leading the cat everywhere.
Like okay, cross this little bench thing.
It's like a little bench thing.
And everything.
It's so cool seeing stuff like that.
Wow.
Okay, thank you.
I was always just curious about that.
That sounds really cool.
Yeah.
And like...
But yeah, like technology has just come so far when it comes to like 3D in general.
So it's really fun.
You should always...
Honestly, you should give it a try.
I want to.
Like that should be on your bucket list.
That is definitely on my...
I've always wanted a 3D model.
And the mocap.
That sounds awesome.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
He's like...
Oh, sorry.
Go on.
No, no.
You go first.
No, it's okay.
I think it's cool that you can express yourself without having to show yourself.
You know?
Oh, yeah.
Because I think showing yourself comes with its whole can of worms as well.
Yeah.
For me, I'm like...
That's why I love VTubing.
Because like, in real life, I'm actually a really private person.
No, that makes sense.
Yeah.
So like, I've only like met IRL in terms of like people that I've like done stuff with.
I've only met like three people in real life that I like connected with via VTubing.
Because like, for me, I'm like, I'm super private.
Like, I don't tell people where I live.
I just be like, I live in Canada.
You know?
But like, no one really knows like where I live or like, like, basically off stream what like, I really do or stuff like that.
And it's just like, I just like the privacy and things.
So like, when I'm outside, I don't have to worry about being approached and stuff.
Yeah.
So it's like, I never had had that.
I guess like, for you, it's different because like, you've been a public figure for a very long time.
Do.
Mm.
At some point, I kind of like, envy that kind of like privacy because, um, like you're safe in real life.
Yeah.
You are safe.
And I think it prevents people from getting a little too weird with you.
Right?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
You have that strong boundary.
I think that's really cool.
But you can also like express yourself just as well, because like, you have so many outfits, you have a lot of models and like facial expressions and everything.
Like people know what your intents are.
And I think that's really good.
Unfortunately for me, I started when VTubing wasn't a thing.
Would you, would you have been like just a primarily VTuber if you were around that area when you started content creation?
In my twenties?
Yes.
Because I was a lot more shy and my self-confidence wasn't as high.
I think it also kind of fucked me sometimes because like, um, back when I started, right?
There wasn't, you know, the whole voice thing.
Oh.
Yeah.
I remember that.
Now, like, you know, people who have high pitched voices, it's like dime a dozen.
Who the fuck cares?
Yeah.
Right.
But back then it was like me and like maybe Nyan or something.
Oh, yeah.
That's true.
Yeah.
So I think we got a lot of the attention, both good and bad.
And that really fucked with 20 year old Lily because I'm like, oh, they would constantly say like, show yourself or you're ugly.
Like, you got to show yourself.
They're the constant pressuring.
So I'm like, okay, maybe if I show myself, it'll stop.
Yeah.
And it did not stop.
Then they just called me ugly.
Oh, yeah.
It was like a lose-lose situation.
Yeah.
You can like appease everyone because there's so many people on the internet.
You'll get like, you'll have aunties no matter what.
Yeah, exactly.
Even though you do like everything right.
No matter what.
Everyone has aunties.
Someone will hate you for something.
That's what I learned later on.
I'm like, you don't, you don't have to do anything and people will just hate you.
So we might as well live your life how you want to live your life.
Right?
And just be like, oh yeah, your voice.
Cause like, I understand that because like, I also have like a very polarizing voice as well.
Cause like for me as a, cause like, you know, like the general VTuber voice is like higher pitch and everything.
So like when I debuted people were like, oh my gosh, her voice is like, like so ugly or something like that.
Like, which is crazy to me, but yeah.
Cause it's like, cause like I have such a unique voice.
And people would be like, oh my gosh, like why does she sound like that?
Like.
Yeah.
I don't.
It's just a redundant.
Why does she sound like that?
Shut up, shut up, shut up.
Yeah.
So like, I get that feeling.
Cause like, um, now nowadays people are like, oh, like when you're lower pitch, like when you're like not a very high pitch voice, then people will also judge you now too.
So I get that.
I'm just learning that people judge you no matter what.
Yeah.
High pitch, low pitch, unique voice, a basic voice.
Who the fuck cares?
Like it doesn't fucking matter.
Someone's gonna hate you in the end.
So it doesn't matter.
Be yourself.
That's like, yeah.
Like when you're getting into content creation, like you're, you're gonna get haters in the end no matter what.
And it's just about testing your like mental fortitude.
And like you're, you're skinny.
Yeah.
So I have to have tough skin to get into this business.
Mm-hmm.
And I think people value authenticity anyway.
Like if you're yourself, people like that instead of like pretending to be who you're not or whatever.
That's so true.
Yeah.
And then there's like, but there's also like, oh, there's like VTubers out there though.
That does like, um, you know, like the ones that like rely, like play heavily into the lore itself too, which is really interesting.
That's really cool though.
Like they're playing a character.
Yeah.
And I think that's really cool.
I, I, I like, yeah, I think so too.
Like I don't, I could never do that.
Like I always crack.
Like whenever I have to like play, I can't like upkeep it for too long.
And I just, I just crack.
I just be like, I can't guys.
It's like, um, like an actor, you know, like you're entertaining people at the end of the day.
So however you go about it, as long as you're not hurting anyone else.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
It's all about like, you know, as long as like the audience like it, the community likes it.
Like that's all that matters in the end.
Yeah.
And that's the moral of this podcast episode.
Just be yourself or be completely different.
Good segue.
We're near the end.
Um, usually for this podcast, people submit like stories they want advice on.
If you, if you'd like to help me with, um, giving advice for one of them to end it off.
Yeah.
Sure.
Okay.
Like, should I swap to the crow for that?
Get advice from a crow.
Let me, let me pull that up.
The croaky.
That's what we call the crow, like croaky.
Um, it was started, it was just a joke, like a one off thing, but then everyone was like, wait, this is actually pretty funny.
That's how it always starts with a joke.
And then it becomes real.
Yeah.
People were like, wait, she, like the crow actually, like your voice really matches the crow.
We love croaky.
You do have a very like unique voice.
It's very unique.
And I think it's very cute.
Yeah.
Like for me, like whenever I'm at like convention, I can't speak because like, I actually got recognized one time when I was at a convention.
Cause I, I was stupid.
I was trying to find my own merch.
Oh, okay.
That's on you.
That's on me.
I was like, they won't know.
And then, and then they're like, wait a minute.
Are you, are you dokey bird?
And I was like, no, I'm just a big fan.
I'm just, I just, I just, I just really love dokey bird.
Like I purposely like pitched my voice higher when they asked me.
And she was like, no, they won't.
They'll never know.
I think they knew, but they'll never know.
Voices are quite recognizable in person.
I've learned.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
A hundred percent.
Oh, you make me want more outfits and you make me want a 3D model and you make me want to do a concert and you make me want to do it.
Why don't you just do it all?
I want to do it.
Inspiring.
It's so inspiring.
And then, and then, and then.
Yeah.
And then what?
And then you'll record the song I wrote.
And that is when.
No.
The only reason I, I pester you so much, it's cause like, it's one of the songs I wrote that I'm like so, I love it so much.
I need, I need you to sing this man.
I need you to sing it now.
Like I like stop.
TJ and I want you to sing it so bad.
We're like, we hope she still wants to do it.
Yeah.
It's okay.
Now, now I have time.
My, my other stuff is done.
I can finally, I finally have time to record it.
While she's changing, I'm going to give listeners context.
Okay.
She asked me to write a song a few years ago, two years ago.
I don't remember when.
So I'm like, okay.
So I started doing this deep dive into Doki Bird, right?
And her lore and like who she is as a person.
And I'm like, like, I need to know her soul.
And I want to write this song.
It's a very like emotional song.
It's very, very emotional.
It's really good.
Like a good meaning to it, you know?
And then, and then TJ had this draft and I'm like, oh my God, it's so cute.
I can't wait to see her see it.
Me too.
I'm glad, I'm glad we finally, we finally, um, had all that.
Set up for it too.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
I'm so excited.
Wait, I'm sorry.
I.
Oh, wait.
Okay.
There you go.
Wait, I'm.
You have set up my expectations show.
So different.
Um, I.
What?
It's a crow.
It's literally a MSPaint crow.
No.
No, it's 3D.
I just can't get the tracking to work.
Oh my God.
It's 3D, but I can't.
Look, see?
Oh, it's 3D.
Okay.
Oh my God.
I swear to God, when, if the tracking works, it's so good.
No, I see the vision.
I see the vision.
You see the vision?
Yeah, no, I see the vision to the audio listeners.
It is a 3D model of a crow and it looks really...
I can imagine it being very cool if it moves the way it's supposed to.
Yeah, if it moves the way it's supposed to move, it'd be so cool.
It would be super sick, yeah.
It would've been so sick.
But sadly, sadly, it did not move the way it took me to try and get it to work.
But sadly, it did not.
It's been so long that I forgot how to get it to work.
It is okay.
From my perspective, it was like, oh, it's...
A 2D crow.
Okay, like...
I swear to God.
No, no, no.
I believe you.
It was so funny.
Okay, bring back Doki Bird.
Okay, but what if I'm just like this?
What if I...
You could just do that.
That's funny too.
Wait, that's so cute.
A 3D crow is really cute.
I want a 3D Pomeranian.
You can get one.
Those are...
Like, 3D models are actually...
Well, it depends.
It depends.
I think for, like, mascots and stuff, it's a lot cheaper.
How...
Can I ask how much your 3D model was?
Um...
For, like, the regular size?
Regular sized.
Um...
It was, like, around...
In...
10k.
But that's for, like, motion...
Like, for mocap too.
10k.
Okay, got it.
Um...
Yeah, cause, like, um...
Cause, like, they have to build it to work for motion capture.
Cause, like, it's cheaper if it's just a normal 3D model without the motion capture.
But the technology for that is, like, a less... a lot more different.
Mm-hmm.
But if it's, like...
Um...
But if it's mostly for...
Like, if you want to have motion capture and use it for normal VTubing.
Like, you know, like, at your desk and stuff like that.
Then it's a lot cheaper.
Got it.
Okay.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Alright, I'm back.
Alright, let's get this advice segment underway.
You can see it on the screen, right?
Yeah, I can.
Okay, we only read a paragraph at a time.
Like, me, you, me, you.
Okay.
I got the shorter paragraph.
Oh, do you want the bigger...
No, that's fine.
I like the shorter one.
Less reading for me.
Okay.
How to deal with a questionable friend.
I met my current friend group through Discord and eventually moved interstate, partly motivated by wanting to be closer to them.
Early on, I got really close with a girl, Kim, who started the Discord.
We talked and played games a lot and she had known the group in real life for a couple years already.
But as we got closer, she would often talk badly about others in the group, which felt really disrespectful.
Kim had a habit of getting upset over misunderstandings, sometimes her fault, sometimes not.
And she would lash out or ghost people.
After a serious talk with her, our dynamic changed and we slowly drifted apart.
When I started dating someone in the group, who she used to ship us when my BF and I were still friends, but suddenly did a complete 180 and was completely against it.
It felt like she wasn't happy about it and distanced herself more.
Our friends even noticed her acting weird toward us.
What really made me lose trust was when she told me she hated one of our friends, but was only putting up with her because of the guy she was dating.
The guy is one of Kim's other close friends.
They eventually broke up, but stayed close friends.
And Kim started hanging out more with the girl she said she hated, which felt fake.
Some people in the group know what she said, but have not confronted her, which bothers me.
I even asked a girl Kim talked about if she would want to know if someone was bad at talking her.
But she said no, because it might cause drama and backlash.
So I respect her decision and stay quiet.
Now Kim has ghosted both me and my boyfriend.
I do not trust her and don't see us ever being friends again.
I still care about the group, but it's hard when no one addresses the toxic stuff.
Things are kind of divided now and feels like our friends walk on eggshells.
Even birthday outings are split between her and us.
I feel bad for my friends and especially for my boyfriend who was part of the original group, but now feels left out.
Lately, I've been thinking about finding new friends.
We've all been close for five years, but now I don't really feel like I belong anymore.
And I don't know if I can get past them accepting that kind of toxic behavior.
Thank you for reading all this.
Hope it wasn't too long.
Okay.
I need a summary of this.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
She met her current friend group through discord.
Yeah.
And moved closer to them, got close with a girl named Kim who started the discord.
Okay.
So they're being friends, but she would also shit talk other people in the group.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's not good for Kim.
And she lashes out.
They drifted apart.
And then the praise, and then the OP, I'm going to call them OP, started dating someone in the group, which who Kim used to chip.
What?
And she wasn't happy about it.
She acted weird.
And then she told me that she hated one of our friends, but was putting, oh my God.
Okay.
This sounds like she's really toxic and like, you're okay without her, man.
Yeah.
Honestly, like I would just cut that.
No, I would also just cut that.
Because like the group is enabling her toxic behavior too.
Because they're like, it's okay.
As long as it doesn't affect us, then it's fine.
You know?
And they're like, like, you know, like in one of it, she's like, she talked shit about one of the other friends.
And the friend was like, I don't want to know if anyone's talking shit about me.
So like, they are all like living in this like little bubble.
Little bubble.
Yeah.
Like to keep the peace.
And that's not healthy at all.
Because like, she's obviously, this Kim person is obviously going to keep doing what she's doing because she's not being punished for it.
And she's basically being like a mean girl in general.
So like, it's just not healthy mentally wise too.
Because you're always going like, who's like, oh, like, someone's going to be a snake today towards me or something.
Oh my God.
That was really good, Doki.
That was really good.
Good, solid advice.
Holy shit.
I did not accept it.
That would be like $5 for your therapy session.
I think it's also good to tell the group, like, you know, just make your boundaries clear.
Like, hey, I don't fuck with Kim, blah, blah, blah.
It's up to you guys what you guys want to do.
Yeah.
This is my boundary, right?
And then, you know, protect your peace too, you know?
Yeah.
And be like, it's just not healthy.
Like, if they're like wondering, oh, why did she leave?
Like, why isn't she hanging out with us anymore?
Like, if they're asking that about OP, just keep it straight and be like, the vibe was just not it.
It was so mentally draining to be part of this group because everyone was like, you know, like, people were being like manipulative and stuff.
So like, why would I want to hang out with a group of people that I'm not vibing with anymore?
Yeah.
I got no other...
Because you want to look forward.
Like, if you're going to be a group of friends, you want, you know, be with a group of friends that make you happy and not like something...
Yeah.
Happy and comfortable.
Not like dread every time.
You know?
Wait.
Yeah.
I got...
I got no more notes.
Hey, thank you for submitting.
That was really good.
Very good.
And that is the end of the episode.
Yay.
And if you want more, check us out on Patreon.
Yeah.
And if not, thank you so much, Doki Bird.
You were an excellent guest.
We were yapping all hour.
It was so fun.
The time flew by.
It did, really.
But yeah, thank you again for having me, Lily.
But yeah, my name is Doki Bird.
I'm an indie VTuber.
You wanna check me out on YouTube?
I usually stream on YouTube.
We'll put our links in the description if you guys wanna check her out, too.
She does...
She's a very good VTube streamer.
I would advise it.
Thank you.
Yay!
See you on Patreon!
Bye!
Bye-bye, everyone!
I'm gonna get ALC and Obama and this one.
Stuff like that, you know?
I'm like, oh...
Sorry.
I'm gonna be one of those insufferable Arcane fans who are like, You never watched Arcane?
Like, what?
It felt like the eating of someone's grandpa.