hello everybody hello today i'm feeling i don't know i was craving some rivals rank today um i was just i don't know ever since i came back from um the marble rival studio i just they got me i don't know what they did they got they put something in the food maybe i've just been so addicted to rivals again they i thought i beat it but i'm back i'm i've been playing rivals rank like so much lately ever since i i came back and i'm like what am i doing why am i not streaming this like why so i was just like uh i was gonna play right rank anyway uh yeah the itch is back they must have it was it must have been in the water i don't know what it was i'm just the addiction it's back uh
um so yeah i was just really craving some uh marble rivals uh rank again and so i was just thinking like why am i why do i keep playing off stream like i should be i should be streaming this and also i went out and grabbed some a new coffee shop opened uh nearby my place so i went and got some uh because i was i don't know today i've been really tired too i woke up at like i think i woke up around like 1 p.m today but i don't know i was so tired maybe i just slept too much i was so tired and i even took a nap in the middle of the day and i woke up and i was still exhausted um so i got myself uh uh ice caramel latte um and also like uh tiramisu i'm gonna i'm gonna enjoy this a little bit before we before we game just treating myself a little bit also let's get have a little show too whoa um but okay today i had um i'm so paranoid today because um today um i was doing some errands today i had to go out i don't know what was i doing why did i oh yeah i had to go out and uh buy some stuff
for some errands uh for i hope for uh for my apartment um Because I was running out of, like, I was running out of shampoo.
Uh, so I was like, oh, I might as well grab some groceries and everything.
Um, so, uh, so I was going out today.
And it was a really quick errand.
And the thing is, when it's a really quick errand, I don't, okay, this might be, I don't know.
I'll reveal this.
But when it's a really quick errand and I'm out, oh, you guys might be thinking, Joki, you shouldn't be saying this out loud.
Um, also, okay, I'm getting way too distracted.
I'm sorry, I gotta stop.
I gotta stop him.
I'm actually getting way too distracted, guys.
But, I actually, I can't open.
I'm sorry.
I'm getting way too distracted for it.
For story time.
I have to be stopped.
Yeah.
But I trust the safety.
Also, oops.
I trust the safety of my apartment.
Because for those who don't know, in my apartment, you can't access my floor unless you have a fob.
You can't access any of the fobs and the fobs are directly connected to your floor.
So if you're living on like X floor and then you're like, you try to go to a different floor, it wouldn't work because you're because the beeper for the elevator was only registered directly to your floor.
So that's why I'm like, I can comfortably talk about this.
um but anyway if i'm doing a really quick errand uh i'll say hey pizza if i'm doing a really quick errand and it's like you know like maybe like 10 to 15 minutes i won't lock my door because i'm like okay i'll be back in 15 minutes anyway and the only people that will break into my apartment would be my neighbors so i was like so i'm like okay if anyone tries to break into my apartment It will be my neighbors.
So, so, because, like, when I, you know, so, anyway, anyway, now that I say that, I'm going to start locking my apartment now.
Now that I say that, because, by the way, a reason why I'm comfortably talking about this is because now I'm going to start locking my apartment because something happened.
So, anyway, so, I was out doing errands.
and then so there is an intercom outside my apartment and um and um the only way for like you know you're getting like uber eats or anything or ordering like or a package just being delivered to your place um they will do the intercom to your to your like uh you know to your phone like the intercom is connected to your phone and then you guys have to have to press a number to let people in and but they can only access your floor um so they only so if you let somebody in to the apartment and they go to the elevator they can only access your floor and it's time too so like um so when i was out doing errands i got a call from the intercom thing and like out of reflex i just let them in i and then i was thinking when i let them in.
I was thinking, wait, am I expecting anything?
I guess I'm just like, oh, okay, so I was like, wait, am I expecting anything?
And I was thinking, no, I didn't order anything.
I'm like, I'm like, it's Sunday, so there's no packages being delivered to me.
So I'm like, what, what was that i was i was like oh my god what did i wait what did i who did i let in i was so confused i was like oh it's sunday like there shouldn't be any packages so um so i came back and there was and i went to my floor but there was no packages outside my door and i was like oh yeah no I was like,
wait, who was that?
Oh, God.
I was like, who requested my apartment on the intercom?
And I got, I freaked out.
I was like, did I got, did someone like, well, they technically didn't break in.
I like, they could just let themselves in.
So, so I went downstairs and I was like, oh, maybe they left like in my mailbox or like in the package room and I checked that and I was like, oh there's nothing there's nothing there and then like so then I was like, okay I'm gonna go in and I came in and then that seems fine so I was just like and nothing was moved at all so I wasn't robbed or anything so I was just like what happened?
I was just like I was like What happened I didn't Those guys are like Oh I must see that I'm so confused So I checked everything Nothing was moved or placed anywhere I checked everything guys And because I was like And like you know Dad would say something you know Um Um Dad would say something if like You know something happened And you know,
he'd be like there's someone here or something.
And so I checked everything and It doesn't seem like anything was moved at all.
And so I was I was like And I was only gone for for like five I did I checked the closets and everything too.
So I was only gone for like
and I was like was there like did they got the wrong apartment did they got like the wrong apartment or something and like accidentally clicked mine and like because like in the intercom you can like click you have to click on you can just like click on the apartment number like they'll give a search of everything and they can just click on like they just tap it and then just like be like ring ring ring and stuff like that so i am i i don't know what happened so anyway i'm going to start locking my door if i go out for for if i'm just outside for really quick hours so now now i'm gonna start locking my door if i'm going out for like less because i don't lock my door when i'm out for like 10 minutes because i'm just like oh i have to go back up i'm going 10 minutes in anyways so it'll be fine so now that i know i'll stop thank you for the ranking thank you thank you i've got a great stream those are new here hello my name is dokeybird um i usually stream on youtube but today i'm here
because i've been craving marvel rivals and um i was telling my chat a story that of i was telling i was giving my chat a story time uh potentially
apartment but i don't know i'm i i i i i'm just going to assume that i'm just gonna assume that uh they just accidentally pressed my apartment because it's just a list and they just accidentally pressed mine and then i just let them in i'd if vampires are real i would most likely accidentally invite a vampire in uh in and kill and get everybody killed I will be that person also in a zombie apocalypse I mean if I wasn't the one that will kill everybody by becoming a zombie because I hid my bite wounds I will also accidentally let a zombie in um 100% now that I think about it I am not very well suited for adult life the the longer I live by myself the more I realize I'm very naive and ignorant Incredibly,
I feel like I lived in a different world compared to everyone else.
Yeah, we can tell.
I have zero survival instinct.
If I was born 200 years earlier, I would be the child that they would discard because they're like, there's no hope for her to survive.
I feel like.
I'm pretty sure I will be discarded if I was born 200 years ago.
yeah you know like survival of the fittest I would not be in that category I will don't sell yourself short they'll marry you off first um to be married off I would have to know how I would have to know how to do chores and apparently um I'm very bad at taking care I literally have a cleaner comes here once a month Because I cannot do it I cannot even clean my own bathroom I have a cleaner that comes in once a month to do that for me
I'm gonna get sent to the nunnery Boy, thank you for the 10 gifted subs Thank you, thank you Oh yeah, I didn't even call a plumber to check my sink I just waited until I procrastinated And then it fixed itself.
And everything was okay.
Everything was okay after that.
Mm-hmm.
It fixed itself.
It was fixed in the end.
Level 5 Hype Trim from Jokey Telling Everyone How She Let Someone.
I don't!
No, no, no, no, no.
We don't know.
It's off.
Hypothetical.
We don't actually know if that's what happened, guys.
We don't know.
That's you in the worst.
We don't really know.
That doesn't make it better.
All right.
Anyway.
But yeah.
no i would definitely natural selection would have selected me um judging by my by how life has been life has been treating me i would be selected by natural natural selection anyway guys uh gaming thank you for the tier one sub thank you thank you okay i think of this 100 betties thank you thank you i go to turkey's house and steal the cheese's combo that's all right everything's fine so yeah that's what happened that's what happens man and to treat myself I bought myself tiramisu
I survived another day of not being selected by natural selection so I decided to treat myself to tiramisu alright let's play let's play rank and I'm most likely gonna lose but let's play for those who are wondering, I have not been playing um, I have not,
okay, so, I mean, I have been playing, I mean, I already had 722 matches played, yeah, ever since I came back from um, the Marble Rival Studios, uh, treat yourself for all of us, for, we don't know!
We don't know!
I treated myself to potentially not being robbed.
we don't know so anyway so yeah no okay see look see zero matches played in the entire season zero I mean for this I went I played until eternity so okay so like how the mighty have fallen will this look one above all and then you know I'm still playing and then I'm still playing and then you know oh so starting less games now.
Celestia 2.
I stopped at Celestia.
And then I'm like eternity here.
And then this is when I took a little break from rank and just stayed in Diamond 1.
And now I'm back.
Now I'm back.
Celestia 3 right here.
Um, I didn't get kidnapped today.
Yay.
Now I'm like, yay!
Yay!
All right, let's play.
Let's play some some ranky rank I think like I'm out of range with it oh my gosh so fast
whoa thank you for the five gift of shows thank you thank you all right
oh yeah I got Lord on Loki like the moon play my comfort pick now who am I gonna vanish from this match
oh I mean, the fact that dad was just chilling and sleeping makes me feel more safe because then I'm like, okay, maybe nothing happened because he's just hanging out.
Like, he was just hanging out.
That just proves it wasn't a man that broke in.
Like,
okay, true.
but there's nothing to steal here it's just basic because I got my wallet so there's actually I will tell you guys this right now in my apartment there's nothing valuable in my apartment it's literally all jokie merch and then because the only valuable thing like like monetary value wise I mean I still have my fucking PC like I can stream um but no there's so much Hulk Hulk players and Celestia and GM I don't know why there's so many of them um but it's only like Doki merch in my apartment like nearly 90% of the things in my apartment it's just Doki merch the only like thing that's of monetary like for monetary value if I am getting robbed would be in my wallet and the wallet was with me like I don't have like anything else in my apartment other than dokey merch and my pc
oh yeah and my lububu sorry and my fucking apparently eighty dollar lububu
they could sell that's true they could but they're all here all my dokey merch is here also this is my first this is my first game of the day so i'm gonna be like super super rusty 4, 3, 2, 1 Okay.
All you need to do is capture the mission area.
Got it?
Oh yeah, and then after I potentially could have been robbed, I took a nap.
I think I have zero survival instincts.
How do you- I checked around and be like, do I have everything?
Or like, and then when it took a nap, like I- I was like, all right, I think everything is, I think I'm safe.
Nap time.
No, she is so smart.
I know, I was like, I was like, okay, now I, nap time.
How are you alive?
I don't know.
I have like zero fear for like.
Like, oh, I could potentially got kidnapped or let some...
Oh, I froze that guy from our Wolverine.
Poor guy.
He was actually gonna kidnap him.
I'm like, you know what?
I feel so safe.
Let me just go sleep for like two hours.
I was paranoid.
I was like, who the fuck called my apartment?
Oh, shit.
I'm gonna stay away from my team.
Oh I knew at least I got solo.
I was hoping I get solo ulted there Worth it No, I like to do it after.
Yeah You know what I took him down with me I'm a dodo bird Hey guys, can we like touch that point a little bit?
Wow Don't worry, he'll be fine I'm like a little concerned that he'll turn around and see me At least he didn't turn around, you know I thought he would And notice that, you know I was there
Because like It's instinct from all the times I've like Got packages and like ordered out I'll just be like I just like let people in Like automatically Because like I used to order out a lot So I just do that.
So then I was just like...
Legendary!
Okay, Starlord.
Whoa!
So it was just literally...
It was just literally me reflex.
Okay, he's not getting...
Oh my god, we let...
He body block me.
No, I was curious when I was like...
Wait a minute.
minute i was like okay maybe it's a i was like maybe it's a package and i'm just like hoping that was what it was and then i was like and then when i looked at the door there was no package and i was like who the fuck like cause you see i'm an adult i never say i was responsible I never I never said that I am an adult though
okay yeah but now now now I will I lock my door after that now now I realized that was that was a little a little stupid of me just a little up i'm just surprised i was like you know what after afterwards i was like it's time for a nap
dokey is that really you no oh sorry that's caps lock more like a lot
whoops i didn't Yo, Sam.
I love your streams.
Yeah, I like your streams too.
This seems offensive.
Yeah, they'll never know.
How would they know?
I'm just a fan account.
Yeah, I'm the Doki Bird Virus account.
Damn, this in this game is so real for that.
Yeah, exactly.
They'll just check my YouTube and they'll be like, Oh, she's not live.
That must not be her, then.
That's right.
Dance for me.
Exactly.
The real Jokey Bird is not Jokey Bird.
Alright.
Okay.
I clap, clap, clap, clap, clap.
Oh shit, sorry, I was not paying attention to you.
I just started clapping.
I couldn't help it.
Oh nice, I have my luck too.
Okay guys, like why don't we just hang out together?
Nice.
Clap, clap.
Start clapping, everybody.
That's right.
What's that quote called?
Where, like, impersonation is not...
What's that famous quote for...
Do you know what I mean?
Also, from the office about impersonation.
Legend, Barry...
Where's my fucking team?
I am Luna Alting, guys.
Please, Stan.
Yeah, Dave Dryden is not a joke.
Also, they made a sequel.
I'm so tired.
They made a... My coffee.
you have to kick in.
Also, they made a sequel to The Office.
Or they are making a sequel to The Office.
And it's about, like, the dying newspaper company.
Yeah.
It's apparently going to be about the newspaper company.
And, like, how newspaper is, like, a dying media forum.
Yeah, it's by the creators of The Office.
I'm pretty sure it's going to be fucking garbage.
I'm pretty sure it's gonna...
It's just gonna bank on the nostalgia factor, I feel like.
I don't know.
Most likely.
Oh, goodbye.
This is where we die.
You're so good, Star Lord.
Wait, is my Loki alive?
Oh, he is.
Never mind.
He's not.
Don't worry, I'm coming back.
I don't know.
I feel like...
I just think it's gonna...
be bad because um um because like apparently there is it's gonna be it's a stream it's gonna be streamed it's a um streaming exclusive i mean to be fair um everything is just streaming exclusive now but it's on the fucking peacock and who the fuck has i don't know who the fuck has a peacock description outside of i saw it i have a mirror like i can't even access peacock i mean we'll just start it because i don't know what else we can do i'm just gonna die actually okay well gretchen i think we can solve this uh 99
one three two one Okay, that's awkward.
Okay, who the fuck let's un-frozen?
Who un-frozen?
Okay, we could have lived that if you know.
You did unfreeze the Captain America and then let him get fucking slammed on fire by our...
Oh, we're dead.
We're so dead.
We're not winning that.
I'm dead too.
I missed it too.
That sucks.
if I didn't miss the freeze.
Yo, you want to go back to Wolf?
Well, no, I used the Luna ult.
I knew we weren't going to win that because we were down too.
I just, I used the Luna ult so we could guarantee 99.
That was the only reason I used the Luna ult.
I knew we weren't going to win it.
I just wanted to get the 99 because it's just safer than potentially using that to...
Because if I use it to potentially try and get the point back and then like, most, more likely that we were...
Oh my gosh!
If we're all gonna hit him after my freeze, you better, it better be a secure kill.
It's, I fucking freeze the iron fist.
Guys.
Oh my god, the pointy thing hit me.
Okay, nice.
That's good.
But I'm definitely not gonna grab.
I'm definitely not gonna grab all in time, though.
nice when did we get a thing oh oh hey nice i got i got shielded i still died it doesn't matter it still died oh and then i don't think we win this round i mean someone has to play strange and pretend okay let's hope we don't see none Oh, that sucks.
Come on.
Okay.
This is the only thing I can do.
It's just, someone better be portaling!
Yay!
We portals!
All right.
Oh, yeah, no.
Unless our mag gets a fucking juicy ass, um, nope.
He had to get, he had to.
I had to hit that mag up.
He literally had to hit that mag up to win.
That's so unlucky.
Aww, that's so unlucky.
Where's my tiramisu?
Oh, there it is.
Hey.
Yay, tiramisu.
Music makes people happy.
Maybe I can do both.
I have no idea.
I'm rewarded.
For losing that round, I'm rewarding myself by a tiramisu.
Yeah, it's good.
Pretty good.
Yeah, I can play it again.
Yeah, I can play you a few of my tracks after the battle if you want.
Well, thanks, but damn, really more of a classic rock guy.
Alright, I have my guard dog here.
I'm safe, right?
I didn't...
I'm the one with the...
He's here.
Hmm.
That's why I'm asking my dog.
I'm safe, right?
Oh, that was unlucky.
That should have been a hit.
The ricochet fucked me up.
Good medicine.
Oh, of course they're going.
Die!
What the fuck?
I hear?
Let...
Oh, okay.
Okay, this might be where we die.
Oh, I'm...
No, no.
We're fine.
The fact I have to stay in this alt, though.
This sucks.
Okay, I froze him.
Oh, my God.
That is a lot of scabs.
That...
There's so many ults.
Really?
We still haven't capped?
Okay.
Dad's side eyes.
I have no.
No, I know.
I have no survival instincts.
Don't worry.
Hey.
Oh, that was...
That was actually like a Hail Mary breeze.
I had no idea if I was going to hit anything there.
I'm not gonna do it yet.
Yep, there we go.
Oh, nice.
Yay!
My old is better!
Dance!
My buddies!
We need, we need to fucking keep our look, we have to get us all.
Okay.
Don't worry, I got you, Loki.
Oh, I should have maybe kept it on maybe our Starlight.
Okay, that is a very scary.
Oh my god, I'm scared!
Oh hey, our strange had like a fucking juicy ass up there.
Don't worry, I trust my team.
I have high ground.
Let's go!
Oh, it was a juicy ass up.
All right, I'm chilling now.
Oh, they didn't know I missed.
They don't know I'm not on YouTube right now, so they can't tell.
Oh, shit.
It's okay.
I got him.
I mean, he's won.
Guys, this is my first game, guys.
This is, guys, this is my first game.
Please, this is my first game, guys.
I am allowed to miss my shots on my first game.
Jesus Christ.
I am.
Guys?
Okay, he's one.
I'm fucking gonna punch him.
Come on.
Get over here.
Get your fucking ass over here!
There we go.
What?
I was like, get down from there!
Fight me like a man!
Get your ass down here!
I think it was actually 1 HP.
I laugh.
It was definitely 1 HP there.
Uh, boys, thank you for the tier 1 subs.
Thank you, thank you.
If it's real you, you are so good at it.
It's not.
They will never know.
You're a big bit of his imagination.
Every time someone asks me if I'm the real dokey, but I just say no.
Just to fuck with them.
And they'll never know.
I'm so humble.
Hey, look, I win.
Oh my god.
Am I actually gonna get Celeste 2?
On...
Celeste 2?
On stream?
I won't be hard stuck Celeste 3.
Wow.
I've been hard stuck Celeste 3 for like...
Like 30.
I think like 20 games now.
20 to 25 games.
also let me well wait not that I need to fix something uh yes I forgot to like untoggle my aim but I just like keeps untogging itself accidentally alright nice but yeah today I just feel chill today I'm just gonna I'm just hanging out I just want to hang out I just want to no brain play rivals because I'm like I'm gonna play I'm playing it anyway so might as well just uh stream it also need a rumor to remove my fake trigger command did i remove it oh wait someone already removed it nice wait no i didn't remove it wait is this on for my youtube this is my youtube okay i like nightbot on you have to have like separate accounts for youtube or twitch for your nightbot so i keep forgetting which one is my yeah okay which one is my night uh twitch one and which one's my youtube one because there's literally like no way to differentiate yeah this fake trigger sponsor is over but um but um where the where the fuck is my where the fuck is my games i'm in celestial not eternity all right what's
rp with some people do i have the money one no i don't all right I'm sorry, let's roleplay.
Oh, wait, are these guys like...
Are you guys roleplayers or not roleplayers?
Or am I real?
Hello.
Oh.
I guess goodbye?
Oh, hey, hello, my fellow roleplayers.
Oh, it's a big head.
Hello, my fellow roleplayers.
Hello.
It's nice to see you all.
Oh, okay, she doesn't like role-playing.
Hello, we are... Hello, we're just fellow role-players.
Please don't hurt us.
We're just here to chill.
I'm so cute.
Am I just schizo?
Was that... was that person real?
Oh my god, is this... Oh, this guy?
Okay.
This guy peaked...
GM, like, this is his first season.
I think it's him.
Okay, wait, I just gotta know if he gets mad, I'll know if it's him or not.
Um, I think it's him.
I'm pretty sure.
But then I don't want to, like, if I don't want to be, like, mistaken identity, but I had a game whose name is very similar to this.
But if he gets mad, then I'll know it's him.
But anyway, so, Black Panther, really?
in the sea though i guess in the sea though usually i just ban human torch but no he get he probably ban torch oh no it's him over in here it's him okay this guy um no he is very easily rage baitable because what happened was that um he was complaining about the lack of heals while we were triple support and um but he was the only one dying because of his lack of positioning and he was like trying to like he was like yelling at my duo who's a pro player and like trying to teach him the game and then um my friend was like my friend was like oh sorry okay i'll heal you better than and then he kept complaining he kept complaining and then our tank was like why are you so angry like he's gonna heal you and then he kept arguing again and then he argues with our player and being like you don't understand he was judging my play style he was judging me he was but i wasn't getting healed and i was in the right and then we're like and then he our tank was like why are you no why are you so angry
like no let me talk he's like he's like no you don't understand he was saying it was my positioning but i wasn't getting healed and our tank was just Like, bro, look, I get it, man.
Like, but why are you so mad?
Like, he said he'll heal you.
And then he kept fucking, he kept going on.
Like, like, my friend stopped talking.
He was just like, yeah, okay, I'll heal you.
And then he, the guy just kept arguing with his inner demons.
He kept, no, he was on DPS.
This guy was on DPS, like, the mining guy was on DPS.
And then he just kept arguing.
Like, we were like, why are you still?
We all stopped talking and he was just arguing with no one That's the thing he was just he was arguing No, but no one was talking to him and he just kept going And I was like bro are you?
I was like bro, do you know your ass?
Like it was crazy because I was like Like are you bro?
I was just like You are not, you are, you, and he's still playing.
Wait, this was this morning, because I played one, like two games of Marble Rivals, and he's still playing.
It's been, it's been like 10 hours.
He's still on, I just realized.
He's still, I played like two games this morning.
He's still on.
Oh my god, and he's, I'm running Venom now.
I just, I just realized he's still on.
That's crazy.
I just noticed that.
I was like, wait a minute.
He's like, wait a minute.
He has not stopped queuing since this morning.
I refuse to believe he was like, okay we i had to use this that's bad though oh my god i didn't even realize they were all behind me i was so close to up i didn't even realize he was right behind me he's right behind me isn't he stalling i'm still one on point uh please please please please nice nice one hp on venom one one literally one nice
I outnumber you.
Alright, I just want to make sure you're doing that.
I just want to make sure...
We won that?
That's crazy that we won that.
I mean, good for us.
She's going to use that, just in case.
I just want to make sure.
Wee!
Dance, dance, dance, dance, dance!
Monica!
Mom, mom, mom!
Oh
My god, that was scary Why why Why me?
Shit, oh my god You yeah, he's okay now because we're winning he was not okay when we were losing Why the six three?
yeah he's very positive now but when he was dying non-stop when he was dying non-stop and like when he when we were losing he was like fighting his fucking inner demons right now he's okay i think he was like you know it's like it only takes one bad day like i think that was like what happened that game was is one bad day like at least you know at least he's okay now at least at least he's okay now joker coded he's still here no he's he's has i'm pretty sure this man has not stopped playing i am i i believe it i believe this Matt has been playing since the morning.
But I don't want him to.
What Rink does.
What Rink does to people.
God damn.
I'm not bunching up with my Luna.
Because of the Phoenix.
I'm scared.
I'm not that good at Loki.
I'm still learning.
But like.
That's why I'm playing.
him more right now because I want to get better at low-key I have Lord though because like what how many seasons it has it been all right check recent matches no he has public his matches are public I'll check it I want to know how long he's been playing for if he did take a break like good for him I I think he needs it.
I hope he did take up Bray because he definitely needs it.
I'm glad they're nerfing Loki.
He's such a...
Come on, Luna!
You got this!
I don't know where people are, but like... Oh, you know what?
That's fine.
He doesn't know!
Oh my god.
We're okay.
We're so healthy.
Oh Luna.
It's okay.
Sorry.
I left you to die.
We're so okay.
I don't know.
I was not supposed to live.
All right.
That was so close.
I thought I was gonna lose my... Thank God for Celestia.
Thank God for this Elo.
Or Luna would be fine.
Yeah, the reason why I shoot the floor is because of the splash damage.
The floor heals more.
Yeah, definitely.
There's only Spider-Man.
Here they are.
The hook.
They don't know which is the real clone.
They'll be like, which one's the real one?
They'll be like, I don't know.
See, they don't know.
Wow!
Ah!
Mag touching, mag touching.
Okay, I don't know.
I thought he wouldn't know, you know?
Okay, how did he know?
How did he know?
I was literally not moving.
He could have shot any of us.
No, how did he know?
He's some menace.
There was literally three of us.
There was three of us.
How did he know?
I didn't move!
I was literally just going left and right!
My disguise was perfect!
There were three of us!
One was at the balcony!
Oh my god, 97.
A fucking course.
A fucking course I didn't get...
I didn't get like 23 or some shit.
I'm at it pretty well.
I got... I got his.
Alright.
Oh, yeah.
Let's check.
Let's check if it's him.
I don't remember what match it was.
Let me double check.
I don't even remember what match it was.
It was...
Oh, it was the one I lost.
Yeah, it is him.
Alright.
Oh, no, he is.
No, no, he is...
No.
Guys, no, he is definitely, guys, today's the 24th, right?
No, he's been, oh yeah, no, oh yeah, no, he's been, he's been playing since, he's been playing since 1.32 p.m.
Yeah, today is the 20, he has been on 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24.
So what is enjoying this Sunday?
Yeah, this, yeah, he's definitely been, he's definitely been playing since this morning.
Yeah, he's melted into the gaming chair.
Yeah.
Yeah, no, that's why I told you all it took was one day.
bad game for to push that man off the edge.
Oh, hey, Pizza.
Aren't you playing right now?
I saw you on earlier.
Alright.
Another... Your Celestia 1?
Wait, what happened?
Pizza?
What happened?
Not even online.
Yeah, I'm down.
A Bad day happened.
Don't know what happened.
Oh, wait.
That's your account?
Oh, that's you?
All right.
Hey, at least I lose less.
If I kill the Celestial 1, and we lose, I lose less.
less because I'm on Celestio 3.
That's the pro.
Don't jinx it.
I mean, pizza lose more, but I lose less.
True.
They're because they're using dual PC.
I have.
Yeah.
But then, like, also, I'm worried about, I feel like I could fuck it up.
Pizza got rid of that.
What even is the hamstring mode?
I don't even have, like, what was the newest one.
I only have better TV on for my channel.
I don't remember what the newest one is called.
Like, I say new, but I don't use Twitch that much anyway.
7TV, yeah.
I don't even have 7TV on.
Because I'm just, I guess I'm just lazy.
Because I don't use Twitch as much, so I'm just lazy.
Who's pizza?
This guy.
Eating pizza.
Yeah, 7TV has a lot of fun emo shit, but I'm just I'm too lazy to set that up.
I mean, my mods can try and set that up.
And they can choose all the emos they want to choose.
He's like, anyway, mods want to set up 7TV.
Emotes for my channel.
Or we'll never have 7TV emotes.
No, he just plays Iron Fist and...
Well, he's playing Meta this season.
This season, he's going Meta.
Hello fellow roleplayers.
Hello.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, this is not a roleplaying lobby.
Oh hello.
Turns around.
Knows there's danger.
Oh my god.
He's a menace spy.
I knew spy.
Spider-Man is a fucking menace.
I knew it.
Just a little bit of trolling.
All right, let's see.
What is...
I wish there's, like, the SR average.
Like, in Overwatch, you can see the average of the SR.
Or the ranking.
So you know who's, like...
Oh, my God, Widow.
All right.
Oh, the Doom Q starts now, I guess.
I guess we're starting the Doom Q.
now.
I knew he was a menace.
They were right.
Don't listen to the fake news.
He's your friendly neighborhood Spider-Man.
I only listen to the truth.
I only, I only read one newspaper and that's daily was a daily boggle or some child with my I only read one newspaper and I listen to my favorite podcaster the daily daily bully bugle days are daily bugle look I keep up with DC and not Marvelous Marvel Rival is the one Marvel Rivalous and James Gunn are the only reason why I ever kept up with Marvelous I'm adding Yeah,
I subscribe to JJ's Podcast That's the only podcast I listen to He once told us That That the 5G rays Are making Are making the The frogs gay And I believe him Yeah
Say so.
Not the 5Gs.
It's true.
They're turning the...
Yeah, the 5Gs are turning the spot is gay.
Oh, trust Spider-Man.
Shut up.
I have powers.
What the heck are you talking about?
That's right.
Donate to me so I can donate to JJ.
He needs my help.
To...
To spread the news.
Spread the truth.
I feel like
I hear, like, oh my, I don't know what Mantis is.
I have not played Mantis in so long, though, so I feel so rusty.
Slamming three, two, one.
No lamps.
I wish I could play Loki.
I'm gonna play Loki after this, actually.
I don't think it's worth playing Mantis for our widow.
I don't see no head clicking right now.
oh i should have maybe i should stop healing our our widow sorry dude i keep i keep accident okay i'm walking i'm fucking swapping he's not doing jack all right there you go i swapped that 60 because like at 50 um if you were more than 50 then like every time you swap it It just goes back to 50 anyway.
I don't think our widow is doing anything.
So there's no use in giving him a damage boost.
Lucky defense.
I am ready to put on a show.
We have combo.
There we go.
Oh my god!
Um, our Luna lives though.
He fucking holds no more anything.
I'm a Luna, she's a Luna.
I'm a Luna.
He's unlucky for me.
Oh,
I wanted to damage boost.
Well, I mean, we both.
I was going to try and damage boost that pizza.
Oh, my God, please.
Get away!
Why are you running away?
Please come back.
some magic on us
i don't think we're i think this is where the doom queue starts 100 oh my god he swapped off he actually swapped off yeah that's a good old widow's special i just feel like widow's not good in this meta anymore or like he's never he is good if like with mantis but like we need to run triple support I feel like Romantic is the way in general.
Oh my god, he's so low.
Sucks.
I thought we could get him.
Oh, please.
No!
I had to reload.
I'm sorry, man.
Oh my god.
That's fine.
I live.
I might not live here.
We heal each other and then everything will be okay.
Oh.
Don't worry, I got you.
We're still fighting this, but don't worry, I got you.
Thanks so much.
Time to fight.
Don't worry, I got you.
Your powers are mine.
Come to me, please.
I'm ready to put on a show.
Hold damage.
This one on me.
Oh my god.
Okay.
I damaged.
I...
Here goes.
It goes.
Magic, magic, magic.
I damaged.
I did my job.
I did my...
Wow, it's like, Widow was just not the pick.
We swapped and things worked out.
Who would have thought?
I thought!
Widow!
Oh my god!
He was Lord Bucky!
It was, it's like Widow was just a troll pic who would have thought.
No way!
That can't be!
What was that Widow player in the, in the beginning of season that was so good?
I swear I don't see that guy anymore.
Oh, go bevels.
There used to be a Widow player that was like really, really, really good.
Um, not...
That streams a lot too.
No, not Peril.
Apparently she was hacking.
I don't know, this is all...
It's all, um...
Sweet shit!
It's all, but like, he got banned and then he disappeared.
Why not Peril?
He's all together.
Apparently, but it's all...
like what's the word it's like um i guess like hearsay from other players other pro players we're seeing it i8 yeah yeah i8 i was thinking about i8 speculations yeah from paros but like apparently what from what i was told he got banned and then he like never came back but people don't know i don't know i don't know he just literally disappeared i don't see him
see him anymore.
Oh my god.
I'm just gonna...
Um...
I might be this.
Whoa, shit, nice.
I mean, I can still get there.
I mean, I don't see him anymore either, so like, I don't know.
I personally haven't seen for, uh, since I've been playing again.
at all on my friends list.
So, or maybe name change, who knows?
But like I said, it's all like speculations.
But I was told from like other players.
Oh,
we win this.
Okay.
I don't know, I thought we were gonna fight here.
This is a little bad.
Because I have four, three.
Okay.
Oh my god, that's so unlucky.
He died so fast.
Because they have...
They have like, uh...
This is bad because...
Oh, this is so bad.
He's won, he's actually won.
Oh my god, I'm so sad.
Oh!
Oh, yes!
C9!
Sorry, C9!
Send nine.
The new C9.
Oh, he did it like, what, two times?
Two times back to back?
Or was it three times?
I don't remember.
I lost count.
I saw that live, too.
I saw that live.
People were like, Mark, I saw Rob Moore, like, put his hands on his head, like, you know, like, like, you know, like, crouch, bent down, with his palm, with his palm in his, like, in his head.
I saw that when that happened.
I'm not a Loki, babe.
I'm trying my best.
I am ready to put on a show.
I really don't.
He sucks.
And do a storm up.
So I'm trying my best.
No, we're dead.
We're so dead.
I don't know if I can.
Oh, we seen we said nine.
I literally was so close.
It's 97.
Damn, said nine.
They said nine.
We said nine.
Oh, it's a back-to-back said nine.
I gotta try to put the gloaky cone there.
I was like, I was so close.
I was 2%, 2%.
Mutual send 9.
Dude, you stop making send 9, I think.
Okay.
Didn't like...
Okay, for...
I think like, what, Cloud 9 when it happened in Overwatch?
Um...
It happened like how many times?
I think it was like...
Okay, to be fair, when Cloud...
I remember because I was like during the Overwatch days.
while oh when because I watched the I actually watched the tournament when it happened but I think it also happened twice I'm pretty sure it happened twice and um and yeah no for cloud nine that's why it was called c9 because it happened it but it was in Korea it was in Korea and it wasn't even like a big tournament for it so that's why like everyone's calling it said 9 because it's like you know it's it's a new it's for the new generation because like because like c9 is for the older older overwatch generation and now that we're in marvel rivals it should be called 79 now no lambs i have to use this we don't have lambs either
Okay.
Oh my god, the reload.
I'm missing and I have to reload.
I panic a lot when I'm fucking playing Loki though, not gonna lie.
I don't know, Loki is scarier.
It's so much more pressure to play compared to Luna.
I think it's because I'm not as comfortable on Loki as I am on the other supports.
Which he's so strong.
is definitely one by weaker weakest please please please oh my god okay i hope she i still die
oh phoenix all the fat that was a huge combo trying to dodge three things can't get any help It was impossible.
It was three alts.
There was nothing we could do.
They literally Phoenix alts in my lamp away.
I don't know why I couldn't copy Luna there.
I was literally just trying to spam coffee but it didn't work.
And it gave me Bucky too.
It fucking gave me Bucky instead of...
Instead of fucking Luna.
Just kill him.
I have many faces I don't have to copy Also like I'm Apparently I'm supposed to copy first I have to Loki is first And everything But it's just so stressful Because it's like when do I copy
It's definitely harder No I do I do have double confirm I had double confirm but like for some reason Because I almost I almost copied Uh Okay, don't worry, I got you.
I am ready to put on a show!
Oh my god, I did.
Alright.
It's fine.
We're okay.
This Hulk is a fucking terrorist.
He's using every cooldown on me.
Damn.
That's rough, buddy.
That's fucking rough.
Yay.
They're on four supports.
Yeah.
Okay, I was like...
No.
I had to look back because I was like, what?
Look, see?
It works.
I did it.
Damage boost that.
Oh, never mind.
You want to get healed so...
I was like, no way.
Boy.
No, you're fucking with me.
That doesn't sound right.
I don't know if I'm going to build ult in time, though.
Well, all the meta supports, Loki is my weakest.
Because normally I'm not put on Loki duty too.
Because like, um, because Loki is like, a lot of people like playing Loki.
So like, I never have to play Loki in general.
Oh my gosh, I have to use that.
I am ready to put on a show.
I have to use that.
Our team was dying.
Oh.
I am ready to put on a show.
Wait, what?
Oh, it's two support olds.
I was like, what the fuck?
Oh, nice.
Bye, bye, bye.
Yay!
Damage boost!
Baby, damage boost to Phoenix salt, you kill everything.
It's okay.
Maybe they do need a force support.
All right.
Oh my god, one more minute.
I feel like I'm even in this fight.
for like 20 years.
Yay!
Dance, dance, dance, dance, do the snow.
Bum, bum, bum.
What the fuck?
Why did he came over?
Oh, oh, no.
Don't worry, I'm helping.
There you go.
Oh, he could have stayed in my thing.
That's okay.
Yay!
Hey, Luna.
Can you heal me too?
I just need one little healer.
Because I'm greedy as fuck.
Okay, this Hulk is actually pretty bad.
Hulk is not meta, but for some reason, Celestia, everybody wants to play Hulk.
And I don't know why.
Everyone's obsessed with Hulk.
Okay, um, I think we're fine.
Fuck on us.
Don't worry.
Hulk is on me now.
Oh, fucking okay.
Don't worry.
I'm still alive.
Oh, don't worry I don't know how I live Where is he?
Come on Kobe Oh shit Hello Oh my god in my little safe space.
I
Oh my god!
Oh my god, my little safe space!
The cup leaf!
I'm glad that, um...
The mag fucking saved us there.
I just have to be in the little house.
Oh my god, we haven't hit Doom.
Yeah, my little bunker, I bunkered up.
Get to cover!
Two, one!
Yeah, mag closed the door for me, but Because I was thinking I was like, wait, no, we're gonna die and there's no like I was like Mag could just chuck this fucking ball into our house and then thank god mag was there Thank god mag was there to like To close that door We did it we overcame the loser queue
nice keep eating the dicks why is he complaining you don't have to you don't have pussy travesty keep spamming cooldowns that's the point of abilities keep eating dicks yay i'm the heart sucks celestial three let's go
Not pussy.
Yay!
Wow.
Can't wait to lose all my games after this.
I think Celestia...
Okay, I think High Elo starts at Celestia 1, though.
Not that Loki game.
Loki is my weakest support, I think.
Out of...
Well, we don't count the non-meta.
Because Sue's not meta anymore.
But I still think I'm better at Sue than Loki.
uh apparently jeff is meta but only in scrims only in tournament play um i'm better at adam than i am on loki adam is so easy to play what's meta from what i know it's luna loki um cloak if loki is banned and for like certain maps sue apparently is not meta anymore because she got like she kept she got slowly nerfed over time um ultron is meta during triple support uh mantis is triple support as well for situational for uh triple support rocket is absolutely dog shit and that will always be dog shit um but uh but i would say like because loki is hard meta and a really good loki player is um then why did you why did you play rock because whenever i'm lazy and I don't want to try um literally literally you don't need hands to play rocket all I have to do is pressed is like I don't remember is it left click or right click that's you all I have to do is just press right click I don't even remember which one's the heel press right click and just stand there sometimes I put e out if I feel a
little um a little wild I'm not putting my E out.
Um.
But yeah, no, like, Rocket is literally, like, if you just don't feel like actually playing the game, and you just want to AFK, you just play Rocket.
If you, like, like the game, but you don't want to try anymore, you play Rocket.
But Loki is hard meta.
A good Loki player is so fucking scary.
Like, um, the things they can do.
Loki is actually a fucking mind game playing him.
Because you have to be more aware of your cooldowns.
Demon, thank you for the 200 bitties.
Thank you, thank you.
What the fuck?
An eternity player.
What he's doing here.
I found your immediate one.
Pop in and say, I absolutely love your mind and voice.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
I'm going to get a good week.
Lots of love from chat.
Thank you again.
Thank you for those 200 bitties.
So sometimes I don't want to try and play.
Yay.
See?
Someone else can play Loki.
to try sometimes.
I just want to relax and chill.
Who am I going to banish from this match?
Alright.
What are we going to do now?
Up, up.
Apparently you can't three stack on.
Apparently, uh, uh, you can't, uh, uh, do more than duos now in Celestia.
They, like, restricted it for Celestia now.
It should be eternity.
Yeah, you can't even three stack in Celestia.
Oh, we all banned it.
I'm banning Torch.
Fuck that shit.
Torch is, like, so fucking broken.
Apparently, Torch and Seiloc are the most broken characters right now.
I mean, I think Seiloc basically gets the Juno treatment.
Where she gets every fucking skin possible.
Oh, no, that's Spider-Man.
Sorry, Spider-Man.
No, Spider-Man is Kiriko.
And, um, and Seiloc is, uh, Jun...
Spider-Man is Kiriko.
in terms of, like, Kyoko gets nothing other than skins.
And Scyloc is Juno, where she can get buff and also get the skins.
Like, she doesn't get touched for nerfs or buffs.
Oh, am I lagging now?
Really?
If I tap out, if I tap out, I lag.
It's only when I tap out.
Luna is a new Kiriko.
No, because Luna skins are fucking dog shit.
You can't change my mind.
I think all Luna skins are ugly except for the default.
Lower accurate spot events.
I hate every Luna skin except for the default one.
You guys think it's good only because she's showing ass.
Like, fucking, if she's she what if her ass wasn't showing you would think the skin is dog shit
yeah and if her ass was covered you would not think this is a good skin it's literally because your ass is showing i think the skin has only redeeming quality is the fact that it's a skin there's nothing else to redeem it okay what the fuck is there oh yeah I forgot to put it on a Captain America you're supposed to put the snowflake on your Captain America and then they'll live forever and can do like Captain America things like that yeah help her Loki more I have to reload,
so I hope he lives.
I like it for...
I think her hair...
I don't like her hair for it either.
I personally...
I don't like the hairstyle and the hair colors on all the alternatives.
I don't know.
Her default one was just...
It's just so good.
That it's hard to make a better Luna skin.
90% of Luna skin has her ass covered.
That's why everyone thinks the bikini one is the best one.
If she didn't have her ass showing, you would all think it's not a great skin.
You can not change my mind.
I would say it.
Oh my god, please just, okay, thank god.
Kill him.
Not me.
Her feet are also, yeah, exactly.
Her feet is also showing.
It's just the fucking, uh, it's just like everything about it.
I love shooting random breezes and then...
Okay, let's hope that...
Oh, he missed.
That's...
I mean, that's fine with me.
I'm fine with that.
I'm actually fine.
I didn't have to use it.
I just, I don't know.
I just felt like it.
Oh my god, I hope you like...
Okay.
That should not have hit.
I was not on it.
The freeze, I was saying, the freeze was absolutely not on that mag.
I have no idea how I got it.
Yeah, yeah, it missed.
It was a miss.
I was like, okay.
Okay, I'll take it.
We take this.
We take it.
Heroes make them safe.
There's a lot like here.
There's a lot to like here.
There's a little something for everyone except for Toki.
30 seconds before you attack.
I'm more than just a gooner, guys.
There's more to this world.
than gooning.
I will say the Scylok skin is a good skin.
The swimsuit one is good.
Not just because of her ass.
It's because of everything that combined together.
It makes it a good...
It makes it a good quality gooner skin.
It's a set pleasing and you can goon to it like that's what we're here for it luna is like the low effort goon can
i get like one yeah i just need literally need like one little here oh okay we definitely did not need that that was oh that's that's a little Thank God they don't know we fucked up.
Thank God they don't know we fucked up our Loki coffee.
They didn't know we fucked up our Loki coffee.
We take those.
Never punished.
The Loki thanking God right now.
He didn't.
Yay!
Yippee!
No punishment.
Yeah.
We're doing it, guys.
We're actually doing it.
I'm going to say that, and then we're going to start losing now.
I mean, it's a nice record.
It's a pretty decent record here.
Oh.
No, how would I roll this?
Today on Twitch.
I just felt like playing Rylos today.
That's really it.
I was craving some rank, and I was like, I play off stream when I can just when I'm going to stream it.
Be more fun for you guys to watch anyway.
Can anyone else please?
Oh.
I'm Luna Snow.
Like the moon, I shine in darkness.
Huey, thank you for the 200 videos.
Thank you, thank you.
If justify your gooning, then you aren't a real gooner.
Thank you for the super chat.
I...
Look, I have standards.
why did he ban emma you're literally playing at emma look i'm a gooner with standards okay a gooner connoisseur like we we don't clearly next thing thank you thank you for the hundred bitties thank you thank you okay but okay oh yeah thank you again for the bitties a goonessure yes i am a goonessure
Over fine taste.
You have bad preferences.
Maddie, as soon as Gripproos are shown, you don't even care what they look like.
Right heroes could make all the difference.
Bro, God, God.
It's okay we ban.
So Venom doesn't get railed.
can talk before type or what the are they talking about i don't even this conversation doesn't even like flow at all it's like people were in like we're on like three different twitch chats but like on the wrong stream this conversation does not flow like five three and six are not having the same conversation Oh,
now this is Loser Q.
And not three DPS.
Guys, we're in Loser Q now.
Yeah, I'd rather have no Torch Player than an actual Torch Player.
Some DPS drop.
Oh, there we go.
We got Rocket.
Alright.
We're gonna lose.
I'm gonna drop the dopest album anytime.
oh my god that's awkward oh no not it's okay he doesn't have wait where's our oh i was gonna say where where did our mag go this guy it disappeared so bad oh i froze myself whoops i got too caught
Such a bad character.
He's so lucky I was looking at him.
Oh my god.
We're getting harassed by...
This Captain America doesn't even have a snowflake, so he should not be living.
I think this is the same Captain America from...
The last game.
A good Captain America is so scary.
Oh, stack, stack, stack.
Rocket!
Why did you leave?
The circle!
Wait!
See it!
Yeah, no, my hate is justified.
He literally walked out!
If he stayed, I could have lived!
Get away from me.
His fucking walks, walks away.
I don't!
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Also, the reason why is also because, like, um...
Um...
How's it say?
It's easier to pocket the other support during...
Oh my gosh, I reflexively do it because I heard, like, the voice line.
Um...
I got it!
He's done!
It's easier to pocket.
Okay.
It's a lot easier to pocket the other support when they're not...
when they're not Rocket.
Rocket is very bad at pocketing.
Holy shit.
Okay, we're still fighting this.
I can go Loki and...
Okay.
I have to use that.
Oh my god, please Rocket.
Play!
Because Rocket players just play for their life.
They don't.
Play for, like, Assists.
Like, I literally can't live.
I cannot live.
Because the Captain America will just chase me the entire time.
The Captain America will just chase me all the time.
And because he'll chase me, since I'm an easier target, I'll just keep dying.
Because the rocket cannot pocket me.
Or, like, support me through it.
This is why rocket is a bad fit.
like it's just so like i just have to fucking run away and pretend that i don't exist oh yeah that sucks doesn't it yeah that fucking sucks man yeah my god wow doesn't that fucking suck rocket it sure does
That fucking suck, doesn't it?
Oh my god.
Oh my please, I literally...
Oh my god, I wish I could just copy...
Okay.
I'm ready to put on a show.
Oh my god, I can't do anything!
Please!
I can't fucking survive!
I can't copy Luna.
The Luna was not in my, like, line of sight.
I want to copy Luna, but he wasn't in my line of sight.
I'm not gonna... yeah, fuck it.
Can you, like, go back out and just sit in our back line?
I...
I can't even shift.
Literally no backline support.
Please, I just want to copy.
I just want to copy.
That's all I want to do.
Let me copy something.
Oh my god.
Okay, that's fine.
This is a- this is a- this is fine.
I'm not copying, dude.
I can't- I can't risk it.
I can't fucking risk it.
Wait, what the fuck?
Who's shooting at us?
Something is hitting us.
I don't like it.
I normally don't play Doki on this map, so I'm, like, struggling.
I'm actually struggling so much when I'm getting dead.
Oh my god.
Don't fuck this.
I can't.
I literally can't do anything.
That, like I said, it's a struggle.
That's the only thing I can do.
I'm just gonna stay up here.
It can't hurt me.
I am ready to put on a show.
I can't.
Good luck, everybody.
Good luck, everyone.
Maybe?
I have many faces Okay
Okay Okay
Just run away Time to search things up Including which side you're on Please leave me He is low.
He said not just to kill me.
That's so fucked.
He actually left the point just to kill me.
Thank you for the red.
Thank you.
Now we had a good stream.
Oh yeah, I am lagging a little.
Wow.
I don't know why.
120.
Oh my gosh, this is why.
Oh my god, that would have been scary at home.
Am I DLSS on again?
No?
I've met many Supremes before, Strange.
What makes you so special?
Is it on?
I don't remember.
Oh, it is.
Wait, it is on.
Why is it on again?
Yeah.
Wait, has it been like...
Oh, that's weird.
I have to I have to cap it because um um It just doesn't work
Am I streaming at 140p?
I'm on eight.
I don't even know
Jesus Christ
Oh my gosh, I don't know why it does that every time it like resets itself and I don't know why please please thank you thank you see look at that see see look at that be pocketed me I live oh my god I live wow I actually live when I get I get pocketed that's crazy that's actually what a crazy concept.
I just need like...
Okay.
Oh my god, he's alive.
I don't know how, but he's alive.
Oh, nice.
C9.
Yay!
So many C9s.
Oh my god, he's not Captain America!
There is a god!
I'm Captain America.
I'm fucking free now.
I wish I could play a 200.
I think I could try if I had a 244 frames.
I'm actually...
Oh my god, I hope he does.
Oh my gosh, I wanted to see.
Save our strange.
That sucked.
I'll shine.
Oh!
This might be where I die.
Good luck, everyone.
Good luck.
Oh no, he's back.
I spoke too soon.
He- he's back.
He's back.
I knew it was too good to be true.
true.
I fucking knew it was too good.
Oh, unlucky.
It was too good to be true, guys.
I wasn't meant to be happy.
I hear him.
Like, he didn't, if he pocketed me, like, sooner, I didn't have to use it.
Oh, okay, sure.
Sure.
I want to get rid of the clone just for now.
Come on, we just got...
Come on, we pocket each other.
Oh.
And we pocket each other, everything will be fine.
Nice.
Oh my god, nice.
It's just that easy.
Oh, thank god we have our own.
What the?
oh thank god oh thank god they said nine again
what a comeback what a comeback bro this guy was literally carrying this entire team on his back like their captain america was carrying the entire team
holy shit i'm surprised we even been held that much.
I'm so surprised we're able to hold for that long.
Like, I think his back was broken at that point.
Like, I think I think he literally broke his back from that.
Wait, change it to 1080?
Is it actually not in 1080?
I thought I changed the bit rate.
Did I not?
I'm so sorry, guys.
Yeah, no, it should be.
Oh!
my god i knew i forgot something i am so sorry okay i'm gonna change it i'm gonna change it back to 1080 guys give me um i just realized i just realized it's on 1440p wait were you guys able is it really crunchy i am so sorry how yeah i all right i'll restart it i'll restart it