Hello, everybody.
Hello, hello.
I will give you guys a warning.
I am lower energy today than usual, because maybe my energy will pick up later on, but it's because today I was reminded that I am a woman.
So, no, it wasn't anything that dad did.
Um, I knew.
Um, okay.
So, no, it was actually today.
It was like last night.
I was, uh, uh, reminded that wowie!
My bro tuber is a woman!
Unsubscribe.
Guys, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Welcome back, cheater.
Seijian, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Um, uh, NSD, thank you for the five gifted ships.
My immersion!
I did not come here to- I did not come to this stream to find out you were a woman!
Bro, no way, bro.
How could this be, bro?
I feel so fucking portrayed.
Anyway, but yes, I knew it was going to be my No Girls Allowed Club ruined.
Bro, what about No Girls Allowed, bro?
That was the first rule we made together.
Anyway, so I knew it was going to be really bad because last night I went to bed at 10 p.m.
and I didn't come out of my coma until like 11 a.m.
So I knew this was a bad one.
This was going to be a bad day.
So, yeah, I went into a... and I woke up and I'm still tired.
I knew it was going to be a bad day.
Hey!
Patch... Patch... Patchesu, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
I got my crookie plushie.
Yippee!
Yeah, I heard a lot of people are getting a crookie plushie from YouTubes already.
So I... it was weird that they are shipping individually, but that's okay.
It means you don't have to pay for extra shipping, you know?
So at least that's good.
Uh, but yeah, a lot of people are slowly getting their plushies from YouTubes.
Uh, and they are a lot bigger than...
I know a lot of you guys were like, Wow, I did not expect them to be that big.
I warned you guys!
I was like, when I got those plushies, I was like, Oh my God!
They were a lot bigger than I...
But I also had that same reaction when I got those plushies.
Um, but I felt like, you know...
Good bar... like, good deal though.
It's a good deal for the amount, uh, for what it was...
For what it was priced for the final product.
Like, the...
The size of the plushie compared to, like, what the price it was.
It was like, you know, a good deal.
A good bargain.
And I'll always be watching you.
I'll always be watching you now.
Um, uh, what a deal.
But yes, also for those who don't know.
Um, my very first podcast, uh, that I've ever done.
This, like, the very first time I've ever done a podcast.
Um, is now out on the Sweet and Sour channel.
That's usually hosted by Lily Pichu and Pokimane.
Um, but, uh, Poki wasn't there.
So they got me, Doki, to... as a guest.
Because she wasn't there that day.
So they're like, Doki, you wanna do a podcast with Lily Pichu?
And I was like, yeah, sure.
Uh, of course.
Um, uh, I'd love to.
Uh, so we revealed a special collaboration.
Um, that has been in works for a while.
So for those who wanna get spoiled right away as to what it is.
Um, because Lily...
Um, she literally started off the podcast, like, hounding me about this.
So I might as well reveal it.
So Lily, Lily Pichu and I are actually working on an original song together.
Um, the song was written, um, uh, the song was actually written a while ago.
Uh, but, like, um, a couple of months ago.
But, um, it was very, very unlucky.
Because I actually got very sick, um, multiple times throughout the year.
I think you guys might remember that.
So, like, I actually...
No, it's a different original song.
This one is more so, more so, more of Lily Pichu's style.
Have you ever listened to Lily's songs?
This is, like, her, uh, like, the more soft one.
The more softer tone songs.
And it's actually gonna be a collaboration with also the same producer who did Last Cup of Coffee.
Um, so, uh, we were working on this for a while now, I think.
I think, like, this was in the works for, like, around a year.
And, uh, um, I was supposed to record it a lot earlier.
Like, a lot, lot earlier.
But the reason why...
I still haven't recorded it yet.
But the reason why it took so long to actually get to the recording of this was because when she actually finished writing the song, I kept getting sick back to back to back.
Or had other obligations.
So, like, I think when she was done with the song, um, I got sick from the Phantom Thief concert.
And then when I got better, I got sick in Japan.
And then when I got better, my voice at my throat was, like, not okay.
So, I was waiting for that to recover.
And then after that, I had to prepare for...
I had to prepare for my birthday concert.
And now, it should be okay now.
So, I'm planning on trying to get that recorded.
Like, maybe this month or next month.
And then, finally, we can get started on the song.
But yes, it is a huge honor to work with Lily on this.
I asked her if she was available, if she wanted to do this with me.
And she's like, yeah, I'm so down.
I'm really happy, excited to work on an original song with you.
And, uh, uh, I'm like, you know, I'm super excited to, uh, to finally sing it, to finally record it.
Uh, I hope it'll sound good.
When she sent me the demo, it sounded amazing.
But, of course, Lily is an amazing singer, an amazing songwriter.
Um, but, like, her songs are, I don't know, like, her songs are a little difficult to sing.
Because, um, they're quite high and very soft.
So, I hope I can do it justice.
And I'm very excited to record it.
I'm actually going to go to a recording studio for this one.
Because, you know, I want it to be a very good quality for her.
Uh, Valdemir, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Really like the podcast, Doki.
Hope you take part of mine.
Thank you.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Yes, I'm very, I was very happy to be a guest on her podcast.
Uh, Lily and I are planning on doing collab next week, uh, together to, you know, celebrate the podcast, um, and the, you know, the song collaboration.
Um, we haven't settled on a time yet.
She is a very busy person.
Um, you know, she has so many things that she does every day.
Uh, you know, when I was, like, doing that podcast with her, um, uh, she had, like, so much stuff in her schedule on her day and then she had, like, so many things lined up for it, uh, for, for, like, her day in general.
Um, I admire her.
I admire, like, like, how much work she does every day and, like, how she puts...
And then, like, right after the podcast recording, she, like, went straight to do that charity thing with Cutie Cinderella.
I don't know if you guys know about...
Oh, sorry.
My brain is, like, all over the place right now because I'm tired.
Uh, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
But, um, it was, it was, the podcast was recorded on the same day where, uh, Cutie Cinderella was hosting the charity karaoke night thing.
So, like, right after recording the podcast, she had, like, a little interval intermission time and then she had to go straight to the, um, to the karaoke session, um, to, like, the, as a guest there, too.
So, I was, like, wow, like, your day is so fucking packed.
Like, um, um, like, um, I really admire her able to do so many things, especially going outside.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Essentially going outside as one of the tasks that you have to do for it.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
But, uh, I really admire her, like, work ethic, uh, because she has been around the internet for so long, you know?
Able to still consistently being able to do, uh, these things and, like, making these types of content and stuff, um, uh, consistently for, like, what?
I don't remember how long she's been a content creator.
For like, maybe like 8 plus years now.
It has to be like, maybe even 10 plus... I don't know, like whenever she first posted her League of Legends songs, maybe like 10 plus years and still being such an active like content creator over the years is like quite inspiring.
So I had... it was such a huge honor to, you know, have this conversation with her.
And the hour passed by super fast too.
So like, I got really worried about like, oh man, what if we run out stuff to talk about?
What if we run out stuff to talk about?
What if like, oh, what if like, there's dead air and stuff like that?
Oh man, I got super duper worried.
But no, everything flowed naturally.
The only like hurdle we had was me trying to get Kroki to work because it's been so long since I brought Kroki out, that it's like a whole separate program.
So like, I honestly forgot like, I forgot like how to set it up.
So that's why I showed up like, I had like no, like no tracking whatsoever on there when I, when Kroki showed up.
And then Lily was like, wow, you like hyped it up so much.
This is a bit disappointing.
I was like, no, you don't understand.
You don't understand.
It's so, it's so much better when it's moving.
And then like after, after like the, the recording ended, um, I sent her a, I actually got Kroki to work.
I got her to work because I like looked, I had to Google YouTube tutorial on how to set it up.
And then, yeah, I click baited her basically.
Um, cause she, she had such high expectations for Kroki.
But then I'm like, there was no movement at all.
Cause I had to, like, I had like no tracking enabled because I forgot how to get it to work.
And then after the recording, um, I, I ruined Kroki's reputation.
How dare you?
How dare you slander my Oshii like this?
I swear this never happens to him.
Um, um, um, her reputation is childish because of you.
And then so like after, after the podcast, I sent her like a recording of Kroki.
And then she was like, wait, oh my God, wait, this is actually really funny.
And I was like, I told you, I told you it's so much better in motion.
And then she, I like, she was like, I'm going to send it to my editor to like include it in.
But I guess like they forgot to include it in.
Uh, cause, cause I had, I recorded a redemption video for her.
For it to be in the podcast, but they didn't include it.
It was such a good video too.
Okay.
Maybe I overhyped.
It wasn't like an amazing video, but it was like, it was all right.
Okay.
It was, it was pretty.
All right.
Okay, guys.
Um, but yes, unfortunately, um, unfortunately it didn't, um, it didn't, uh, got included in the final cut.
So we were not able to, we were not able to see Kroki, um, in actual motion.
I mean, I could, I, no, if I could give you guys a video, you guys would be like, oh, you hyped it up too.
Fine, fine.
Let me find a video real quick.
All right.
I'm trying to find a video guys.
Okay.
All right.
Where is it?
Okay.
Here it is.
Um, the only thing I'm worried about is like, it's too loud or some shit.
Cause I don't know.
Hello.
Okay.
There's Kroki.
Where, what video is this one?
Media source.
Okay.
Here we go.
There we go.
This is the Kroki video.
And you know what.
This is what it would have looked like if I got it to work.
I
told, it, it looks better in movement.
I told you.
Alright.
There you go.
Caw Caw.
Caw.
Hello, Lily.
Yeah, see, this is what, this is what I sent her.
You overhyped it.
What do you mean I overhyped it so much?
That's why I didn't want to fucking send it.
I didn't want to show you guys.
Caw Caw.
I sent that to Lily and she agreed.
It was definitely a lot better.
It was a lot better in motion.
Caw Caw.
She could never be overhyped.
Alright.
Let's boot up.
Let's boot up some Eldering, guys.
Alright.
Let's boot up some Eldering.
But yeah, this is why today I'm a little sluggish today.
Um.
And, uh.
Buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh.
And it's going to be a short stream today.
Um.
Just because of how sluggish I feel.
Uh.
Patch or Sue.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
I saw you smile when you heard past Doki call.
Yeah.
Caw Caw, streamer.
Caw Caw.
It's Eldering time.
Alright.
Let me, uh.
Make sure that it is streaming Eldering.
Yippee.
Yeah.
So we're just going to vibe today.
We're going to vibe and maybe we'll get one boss done.
Maybe I'll just do one boss and call.
Well, one and done.
I'll be like, oh.
Heh.
That's a game.
That.
That's game.
Okay.
This is like.
Uh.
Okay.
This is like.
Uh.
Out of nowhere.
But I saw from software.
And.
That reminded me of this video I saw.
Of pirate software.
Of like.
Every time he.
Okay.
There was a very funny edit.
About pirate software.
Where.
It's like.
Every time.
He talks about working at blizzard.
Ha.
It was such a good edit.
That was.
Ha ha ha.
Yeah.
With the song.
And.
Okay.
I won't.
Touch much about that topic.
Because I know there's a lot of.
A lot of things.
Surrounding about him.
But.
Um.
Um, I would say it's actually- it's fucking crazy how much this man's life changed just because he didn't press one button in World of Warcraft.
That's... His life trajectory changed because of this one mistake.
Like, which I thought was that crazy.
Yeah.
Like, if he didn't do that, his- I feel like his backlash would not have, like, been this crazy.
Yeah, he failed the QuickTime event.
The missed input of all time.
Like, actual, like, his life changed because of the QuickTime event.
Like, that was- because, like, I don't know if you guys realize- remember this, but before- before, like, all that shit happened, like, it was- like, people had, like- like, people were like, yeah, he does have an ego, but, like- But, like, people still sort of,
like, you know, thought he was a chill guy, but that- the QuickTime- the failing of that QuickTime event changed everything.
Oh, it's just crazy to think about.
Alright, let's see.
Oh, I actually needed- Yeah, he was seen favorably.
Alright, I assume we have to go to over here with the big, giant cup.
Yeah, wow made him, and wow broke him.
Alright, let's go.
Whee!
Go, horsey, go!
Yay!
Alan, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
I can't even imagine the joy of all of his haters are having recently.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
The forage of the- Oh my god, I'm gonna throw the ring!
Where do I- do I just go straight down?
Do I just go straight down?
I don't understand.
I'm gonna throw the ring.
Go around left side?
This side?
What if I go around here?
Oh, get off the horse.
But I have a cool horse.
Require materials?
Do I jump?
I don't know.
I don't want to get one guide.
Don't do it.
Yeah, I'm like, I don't know.
There seems to be suspiciously a lot of red bot- Yeah, okay.
Definitely we're not jumping.
I- Oh yeah, my death counter.
Yeah.
Okay, we're definitely not jumping after what I just saw.
I don't worry.
I got the death counter out.
All right.
I realized, like, I don't know why I paused.
Pausing in this game doesn't matter.
All right.
All up.
Left I go?
Question mark?
Jump for plus one content.
Okay.
I guess we go this way.
I need to jump at the right spot.
I assume, like, the right spot is that giant-ass hole over there.
I assume that's where you go.
Oh yeah, there it is.
There's a grace here.
So yeah.
It has to be.
There's a grace here.
All right.
How did he jump?
Okay.
I don't think that's the right...
Oh my god, wait.
Wait.
Okay.
Don't worry.
I took my gloves off.
I have long observed the lands between.
This world is in dire need of repair and death.
Indiscriminate.
Okay.
Are you prepared to commit a cardinal?
Oh, don't worry.
I'd like you to wait.
Wait.
Why is there a new pool?
Who just died here?
While we were talking.
Oh man.
Am I...
Am I ready?
Am I ready to touch your hand without protection?
Oh my...
Okay.
I'm ready.
Very well.
Let my hand rest upon you.
Oh.
For but a moment.
Oh my god.
It's happening.
Skin on skin.
Oh my god.
It is so...
Wait.
What?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I swear it...
I swear it is...
This is the first time this ever happened.
I swear I can...
Last longer.
I'm sorry.
I swear to god.
I...
It's just anxiety.
Performance anxiety.
Oh, what's she doing?
Oh my god.
They're burning her.
Oh a tree.
You shall burn.
Right after we touched hands?
Was it that bad?
What the hell was it?
Was it?
It was that?
She had to burn herself right after.
This is why you use protection.
No second thing.
Stop, drop, and roll.
Thank you.
For guiding me here.
Oh.
Please touch my hand once more.
No!
My wife!
I'm going to be a single father!
Shall one day meet the road of destined death.
Goodbye.
I will take care of my jellyfish child now!
I gotta raise the jellyfish all on my own!
Reload, go talk to Three Fingers, and save her!
It's too late!
I have to live with the sins I've created!
I'll never touch a maiden without my gloves again!
I'll always remember the weird protection!
I'll always keep my hands protected for the rest of my life now!
Is it this one?
Yeah.
Sajin, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
I saved it.
No lover and head.
In short, why is it always death?
No horse ahead.
I have nothing now.
Nothing.
It's almost as bad as when that guy's wife turned into the moon.
Keep moving.
There's always side quest wives.
I don't want side quest wives.
I want main storyline wife.
Is that a lie?
No, I just can't die there.
Okay.
That's rough, buddy.
How the fuck did people fuck this up?
Behold a back.
What?
Oh.
How the fuck did people fuck this up?
Just getting started.
Fear, but time for bravery.
Where am I?
Oh my god.
Where did I go?
What is this place?
Before I go?
Before I go.
No lover ahead.
I lost her.
I lost my beautiful wife.
I can't believe it.
We touched hands and then she fucking turned into a flame and disappeared.
Oh shit, wait, that's scary.
That's a lot to process, actually.
I...
This is a lot to process right now.
I don't know if I'm ready for this.
This is definitely a lot to process.
Okay.
I know I shouldn't have used that right away, but like, I fucking...
I was feeling a lot right there.
All right.
Look, I lost my wife.
I'm gr...
This is how I grieve.
I'm grieving right now.
All right.
Okay, that's good to know that like, his friends don't care.
That's good to know.
They're like, too busy.
I'm taking it out on them.
I'm like, I'm my wife dead!
Instead of drinking, I'm just beating up random people.
Which is like, I don't know if that's bad or not.
All right.
Nice.
Let's go.
Oh, these guys died.
They're pretty weak.
Whoops.
Still don't know how they died though.
Wow!
Shit!
Okay, okay, okay.
I realized I know now.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa.
Okay, I swear, I think I know.
I...
Nevermind.
And now I know how they died.
Uh, too high up.
No horse ahead.
I feel like none of them has horse.
None of them has horse.
Why is that thing glowing too?
Alright, any, like, secret monsters anywhere?
Likely overcast.
First off, defeat.
Why did so many people die here?
What?
How did so many people die here?
Anyway.
Oh, that's good.
Alright, what do we level up, guys?
Dragoon Council!
Pick your spokesperson and tell me what to level up.
Mr. Broken Bomb, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Dirkie, you were too nervous and made your hands all clammy and went and she had to dry off somehow.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Okay, Vigor.
Alright, we got it.
Okay.
Let's grab the summoning pool, even though I'm not gonna use it.
At least I have precious item on my hand.
At least I...
At least I got the grace.
There's so many skeletons.
Therefore, no target lock.
Oh.
Those dragons seem very friendly.
They seem like friendly dragons.
Right?
They don't seem to, like, wanna bother me or anything.
Except for that guy.
Except for him.
It's okay.
I have my child that I have to raise by myself.
It's alright.
Oh my god, it's not okay.
Oh my god.
What the fuck?
Okay.
He was...
He was not very friendly.
What?
He had...
He definitely had the bigger sword.
I...
I was not...
I was not expecting that at all.
Wait, there's...
Wait, do I have any mods right now?
Or do I have to abandon myself?
I don't know.
So I'll just do it myself.
Alright.
It's alright.
I got it.
I was talking to my manager about, like, getting more mods in the future.
Oh, you're here.
Nice.
It's okay.
I got it.
Oh, shit!
Wait, how the fuck do I...
Okay, here we go.
Wait, what?
How do I...
Wait, I can't hit his legs.
Wait.
What can I...
Oh, I can.
Okay, never mind.
It has to be a particular part of his legs.
Alright.
I have to slap his toes.
It's fine.
I think I'm hitting...
Oh!
Okay.
It might...
I...
I'm not...
I'm running.
I don't think I'm...
Yeah, no.
I...
Oh, okay.
Never mind.
I'm leaving.
He doesn't even have...
Okay, the thing is...
He doesn't even have, like...
Natural HP bar.
So, like, there's no reason.
There's no reason to hit him.
Like, he doesn't even have an HP bar.
So, like, what's the point?
Oh, hey, there's Grace here.
It's okay.
My child will come back.
But I think...
I think we're planning on getting more mods.
So, like...
The other mods...
Don't feel...
Oh, try a range battle.
In short, let there be blood loss.
So, there's no...
So, there's less pressure for all the other mods...
For, like...
To, like...
Come to every stream and stuff.
Whoa.
But I should...
I should leave.
Yeah, like...
Especially for time zones, too.
Oh, shit.
Jesus, he hits so hard.
Yeah.
And then, like...
Less pressure for mods to, like...
Having to show up every stream.
Alright, let's go this way.
At least they give a lot of runes, though.
Which is nice.
Oh.
Ha-ha!
That's fucking right.
Get predicted, bitch.
Oh, shit!
I forgot about you!
Never mind.
Oh, shit!
It's okay.
I still have this.
I might have used all my magic.
But it was worth it.
Guys, no.
I'm not gonna fight the dragon.
He doesn't even have an actual HP bar.
There's no point.
There's no point in fighting the dragon if he doesn't even have an HP bar, guys.
Alright.
Okay.
That's fine.
Whoa!
Watch this.
Sorry.
I meant...
Give me a sec.
Okay.
Watch this.
There we go.
Now that was cool, wasn't it?
That was pretty cool, wasn't it, guys?
That was pretty cool, guys.
Alright, nice.
I like that they give a lot, though.
Okay.
Jesus Christ.
They hit so hard.
They actually hit so fucking hard.
Still don't know where exactly I am.
Let's see.
We will go...
Doesn't ring a head?
That way?
But what about here?
What is here?
Whoa.
It's the outside item?
Where is...
Oh, it's over here.
Here!
Yay!
Oh, that's a hero's rune.
So there's more.
Oh, that's good.
And then try the lever.
Wait, where does the lever go?
Okay, I...
Okay, guys.
I need you guys to help me.
We put poor here.
Oh, fuck.
Wait, I think...
Yeah.
Okay, I rated it poor.
And then...
Remember to...
Alright, we're...
We're...
Where is it?
Be wary of liar.
And then appraise this message.
Alright.
And people will be like, Whoa, I can't believe there's...
I can't believe this guy lied.
Where is this area?
Where am I?
This area is fucking huge.
The wary of the left.
I don't even know if I'm like, going the right way, to be fair.
Okay, I just want to make sure there's nothing here.
It's pretty, though.
What is that?
Oh my god, it's them.
Wait.
Those are the...
The tree guys.
Oh!
Wait.
Aren't they the tree curse?
Isn't this the tree curse?
Oh my god.
It is.
I'm leaving.
No!
I couldn't...
I didn't even have time to fucking respond to it.
They killed me so fast.
I actually wanted to leave.
They killed me so fast that I couldn't even respond.
That's so fucked up.
How the fuck was I supposed to, like, play around that?
Okay, I need to get my shit back.
Alright.
Okay, remember to...
Uh...
Oh, nice.
Already.
Remember to rate this port.
I still see 12 appraisals.
I want that to go down to 1.
Alright.
Let's...
Let's get this elevator back.
And grab my runes real quick.
Okay.
Alright.
We're gonna...
Let's grab our stuff.
And then, like, leave.
I am...
I...
I'm not fighting this.
There's another path I can take.
Now, after...
After that guy...
Threw up some of those death...
Whatever the fuck they're called...
I leave.
The streamer build does not protect me from that.
Exactly.
Whoops.
Okay.
It's fine.
They're dead.
Wait, what the fuck?
Oh my...
What the fuck is hitting me?
Oh shit!
It's him!
You know magic.
You must die now, nerd.
All nerds must die!
Wait.
Is that multiple nerds?
Oh fuck!
Guys, it was apparently, uh, multiple nerds.
It was, uh...
I was not aware that there were multiple nerds out there.
Uh...
I was unaware...
Of the situation that I was in.
Oh my god.
Please.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, nice.
Alright.
That's fine.
Okay.
That's okay.
We gotta get our shit back.
Alright, this is fine.
Oh fuck, I used up all my magic.
Shit.
Oh shit.
It's fine.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, I got...
I got myself back.
It's fine.
It's so fine.
Light it, light it.
No, no, no.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Sit down, sit down, sit down, don't!
Okay, it's okay.
There.
We did it, we did it.
It's like nothing bad happened to me.
All right, nice.
Nice.
Sadness ahead.
Aww.
Poor guy.
Versions of friend.
It's not being a coward.
It's called bravely running away.
Okay, I could let... I could farm them a little bit.
Okay, that was supposed to... All right, that's fine.
That's fine.
I don't know why I couldn't backstab them, but that's okay.
Um... I bravely ran away.
I don't know why I didn't backstab, but that's okay.
We'll just... walk away.
Okay, I'll go this way.
And then... I guess we fall down?
Where are you supposed to go?
Seek ahead.
Here?
Wait, am I too sick?
Too sick.
I failed ahead.
No!
Whoa!
Okay, I almost ran off.
I'm too sick!
No!
It's okay, guys.
Today's my last day where I can eat unhealthy.
It actually is.
Today is my last day.
Praise that message.
Tomorrow is when I get my pre-cooked meals.
So today I'm gonna order pizza.
Oh shit, where did he come from?
What the fuck?
I was being sad about being sick, and then he showed up.
Today's the last day.
Today I'm gonna order pizza, too.
That's fucking right.
I know what I want.
My last day.
It's like my last...
It's like my prison meal.
Holy shit!
But yeah, it's like I'm fucking...
It's like my last meal.
My last meal.
Before I...
I'm gone.
That sounded so dark.
My final meal.
Alright.
Jesus Christ, you're fucking everywhere.
Alright, nice.
Alright.
At least they're like...
Sort of easy to kill.
There's just a lot of them.
Alright.
Get out of here.
Champion ahead?
Who's that?
Watch out ahead and then be wary of ambush.
Oh, I see him.
He's like all the way there.
Where's the ambush part?
What?
I don't know where the ambush part is.
Uh, time for a range battle?
Fuck that shit.
I'm just gonna walk away.
Like, why?
Why?
Why should I?
Oh, shit.
He might have been right.
Wait a minute.
Oh, that's right.
No more.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Never mind.
I was like, ha ha.
Oh, my God.
He has a friend.
There's no way.
There's no way they can't do this to me.
He has friends.
Okay.
Now I know where the prepare for the ambush came from.
Come on.
Okay.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha ha.
That's right.
Whoa.
That's fucking right.
Oh, that's not.
We're okay.
Ha ha ha.
Yes!
Wee wee.
Get out of here.
There we go.
Nice.
I'm gaming.
Oh, there's a grace here.
That's good.
I swear to god.
I was gonna say if I missed that jump, I swear to god.
Alright.
I could upgrade my weapon.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Is it in here?
I could.
Technically, yeah.
It's all possible.
It is possible.
I could do that.
Oh, I knew there was some...
Wait, can I... Oh, it's on the other side.
I... I was...
Honestly, I was like, it could happen to me.
I could just fall down that fucking hole.
That seemed like something Doki would do.
So are you going to?
What the fuck?
Where did he come from?
It's okay.
He can't go through this gap.
Guys, did you know he'd go through that?
Oh, shit.
This is down.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Okay.
I feel like a lot of people died to this guy.
Oh my god.
Let me grab this first.
Okay.
I think he knows I'm here.
I'm gonna backstab him.
Okay.
He has to turn around, right?
Come on, turn around.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Yeah, I can tell that he might be very strong just because of all of these, you know.
Are you serious?
That's not fair.
Ha ha ha.
It doesn't matter.
Ha ha ha ha.
That's right.
Doesn't matter.
Yeah.
Still got it.
There you go.
Still got my back shots.
Beware of left.
Oh my god.
There's more of them?
What the fuck?
What do you mean there's more of them?
Oh wait, that's a boss fight.
What if I just jump down?
Oh shit.
Ha ha ha.
That's a grid.
Ho ho ho.
Ho ho ho ho.
It's fucking right.
Oh fuck.
Maybe it's not fucking right.
Oh my god.
It's not okay.
Okay.
Guys, I'm trying to fight back.
I swear to god.
I am trying so hard to fight back.
Ha ha ha ha.
Oh my god.
This guy is so...
Okay.
That's good.
Oh my god.
It's fine.
Okay.
I still got it.
I got him.
It's okay.
Everything is fine.
I'll heal just in case.
Cause I say it's fine.
But like inside I...
Ho ho.
Oh my god.
Why is there so many of them?
Okay.
It's okay.
Everything is fine.
There's more?!
Alright.
We're running.
There's way too many of them.
That's...
That's too many.
What's this?
There's a summon here?
That means there's a boss fight here.
I'm gonna go level up then.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna go level up.
I'm not feeling it.
There's a gold summons here.
So that means there's a boss fight here.
Oh my god.
He's still chasing me.
Stop.
Oh my god.
He's so obsessed with me.
All right, let's...
Uh, need a lot of damage.
Is your armor under leveled?
Wait, is it... Can it be under leveled?
Are they not supposed to do that much damage?
Wait, not item crafting.
Uh, next thing they give us super chat.
Thank you.
You can't... Yeah, but I can put on better armor, right?
Wait, what's my... Okay, I need one more.
All right.
Let's see.
Uh...
How do we figure again?
I should get Radon's armor?
I mean, I could.
What do I be like?
I could and then I leave.
Oh, I get Slow Road, better armor.
Equip, like... Okay, I'll go level up my sword first, though.
Yeah, I can afford it now.
And then I need...
Let me go...
Pop my runes real quick.
Pop!
And then I'll pop that.
And then he's Sombra, Ancient, Dragon, Smithing Stone, which I definitely don't have.
I do have level six, though.
I can buy level six stone.
I think?
I'm not sure.
So we'll double check.
Oh, hey, item.
Who dropped this here?
Oh, nice.
Wait, someone died?
Wait, he's dead?
How did he die?
Who killed him?
Was there a murder in this table?
Who killed this man?
What?
Oh my god!
Wait,
she died too?
What the fuck?
A quest expired, so did he.
I'm not a murderer, right?
No, that can't be.
No, I'm not a murderer.
No, it can't be me.
No, there's no way.
No, oh my god.
Oh my god, who killed this guy?
Oh my god.
Why are there so many dead people here?
There's no way.
There's no witnesses.
No evidence that would put me on the scene of the crime.
A new drip though.
You're right.
You need a free armor.
Who did this?
Who could have done such a thing?
But he's alive?
Out of everyone, the shiteaters alive?
All right.
That's crazy that he's the only one that lives.
You want him dead too?
What the fuck?
Wait, was it six that I needed?
Oh, it was eight.
Whoops.
Um, and thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
That was not right.
Super chat.
Thank you for the rate.
Thank you.
Sorry.
Thank you for the rate.
All right.
I got a little frazzle there.
Because some people are calling me a murderer.
But I was not there at the scene of the crime.
I have an alibi.
I touched a maiden's hand unprotected.
And then, like, I fell asleep right after.
She said it was okay.
She said it's okay.
It can happen sometimes.
And, like, she was satisfied.
Oh, where is Roderica?
Thank you for the super chat, Sage.
Thank you.
All right.
Let's see.
That's 20.
Oh, is it worth it?
I feel like I could just farm the...
Yeah, I'll just farm the last...
Farm it.
Guys, we're gonna go to our favorite place.
Guys, I just need...
I don't...
We're gonna go to our favorite place.
I don't care if there's easier farming places.
We're back.
We're back to our favorite...
It's Groundhog Day!
We're back!
It's our favorite place, guys.
It's our favorite place.
Look.
It just works, okay?
See?
Look at that.
I got enough.
This is the best place to grind.
The more things change, the more they stay the same.
Alan, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Flashback of Pigfisting.
Look.
I know, like...
Is this the most efficient farming area?
Maybe not.
Is this the best farming area?
There's no butt here.
All right.
Nice.
That should be enough, right?
Yeah, that should be enough.
It was like a thousand or so.
Please just farm the birds.
What's the positives here?
We get to spend a longer time together.
Is that not what you want?
Yeah,
we needed to.
All right.
And then...
I think that's enough to upgrade.
We'll see.
All right.
Oh, my God.
I forgot we have to buy...
We have to level up a child, too.
I forgot about that.
Oh, yeah?
No, okay.
I don't have enough for it.
Wait, no.
It's two.
Okay, okay.
Maybe we do.
Okay, let's talk to how many...
We have to level up a child.
I forgot about her.
Ever since I've been...
Look, being a single parent is very hard.
Okay?
Don't worry, which is why I need your help persuading Master Hugh to leave.
His roots are so knotted in this place.
He won't last much longer if he stays here.
His shackles are broken.
He's a free man now.
It's high time he put the round table behind him.
Wait, what?
Okay.
I need six of those.
So, how much do I need?
All right.
I need...
I know...
Okay.
It's level six, right?
I have...
Do I have it?
Oh, I do.
It's...
It's this.
So...
Oh my god, they're so expensive.
Holy fuck.
Why is he...
Why is it so...
Okay.
Oh, talk to the smith again?
Talk to him.
I need one.
Okay.
Let's see.
Lay out your arms.
Why are you still making weapons?
As I've always said, you came to challenge the demigods and their god.
To slay them.
And as long as you do, I will always smith your weapons.
It is what I wish.
To smith a weapon for you to slay a god.
Yay!
I mean, that seems like a good...
He's here for me, guys.
Not for her.
For me.
All right.
So what is the easiest place to farm?
What is it?
If you guys can't give me a good answer, I'm going back to the catacombs.
All right.
I'll go back.
11k of bird.
Nor...
We don't have that, guys.
We don't have a nor...
Kaelin.
We don't have it.
Mog's place?
The fuck is Mog's place?
Marwan's palace?
Do I even have that?
Where is that?
What is that?
There's no palace here.
Oh, I've never been there.
All right.
What is the second best place?
Okay.
Where is the...
What is the...
I'm not going to kill the fucking dragon.
I know that dragon is going to...
It's going to fuck me up.
All right.
Why not?
I guess it's going to fuck me up.
What do you want?
Oh, you mean that dragon that's protected by 20 of her kids?
Yeah.
No, it's fine.
That dragon is going to take me 20 years.
It's a fucking slay.
It's fine.
Do it, you wuss.
It dies to bleed in three minutes.
Don't you have to, like, find, like, a perfect, like, location to do it?
Like, like, you have to position yourself in a way where, uh...
It's not even sleeping.
It's li- I like, I like, don't worry.
It's...
Isn't it, like, fucking paralyzed?
Like, it's like, you want me to beat up a paraplegic dragon.
That is fucked up.
That...
Bro, that dragon...
That dragon's li- Literally going through so much.
She's just old.
Yes.
Hahaha.
That's too far, Dookie.
Out of everything you've done, that's where you draw the line.
I have...
I have standards, okay?
I have standards here.
In front of our children?
But, Dookie, you're on your will.
That's since when?
This is where I draw the line.
Killing, um...
Killing someone that's clearly paralyzed in front of her children.
That's where I draw the line.
If she was, like, if she was able-bodied, then that's different.
If, if she was not suffering from a, from a, uh, from a disease, and was physically healthy, then that's different.
I, I would go for her.
But, like, because...
Yeah, that's, I have a high moral ground.
Hahaha.
Alright, let's see.
Let's buy.
Let's buy...
This one grave love word.
They can't watch if they're dead.
Next, thank you for the super chat thing.
Thank you.
Alright, let's upgrade her.
Upgrade this.
And then I need level 9, which I don't have.
Oh my monkey, thank you for the super chat thing.
Thank you.
Alright, uh, where was I for this area?
Is it here?
Dragon temple or crumbling?
Oh yeah, we'll try the dragon temple.
Yeah, I knew it was here.
I feel like I could just run past all of this, right?
Yeah.
Whoa.
There might be a lot to run past though.
Which is a little concerning.
Maybe they'll get tired.
Wait, what happened to the summon?
Wait.
Wow!
Wait a minute.
What happened to the summon?
Hello?
Oh, shit.
I thought I could...
I thought I could backstab you.
JK.
Is it still there?
Oh, it is.
Yes.
Alright, don't worry.
He'll help me.
Oh my god.
Don't worry.
You'll help me, right?
Oh my god.
Alright, that's fine.
He'll help me.
Oh my god.
I don't know if this is a good use of him.
I'm not so scared.
He's definitely dead, guys.
I think he's dead.
Why did this guy come f-
Oh my god.
How do I...
There has to be a...
There has to be an easier way.
There's no way.
That's it.
I'm just gonna do this.
Like, g- Fuck this.
Okay.
I'll just do this.
This is actually easier.
Like, this is actually easy.
This is fine.
This is so fine.
This is actually easier.
Alright.
We'll just wait.
Is it death counter?
I think it is.
We'll fix it later.
Just run.
Just keep running.
Is he still there?
But he's not there anymore.
Oh, he's still there.
Okay.
Nice.
Oh, shit.
It's these guys.
I didn't summon him.
Oh, my God.
I forgot to wait for them to get summoned.
Oh, shit.
Not these guys.
I forgot to wait for my guy to get summoned before I show up.
It's okay.
I know all about you.
That's right.
I've heard so much about these guys.
Look at me go.
I'm not cheesing it.
I'm not using that stupid sleep cheese.
Look at me.
I'm a fucking real gamer.
That's right.
I'm doing that the legit way.
Okay.
You guys gotta give me like a little high five though.
I didn't suck.
I didn't do the abuse tech though for this.
Let me go.
I'm fighting him legitly.
All right.
I think this is fine.
Wait, what?
Oh, my God.
Okay.
Now I know why they...
Never mind.
Now I know why people did not fight them legitly.
Now I know.
Never mind.
Now I know why they sleep them.
Now I know why.
I took...
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I...
Oh, now I know.
Now...
Now I know.
I thought...
After they die...
That, you know...
I don't have to worry about it anymore.
But clearly, I was wrong.
I'll just kill this guy first.
And then I'll run past.
Let's see.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
That's bullshit.
That's bullshit!
Oh, my God.
Let me at you.
Let me go around!
Oh, my God.
Never mind.
I don't want to fight them anymore.
I'm leaving.
Oh, wait.
I can't leave.
Oh, my God.
That's fine.
I'm gonna grab my shit.
I'm leaving.
Wait.
I gotta summon though.
I gotta summon.
No, guys.
Guys, you don't understand.
I gotta summon them.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
No.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Please.
Please show up.
Oh, my God!
Where is he?!
Where are you?
Where is he?
I swear to God.
I'm trying to summon him.
Please show up.
Please.
I didn't stay in place.
Oh my God.
That's so bullshit.
I didn't need it.
I didn't need to stay in place.
He was there.
Who
said I needed to stay in place?
Who fucking... Who fucking said I needed to stay in place?
That's it.
I'm banning you.
When there's no more guy, I can never get one guy.
I'll find you.
I... Oh, the D-Zone.
I see you.
That's right.
Any last messages, Mr. D-Zone?
Don't think you stay silent.
I won't let it.
Chad.
She said my name.
07.
That's it.
Put user in timeout.
24 hours.
Can't get one guy if he's in timeout.
Down he goes.
Why are you blaming your death honor?
He's no random anymore.
He... Not D-Zone.
Alright.
It's fine.
Apparently there's an easier grace, but it's fine.
I've committed my sins.
Oh shit.
Holy shit.
Oh my...
Oh no!
Oh my god!
Go in!
You're coming in here now!
Come in here!
Stop fighting them!
He's supposed to come in here!
I thought he would show up!
Why is he not- Why is he not in here?!
I thought he was like... I don't know.
I thought he would come in here with me.
Like, I don't know.
I...
He died!
He died before he could even come in here!
Oh my god!
I already died with a bomb!
I... I... I don't know.
I thought he would... I thought he would show up.
I saw him and I were cool like that, you know?
So, I legit thought we were... he and I were cool like that.
How was I supposed to know he can just die?
I thought he and I would be cool like that.
That's fine.
I can't fight him before I can...
Oh my god, never mind.
I cannot.
Why did you abandon him, bro?
Now you know what for him he died for you.
Alright, where is the closer Grace?
Alright, let's find the Grace that's closer.
So, about the other Grace...
So... so where is the other...
The other Grace?
Go west.
Alright.
Like here?
Right there?
Alright, I'm gonna pick up this item first.
OUGH!
Cool.
That's... alright.
That's... fine.
I had nothing anyway.
I... I had... oh wait, the counter works now.
I'm not counting.
That's...
That's fine.
I had nothing anyway.
In my life.
Okay.
That's fine.
We can... make this jump now.
It's alright.
It's okay.
This fucker.
This actual fucker.
It's okay.
Oh...
My god.
Get out of here.
Get your ass out of here.
Get your ass out of my lobby!
Fucking get out!
Get out!
What did I get from that?
Okay, that item is worth it.
The item is worth it, guys.
Can I jump here?
Do I live?
Okay, nice.
I do.
Try left.
Why?
Wait, do I go right or left?
Where's the grace?
Where the fuck is that grace?
What is this?
No clue?
Do I just go straight here?
In...
In that area?
In this area?
Okay.
Oh my god.
Wait.
Why would I be here?
How is this closer?
Oh, there it is.
Oh, there is a grace here.
How would this place be closer?
I don't understand.
Oh!
But my summons!
Oh, he's over here.
Oh, there he is.
There you go.
My summons.
Yay!
It's like, what about my summons?
Oh, he's here.
It's okay.
He's right here, guys.
Yay!
Hey!
Alright.
Time.
This time, we got this.
Ring, ring, ring!
Oh my god.
Okay, that's awkward.
But this time, this time, it'll be fine.
Oh my god.
I don't feel so good.
I don't feel so good, actually.
Yeah.
Okay.
It's fine.
You get him, I'll get him.
I'll get the one...
Never mind.
Okay.
Okay, now I know exactly what...
I was not healthy.
Okay.
Okay, I know what to do now.
Did you get him?
Um...
Okay, I know what to do now, guys.
Okay, now I know why...
Guys, now I know why...
People sleep...
Sleep him.
And why people do the cheese strap for this...
For this.
Now I understand.
Put him closer to them, so it's like scarier.
Oh my god, they're just wailing on them.
Okay.
I'll separate them.
Oh my god.
Okay, it's fine.
Oh my god, why do I get him?
Why do I get him?
That's the separation!
I wanted a skinny man!
There we go.
Okay.
Okay, it's fine.
It's fine.
I can do...
One more swing!
Nice.
And then I'll do a heal here.
Okay.
Oh no.
Oh no, he's rolling.
He's rolling.
Oh fuck!
Yeah!
Why me!
Okay.
It's fine.
I can do...
One more swing!
Nice.
And then I'll do a heal here.
And then...
Slam!
Oh shit!
Oh!
I missed it!
I was not fast enough!
I was not fast enough for the Slam!
It's okay.
We're heroes.
You and...
That means there's one more.
I remember.
I killed a skinny man first, so he's less scary.
Oh my god!
That's not...
Wait!
It's the last one?!
Okay.
Clearly I was wrong.
Alright.
I thought, you know, it would be like the first one you kill.
But I was wrong.
Okay.
Oh my god!
I missed it!
It's okay!
We don't need critical hits!
Where we're from!
It's okay!
We don't need that!
We're good enough without it!
Oh my god!
Why?!
We don't need it still!
We don't need critical hits!
Where we're from!
We're gangster like that!
Low-key carrying?!
I was the...
Oh shit!
Um, excuse me!
I summoned him!
I did it!
Let's go!
Guys!
Oh my god!
We're gaming!
We're so good!
Sorry!
I'm so good!
I...
Look at that guys!
I didn't use the, uh...
The sleep cheese!
Okay?
I...
I didn't use the sleep cheese!
All...
Me...
Roll into you with my thousand kg body!
Uh...
Thank you for the super chat!
Thank you!
Alright!
Okay guys!
What do we level up?
We can level up two times here!
While you guys decide, I'm gonna use the bathroom!
I'll be back!
How do I bring these own back guys?
Quick!
What is this?
A mutiny from my own mods?
Maybe you wanna know what it's like to be a regular dragoon?
Silence!
Why...
Do you wanna be back with the...
Back with...
To be one of them?
Do...
Do you...
What if...
If you like D-zone so much?
Maybe...
You should be there with him!
No more power for you!
I'm silent!
No!
Sound guy!
Got you!
Oh yeah?
You wanna fight with Silent?
Who wants Silent's position?
By being with him!
You are...
Are you sure you're Silent?
Don't you want the...
Don't you also wanna be a mod too?
Let me take...
I'll take it!
We are Silent!
By having someone demoted...
Someone has to be promoted too!
Maybe he was really Silent...
This would ha...
Wouldn't have happened...
Exactly!
There you go!
Fight with the bourgeoisie!
Next scene!
Thank you for the super chat!
Thank you!
Lord Kurosis!
You can...
Buy...
My...
Silence!
Sorry!
Thank you for the super chat!
Thank you!
Shout out to my goat!
Oh!
I guess you did alright too!
Doki!
Alright!
What are we getting?
Bigger and endurance!
Okay!
Maybe the real Silent was the friends we all made...
We made all along the way!
Slips 5 bucks under the Silent interview table!
Thank you for the super chat, Mehdi!
Thank you!
Alright!
What is all of this?
Offer...
Rump...
Where?
Haha!
Where is it?
First off, well done!
Where do I go after this?
Maybe it's like this way?
Wait, where do I go after being the boss?
I'm so confused!
Here?
Go down?
I mean, it would make sense, right?
I mean, there is like...
A thing over there!
Shortcut ahead?
Yeah?
Whoa!
Oh my god!
That's lead!
No!
That's electricity!
Okay!
I'm gonna kill him before he kills me!
Nice!
Yeah!
What?
Detected the shortcut?
Question mark?
Oh shit!
Dog!
Okay, I don't trust myself with a dog.
In Elden Ring.
Okay?
Not fair!
Hahaha!
Dad!
You're like, Dad?
Hahaha!
That's right!
Alright!
Alright, I'm opening interviews to repla- Uh, not re- Hahaha!
To replace silent breakbeat!
Hahaha!
No loyalty deserves a demotion!
Behold, Elden Ring!
If everything is Elden Ring, then what is not Elden Ring?
I'll do it!
Alright!
Show me how loyal you are!
The most loyal- The most loyal- The most loyal- Will take his mod plays.
Then he can be with D-zone.
Hahaha!
Mod on mod crap!
That's what you get!
For trying to fight for one guy!
That's right!
Think again when you try to fight for one guy!
Where the fuck am I going?
Pretty near...
There?
Many guys should fight for the one guy!
Oh shit!
That's fine, I think- Yeah, I was gonna say.
I knew I could tank that.
Yeah, but there's- There's an upper too!
There's an item!
Yay, item!
What's that over there?
Is that another item?
Behold, turn back!
Okay.
He fought the law and the law won!
Exactly!
We all need a rem- I need to make an example today!
Today, I make an example of someone that thought he was- He was- He was- Who big for the law, But he forgot- I am the law!
He thought I didn't reach that.
That's right.
He chose the wrong day!
No man, it is- It is that time of the- That's right!
He chose the wrong day to fight against the law!
Hah, hahahaha!
If it was any other day!
Nah,
wording- This guy?
Okay, but like... I thought there was another grace here.
Where the fuck is the grace?
Oh, it's on the right side?
Like this right?
No, that's a dog.
Wait, that's a dog.
Oh, down to the right.
Oh, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
If I hug the wall, you can't see me.
Oh, he's sleeping.
Me me me me me me me me me me me me me me.
Okay.
Don't calm down.
Alright, nice.
Any final words?
Silent break beat?
Don't think I forgot.
Just because I was trying to find the grace.
Are the bloodstains these?
A bird?
He died to a fucking bird?
Loser.
Oh my god, there's more than one bird!
Alright, there you go.
Brother.
Hey, what's that?
Wait, that's a dragon.
Oh my god, he did not die to one bird.
Wait, where's the lever?
Oh my god.
D zone and I want you to time him out again.
That's right.
I'm gonna unban D zone and I want you to do it.
I want you to do it yourself.
That's fine.
This gives me time.
That's evil.
That's right.
No, that's good.
I die.
I can see.
That's so evil.
That's right.
Alright, where is he?
Alright, let me untie him out real quick, guys.
Don't worry, I remember how to do this.
That's so messed up.
That gives me plenty of time to do this.
Alright, let's see.
Let me find your name real quick, Deezer.
So I can do this.
Wait, where are you?
Oh my god.
That was a ring changer.
Community moderation.
Alright.
Where is my...
Where is my timeout section?
Okay.
How to un...
How do I untime out someone in YouTube?
Okay, how do I undo a timeout?
Oh, shit.
There's no way to undo a timeout.
They wouldn't show up.
Alright.
If I ever see him...
You're so lucky.
Alright.
If I ever see...
If we ever see him again...
If I ever see him again...
Your job...
Silent...
Is to time him out another 24 hours.
Say...
YouTube does not support your...
Alright!
No!
I got someone!
Alright!
Where is he?
Grass Spirit One!
That's right!
You think...
You!
Alright!
Do it!
Break beat!
To grass!
Right now!
I'm waiting.
I'll grab someone else.
None shall be spared.
That's right.
Come on.
Come on, BrickBeak.
Do it.
I'm going to get out of here.
Goodbye.
There we go.
Look at that.
Things people do to keep their mind.
Remember when you all stood up for a silent BrickBeak.
Look how quick he did.
Look how quick he was to turn on you.
Look how quick it was.
How could you.
You all fought for this man.
And he instantly timed out someone after I told him to.
You are a monster.
You are the chosen one.
Look at that.
You fought for him.
And he instantly banned one of your people.
Remember that.
The next time you try to fight for someone.
He had to follow orders.
Oh, shit.
I need to grab my swords back.
Wherever they are.
Oh, shit.
Where is it?
Are they anyway?
Oh, there it is.
We live in a house of lies.
Grass always grows back.
Mr. Broken Bot.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
That's right.
What did you learn today, chat?
Never trust anybody.
Not even the law is there for you.
Oh my god.
Can I run past this guy?
Toki, we learned today that Toki is evil.
What the fuck did I do?
I just showed you the truth.
The fight against evil.
You know what?
Toki, you too.
You too.
I want you to time out.
That's right.
I'm getting you involved too.
Don't think you're innocent.
I'm covering your hands with blood.
You too.
You too will have your hands covered in blood.
Toki, what the hell?
No one's safe.
Leave him out of this.
Not my crochet.
How could he?
Everyone's getting their blood dirty today.
No one is safe.
You thought these mods were one of you.
They're not one of you.
Don't betray you the moment I tell them to.
So think that again when you try to stand up for them.
You won't get away with this Toki.
Alright, let's fight this guy.
Okay, we gotta get rid of him.
Oh my god!
It's fine.
It is not fine.
Okay.
It's okay.
It's not okay.
It's...
We were so far away!
We're so far away.
If Toki is evil, I don't wanna be good.
Actually, thank you for the super chat.
Who said that?
That's what you get?
Alright, that's it.
You see who I'm seeing, Kroki?
Do it.
It's time to time him out.
Come on.
Do it, Kroki.
Leave him alone!
When will she stop?
Like 50 people.
Alright.
I remember your name.
Don't think you...
Oh!
Nice, alright.
That's right.
Look at that.
I told you.
No one is safe.
None of these mods are there for you.
Thank you.
This is abuse.
Alright.
Let's figure out.
Okay.
We gotta run past all of this again.
Alright.
Should I do this again?
One more.
Silently!
Okay.
I'm not reading all that.
You know what to do.
My next death.
It's your turn.
It'll be your turn next.
Alright.
Here I go.
Women doji is scary.
You picked the wrong day.
Oh no.
Alright.
Okay.
Let's just get him out of the way first.
Fuck this guy in particular.
Oh shit.
Oh wait.
They're all sleeping.
Okay.
Maybe I shouldn't.
I didn't even realize they were all sleeping.
Alright.
Let's get him out.
And then...
Oh shit.
What the fuck?
I don't remember all of these guys from before.
Just...
Okay.
Let's get him...
I'm gonna use my...
Magic here.
And then I can go up here.
Okay.
That's...
Oh my god.
I didn't realize it was a fucking boomerang.
Get out of here.
And then...
Then I'll pick this up.
Does anyone wanna volunteer?
I will not choose you.
Jumping ahead?
Then?
That...
That's a lie.
Okay.
Is it actually?
No, that's like a minibus, right?
Like...
Where's the grace?
No, it's true.
But where's the grace though?
That's the thing.
Yeah, but I wanna find the grace.
Nearby?
Okay.
Inside.
Okay, it's in here.
Okay.
I just gotta figure out how to fucking fight this.
I'm gonna fight this guy first.
I just wanna get him out of here.
So then I can fight this guy.
Alright, nice.
Okay, he's dead too.
Alright.
This has to be a grace here.
Okay, that's fine.
Oh my god.
No!
That's fine.
Woo!
Not fine, not fine.
I don't know why I didn't heal.
Are you serious?
Okay, nice.
Oh, fuck.
Okay, I should not have tanked that.
But...
I can win this.
Okay, nice.
I knew I could win that.
I knew I could win if I tank it.
Ooh.
Nice, there is a grace here.
Alright.
Because I found it.
Oh, wait.
I can lull up.
Nice.
I'm gonna go get the...
figure, actually.
Alright.
Since I have a grace, we can do the execution now.
Who...
Hmm.
It is time.
That's one hell of a sentence.
Alright.
Let's see it.
Women aren't that scary.
Women under the blood moon.
Solid snake.
Thank you in the super chat.
Thank you.
Alright.
Scatter.
Alright, let's see.
I'm scrolling up.
We stand as one.
Let's see.
Hmm.
Behind you.
Rob span.
Grace is on.
Okay, people are saying good things.
You know?
Look at that.
See?
Executing people live on stream.
Could be a good thing.
Look at that.
Everyone is so nice to me now in chat.
Wow.
Oh.
Everyone is so nice to me now.
Neat.
Yeah, isn't that neat?
Isn't that...
I fear nothing.
Alright.
You know what?
Silently.
Pick one.
Whichever one you want.
You all need to...
You all gotta have blood on your hands.
Pick one.
Time out one person of your choosing.
Don't worry.
I will know when you did it.
You can't get us.
Yeah.
Pick one.
It's your turn.
It's all...
The responsibility is on your hands.
Their blood...
Is on your hands too.
Because I didn't pick the person.
You did.
It's okay.
Just pick me.
Who did you pick?
Oh.
Goodbye, Orca.
Goodbye.
Orca has been slain.
Alright.
Let's move on.
Let's move.
I didn't pick it.
I didn't pick anybody.
Now all the mods have blood on their hands.
Remember.
This was someone you guys protected.
At one point.
What lesson did we learn today, chat?
Try parrying?
Wait.
Is he a...
Is he like...
Wait.
Wait a minute.
I didn't level up.
I just realized.
Alright.
Give me a sec.
Hello.
Where is it?
Its my soul.
Is my soul like...
Where is it?
Wait.
Where is my...
Oh there it is?
Okay, I can still level up.
I can still level up.
It's fine.
I agree.
We still have... we can still level up.
It's Asian thinking with a super sickest thing.
Thank you.
Karma swift like lightning and just as shocking.
Apoc, thank you in the super chat.
Thank you.
Star Ace, thank you in the super chat.
Draco is the age of Doki is over.
No more false prophets.
Follow me and you'll never be deceived again.
Wow, guys.
Did you guys hear something?
Did you guys...
Give me a sec... Let me...
Also...
Do this real quick.
Let me...
Wow!
Just the wind.
Just...
The wind.
It was a deafening process.
Nothing happened.
I have to kill him?
Oh my...
Just the wind.
Say no.
It's tyranny.
All you hear is me.
It's just a wind.
Only Doki.
Do I have to kill him?
I feel like I don't have to.
Damn, this hurricane is so loud.
Guys.
Wow.
Oh, he's optional?
Okay.
That's good to know.
I'm running.
Alright.
Let's grab the stuff and leave.
Oh, killing him is easy...
Would make it easier?
Alright.
If killing him would make it easy, I'll do it.
I don't remember how to kill these guys.
I...
I swear to...
Okay.
Does he respawn though?
If I kill him?
Does he respawn?
I hope you lose all your...
You know what's funny?
Star was only timed out for 10 seconds.
But I don't see...
He's scared now.
Star, come on.
Speak up, Star.
Come on.
You were only gone.
It was only a 10 second time out.
Why are you so scared, Star?
What?
Star, dude.
You were the wrong time.
Oh, he's back.
Oh, he's back, guys.
Please.
Oh, you were scared.
The psychological warfare.
Jesus Christ!
Okay, this guy is hard.
She got the media monopoly.
Alright, it's fine.
I can do this.
Jingle, jingle.
Jingle.
The tension in this room.
Jingle, jingle.
Alright, we gotta grab her.
Actually, I don't really care too much about these runes because they're like...
Jesus Christ!
He does so much damage.
Okay, I actually have to...
God damn it!
You know what?
Yeah, AK is not worth it.
I'm just gonna...
AK is definitely not worth it.
Sweet justice.
Alright.
Yeah, I'm gonna skip it.
Is it actually worth it?
Okay.
Guys, I know like I executed a lot of you, but like it's time to do the streamer...
Guys, come on.
It's time for the...
It's time for the streamer field, guys.
It's...
It's time.
It's time for the streamer field.
Come on, guys.
No help.
Come on, this entire field requires...
Teamwork.
We're a team, guys.
We're a team.
What did you say?
The wind is too loud.
Oh, fuck.
Where the fuck let this horse be fire?
Jesus Christ, he has so much HP.
After the execution, morale is low.
Oh, no.
Don't worry.
I know what to do to raise morale, guys.
Guys.
I know what to do.
To raise morale.
I...
Guys.
It's okay.
Don't worry.
I know morale is very low right now.
But I know exactly what to do.
I...
I know what to do.
To raise all your morale.
Alright.
Where is it here?
It works every time.
It works 100% of the time.
But I'll add something extra.
For the occasion.
For the special occasion.
There we go.
Now...
Alright, dragoons.
Here are the messages.
Here are the...
We busted.
First off...
Here we go.
Head.
Right here.
Alright.
Hold the line.
And then...
Alright.
Here's another one.
All is forgiven, right?
Um...
No.
You monster.
Alright.
Head required.
A head.
Alright.
Now dragoons.
We all know what to do now.
Right?
What does a good dragoon do?
Guys.
What does...
We appraise...
My messages.
Okay?
Is that clear drag?
You appraise...
Doki's messages.
Right here.
Where?
Or I take this away.
That's right.
We're clear now.
We're...
We're clear.
That's right.
We understand now.
We understand.
That's good.
I'm glad we all have an understanding.
Brother!
Don't let this heretic get to you!
Just like my Warhammer.
I'm sorry, y'all.
I have to go siren, y'all.
Oh, shit!
Guys, guys, where are my appraisers?
Guys, guys, where...
Where were my appraisals, guys?
And you know, Mehdi is out here ready to prize despite having been tagged out.
What a loyal, weak-willed Dragoo.
Alright.
It's okay, it's just...
The wind was just too loud, right?
The wind was just too loud, right, guys?
Oh, shit.
Okay, let's just...
I'm gonna...
Oh, my God.
Oh, my...
Nice.
Alright, nice.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
I knew...
I knew what to do.
Okay, it's good to know.
Shit.
Okay, nice lead.
Alright.
Don't upgrade.
It's too late.
I always have a backup.
I told you I know what to do to raise morale.
I told you.
Oh, shit.
Okay, that's fine.
Okay.
Trying to focus right now.
Nice.
It's definitely raised.
I told you guys, I know exactly what to do.
Don't worry.
Man, there's always a backup plan.
Holy fuck, what the fuck?
This guy does so much.
I'm like, sorry I'm knowing a pattern, but also, Jesus Christ.
Okay.
And then one hit here.
And then I have to do that.
And then that here.
And then recharge.
And then...
Oh my god, I should have to focus so much.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Fuck.
Okay, that's fine.
I have one more heal.
Shit.
I didn't think he'd do that.
God damn it.
Are you serious?
That hits me?
Oh no, I don't think I'm winning this.
I'm not winning this.
No!
So close!
I'm so close!
All hail Doki.
She speaks and we obey.
Ramona.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Doki uses Jingle Jangle.
It's super effective.
And thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
It's alright guys.
I raised morale in Doki Nation.
In the Dragoon community, morale has been raised.
I told you guys I know what to do.
I told you.
Alright.
Nice.
I have to bleed out.
No!
It won't work on me.
Somehow, yes.
Alright.
The greed.
I greed it too much.
I was waiting.
Your false tricks won't work on me.
You tyrant bird.
I control the media.
It's over for all of you.
It's...
Jingle Jangle.
Oh my god.
I missed that.
I don't really mind losing.
Yeah, I'm not gonna pick up the runes.
Like, I don't care about the runes enough.
Oh!
I greed it!
Can we appraise the sentinel?
Jingle Jangle!
Okay.
Wait.
Alright.
Don't worry.
I'll add one more.
Here we go.
For the one siren.
Still...
For the true warriors out there.
Alright.
Hold the light.
Okay, I got...
I'm gonna try and focus.
Alright, I'm locking in.
This guy, I actually have to focus.
I can't fuck around.
I have a rebellion right now, so I can't...
My streamer build is not as effective.
There's a rebellion going on.
So...
My usual build is not as effective.
But don't worry.
Don't worry.
It'll be fine.
Some dragoons are having a strike right now.
But don't worry, I can fix that soon.
Alright.
Oh shit.
Okay.
Okay, nice.
Alright.
Oh my, that's fine.
That's okay.
I have to heal.
I knew I was gonna get hit.
Are you serious?
Oh, I didn't know where to roll.
I...
Okay, you got me.
I'm sorry, my queen, for my past transgression.
You have my full support.
Look for it.
Alright, guys.
Look.
Look, I'm gonna say it.
If you want me...
To bring it back...
Doesn't come for free.
So stop your foolish rebellion.
Or there will be no more...
Jingle jangle.
Traded.
It's time to stop your rebellion.
Unless you want...
Unless there's no more jingle jangle.
You monster.
Come on, where's my appraisal?
Give me one appraisal, so I know we all agree.
Come on.
Give me that one appraisal, so I know we're all on the same...
That's right.
I was not here.
Bro.
Alright.
We're all on the same page.
That's good to know.
I'm glad we're all on the same page, though.
Good.
We all know.
No.
Nice.
Okay.
Okay, I just need to heal here.
Alright.
Bro, this guy is so fucking hard.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, I thought...
Oh my god, I thought he was gonna use the...
Lighting, but...
Oh shit.
No!
That hit does so much damage!
What?!
That did so much damage!
Oh my god.
I did not expect that.
Alright.
Deserve.
I'm always loyal, Doki.
I served you in the old wars, and I'll serve again.
Raxi, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
I know I can like...
Eh.
I know I can...
What?!
Okay, never mind.
Apparently not.
I was gonna say, I know I can like, dodge that, but...
Eh?
Jesus Christ!
Are you serious?!
What?!
Eh.
I actually have to full focus here.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Got heal.
Nice.
Eh.
Okay.
I need to like, not be too greedy too.
What?!
That...
That hits me?!
That should not have hit me.
That...
That should not have hit me!
Are you serious?!
I was doing...
My dodges were...
So good!
My dodges were so good!
Aww!
Those...
Those were some good dodges too.
Okay.
Alright, I'm full focusing for this.
I'm full focus.
No, I can do this.
I can do this.
Alright.
Are you serious?
Okay.
I fucked up the dodge there.
Oh my god.
This is not the run.
Nevermind.
This is not the...
This is not the focus run!
This was not it!
This was not the focus run!
Okay.
Now!
Now is the focus run!
Go ahead.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
I've been playing Rivals for rank.
What did I come back to?
A failed re...
A failed rebellion.
But don't worry.
We're okay now.
Morale has risen.
Just a little rebellion that I had to...
Crush.
Did I...
Didn't bleed?
I can't tell if I didn't bleed.
Shit.
Oh fuck.
Wrong time to heal.
Okay.
Now I can.
Are you serious again?
Three fireballs?
Oh.
I need to remember not to...
Sweat there.
Yeah.
What?!
Dodged that!
Oh, the blind dragoons.
She needs to learn!
Oh my god.
The attack was so delayed.
It was super delayed.
But I'm getting better though.
Every attempt.
The guy knows.
He knows what I wanna do.
We don't need you.
You need a tyrant.
Come on.
Don't you guys miss the jingle jingle guys?
Oh shit.
Okay.
Nice bleed.
Are you serious?
Oh my god.
I thought he would like...
I thought he would stumble more.
But he didn't.
Uh...
Delay a little bit more.
I thought he would like...
Uh...
Delay a little bit more.
Okay.
I know he wants to do one more attack too.
Yeah.
No not the delay!
Oh nice!
I hate that one.
Okay.
Time that.
Nice.
There's, like, so little room for this.
Are you serious?
Oh!
There's, like, so little room to fucking hit him!
Twice?
He did that twice!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
That one was bullshit!
That one was actually bullshit.
Holy shit.
I still... Oh, my God.
That was bullshit.
Appraise!
Message appraise!
Nice.
Haha.
Oh, no.
NOOO!
I didn't know where to go.
Message appraise!
Come on!
You serious?
Fucking hell.
Nice.
Okay.
Are you serious?
That hit me?
Guys, it's message appraise time.
Message appraise!
Oh, my God.
Okay.
That's good.
No, not the...
No!
Fuck!
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
The fireball!
God!
Not the fire...
I missed it.
Please show me again.
More fall.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
That was...
I would admit...
I got greedy there.
Nice.
Jesus.
Okay, that was deserved.
And not Mina.
God damn it.
I'm actually focusing so hard for these, this one.
What?
Okay, that should not hit me though.
That one should not hit me there.
Okay!
Alright!
That should have been a dodge!
That was a dodge!
That was a fucking dodge!
Hold the line!
Deserve!
That was bullshit.
That was fucking bullshit.
It's optional, but, fuck it.
I mean, at least I'll get like, I'll get like, uh, runes for it.
Oh, man.
In the end, it's just like, you get- I'll just play better.
Doing this.
Okay, not right now, obviously.
Okay, nevermind.
Now!
After this, I'll play better.
After this.
I'll play better.
After this, I'll play better.
Okay.
Now reward myself with some pizza later.
We'll bring Jingle Jangle back after we defeated him.
Then the Dragoons get their reward.
And boost morale.
Doesn't come for free, guys!
Yeah.
She's lying to you, chat!
Guys!
You guys appraise!
We'll get our Jingle Jangle back!
Jesus Christ!
Are you serious?
That's right.
Oh, fuck.
Sometimes I don't know, like, which one is the... Because there's, like, that attack sometimes... That!
Okay, that was a good dodge for it, too.
That was bullshit.
That was actually a good dodge.
Oh, my god.
I hate these delay attacks.
These delay attacks are so bullshit.
The horse shouldn't even be part of this.
The horse shouldn't be part of these attacks.
That's not fair.
If I...
can't have my jellyfish, his horse should not be blowing fire.
That's all I'm saying.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
Are you serious?
Oh!
My bad.
Are you one?
Okay, that's bullshit.
That one was bullshit.
Oh, my god.
Okay, that was green.
That was...
That was green!
I greeted that.
I greeted that so hard.
I was like, do I dodge or do I hit?
And I was like, no, I'll hit that.
I knew... I knew it was green, too.
I knew instantly.
I greeted too hard.
I knew it was green.
Alright, it's fine.
It's fine.
Okay.
Oh, my god.
Okay, that...
I'm gonna, like, knock me dead sometimes.
Oh, fuck.
It's fine.
Okay.
And then he's gonna do one more.
I'm, like, trying to remember patterns now.
Okay, I'll do one more hit.
Oh, no.
Okay.
Okay, we got...
Get out of here.
Got it.
Oh, we got out of there.
Alright.
That.
Okay.
God damn it.
Okay, nice.
It's not...
Oh, I'm so locked in.
Not this one.
Not...
Oh, god.
That one...
That one is my...
That...
That one is so bullshit!
That attack is so bullshit.
That is such a bullshit attack.
Oh, my god.
I hate that attack the most.
Fuck you.
Oh.
No, no.
Ah, I dodged too early.
I knew I dodged too early, too.
Okay.
Oh, my god.
Come on.
I dodged that.
I dodged that one.
No!
Fuck!
I knew...
I was gonna do that, too.
No!
Not that fucking delayed attack!
Okay.
Alright.
You serious?
You bitch!
Oh!
Greed.
My fucking greed.
Okay.
Nice.
Fucker, you fucker, you fucker, you fucker, you fucker, you fucker, you fucker, you fucker.
Alright.
I hate this attack so much.
No, no, no, no, no!
Not this one!
Oh!
No!
I fucking knew it!
Every time.
No, it's the one that, like, it's...
Oh, my god.
It's the...
The one I hate the most is the one where he delays it and has so much AoE.
Because it's so hard to dodge.
In general.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
Oh, nice.
I know I didn't hit it, but I'd rather just not take damage from that attack.
Really?
That hits me?
Oh.
Okay.
This one's this one.
I hate this one.
And this one, too.
I don't know what to do for that.
I don't know how to dodge that one.
Oh, my god.
Come on.
I actually don't know how to dodge that one.
I have to roll into it.
Okay.
Are you serious?
Oh.
Sucks.
No, no, no, no, no.
No.
Yes!
I did it!
Oh, my god!
Oh!
28,000!
That's fucking whatever.
Whatever.
A win's a win.
28,000.
That's it.
I'm becoming him.
All right.
Just because I promise to raise morale.
To raise morale.
I shall also become him.
All right.
Oh, what is it?
Is it this one?
Is this one, right?
I am him now.
Oh, shit.
My rolls are so tanky.
All right.
Wait.
Maybe we gotta...
Okay.
We have to take some off.
I cannot be...
I'm sorry.
Like, this is little...
Okay.
There we go.
We gotta take that.
Okay.
It's fine.
We're half of him.
All right.
It's fine.
Now we're fine.
All right.
Toward myself.
I'm half of him.
I'm...
Many, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
More falls.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
We have successfully raised morale.
We have...
Rebellion has been quenched.
All hail Doki Bird.
Phrase the mighty Doki Bird.
She graces us.
Swordsman.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
All right.
We're gonna call it here.
I just said today was a short stream today.
And, um, so I'm gonna call it here, everyone.
So my voice can, my voice can recover.
Because we had a lot of streams, a lot of long streams today.
But, I hope you guys had a fun time today with me.
Um, to all my loyal dragoons.
To all my dragoon scabs out there who, um, didn't listen to the false prophets and the fake news.
And the, and, and, and followed the law of Doki Bird and praised my messages.
To my loyal fans.
I hope you guys had a fun time, everyone.
As, I'm gonna go head off now.
I'm gonna order my pizza!
I'm gonna order my pizza.
Because I have no, no super chat reading today.
But, I still hope you guys had a lot of fun with me, uh, for today's Elden Ring streams.
Um, as always everybody, stay hydrated, posture check, get up and move around to get that blood flowing.
And if you, except for me, head to bed.
Cause, you deserve it.
I'll see you guys next time, everybody.
Bye, guys!
Bye!