Remember what it is.
Hold on, let me go to Twitch.
Alright, I'm inviting friends right now.
Um... Okay.
Wait, I went straight in live.
No intro.
Oh my god, wait!
Someone's streaming!
Oh my god, sorry.
No intro.
Either way, I've been live this whole time.
This is me, Laimu.
What did you say?
It's a real account, I promise.
Super real, totally legit.
Oh, you sent the thing.
Yeah, I sent it.
Oh wait, it says invited you, but it doesn't show up.
Like, there's no, like, join.
There's no join?
Yeah.
Can you join my lobby just through this thing?
I'll see if I can.
It says you're playing VTube Studio.
Oh, exactly.
Wait, how do you change how you don't run the non-Steam version of VTube Studio?
I do run without Steam.
No, I run without Steam.
But instead it tells me that I'm playing VBridger.
Oh, yes.
Oh, I didn't know you could do it without Steam.
Yeah, I know you can.
It's very less performance intensive.
You have to do it, like, on the...
You can do it for VBridger too.
Yeah, the file.
It's, like, on the...
You open where the file is, and you just click the .ex file.
There's where you click, like, open file location, and then you'll see, like, VTube Studio.
Yeah.
And then it'll be, like, VTube Studio without Steam.
Without Steam.
Yeah, yeah.
How do you change what you look like?
Scary.
I don't want to be green.
Oh, look at your passport.
Are you wearing my...
Passport?
How do I get in?
Yeah, how do I get in?
Let me in!
Wait a sec, I'm customizing my character.
No!
Let us in!
That is my point!
I can't join Donkey because she's playing VTube Studio.
Okay, I'll show myself online on Steam.
I don't want this.
You are already online.
It just says you're playing VTube Studio.
Oh, my God.
Let us in!
How do you guys see it?
Everything is private.
I don't know.
Clearly, there's a, like, security breach.
Oh, there is.
So, like, you guys are preaching my security right now.
All right.
Let me in!
All right, here we go.
You guys should go see game details.
And then I'll invite people now.
They'll invite people now.
Yeah, now I'll invite people.
I invited...
Lamu.
I invited Mint.
Where is it?
No, it's the same thing.
I'm still seeing...
I'm still seeing VTube Studio.
What the fuck?
It looks like this.
Okay, I'm gonna reboot the game.
I'll reboot the game.
That might help.
I can never remember what order you're supposed to open stuff up in to make that work properly.
Wait, there's an order?
Oh, my gosh.
I didn't know that either.
One game will, like, supersede the other.
Like...
I think it's the one you do first, which is annoying.
But maybe if you add VTube Studio to your private games?
Like, if it was, like, an illicit creepy...
Wait, I can add them to my porn one or something?
I'm learning so much right now.
I thought that...
I don't want people to know I'm a VTuber.
If you were ashamed to be playing VTube Studio or something...
Oh, I don't want anyone to know I'm a VTuber.
Personal confession.
Can I have...
Can I also blast a game to everybody so that they know that I'm playing?
Orc Massage.
Really?
You want everyone to know you're playing Orc Massage?
You've never been, like, the victim of somebody booting up, like, Skyrim's script extender, like, 500 times?
Yes.
You know, like, old YouTube montage videos in the bottom right corner?
You'll see such-and-such has begun playing Team Fortress 2.
Over and over again.
Yay, I got the invite.
Okay, I guess I had to boot it.
I'm gonna...
Oh, I got it too!
Yay!
Failed to find Lobby.
Okay, well, that's on you.
That's on still.
Okay.
Mint.
Oh, I got it.
Snuffy, what is...
Are you not inviting me?
Wait, are you not just...
Are you not called Snuffy?
What the fuck is your name on Steam?
I'm...
It's Snum?
Oh, okay.
Who the fuck is Snuffy?
Snum.
Okay, there is no Snum on my...
Are you a pure offline?
You're a pure offline.
You're a pure offline, aren't you?
I would've messaged you.
Hello?
You are not on the fucking...
Choose friend to invest.
Oh, hi...
I'm muting everybody in Discord.
You're a pure offline!
It's not even my fault!
I would just blast everyone's volume in this goddamn game.
Everyone is so peaky.
What?
It's awful.
You're gonna take this from me?
Okay?
You're not going on vacation with us.
You're gonna be left behind.
This is a vacation?
You're gonna be left behind from this vacation.
How do I use my passport?
All right, I'm muting myself.
I'm putting myself on low now.
Okay, cool.
All right, Snuffy.
Snuffy, remember to, like, instead to deafen, to just, like, un-deafen and turn us down so we can still see your foogie.
Oh, yeah.
So we'll know you're alive or not.
Yeah.
You have to promise not to actually turn me back up because I'm gonna be talking to my chat and I'm gonna be talking mad shit.
Yeah, exactly.
All right, now...
All right, give me a sec.
I'm gonna put on my makeup.
I gotta change myself.
Megan, your eyebrows just got angrier.
Give me a sec.
I gotta be angry.
I gotta get serious, guys.
Lock in.
This is a serious game for serious gamers.
Charlie Brown.
Give me Charlie Brown.
Wait, which round are you doing?
You're muting everyone else, right?
Yeah, I'm turning everyone else down, but I'll still see the foogies.
I can't wait for, like, in four months from now when we do another game via Discord and we can't figure out why we can't hear each other again.
Yeah.
This is how I feel right now.
Whoa, whoa.
You're stanned.
I've never played this game.
Actually, I've never played this game.
I haven't watched anyone play this game.
Me too.
I've watched people play this game, but...
It's going to be very exciting.
I haven't...
I haven't, like, played it myself.
I waited till this very moment to play this game.
Me too.
The first sloppy experience?
Yeah.
That's amazing.
Did you two play it yet or no?
I played it when it came out, so if we can be, like, Snuffy and I can be, like, the tour guides.
Alright, this is...
You're so mad.
Wait, this is, like, all of us.
This is so good.
Alright, this is how I feel.
Wait, you have glasses.
Yeah.
How did you get glasses?
How do I take...
Oh, there we go.
Uh, Snuffy, if you've been talking, we can't hear you.
It's not that we don't love you and we're ignoring you or anything.
It's literally we can't hear you.
You're just kind of Dreamworks facing us silently.
Yeah, it's actually really creepy.
Oh, there you go.
Yeah, you're talking.
You're talking now.
What...
How are you...
Dead?
Ew!
I put on voice activation.
Okay, there we go.
We can hear you now.
Yeah, we can hear you.
But how did you get sunglasses?
I want sunglasses.
Oh, there it is.
I see it.
I want to be angry.
Don't take my glasses.
I'm...
I played it and I got really obsessed with trying to, like, beat it.
Because I thought it was, like, a cozy game.
And then I realized that it's a game of nothing but trials and tribulations.
It's not cozy?
No, apparently it's not cozy.
No, it's...
Oh, Snuffy, you're a bit quiet.
It's quite stressful.
Wait, Snuffy, you're a bit quiet.
Can you turn up...
Is it possible to turn up people's volumes in game or no?
Uh, yeah, hit escape.
Is this better?
Oh my god!
Oh!
No, it's okay.
Keep your...
Keep your old...
Keep your old volume.
Keep your...
Okay, um...
I'll turn you up on my end.
It's okay.
Keep your old volume.
Oh my god.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Alright.
Death.
Alright, I'm ready.
Uh, but yeah.
How do you turn up individual people?
Escape, press escape.
Uh, hit escape top right corner.
Oh, I see, I see.
Okay.
I have to turn everyone down to like 30%, otherwise I go fucking deaf in this game.
Oh.
It's not that loud on my end.
Yeah, you guys...
You guys sound great.
Yeah.
Alright, let's see.
Do you wish to know how to climb?
Yes, how do you climb?
Oh, there's a trial.
Okay.
Left click.
Alright.
There's a rope.
This is...
I can do this.
Let me go.
I'm ready.
Cowabunga, dude.
I'm ready for my vacation.
And the thing that you can do is when you're on like top of the cliff, if you right click you hold on your arm and you lift your friends up.
Like that.
Okay.
Alright.
What do you do?
You put...
I got your...
Oh, okay.
You don't need...
Oh, right click.
Oh, okay.
I got you.
Yeah, you literally don't dip.
Oh, no.
Wait, did you just push her off?
No, she fell.
She fell off.
Nice.
There's actually a mod where you can push people off too.
That's what the...
I wanna play that mod.
I wish...
Dude, the rocks don't matter.
I'm just climbing.
I wish I got the Mount Everest mod working.
No, you can climb any surface except if it's raining and then it will...
You'll take more.
Yeah, I'm alive.
There's no...
Guys, there's no fall damage.
You get fucked.
No, there's fall damage.
Guys, I survived.
There's no fall damage from what I learned.
There's no fall damage.
Yeah.
See?
Wee!
I'm okay.
Yeah, definitely.
You should definitely get straight into the game and jump off the cliff.
It'll be fine.
Okay.
Yay!
That's what my tour guide told us.
Thank you.
You know, like, right...
Yesterday I was watching videos of, like, um, uh, freakiest cave... cave climbing depths and everything.
Oh my god, that's scary.
And...
Yeah, and then they were talking... cave diving.
I can live that today.
People that are like cave...
You know?
Like, those who, like, dive in c- like, fucking caves and there's, like, water in there and everything.
No!
And, then, like, like...
people that go into caves and they get...
Yeah, yeah.
Start diving in c- yeah.
Cause, like, like, that's not working right now.
They're just like stance, up,
There was one where, like... I'm talking about cave diving.
You know what that is?
No, I don't know.
Tell me.
Okay, so it's like you go in a cave and you, like, dive in the cave and that's why...
and there's, like, water there and that's why you have to dive.
And then... And then, like, sometimes people die in there because, like, you're in the water.
What?
Do they die or do they die?
They die.
And then they die.
They should have just brought the V with them.
What the heck?
It's because, okay, so, like, in one of the incidents, because of the tour, it's the tour guide's fault.
So, like, that's what I mean.
It's gonna be all Lybu's fault that we die.
Wait, what the... What the... Holy shit, that was a huge detour just to blame you.
Yeah, that's where it was gonna go.
I was like, what's the point of this story?
In one of the...
Yeah, you were, like, a trumpet of tangent for that.
Holy moly.
I thought you were just gonna...
That's all I wanted to say.
It was a crazy video, though.
It was...
Because the tour guide...
Because the tour guide was like, we should go dive in this cave, you know, to go cave diving.
And they're like, oh, it's very dangerous.
But he's like, no, we got this.
And then...
And then everyone died.
How did you do your emotes?
Oh, R?
Nice.
Okay, you guys can stare until I just woke up, right?
Yeah.
That's what it feels like.
I guess we all have little...
There's a mirror.
You gotta practice that.
Don't sing it.
Oh!
Oh, nice.
I think everybody's like drunk at the airport.
I don't know what's going on.
She's like...
We're in one of those...
Yeah!
Don't worry, guys.
We're gonna survive.
Just like the boys in the...
In the...
In that...
Firefly book.
Lord of the Flies.
We're gonna...
He's gonna be the boys in Laurie of the Flies.
We're gonna be the boys in Laurie of the Flies.
You six boys were real gasping about.
Ahahaha!
Oh my gosh, so ready...
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
I'm going to board us.
Yea.
Yeah.
Nice boy of the lambs.
Let's go.
So how's the volume going?
Stop.
Is the volume okay?
I feel like I caught the stupid from both of you.
We caught the stupid!
We were bored this way!
What?!
Oh my god, we're dead?!
It is Lord of the Flags!
Oh my god!
I told you it is Lord of the Flags!
We are the boys in the Lord of the Flags book!
I thought we were going for a hike!
Oh my god, we're actually... Okay, how to not die.
I'm reading the book, don't worry.
I can read.
How do I flip the page?
Oh, okay.
Okay, okay.
Never abandon a friend in need.
The point is...
Wait, you can run!
Guys, you can run and you press shift!
Hey, Doki, come and touch this with your face.
Okay, wait.
Give me a sec.
I'm trying to figure out how to...
How to say a lie.
It's okay, just walk towards my voice.
Okay.
That's...
I don't know what this is.
His name is Dingbong.
Keep an eye out in survival situations.
Oh my god, Doki!
Wait, I'm poison!
I'm poison!
Oh my god, oh my god.
Does anybody know first thing?
I have no idea how that happened.
What did I slip?
Oh my god, can someone pee?
Oh my god, the man of war, Jellyfish, quick!
Everybody start peeing on me.
Everyone, everyone, everyone, don't worry.
Alright, everyone start peeing.
Everyone, I'm not...
No!
Somebody help!
It's okay, it's okay!
It's alright, I'm gonna start.
Don't worry.
You know it's poisonous, Myth.
I'm warning you.
I know, someone help me.
I've been stuck.
Oh, yeah, lie down, Myth.
Sloppy, I'm stuck.
We're so...
How did you get the backpack?
Ew, there's one backpack and I took it.
Oh, how did you wear it?
You can just open it on your back.
You can just take what's in there.
Wait, I have a compass.
What do I do with this?
Super useful.
It points to north.
Oh, yes.
Oh, wait, I'm getting unpoisoned.
Wait, I'm getting hungry.
I'm gonna get a coconut.
Oh, coconut!
Wait, is this a survival game or...?
Yeah, we have to climb.
You see that big mountain in the distance?
Yeah.
We're gonna get up there.
Yeah, and that's all we have to climb.
And that's...
Yeah, definitely.
...how we win the game.
Look at Lime go.
What's that?
Is that a crab?
Look at her go.
She's grabbing the coconut.
Oh, no.
That's another thing that I...
She's gonna...
No.
She's got...
Don't worry.
I got you.
Land on us.
We got you.
Oh, I did it.
Can I get...
I'll climb.
Ow!
Sorry, it's Jordan Brickley for the coconut.
This is Lord of the Flags.
You won't.
Fuck you.
I'm eating it right now.
Okay.
I'm gonna eat it.
That's right.
I'm not done.
How do you climb the tree?
I wanna be a little monkey.
Same...
Same like the...
Same as the cliff.
Like this, see?
Okay.
I was like...
Get the coconut when you're at the top.
I'm gonna get it.
Get it.
It's mine.
Oh.
I broke my legs.
That's like you're right.
I'm eating this.
Yum yum yum.
Wait, it doesn't heal me.
No, no.
You need bandages for that.
It doesn't heal you.
Oh, wait.
I ate it though.
You fell off the tree.
I ate it.
I thought...
I lived.
Probably because I landed on your big ass head.
That's it.
Stop climbing this other tree.
Guys, we gotta survive.
I wanna taste the sweet, sweet, succulent coconut, please.
Guys, I have a broken leg.
I ate the other coconut too.
Wait, there's another coconut.
Min, climb that tree.
There's a flying jellyfish.
Wait.
As long as it's not just me.
Min, go climb this tree.
We need more coconut or we'll die.
Ooh, there are other things other than coconuts.
Stop.
That is unnatural.
I see my hello kitty luggage in there.
I lost my blood.
What did you get in your luggage?
Yeah.
Steffi, what did you bring to the vacation?
Wait, this is literally like the age-old question.
Like, if you got stranded on an island, what are you taking?
It's like who...
Oh yeah, and then...
The only thing is we need to stick together.
Because if we don't, the Scoutmaster will be mad at us.
And then who do you think...
It's like, who do you think will survive on an island?
I know I'm...
Not me.
That's for sure.
Or he broke my leg.
I broke my leg in the first five minutes.
Oh!
Nap bus!
We need to test it to make sure it's not poisonous though.
Don't worry.
It's not poisonous.
There's a trail mix over here.
It's not.
Oh, oh.
Wait, there's mushrooms!
Wait.
You guys need this.
Wait a minute.
I ate this already.
It's not poisonous.
If you're hungry.
Do these come in?
What's that?
It's a mushroom.
Take the medicinal root and eat it, Doki.
You'll feel better.
Oh, okay.
Give me a sec.
Cluster shroom.
This is an ancient herb.
I'm gonna feed it to you.
With medicinal properties.
I already ate it.
Oh.
Wait, am I still hungry?
Is the shroom good?
Are you still hungry?
Yeah, the shroom's good.
I already ate one.
Okay.
Excuse me, but mushrooms are really dangerous, you guys.
We shouldn't mess around.
No, we have Doki to poison test it.
Yeah, I already broke my leg.
It's fine.
Wait, you fucking lied.
It's poisonous.
That's for breaking my leg.
You deserve it.
Why did I break your leg?
That is right.
You let it happen.
You broke your fucking leg.
You didn't cushion my fall.
That's what you get.
Hey.
There's another luggage.
Oh, hey.
Mint?
Is she okay?
I get pranked.
Okay.
Oh, can I have that?
All right.
Where do we go?
Oh, there's so many luggage.
Wait, how many people have died on this mountain?
There's so many things.
Oh, hey, look.
Watch this.
I think it's just all our luggage.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Watch this.
Give us a head start.
We definitely should have used that there, yes.
Yay!
I'm a hero, everyone.
You might have broken her other leg if we didn't use this here.
Yeah, exactly.
It's for the sake of my leg.
Look, see, my thing.
Oh, my God, yes.
Look, and then I got water for us.
Look at that.
And I got... Oh, my God, wait.
I'm glad to hear it.
Oh, my God, wait.
Wait, is that... Oh, my God.
That's a bad... Look at that.
I'm cured.
Watch that urchin, it will poison you again.
Look at that.
I'm cured.
Yeah.
I got the bandits.
I don't think this is the best route to go.
We're going, like, the absolute worst.
Wait, do you have space on your inventory, Snuffy?
No, I don't.
But we can put it in Lemo's backpack.
Oh, that's true.
That's true.
I want to put this on her backpack.
I'm grabbing it.
I'm grabbing it, too.
You gonna root around in my backpack?
Okay, be gentle.
Yeah, I got it.
I got stuff in her backpack.
Where?
I think someone took something out of it.
You stole my fucking drink.
Um... No, you're okay.
You're fine.
Wait, where are we supposed to go?
Up here?
Shouldn't we go left side?
I've not played this one yet.
Maybe on the left side?
I've got the lantern.
Oh, cool.
I'm probably this way.
Wait, where... Who said that?
This way.
Oh, middle mouse button you can, like, point.
Yeah.
Oh.
This way.
Oh, really?
Oh, cool!
No.
What's up?
It's mad.
What?
Oh, fuck!
I took my other leg!
I thought... I thought she was so... I thought she... I could make it.
I thought I could make it.
How do you go down?
Please!
It's a problem.
I'm slow.
I need help!
Okay, I need help.
Okay, wait, wait, wait, Toki.
I've got a remedy for you.
I have my arm.
I'm going!
I'm climbing!
Let me... Grab your...
Alright, don't worry.
I can... I'll help next one.
I'll help next one.
Alright, grab my hand!
Grab my hand!
No, wait, who are we asking?
We're Snuffy.
Grab my hand!
No, my hand!
My hand is the same hand!
Get your ass!
I will push you down!
I will push you off this cliff!
Snuffy!
Grab my hand!
It's so mean!
It's so gross!
I told you not to trust her!
Oh, God.
We're gonna make it, guys.
We're gonna...
We're gonna get our badge from the Scoutmaster.
That means we've pushed around for so long, but the fog is already coming.
Wait, there's a fog?
It was...
I need a hand!
Someone let down their golden hand!
Wait, wait...
Please!
Stop for your own turn, please!
I'm fixed!
I did it!
Are you good?
Yeah, I'm good.
Grab my hand!
There's so much...
Oh my God, Bryden!
You're gonna fall!
That's so scary!
Oh my God, that totally doesn't look like you can make it.
This looks like pro gamer moves that I'm abusing on.
Oh my God, my heart!
I'm okay!
Don't worry, I have one too!
No, this is not a good route.
This is not a good route.
Did we mess up?
Should we climb down here and try a different one?
I don't know.
So, we want any ledges that have this sandy texture, because that means we can climb it.
If it doesn't have the orange, then we can't, like, stand there.
So we wanna try, like, up here has, like...
There's, like, sort of...
Oh, the sand!
Whoa!
Wait, there's, like, something up here!
Do you guys see that?
Oh, yeah, we...
Maybe we can make that.
Okay, who if it was the one that wasted the gun thing?
Wait, I have this!
Is this helpful?
I have this.
Okay, that's definitely not helpful.
Oh, oh!
Okay, okay!
Let me grab your hand!
Grab my hand!
Take it!
Oh my God!
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
I have an idea.
Okay, I have an idea.
Yeah.
Okay.
Where's the head?
Where's the... Sorry, I forgot.
What do you mean you forgot?
The whole thing was about grabbing hands!
Is there nothing up there?
Wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, there's nothing up there.
Wait, then why the fuck did you guys go up there?
Wait, where did Lime went?
Where did she go?
Um... Wait, can I grab your head?
There's nothing.
Oh, no, we're paying back.
Wait, where did Lime go?
Did she leave us?
I'm down here.
Oh, oh, oh.
Which way did you just like to go?
Yeah, yeah.
Uh-oh.
Where are you?
I'm not coming to you.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm scared.
This is it.
This is it for me.
Wait, I might be dead.
I might be dead.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That didn't break anything more.
I think we want to go slightly around.
Okay.
This kind of seems like...
Alright, Lamu, you go tell us where to go.
I didn't remember the deed.
I'm drinking my drink.
Don't push me.
Don't do it.
Grab my hand!
I'm gonna try a different one.
I'm following Lamu because she knows what she's doing.
Are you ready?
I'm ready!
Wait, there's a bridge!
Why did we not go through this bridge?
Be careful about this bridge.
It doesn't like more than one person on it.
Oh.
Can we reach that?
I don't know if I reached that.
I believe.
I'll watch.
Wait, do you think I can reach it?
Yeah!
I did it!
Good job.
Alright!
You know, we can... let's just leave.
Transformation Central.
Yeah!
Are you already suggesting a dungeon of friends?
Look, we can...
I know there's a checkpoint where we can revive them.
Not to the very top of the mountain.
Well, I think we can get there.
I don't like... I don't like this mountain.
This mountain is actually kind of nuts.
This mountain?
Isn't there like three other mountains after this?
Yeah, something like that.
Aren't they supposed to be harder than this mountain?
Um, the second one I would actually say is the hardest.
Um, hand!
Hand!
Oh!
I'm okay.
Look how beautiful you are.
Yeah!
No, they're fine, right?
They're fine.
Are you guys okay over there?
No, they're fine.
I see them.
They're fine.
They're just fucking around.
What?
Hello?
Wait, what?
They died?
No, they're shouting cave and die.
Oh, cave and die.
You know like when you dive into a cave and there's a chance you can die while you're cave diving?
You know?
I see them!
They're over here!
Yeah, that's us!
We have made like literally no progress.
Oh!
Oh my god!
I couldn't see on my game!
Oh my monitor died for like five seconds, but I'm okay.
Oh no.
Thank you Nvidia drivers!
Oh, there's suitcases here.
Oh, that's good.
I don't think we're there.
Oh, there's a white suitcase!
You know that's a bougie suitcase.
This side is so much better.
I thought you guys were supposed to be poor dying.
What's in the white suitcase?
Wait, I need a med kit!
I'm, I'm, I'm, I burped too much with my legs.
Okay.
Oh, let me eat this apple too.
Oh, I can, I can pick that up.
Move her here!
I can, I can hold it.
I have inventory space.
Yeah!
Alright, I'm climbing up.
I'm a little better now.
Have you, have any, has anybody sampled a bungle shroom?
Oh yeah, it was, it was okay.
I ate that.
Get my hand!
This is a trustworthy source.
Pick up my hand!
Okay.
Hold my hand!
Oh, you don't wanna touch my hand cause there's cooties on it.
Oh my gosh, we're actually making it up the mountain!
Oh, yay!
Laimu, thank you so much for grabbing my hand!
You're welcome!
This side of the mountain is so much better.
Why did we not, why did we not go on this side of the mountain?
Why did we go the hard way?
Who, who chose the other realm, hmm?
Who was it?
The weather in the elements.
Okay, I'm going up this way.
Probably in a bad way.
Wait, yeah, when did Doki start leaving?
I don't know.
Wait, there's a bridge here!
Thank you.
You know that's a good route.
One at a time on the bridge.
How'd you get up there?
I don't know.
Just climb on it.
But wait until Doki's off.
Don't have to wait.
Last time I had two people on the bridge and I was okay.
Why were you guys not doing it one at a time?
You didn't listen to Scoutmaster Lamu's instructions.
You're not even looking at us.
You don't know what's going on.
I don't have to look to see some...
To see, know when somebody fucked up.
I didn't do anything.
It was your fat ass that made it loose.
Well, my thing didn't shake when I was on it.
Oh no.
Oh no!
Guys, guys!
I'm gonna break it away!
I'm okay.
I'm okay, by the way.
But I think go this way.
I don't know where you are.
Here.
I'm gonna drop a mushroom.
I hope it helps you come out.
Oh, I didn't...
Ooh...
Uh, there might be a spot on the slide here.
Okay, give me a sec.
Alright, I'm here now.
I made it if I had.
Hey, guys.
I'm here.
I got my arm down.
Come up here.
Alright.
Yeah, this way.
I'm coming up.
I need a hand.
Don't worry.
My turn.
No, Aibu, no!
No, Aibu!
You've been turning your back on Dokibu!
What did I do?
You're a snitch!
You're a fucking snitch!
Stop it!
Stitches get stitches, remember that!
Keep your eyes open tonight!
Peace!
I don't know if I'll make it.
Nevermind, I give up.
I know what you did.
You snitch.
I believe in this.
You do?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wait, wait.
I already started.
Oh, is this it?
Sleep with one eye open, Snuffy.
Oh, actually, I don't know.
I don't know if you can make this.
I shouldn't have done that!
Sleep with one eye open.
I'm coming, I'm coming over.
Wait, where's the game?
Where's the, the whole, everyone else?
I know.
Yeah, she's alone with me right now.
Just us in this beautiful, large cliff.
In a mushroom.
Hold on.
I thought you actually died!
You scared me!
I thought I just committed a murder!
It was your fault.
Wait, what happened?
Wait, oh my god!
You are committing a murder!
Oh my god!
I fucking died!
What are you saying?
You!
You said you had a buckle before!
You, you're like grabbing me by the neck!
You!
Oh, you're lucky I didn't have the mod where I can grab people!
Oh my god!
You're so lucky!
I didn't download that mod!
Oh my god!
I have a rope!
What is this?
Oh, I thought you had that!
I'm gonna tie you up!
You're gonna do it!
I'm gonna do it!
Oh my god!
Ow!
She's all dying to me!
That's right!
We're not gonna get out of this island alive!
I will be the boy who lives!
I gotta make a run for it!
I don't- Alright, that's right!
Get up there you fucking coward!
Run!
I don't wanna have to help you but- We have to do it together!
Are we leaving Mint?
Are we?
I think you need help!
Um...
Okay, okay.
This- This is not gonna- I don't think I can make it.
Alright!
Don't worry!
Help me!
Wait, Mint!
I told you I'd help!
Wait, what happened to Lime?
Lime never made it!
I think she ditched us!
Lime is here!
I think she's gone, guys!
Lime would never- She's our tour guide!
She's gone, guys!
I'm waiting for you!
Where the fuck did you go?
Wait, what do you mean waiting?
I think we're above you!
Yeah, we're above you!
No, I'm not!
No!
Hahaha!
Let's go to this bridge!
Let's go here!
Right here!
Wait, it's getting kinda foggy, no?
Yeah, but it's cause like- It's getting a little dark over here!
Yeah, this area is very, very foggy!
No, I think it's fine!
This seems very safe!
I'm gonna go up!
If you're happy and you know what, clap your hands!
I think I can see the bridge and you're going towards the edge of the map!
Oh!
Is that bad?
Um, I'm gonna go on the bridge!
Ow!
Okay, I'm on the bridge!
Okay!
I'm going this way!
Oh, this way!
Oh, there's like another bridge!
Oh, I see you!
I see you!
Oh!
Hello!
Oh, I'm climbing on this bridge too!
I'm already gone!
Alright!
I'm heading up as well!
Wait, why am I not recovering stamina?
Up here!
Wait, there it is!
Sometimes you gotta shimmy a little bit so I can figure it out!
Stop!
I'm trying to recover stamina!
Come over this way!
I gotta hand up for you!
Oh, the fog is coming!
Snuffy, you coming?
It's really, it's really bad!
Don't worry!
Take my hand!
Yay!
Okay, or not!
Fine!
I literally took your hand!
Where's Snuffy?
Oh, jeez!
Take my hand!
You yell, take my hand, and then take your hand away?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
That's why I'm...
That's why I'm going to the timeout corner in the voice.
Oh, nice!
It's so clear!
Channeling, like, the middle-aged uncle at the family gathering that keeps, like, being, like, you got something on your shirt!
I'm the Boy Scout where the parents were like, this...
Join the Boy Scout would definitely change her behavior for the better, right?
No!
They're like, instead of sending her to Juvie, we could just send her to the Boy Scouts.
Wait, how do we do this?
I'm gonna fall here.
Just jump!
It's a leap of faith!
Oh, I believe!
Okay, I'm coming!
I'm coming!
Oh, I'm coming!
I'm coming, too!
I got a hand up!
You can do it!
I did it!
We did it!
I'm so heavy!
I'm sorry!
Wait, you have food and you share it with the class?
I'm starving!
Oh, me too!
Wait, oh, I just ate something bad?
Oh, I'm dying.
Oh, it was poisonous.
You'll be fine.
That's not true.
It's a temporary death.
Okay.
You look fine.
Nice.
I like temporary deaths.
I feel...
I feel pale.
Maybe you're taking...
You're great.
You're okay.
Oh, there's a suitcase!
There is!
Yeah!
Don't eat those berries!
There's a flying rock in the sky.
Wait, there's a coconut!
There's a coconut!
That's known as the sun.
Alright, someone else climbed this tree.
Cause I know I'm not good at that.
Okay, if you climb it, you can throw the coconut at everybody.
Oh, that's true!
Yep.
I gotta give her a hand.
You can give me some of this first and then jump onto the tree.
Oh!
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, okay.
Who's gonna caught me?
Who's gonna catch me, though?
Just don't land on the giant spikes.
Who's gonna catch me?
Yeah, catching is definitely a thing that I can do.
Okay.
Watch this.
Oh!
Oh?
You got this, bro.
You got this.
Knock him down.
Yes!
Got one.
I did it, though.
I did it.
I...
I did it, though.
Wait, you guys ate the coconut!
We're making it!
I'll get another one.
I can see the top!
I was really angry.
You can already!
Where is it?
There's smoke!
It's endgame!
We're definitely the endgame!
Oh my god, we're gonna beat the game!
We're gonna commit a new world record right here.
Oh, there's...
There's apples!
There's lots of food there.
How did a dead jellyfish get all the way up here?
What the fuck?
I don't know if those mushrooms are okay.
Is the tide really that crazy?
Wait, I'm hungry!
I'm hungry, too!
I'm hungry, too, but fine!
Eat your fuckin' mushroom.
Uh, Crisberry, whatever it is.
Hey, I climbed that tree for us.
I'm gonna have a marshmallow.
Oh my god, we are getting mushrooms...
marshmallows.
Yeah, marsh mushrooms.
Marsh mushrooms.
I don't even know which one you're talking about.
Oh, it's not fine, actually.
I'm so fine.
No, I was okay.
You can eat one, but you definitely can eat two!
Oh, wow!
I'm really taking a lot of damage.
Wait, wait, I got this.
Yay!
Wait, I'm taking like a lot of...
Don't worry, I'll be fine!
If you...
Oh, wait, wait, you can die, so...
Mint, if you die, we can rez you!
Where's Snuffy?
Oh, where is Snuffy?
Help me!
Snuffy!
Yay!
Oh, there she is!
Where the fuck are you all the way over there?
Well, how did she get there?
Look at her, she's right over here.
She's like right over here.
Uh, Doki, can you take Min?
I can't take her in the backpack.
Sure.
Uh, you wanna do it quick, otherwise she'll collapse and die.
I don't sense your urgency here.
That's fucked up.
That's fucked up, Doki.
That's yours fucked up.
Don't worry, Snuffy will bring her back up.
It's just awful.
Wait, how is she gonna come back alive?
Um, we need like health.
Oh, so she'll be...
So where did Snuffy go?
Hell no.
Snuffy!
Isn't it res...
Can you take the backpack here?
Yeah, I can carry it.
How do you carry it?
Oh!
She's back!
You're alive!
Nevermind!
She said it!
I told you, she's alive!
Welcome back!
What happened to me?
I'm a little blue.
I have no stamina.
All poison, baby.
Here's your bugle.
Thank you!
You might have taken too many poison.
You're welcome.
If you play that, something good might happen.
Snuffy!
And
then all the way over there, and then all the way over there, and never reach here.
Oh, that's actually impressive.
It's like the 20th century fox sounds.
Oh, Mint kinda died, so I had to pick Mint up.
She looks good to me.
I definitely died.
She temporarily died.
Yeah, she's building her poison resistance.
I have no stamina.
Oh, nice!
We got marshmallow!
Hey, there's another backpack!
Wait, how do I wear this backpack?
Oh, there you go.
Okay, wait.
I can put stuff here, too.
Whoa!
There's some marshmallows!
Yeah!
Oh, is this our wilds?
Yeah, can...
Snuffy, can you use a chain launcher?
Whoa!
Does anybody want to eat mushrooms?
No, that's not a mushroom.
No, it's fine.
I have a marshmallow.
Oh, I thought it was wrong.
Oh, day four!
We made it!
Nice!
Wait, what's this?
There's a little man up here.
Wait, there's a chain launcher.
What's a chain launcher?
Launching a chain?
Bad news!
The ship captain made an oopsie, and we've wound up crashing on this mysterious island.
Thankfully, mysterious islands are my specialty.
With our whole troop working together, we'll reach the top of the peak, and signal for heaven at no time.
In the meantime, I'll take this opportunity to add some additional pages to my famous guidebook, Scoutmaster Myers.
Whoa!
Scoutmaster Myers must have definitely lived, right?
I'm gonna touch the ancient statue.
I thought...
I thought you were the Scoutmaster.
Wait, what does it do if we touch the ancient statue?
That's a different Scoutmaster.
I think he fragments.
Oh!
And it makes a horcrux, right?
I'm touching you.
Oh!
It's a revive thing, right?
It heals you.
Is anyone damaged?
Oh!
No, I'm okay.
I have poison.
Poison?
I don't know if it heals poison.
Wait, how come I have so much energy?
Yeah!
What is my electricity bar?
That's your extra stamina.
Oh, I have extra...
Okay, who fucking fed me a mushroom?
Who fucking fed me a...
No, someone fed me the mushroom.
Who was it?
Who fucking...
Who gave me the mushroom?
It was you, wasn't it?
I know it was you!
I will have the good mushroom, I promise!
I promise!
I know it was you!
I will brush you off!
Off getting you to the cliff!
No!
Wait, you're also taking damage, Nubby.
Did you eat the mushroom, too?
I think Nubby is eating poisonous mushrooms from the sun.
I don't know.
I said it to everybody!
She's trying to be so helpful in just poisoning her friends.
She's trying to find me earlier!
Okay, all in favor!
All in favor!
All in favor voting Stuffy!
Aye!
We vote Stuffy off the island!
Take your tiki torch and leave the island, Stuffy!
If that's what you want, I'll just jump!
Do it!
It'll get so cool!
Do a flip, too!
Do it!
That's right!
Did she jump!
What did you do?
I did- yeah!
That's right!
It's what she deserved.
Oh, sir!
Oh, shit!
Wait where is she?
Is she down?
Oh, my God!
My monitor died, so I thought I died!
No, she's down there?
Well, she's alive!
He's alive!
She's alive!
I was like, whoa.
Caring at the wall.
Yeah, in the corner.
You guys are going crazy, but I'm like cabin in the woods level snapping.
What do we grab onto here?
I'm scared.
Okay, so when there's a little bit of a drop, you can actually turn and face the wall and like just grab it in increments when you're dropping down to stop your fall.
I have a magic bean, is it good?
Oh my god, why not magic?
Yeah.
Tell me more about your magic bean, Dougie.
Don't feed it to me.
The beans, the fruit that makes you toot.
How do you give it to people?
There's like a whole children's rhyme about magic beans.
Wait, I can't do anything with this magic bean.
It just says it's magic.
I'll plant it.
Oh, I can plant it?
Okay, we gotta find a place for me to plant this magic bean.
Why does the magic bean have to do anything for you?
Do you hate whimsy?
Perhaps it's just magical.
Oh!
I made that.
I'm a father.
Dude.
Oh, I get it.
Oh, it's like...
Yeah.
James and the giant...
Yeah!
Okay, maybe I should've saved the...
James and the giant fucking drill.
I should've saved that magic bean.
Wait, there's a red suitcase over there.
I'm going for it.
Yeah, I see it.
Wait, are we supposed to keep going up again?
Red means good.
Yeah, we're going up there.
Wait, give me a sec.
I'm going for the red.
I don't trust you with mushrooms.
Ah!
Red means good.
This seems like a good berry.
Alright.
I'm opening it.
Oh my god, I got airplane food.
It is good.
Nice.
I told you, red is good.
Hey, where are you guys going?
Where are you guys?
Hello?
Oh my god, hello?
Look at me go!
Ooh, ooh, ah, ah!
Oh my god!
Did you guys see...
Oh my god, there's a banana!
Oh, there's some good apples over here.
There's so many bananas!
Are you sure they're good?
Are you sure?
Yeah, I ate one of those apples.
They're pretty good.
Are you okay?
I...
I did...
I did not realize that that's what that was.
What is this?
I didn't stop.
I don't know.
I was wondering if you could eat it.
Good.
I just had to drop it on the floor and it like...
got really big.
Well, I just went...
Snuffy, get up here.
Cool.
Oh, what the...
I'm getting the apples.
Snuffy, get up here.
I'm coming.
Where are you guys?
I'm ready up here.
I got it.
You just belly flopped your way up there.
That was cool.
Oh, it's a platform?
Oh, it's a foot.
I have a shell fungus.
Apparently, it's an extra platform.
Like the magic bean.
Bananas!
Is anybody hungry?
I don't think...
Only a little bit.
I have this.
Can you touch me with a ripe apple?
Can we touch the spikes or...
I think I did.
I did.
Oh, cool.
No, you can't.
They're similar.
They are...
Hey guys, I did a swing.
We have a little place to sit now.
Yeah.
Why are you always poisoned mints?
I'm putting these in your mouth.
Stop eating!
I'm like a baby!
Can I eat a banana?
My new son.
I'm so helpful.
Do you think these bananas are safe?
Yeah, I ate one.
Yeah, they're bananas.
They have to eat.
Yeah.
It's weird that there's no more monkeys on this island.
But I think it's not because of the bananas.
Can't be.
This one is actually safe.
Here you go.
It made me hungry.
Oh, I'm up here now.
I have no idea.
Take my hand!
Yoinked.
Thank you.
Too slow.
How did Mint get all the way over there?
She just walked, I'm pretty sure.
Wait, where is she?
She walked?
I wanna drop the filthy up this mountain.
She just walked.
We would all clap.
Mint, don't worry!
I've gotten my hand out.
Wait, what's this?
Don't lie!
Scout members, be careful!
I know what you did, Snuffy.
Keep one eye open tonight.
Watch out for the spikes!
The rain makes it harder to climb.
Wait, really?
No, it doesn't.
You're lying.
Look at me go.
I'm climbing.
I wanna try a banana.
Alright, fine.
Climb in the rain.
See what I care.
Banana?
Wow, I can't believe we came from all the way over there.
I know, right?
We did that.
We've grown so much.
We're climbing the sea.
I know!
Oh my god, if only our scoutmaster could see us now.
Yeah.
I'm climbing up.
We got you.
I thought this game was supposed to be scary.
Guys, I'm getting poisoned.
How am I...
Oh, it's these.
Don't touch these.
Thank you!
Don't touch the poison ivy!
Don't touch poison ivy, guys.
Scouting one on one, man.
The fog rises.
How was I supposed to know?
Purple is bad.
That's the only reason why I haven't done it.
I think that's for personal respect.
Which way could we go?
Where did Dokino?
I'm up.
You guys should have followed me.
Oh, beautiful.
Purple.
Guys, guys, guys, guys!
Don't follow me, guys.
I broke my leg.
Guys, don't follow me.
No.
I have a banana peel now.
Wait.
I fucked up.
Watch her flip on it.
How do I drop it?
Oh, here we go.
You're...
Hey, take a step forward.
Oh, shit!
I got poisoned ivy.
I fell down.
I think we gotta maneuver our way through here.
This one's okay.
I don't know if you can, actually.
Don't touch me.
Don't stop.
I'm feeling pressure.
Stop.
Oh, wait.
Yeah, that rate actually worked, but, like, I fucked it up.
And then I broke my leg again.
I broke my leg again.
Go back the way you went.
This way here.
Yeah.
And then you can walk most of the way along here when it's not raining.
Not the rain.
How do I take it?
How do I take your apple?
What?
Take it.
Oh, another what?
Yeah.
Kind of shove yourself with the right side, so you...
Not when it's raining.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you can...
Oh god!
I'm okay.
Wait.
I'm getting poisoned.
Me too.
Why don't you set off a giant poison explosive cloud?
I don't have much.
You're poisoned.
I got you.
No!
You did that!
Help me!
I don't think you helped her.
Is she okay?
I think she's okay, guys.
You won't be hearing, like, actual screams.
Guys, does anyone have meds?
I think I broke more than two meds.
Oh, I have this.
I got you.
Wait for Doki.
She needs it, too.
I think she used it.
No, I don't think I will.
Okay.
Stop hitting me, spread of shit!
Stop hitting me!
I won't push your arm!
I'll slow it!
You're playing it!
Try your timing.
You know what you want to do?
I won't!
No!
Okay, you're right.
That's right.
You deserve that snub!
I don't really know what to do.
It's the king.
Min, you can walk.
Just push yourself into the corner.
Walk along it.
Okay.
I swear you gotta be bringing that out one more time.
And you bring it out.
Help me.
I made it so you can look at you.
Can you bring up the fairy lantern now?
Holy shit.
Oh, it's empty.
Oh my god.
You fucking bitch.
No, I'm gonna...
Whoa.
It's actually gonna be.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna bring you down a cliff.
A little pause.
Your dog says the violence.
He took back to see us survive.
Yes, let's see.
I'm making an example out of you.
He knows what I wanted to do.
Run.
He wants food.
And I want food, too.
Yeah, you have an apple in your backpack, okay?
That's not an apple.
Wait, don't touch that.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, don't touch that.
What is that?
Don't touch that.
Maybe you should touch it and find out.
Or wait, wait.
I'll throw this, and it'll activate.
Nice throw.
Great.
Good job.
Don't worry.
It's laying a pad.
I don't think- I hope we didn't need that.
Yeah, me too.
I hope so, too.
I'm sure it just fell somewhere in this hole.
It'll be fine.
I'm pretty sure.
Ow.
Oh my god.
This is a hole.
You can make that jump, but it's far.
Right here?
From where I'm standing, or from there?
From where you're standing, I think?
I think that's what I did.
I got you.
I want to feed my dog.
I think I'm dead.
I think I am dead.
Come on, pretty shit.
Oh, hey Doki, what's up?
I shall haunt you for the crimes you've committed now.
The crime was lit!
I had so many items!
I had so many!
I had a backpack!
I'm here to haunt you.
I don't know if this is the better way to go.
We should go that way.
What?
Wait, can I not?
I trust you.
Oh, don't do that.
That's terrible.
Wait, how do we... How can I like free...
Free haunt?
I might like stuck 50.
Yeah, so I can like... You can ask Mint how to start getting your haunting career.
It's not.
Yeah, you have an expert right here.
I can't tell if that's getting hit by the rain or not.
It's not.
Hmm...
You're just like Doki.
Your face is so ugly.
Wait, this is so scary though.
Maybe... Mint could put her...
Yeah, Mint could put her peton or something on...
Her what?
Peton!
I stole that from your back!
No, let me wait for the rain and I'll see if I can do it.
Hold on.
I got lots of extra stamina, so...
I stole it!
And it actually worked!
It worked out, cause I have it.
Oh, I can!
I can zoom out!
Oh, I see the top!
I see the top!
You're like almost there!
What?
I think that's the top.
Oh, thank you!
Whoa, whoa!
Whoa!
Oh, there's some...
There's some things here!
What's these?
There's some bees!
Oh, there's bees!
Don't touch the bees!
Touch the bees!
Stuffy, touch the bee!
Touch it!
Who wants to try the mouse?
I'll take it!
Here you go!
Oh, that looks so poisonous there!
Oh no!
It just looked like a cantaloupe!
Wait, sound guys, the sound been okay?
Ooh!
Rope cannon!
And the water!
Do you want any?
Oh my god, you guys are not close to the top!
Actually, that fed me, like, I'm so full, just a little poison.
That was actually the best thing I could've had!
Yeah!
Just walk it off!
The poison will eventually stop, you know?
It's like when you eat pineapple and it makes your mouth a little spiky, but it's still a little bit.
Cause like pineapple technically is like...
I think that's called an allergy!
No, pineapple...
No, pineapple is technically acidic for...
Yeah, it's eating you.
So like...
It's acidic.
You're not supposed to eat pineapple.
Cause it's slowly trying to digest you.
But...
For some reason, people just like that.
I'm actually, I think, allergic to kiwi, because when I eat kiwi, my mouth goes funny.
No, I'm pretty sure...
I'm pretty sure, like...
Like, um, it's supposed to do that, right?
Oh, is it?
I don't think so.
Oh, there's some more shrooms that I don't know if I'm eating.
Oh, these ones are good.
I think.
Maybe we can test it out.
Oh my god, no.
I don't trust your mushroom opinion.
Eat two, eat two.
Eat it, Snuffy.
Eat two to see if it...
If it's extra poisoning.
I did, I ate two and I said what's alive now.
See, she's okay.
She's not turning purple.
Yeah.
This one was good, I told you.
The boogle or whatever.
You know this game was made in two...
Was made in two weeks?
That's crazy.
This game was made in two weeks.
Yeah, it was made in two weeks.
It was supposed to be, like, a one-off game.
I wonder if I can jump up there or if I should go over there.
Hey, Snuffy, I'm gonna hurt you.
I don't recommend the route that I took, actually.
Oh, I was gonna say, I think we should...
No, you go left side.
See, there's a left thing over there.
Oh, I know where it's raining.
See?
I know where it's raining.
That's a good...
I don't think so.
Oh, never mind.
Yeah, you went the harder route.
Do you see?
Wait!
Oh, please!
No!
Oh!
Yes!
You did it?
You're okay.
She's okay.
Are you okay?
Um...
There is something up top.
I don't know if you can climb up there.
I don't know if you can make it.
Let me see.
Yeah, I'm just having a little...
Yeah, no, no, you definitely can't make it.
You definitely can't make it.
It's really, really far.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
No, you definitely can't make it.
I don't like this game because I have to watch you guys fall to your desk like a million times.
What do we do?
Alright, let me try this one then.
Hold on.
Okay.
I think this is our best option.
I think so, too.
I mean, you have the rope.
Yeah, you have the rope sitting.
Yeah.
Where'd the rope go?
No.
Yeah, it's um...
Um...
We didn't need...
Okay.
But it's there now.
Hold on.
I think...
Well, they need it.
They need it.
I need it.
Yeah, yeah.
The babies need it.
Yeah.
I put it down.
It should be there now.
Alright.
Man, you can just drop to the ground and pick it up from there.
I don't know if I'm gonna make it.
Line!
Oh!
Grab the rope!
The baby is fall.
Shut up.
Just because you fell and died doesn't mean the rest of us have you.
Someone did not catch me!
They're like, you'll make it!
Make it!
And they lied!
You didn't!
Why?
They lied.
I was lied to.
I ran and everything.
This ghost is annoying.
I had a...
Why?
I know.
How could I fucking catch you to plummet halfway through the chasm?
I should have been caught!
I don't know if we can get around here.
This is really sketch.
Yeah.
There is a ledge on the...
There is a ledge on the far right.
You can just walk it.
I think it's okay.
Yeah.
See?
Look at that.
I'm such a fucking helpful ghost.
I deserve a tip.
She's backseating us.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah?
Weird.
We're in the crevice.
Ooh!
Look!
We're cave diving!
Oh my god!
This is it!
This is the cave diving part!
There's no way...
That looks really dangerous.
Oh my god!
The fuck?
Wait, no.
You climb up.
I'm mad about the fog.
If you climb up from that side.
I don't know.
There's like the left side.
There's something on the left.
Where?
No, no, no.
On the...
Behind you line.
Behind you.
There's...
It's green.
No.
Behind you.
That...
Rock.
Okay, yeah, but...
But, like, I don't think we can get any further from there.
This is, like, closed.
Oh, shit.
Okay, I...
Yeah.
Okay, hold on.
Yeah, I think we found the edge of the map.
We're too far over.
Oh my god, the fog is so high.
Snuffy's, like, fucked it?
Wait, where do you go?
Yeah, where do you go?
We kind of lifted too far to one side, I guess, maybe?
Wait, look.
There's a ledge on the top.
If only you had another rope.
If only.
Oh, man.
My backpack had so many ropes, guys.
It didn't have any ropes.
It had so many ropes.
It had none.
I looked in your backpack many times.
No, no, no.
I had at least one.
I'm gonna try if I can maybe make this.
Wait, men had...
Wait, no.
Why not use the yellow thing?
Can I use a baton?
I have a baton.
No, I...
No, the baton.
Oh.
The baton.
Whatever that is.
It's a wall?
It...
It goes in a wall and you hold it.
It looks...
It looks like it's, like, sheer, though.
Oh god, the fog.
The fog!
I think you guys might die.
I'm afraid of ya.
Hey, maybe...
Just jump in the fog.
What's that?
It's saying...
It's where all your friends are.
Oh wow, I see it.
It really is kind of foggy.
Yeah.
Whoa, it's like getting all...
Whoa.
Say hi.
All your friends are over there.
Come on.
Chat's over there too.
Oh, you're not gonna make it.
I will.
You're not gonna make it.
Grounds, you're right.
Whoa.
Oh!
Hello.
I don't have enough stamina!
You're gonna...
Keep going!
Go!
I don't have enough stamina!
Wait.
Min, do you have your peton still?
Yeah.
You're...
You can...
Oh, she's getting eaten by the fog!
And then put your peton whenever you can't have enough stamina.
He's getting...
Um, yum, yum!
He's gonna die!
She's gonna die in the fog!
I'm gonna watch it happen!
No, no!
The fog calls for you!
I'm gonna die in the fog!
Yes!
Oh, it's healthy.
The fog calls.
Wait, I keep grabbing, but it's not grabbing.
Do the last dupe before you go.
Play your depth.
Play your depth sound.
I'm grabbing it?
Oh, it didn't work.
It's time.
Bring out the trumpet.
Go down the Titanic.
Wait, why did Stuffy die?
Wait, what the fuck?
Stuffy don't know.
I get, we gotta keep the dream alive.
Stuffy, when did you die?
We'll never know.
We'll never know when she died.
Ooh, the ghosts of all your friends are watching you now.
Hello?
Am I a ghost?
Yeah, you are.
Stuffy, when did you die?
I didn't have enough stamina to climb, so I just tried and yola'd it.
And you had enough.
Mint, like, played the trumpet while she died to the fog until it consumed her.
Oh, football, brain.
I don't think Mint knows that she... Oh, there you are.
There she is.
Oh, she wears it.
She's wearing her sunglasses, too.
Oh, you're so cute, and your little Mint fan told me for her.
Yeah, she's a whiz now.
How do you move around?
Oh, you scroll wheel.
It's just that.
So he is like, forward, back.
Oh, I can get so close to you.
Yeah, me too.
Remember what you did!
We are the ghosts of Christmas past, present, and future!
Wait, you're so close!
You're so close!
Right?
Is she?
Maybe?
Sniffer.
I don't know.
You're on a ledge and it's more open.
Oh yeah, there it is.
Oh yeah, I see a campfire!
I see a campfire!
You do?
Yeah, it's at the very top!
You see the smoke?
Oh my god.
No.
Okay, you look up.
Like, look up from it.
We are looking up.
There's like a luggage on those vines.
That's crazy.
I am not touching that shit.
The luggage is so evil.
Why did it do that?
Oh my gosh, you have such good health and everything.
That's why she's a tour guide.
Wait, why do I have a grungle?
Oh no, that's you.
It's a grungle.
Apparently you can...
It's that little bird place.
Yeah, it's the...
It's name is Bing Bong.
Is it?
Oh...
Wait, where did you get grungle from?
Yeah, where did you get grungle from it?
I don't...
I don't know.
The hottest new thing, the grungles.
Wait, I'm gonna move myself.
My favorite character, Mr. Grungle.
Oh, whoops, that's the game.
Is there a better path to take here?
Um...
Maybe to the left?
Yeah.
To the left, you climb up.
I don't think I can make that.
Hold on.
Oh, I don't think...
I don't know, there is a...
There we go.
The left side seems nice, though.
Seems a lot nicer.
How are you gonna get past that?
I think there's a lot less poison up here.
That's nice.
I'm just having trouble, like...
Like, ugh.
I think you gotta go right, man.
I don't know.
Really?
Unless you can walk up left side.
Like, it's like...
Just grab a sports drink, and then YOLO.
Yeah, drink that sports drink.
Yeah, and then...
Okay, you picked the scarier part, but that's...
Oh, wait, wait, wait!
There's this!
Then you go up, then you keep going up!
She's gaming!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
She's doing it!
MLG!
4...
420, no scope!
Yay!
No bad!
MVP!
We didn't do it!
Yay, bring us back!
Oh, she eepy now.
Lime's eepy.
A little bit eepy.
Not too bad.
Not we.
She did it.
We did it!
No, we were help.
We helped.
We backseated.
Yay!
What's up?
I'm hungry.
I'm gonna go eat.
Om-yum-yum time.
Wait, what's the darkness mean in my little meter?
It means we died and came back.
It means like when you revive.
Where's the luggage that you're supposed to- The- What the heck?
There's one up here.
What?
I don't think it's supposed to- Is it supposed to spawn there?
Can you even get- You can't climb these kinds of trees, can you?
Yeah, what is that?
What?
Okay.
Can you?
I got morale boost.
Ew, I'm cooking my mushroom.
Did I just- Did I just not get a mushroom?
I guess so.
Marshmallow?
Did someone steal two marshmallows?
We all keep- I took only one.
I took one.
Wait, there's a- Here.
I can cook it again.
Doki.
Well done, Marshmallow.
Did you just feed this to me?
Oh.
The yellow- I was resurrected to live a life of nothing but suffering.
No!
It does.
No, the yellow ones are good.
The yellow ones are good.
Are you sure?
Oh, wait.
It's your marshmallow.
It is your marshmallow.
That's right.
Okay.
I'll cook it quick.
Okay, I'm gonna eat mine.
I'll cook it.
Oh, wow.
That's nice of you, Mint, though.
Double cook it.
See?
Look, thank you, Mint.
I gave her my marshmallow.
I'm such a good person.
Shut up.
Uh-huh.
I have a curse placed upon my soul now.
That looks intense.
Alright, where do we go?
Oh, it's the ice one.
Hi.
Is there a berry in here, too?
No, we ate all the berries.
I don't know how long we're gonna make it here, guys.
I feel like this one, uh...
What?
Oh, this one?
Yeah, isn't that the death mountain?
Mint, though?
Isn't that specifically the death mountain?
I'm here.
I'm on, Mint.
Maybe we're supposed to use, like, one of those, like, ropes and, like...
Yeah, I feel that.
Yeah, I feel that this is where we should have kept all our materials.
The last part is kind of, like, good for that.
Yeah.
This is the end.
This is where Mount Everest mod would have came in handy.
Where I've seen all the...
All the skeletons.
All the skellies.
Yeah, all the skellies scattered around.
This is saying around...
Ow!
There's a!
Get into shelter when that happens!
I feel it.
I'm so cold, Scoutmaster Lama!
Oh my god.
Is it still happening?
It's like on the edge of the biome!
I'm so cold!
it's like on the edge of the biome.
Yeah...
Scoutmaster We got warm..
This way is slow, this way is slow.
You can actually hablar.
Come, come, come.
This is safe.
I'm feeling so safe now.
I'm here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's always good in this biome that we'll have to stay near objects where we can hide behind.
To protect ourselves from freezing wind.
Oh, that's smart.
Don't worry, I can't catch you.
I caught you.
I'm a hero.
It's a bit chilly, isn't it?
Yes.
I'm a hero.
Maybe.
Is it Tuesday?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Don't worry, there's shelter here, guys.
There's shelter here.
Yeah, sheltering, sheltering, sheltering.
Don't worry.
Hi.
Buddy, buddy.
Don't worry.
We got huddled together, so we'll be fine.
We're so safe.
It's chilly, ain't it?
You guys look so cute huddling behind the tree.
We're good.
Yeah.
Little babies over there.
Oh, there's a chest over here.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, we need that.
We have nothing.
Don't worry, I'm fucking sprinting.
A little springtime breeze.
I'm sprinting over.
Don't worry, I got this.
Okay, what's in our treasure chest?
Wait, it's orange.
I'm coming up.
Special.
Oh, it's a special rescue kit.
Luggage.
Oh, I've been a good boy!
Father said, I've been a good boy.
Oh, my God.
Wait, that actually suits you all the time.
You're filled with nothing but joy and bendy.
Wait, that actually suits you.
Father said, I've been a good boy today.
But your face is so mean looking.
You're so unhappy about it.
I got a dentist so we get the lollipop.
No, it's my lollipop.
No one can have it.
Maybe one of the little spitterhots.
Yeah, a little spitterhots.
I can't have it, it's a little dog taste.
No!
Go back to Poresville.
Oh, wait.
Double one is over here.
Oh, really?
Oh, yeah, you're right, you're right.
Oh, wait, there's two lollipops.
Oh, wow, yeah.
That's a lot.
Oh, oh, the blizzard.
Don't worry.
You guys wanna see my lollipop?
Oh, there comes a blizzard.
You wanna see it?
I'll let you...
I'll let you look at it.
Yeah, it's huge.
It's bigger than your head.
I'll let you look at it.
Can I lick you just a little bit?
Nope.
Ten dollars.
Ten...
Ten dollars?
Ten supas.
Ten supas?
To me, or...?
To me.
Now it's twenty supas.
Oh, there's stuff.
Gosh, inflation is hurting us all.
Oh, wait.
I'm coming.
What's in...
What was in there?
Um, a heating pack and an energy drink.
Oh, there's an apple.
Wait, that's...
We should get that apple for...
Like, and put it in...
There's a couple apples.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
They're good.
They're winter berries.
There's a few down...
Up here as well.
Oh, okay.
I'll go up there.
Oh, there's a tree up there too.
Okay, we'll go.
Yeah, cause we can only fit like...
A limited amount anyway.
Are orange ones okay?
Let's find out.
I'll test it.
I'll taste test it.
Okay.
Look at you grabbing that.
Oh, they're real good.
Grab a bunch.
And put them in there.
I have pack two.
I can't climb it.
Or in your pack.
How do you put things in your pack?
Alright.
Take your pack off, put it on the floor.
And then like hold E and put it in...
Ooh, ooh, ah, ah.
It's really fiddly, so be careful in the mountain.
So you can actually throw your backpack off the floor.
Okay.
I got some oranges.
Can you hold your...
Wait.
I don't understand, but I...
I got one orange.
Uh oh.
I don't think this is enough.
I'm an...
I'm okay.
Right here, right here, right here.
I got a backpack, so I can put the orange in here.
Okay, hold on.
Wait, actually, yeah.
No, actually, you drop in, I'll put it...
Oh, I was gonna say, I can put it in.
There you go.
How do you put it in?
You, uh, you get your item out, and then you put it in.
That's what you got.
Oh!
Oh my god!
Yeah!
Look at that!
Now we have two oranges.
All right, where do we go?
Hello.
This way!
Wait, there's something over here.
What is that?
Wait, I got a heat pack.
Someone just left...
Someone just left a heat pack on the floor.
The musicals?
That was me.
I ran out of room.
Oh.
I have...
I have room.
It's beautiful.
Okay.
Oh my god, it's so beautiful.
It's beautiful.
Oh!
It's not beautiful.
It's not beautiful anymore.
Oh my god, it's not beautiful.
It's safe here.
It's safe here!
Oh, I have found something.
Hey, guys.
I got a fungus.
Hey.
I like your punches.
Yeah.
I'm climbing.
Here, take my hand!
Thank you.
Yeah, see?
Look at that.
I'm a teamwork person.
Teamwork.
That's me.
Teamwork makes the dream work.
Don't touch the lava.
Lava's dangerous.
It's like the floor is lava.
Can I do this?
The fog rises.
Oh, this way?
Is that what he said?
I don't think I'm okay.
Oh, god.
Oh.
I'm not okay.
What?
I'm right there.
There's lava.
If you can get near.
Yeah, over here.
Over here.
Come in.
I'm coming up.
Yeah, we'll huddle together for once.
Snuffy can never do.
I'm gonna huddle over too, guys.
Hi, Tucky.
Hi.
Come huddle.
We're like little penguins.
I don't know where Snuffy is.
I don't know.
Well, she's clearly not dead.
I can hear her.
Yeah, she's not dead.
She's on the way.
So she's fine.
Marco!
Oh, I'm another shell fungus.
Yeah, no.
It's a shell fungus.
So you can make it to platforms.
Put it in your little backpack.
Okay.
Wait, where do we...
Wait, Lamo!
Yeah?
Where do we go?
Oh, there she is.
What's up?
Lamo, we're lost!
We're lost!
Go master Lamo!
Where do we go?
I think maybe this way.
I hate this map.
I changed my mind.
This map sucks too.
Yeah, no.
I heard this map was the hardest part.
I thought it was like, what?
Surely the next one will be really easy.
Yeah, surely, right?
I actually like the next one.
The next one's good.
Wait, have you ever beaten it?
Yeah.
Wait, you have?
How many tries did it take you?
Uh, a few because a couple of times I played and people were like, PVP'ing.
Oh, this is like, not like us because we clearly are working together.
Yeah, I know.
We're working together real good.
We're working together.
Yeah, together.
We're good teammates.
Wait, what's happening?
Yeah!
What's happening?
It's kinda weird that spot there.
I don't know.
I don't know about this section.
It feels kinda weird.
KICK MY HAND!
Is Mint okay?
Wait, where's Mint?
Where did Mint go?
I was like, wait a minute.
Wait, one...
One...
Two...
Three...
I was like, wait a minute.
Did we have three when we started?
Wait, Mint has the backpack filled with oranges.
So we can't let her die.
At least grab the backpack.
She's like a capybara.
Yeah, she literally has all our materials.
We can't let her die.
I'm alive!
Yeah, I meant we can't let you die.
So you have...
Quick, give us the backpack.
And we'll pick you up later.
Okay.
I see the hot springs!
With the capybara!
Wait, you do?
There is hot springs with the capybara?
I see them!
Oh, I see it!
We can't go there.
We'll get fogged, I think.
Wait, but there's the capybara!
Yeah...
I'm gonna go see it.
Oh, they've got a way out.
Goodbye, everybody.
Sophia's like, I don't care.
I wanna see...
Wait, where are you guys going?
Okay.
Where do we go?
I'm watching the capybara.
Oh, there's a spot over to the right that might work.
Okay.
You mean the left?
I just got caught by the...
And thus...
The internal's okay, but you have to go over freezing rocks, which kinda sucks.
Woo!
This
place sucks.
Yeah, this place sucks.
I think Sniffy might actually die for the capybara's.
No, she won't.
I believe.
I see her.
Oh, she's...
She's going there.
I see her.
Yeah, I see her.
There she is.
She made it.
Wait, Laimo, is your...
Is your path the correct path?
No, this place sucks.
Hold on.
I think we should go reconvene at the capybara and decide if we can grow out.
You just wanna...
You just wanna see the capybaras.
Oh my gosh, she's dancing with them.
What about the left side?
Can we just go left?
Yeah, I think we need to head over this way.
Alright.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Before you...
You have to get the backpack!
Men, you have the backpack!
Why is she like...
Oh my gosh, she's echoing.
I'm coming!
Okay.
Wait, where do we go from here?
Wait, I have to...
You can use...
You can use that to jump across.
Wait, you do it.
I don't trust myself.
But you can only do it once.
Wait, I don't trust myself.
You do it.
Oh my...
Wait, you do it.
I'll...
I'll drop it here.
Damn.
You do it.
I don't trust myself.
You could...
You could throw a shelf flick here.
Oh my god.
Do you think I'm gonna hit it?
I think so.
I have faith.
Gamer.
Oh, I did it!
Woo!
Alright, you first.
Very nice.
Oh, shit.
I'm...
I'm so cold.
Don't worry, I'm warmed up now.
Alright, I believe.
I think they're actually...
They're just running around the capybara.
It's alright.
They'll write stories about us.
Why do they sound like they're panicking?
I think...
Capybara's don't induce panic.
I think something's going...
I think they might have fucked up.
It doesn't sound like it's going right.
Whatever's happening over there.
Got it.
Have they just decided to die over there?
I think they're gonna die with the capybaras.
Yeah.
Guys!
Yo, are you coming?
I don't think...
No, they're just...
Okay, whatever.
They've chosen their path.
I don't think they're coming.
Oh my god, I'm so...
I'm so...
Is there anywhere to go up there?
Or are we gonna have to go around the outside again?
I don't know.
I'm so lost.
Alright.
It sucks here.
Okay.
You gotta figure this out, Scoutmaster.
At least we get a closer look at them.
I think they're at...
I think they're gonna live.
I mean, if you thought that you wouldn't make it all the way to the end.
Maybe, you know, death by capybara is actually kind of nice.
You know what?
Yeah.
Wait, why am I not doing that?
Why am I following?
You can come around this way.
I'll try and put an arm up for you.
Cause it's pretty...
It's pretty tight.
Okay.
One more step to the right.
What?!
Dude, oh my god!
Oh my god!
That was so fucking crazy!
I can...
Don't fuck on that!
That's fucking adrenaline!
Holy shit!
You did it!
I did it!
I'm gaming!
The adrenaline!
Oh, this one sucks.
Hold on.
Let me go back.
Okay.
Wait, I don't think this is right.
This is fucked.
This whole thing is fucked.
I think we are not supposed to go...
Maybe the capybara's with the right choice.
Yeah, the capybara's were the right choice.
Hey, kids!
Hey, guys!
Do we have any pitons left?
I don't think we do.
No.
No, I don't.
I am scared.
Oh, this sucks.
Wait, there's no cover.
Wait, are we gonna freeze?
Do you still have the chain launcher?
No, that's when I die.
Oh, unfortunate.
I'm gonna heat up.
It's okay.
I have a heat pass.
It hurts.
It hurts so bad.
It's okay.
I'm okay.
If we could get to this, it would be alright.
But I don't think we can make it.
How do we...
Yeah, I don't think so.
Are you sure we're supposed to go through this way?
Maybe we should go down.
No, there's like multiple pathways you can take, and I think we could have ended up on one that's not great.
Yeah.
Wait, do you want...
Maybe you get the lollipop.
Lime?
Guys!
LIFES DEAD!
OH NO!
YEAH!
YAAAAAA!
Guys, it's okay, I ate my lollipop before I died.
Oh no, don't quit so easily.
Go back to them, Capybara, and I'm here.
I swear to Floppy, go back to those goddamn cave bars.
The fog is coming.
And Doki died, like, right next to me.
I ate my Isaac.
Yeah, we're both dead.
It's okay, guys.
I ate my lollipop before I died.
I ate my lollipop.
Wait, wait, why are you guys going to the cappy bar?
I want to see you.
If you go around where Snuffy's going, you'll find our bodies and our subs.
I want to see the cappy bar, Azmin.
Go back, I want to see.
No, I'm not giving you that satisfaction.
Oh, that's fucked up.
That's fucked up.
I'm going to haunt you.
I guess my backpack is here.
Oh my god.
Oh, there's Grungle.
There's Grungle Sand.
Grungle Sand, there he is.
I mean, it looks like you might be able to climb up there as well.
You know, if you want to do that.
No, they are definitely not.
No, look at Mint's health bar.
Yeah, there's no way I'm going to make it.
I told you, I think he's going to gamer her way up.
We can, we can.
No, no, don't give it to me.
Don't feed it to me.
Don't waste it on me.
You look allergic.
No, please anything.
Please save it for yourself.
I don't have my empty pen.
I don't have it.
I have, like, almost more than half.
I'm good.
No, if you see what we saw on Mint's health bar, you do not want her to have anything.
I know.
I don't know.
Should we go here?
It's okay.
Just jump into the lava.
I'm going to follow you Scoutmaster.
You're the new Scoutmaster.
It's like, she's like one year above you and she's now the Scoutmaster.
Oh, there's a baton on the walls here.
You can actually climb internally, but it's like, there's cold rocks and stuff.
So, it's like risky.
I think I see a mushroom.
Oh, look at that.
What's that glowing thing?
Look at that.
Oh, what did you get?
What did you get?
Oh my god.
It was a flashbang, I think.
Because I can't see anything.
I think I just look blind.
She's blind now.
Oh?
Follow the sound of her voice.
Use echolocation.
Oh, ah!
Are you over here?
Don't go!
I can't...
I can see your name.
You look like god.
I can see nothing but bright lights and you're just radiating behind it.
You look like a...
You look like a holy intervention.
No, I can't make it.
It's like your guardian angel.
No, you can't climb that.
You literally almost...
Hey, we could've just followed the old thing.
Oh, there's a suitcase up there.
It's gonna have stuff.
Yeah, yeah, there's a suitcase.
You literally stuffed and you almost walked into lava.
The right side's less steep.
It didn't look like that at all for me.
I must have a street.
Is this a better idea?
Oh, you climb the tree to the left and then press on the branch.
Oh, never mind.
I made it!
Wait, what?
Mint made it!
Mint made it?
She barely has anything.
Yeah, she has nothing.
How did she make it?
You got this, Snuffy.
I believe.
The scoutmaster left you.
This is such a bait, dude.
The scoutmaster left you, but I still believe in you.
Mint, you're the new scoutmaster.
I like all the ice rocks hanging out next to the actual lava.
That seems okay.
I think this was actually the more correct path.
There's a hole.
You can do either.
I fucking hate internally.
So internally, like, takes out the storm.
Oh.
But then every time you touch those blue rocks, you accumulate freezing points.
So if you have to, like, run across them or something, it hurt.
Oh.
Here, I can think I can make it.
You can pull the heat pack, though, and do it.
You can probably make it.
Well, the problem is, is there anything above this, though?
I don't think so.
No, there's not really.
Go to the left.
Go to the far left.
You see what I see?
There's rocks there.
And if there's rocks there, that means more climbing.
Are these good for your soul or bad?
The, the glowy blue one?
Oh, that, that is good for your soul.
Oh!
That was not good for your soul.
That was...
You got burned.
You are?
Yeah.
Too, too hot.
What does a Grunkle do?
Is he just there?
He didn't do anything to you.
Oh.
It's just like a little companion.
Okay.
This is definitely the right way.
Yeah, yeah.
Go, go.
Definitely.
I told you guys.
Wait, but how are you gonna climb that?
Oh, luggage.
Oh, there's snaps!
Eat it!
Ooh, delicious!
No, she's not hungry.
She's not hungry.
Min's not actually hungry.
No!
It was just a little treat.
It's for your whimsy.
It's for your...
Your happiness meter.
It's a passive.
Snuffy's absolutely gonna be that kind of grandma.
Where you visit, and then, like, you're trying to leave, and she's like, Oh, take these with you!
Oh, and these as well!
And then she, like, finds, like, I don't know.
She overfeeds you.
And she's like, you should take some of these as well.
And then a snack for the road, and you can use this for your dinner.
That's a nice grandma.
I can see the capi bar over here.
Oh, shoot.
Uh-oh.
I'm safe.
Snuffy isn't.
Oh, she's safe now.
I'm good, I'm good.
Come to me!
It's good here.
Be careful, though.
If I fall, I'll die.
No, you won't.
You'll be fine.
We'll see about that.
You'll be so healthy.
Why is the grunkle so heavy, actually?
I'm gonna get rid of it.
No!
Do it!
Do it into the volcano!
Yes!
I don't even have anything in my inventory!
I lost, like, ten pounds in my inventory.
I like how Snuffy's like, no!
That was the weight of your heart shriveling into a prune.
Do you see my health?
There is no...
You couldn't give it to Snuffy!
She's not gonna give it to Snuffy!
Snuffy is supposed to be made!
Yes, do it.
Oh, the snowstorm's gone.
Okay, I'm gonna jump over.
Throw the ring in the volcano!
Do it!
I...
It's like...
It's like the ring from Lord of the Rings.
Yeah, but throwing it in the volcano was the evil decision.
You know, you've cursed the entire run because you let him die.
This run has already been cursed.
Do you really think you two are gonna make it to the top?
Do you really think?
You guys were like, my precious Grungle.
You just couldn't see...
It's Grungle!
Yes, it is.
Who the fire!
You couldn't see...
The...
The truth!
I showed it...
I showed it to you.
I'm following snum...
Snum vision?
Thank you.
Snum vision!
I mean, snum...
Snum nation?
You're pretty good in the snow, so...
Yeah.
All right.
Oh, there's the blizzard.
It's actually...
You're making good progress.
You found a better part of the mountain to climb.
I believe in you.
That means...
Wait.
Is it a procedural generated?
I have a rope.
Actually, hold on.
Let me put this into your...
It's...
It's a new map every day.
Okay.
But it's the same map each time.
So if we tried it again, it would be the same map.
Yeah, so we'll know...
We'll know how...
That it'll be this way.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Wait, so then like...
They should just die, so then we know how to do this.
And then...
And then either...
I think...
Oh.
You just tell your friends to just die.
Just do the...
Just jump out.
It's right there.
It's such an easier decision to make.
Don't you guys like the easy toys?
Yeah, I love e...
Oh, no.
Uh-oh.
Right here, right here, right here.
Maybe?
Just do a flip.
Nope.
Nevermind.
I'm dying.
No, I'm dying.
Let's do it though.
Oh gosh.
Yeah!
She's dead.
It's just you, Snow.
It's just you.
Oh,
new hat.
Yay!
And then there was none.
Oh shit, my monitor died.
That's not good.
Oh.
Ooh.
That's not good.
My monitor fully...
I told you, you throw bing bong in your ears.
Why are...
Why do you look like that?
Hey guys.
Oh.
Say that about your friends.
This is not good.
Oh.
My monitor's not good.
Dude.
My monitor's dead.
You dead?
No!
Oh shit.
Sorry.
Oh no.
I was trying to go on YouTube to the...
Oh my god.
I was trying to go on YouTube.
My PC's on fire.
Computer might be...
Donkey!
Help!
Hello?
I'm back.
What happened?
What happened to me?
My main monitor died and then like everything... I just hear like...
Like everyone cutting in and out and then like everyone just kept looping.
All I heard was just meant laughing and it was the same laugh over and over and over again.
It never stopped.
And then I forced quit my game.
It was like I was living in hell.
That sounds like a nightmare.
Yeah, it was... It was... It was...
What did I... She was the one that threw it into the hole!
What did I do?
Whip, whip, watch me nae nae.
Whip, whip, nae nae.
Whip, whip.
I need sound guy to fix this.
I taught her to whip and nae nae.
I need a... Am I the same character?
Good, I'm still angry.
I'm still...
I need sound guy to help me again.
Everything reset itself.
How do you... What the fuck did you do?
Wait, what did you do?
I was doing the lawnmower.
The dance.
Oh, you have a new hat!
Vroom, vroom, vroom, vroom.
I have a new hat.
Oh, yeah?
Oh, nice, yeah.
Yeah, look at my hat.
Oh, I like your hat.
Yeah, this is my hat.
Well, I don't like your hat either.
If you bring the bugle to the capybaras and play it to them, you get a hat.
Really?
What kind of hat?
Yeah.
Oh my god, it's happening.
I didn't know that.
It's happening.
Everything paused.
Oh my god.
Wait.
Is your computer dying?
Oh my god.
I'm not okay.
There's no way Peek is gonna destroy my PC.
Is your framerate capped?
Yeah.
It was.
I capped it!
No.
I capped it at 200.
I'm gonna cap it to 144.
I'll add two hundred.
OK, you shut the fuck up right now, you shut- Yeah, you shut up.
You shut up.
You shut up, you shut up.
You shut up right now, no ing you in the locker.
No!
Let her go!
Alright, wait... Yeah, wait, I need to...
If my sound guide lets me know if everyone's volume...
Apparently when you rejoin a session, it resets your volume sliders.
It does, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so I need to know if everything... I need to know if all the volume's okay.
Oh my god.
I'm ready though, I'm ready.
Go on vacation.
Come on, vacation!
Demon's doing the splits on the elevator!
Wee!
Oh my god!
So are you!
Let's go!
They call me the man of steel.
I'm ready.
I'm locked in.
I'm boarding my ticket.
Wait.
He's doing the thing.
Yeah!
Yippee!
I'm crying.
I'm alive.
We're all alive.
Alright, skarts.
Let me double check something real quick.
Give me the bugle.
It's always about the bugle.
Give it to me.
Maybe that's why you called it the bungle.
That's only one letter away from bugle.
You were just thinking about your bugle.
Oh, that's true.
Maybe...
Oh, there it is.
There's Bing Bong.
I think he'd get a hat if you take him to the top, too.
Alright, well, we have two missions, Scout.
Thank you.
Alright.
Take Grunko's dad to the top.
You take him, Snuffy.
I got food.
I want to grab the food, too.
Wait, who has the backpack?
Me!
Alright, let's go.
We know the way now!
Alright, lead the way, Scoutmaster!
Lead the way!
I'm running, I'm running, I'm running.
Alright, I'm putting... Wait, why do we need a compass?
I thought we don't need a compass.
We don't need the compass, I don't think.
Boom!
You take the compass...
Oh, the compass...
We don't need the compass where we're going!
Scout!
My lung capacity is...
Oh...
Oh, there's that floating guy again.
Wait, so it's the same map now, right?
Yeah, it's the same map.
No.
I... I trust in Lime.
Don't worry, I have this.
No.
Yeah, exactly.
Put it on the floor!
Yeah!
I have a little...
And I drew it on the floor!
Ow!
Ah!
What happened to me?
Wait, Lime, I'll put it in your backpack.
Oh, yeah, me too.
I'll put this in the backpack, too.
Now, I think.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, they're, like, super heavy for what they are.
Yeah.
I just...
You put that shit in my backpack, didn't you?
No.
Yeah, I believe you.
I mean, the number went off to show that you did, but okay.
No.
Let me check, let me check for you.
Maybe you went through, like, a growth spring.
Yeah, maybe you grew...
at pu...
second puberty.
You gained an extra...
Wait, did you check?
Yeah, I did.
Yeah, did you get more in my fucking backpack, man?
Did she check?
No, I just went to check.
What do you...
Why did I get it?
She was the one that put it in!
It was her fun!
And it's nothing for when my fucking backpack is low, because I still have fun!
Skull Master, then put your coconut in your backpack!
It wasn't me!
Wait, you guys need to look at this.
There's something of...
This whole map is very obscure.
What?
Why is there a mushroom growing on this area?
I like the mushrooms growing on this area.
Those are the roots that I...
That was the...
The roots from before.
I really got some home growing in here.
Are you safe?
Are you tired?
Are you okay?
Okay, let's drop, guys.
Alright.
It's safe.
Is it?
Maybe if you eat one.
Maybe just one.
Just one.
Yeah.
Just a little poison as a treat.
I think I have a better tolerance now.
Yeah, like you...
I've never seen that!
Once a day you become a man.
I saw an art...
I saw like a tweet where someone was like, I shot myself in the leg every day until I can...
Oh yeah.
I can make my skin bulletproof.
And then I see that tweet.
Nothing to lose.
Hang on.
Thickman.
A scout cookie.
Thickman!
Woah!
I got energy drinks.
Scout cookies are not allowed in Canada.
It's an American only.
It's an American only thing.
Woah!
Wait, we need those.
Wait, I don't...
Did you just use the energy drink?
Was I not supposed to?
Wait, are you holding the cookies?
It's fine.
Oh, I'm tired now.
To eat B.
Yeah, you can microdose on...
Apparently this guy was trying to microdose on bullets, and then he like...
tried to... and then he like upgraded to a really strong bullet, and then he went to the hospital.
No, he was like, I had to stop, so I hope someone else continues my research.
More energy drink.
You have to stop shooting himself in the leg.
Wait, you're the ones that were supposed to remember for us.
Wait, I'm gonna...
I'm eating this coconut so I can keep the...
Yeah, me too.
To be fair, the first two mountains were like super easy, and then there was like a...
some difficulty spike for some reason.
Uh-oh.
Wait.
I remember we crossed the bridge.
We just gotta find the bridge.
Yeah.
Oh, there it is!
I see the bridge!
I see it!
Wait.
I don't know if anyone was in a hurry.
You look... you were like throwing yourself into a pit.
Me?
Yeah.
Do we go yeah?
Can we climb up here?
Can we walk on this?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure.
Just a little bit.
Yeah.
You can then go like here, and then here, and I'll... I'll catch you.
I'll like bring you up.
Okay, like walk up.
Yeah.
Wait, what is that?
You might be able to walk up that way.
Yeah?
I'm heading up.
Fire away, fire away.
I don't even know about my little pony version of that song.
What's the pony version of that song?
Yeah, what's the pony version of that song?
Yeah.
Octavia.
What's the...
Oh, I know that song.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I almost...
I almost gonna make it.
Imagine not making it.
Oh, I see the bridge.
I see the bridge.
I'm heading to the bridge.
Oh, we're already at the bridge.
Yeah.
How do we get to the...
Oh, we have to go down.
Look at us go.
We're speed running.
Oh, I'm gonna speed run.
Guys, I might need a new monitor, guys.
This is not looking so good.
I...
If your whole computer turned off, I think it might be like your graphics card or driver.
Oh, not again.
Not again.
Why is it...
Why do I always get these PC problems?
Not again.
Cat.
What are you doing here?
I don't know.
I don't even know.
Wait, where do I go after this?
Up.
Go up.
Just keep going up.
Yeah.
Is it this way?
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
You just said, yeah, because...
You say, yeah, because...
You're installing Marvel Rivals?
Yeah.
All right.
Where do I go, Lime?
Oh, you're not Lime.
Where do I go, Snuffy?
Yeah, it's mining crypto.
You just go up here.
What?
Oh, yeah.
I launched Marvel Rivals for like the first time since the tournament just to buy Loki in a swimsuit.
Oh, yeah, dude.
His like...
Has a bulge, too.
Like, it's crazy.
His whole thing is amazing.
It's actually an actual bulge.
Wait, what?
Yeah, they're finally giving people what they want.
Yeah, yeah.
He has a bulge.
Yeah.
Look so far.
Thank you.
Where do we go after?
Left side?
Praying crunch.
Help me.
Thank you.
Is it left side?
I don't remember.
Uh...
I don't remember which way they went.
Me, too.
I'm gonna Google it.
If I...
Wait, are you Googling Loki's bulge?
Yeah.
Okay, maybe do Marvel Rivals Loki summer skin.
Yeah, I was gonna say, don't just Google Loki's bulge.
Don't just do that.
That might not be the best idea.
Tom Hiddleston.
Depending on what you wanted.
I have...
Oh my god.
Mr. Tom Hiddleston.
That's not fair.
He was naked, apparently, in the show.
So this was a setup.
Oh yeah, and then Luna's like...
Luna's...
Mint, are you okay?
Are you screaming because you're falling or screaming because you looked at the leaves?
I think she's screaming because she saw it.
She saw the skin.
What was that?
She saw it.
We just kept going up while you were Googling.
Okay.
While you're going to Google.
Thank you.
This one here.
This one here first.
Okay, Luna's ass though?
In the bikini?
That shit's crazy.
Wait, she sent...
Show her, like, Luna's ass too.
Oh, there's a suitcase over here.
We don't have to grab that suitcase.
Oh my god.
Is it real?
Real?
Yeah, it's real.
It's real.
Who's screaming?
She...
Mint, are you okay?
I was gonna say it.
I am not close enough to help anyone.
I was like, there is no way I can help anyone right now.
I'm so up ahead.
Oh, hey, nice.
I got a rope.
Rope time.
I don't know what to do with this rope.
I got a rope.
Okay, wait, guys.
Do I keep the rope?
Or do I not keep...
Oh, actually, I'm hungry.
I'm hungry.
I'm at chat right now.
I'm out here trying to win.
Alright, I'll climb.
Climb, climb.
Yeah, exactly.
That's right.
Look at me go.
No time.
Okay.
Okay, don't climb this way because this was not the right way.
I got too confident.
It is this way.
I have your specialty.
No, it's not.
Wait, maybe it's like...
Wait, who said that?
Yeah, of course.
It's like mopping you.
You can have a...
Yeah, yeah.
This way, this way.
Wait, which way?
Of course.
This way, this way.
Eh?
I've realized I have a granola bar too.
Oh, me too.
This way, okay.
Alright.
This way.
Follow the Scoutmaster.
There.
Scoutmaster knows da way.
She know da way.
Does she know da way?
Don't help Doki up.
That's fucked up.
Yeah.
Ideally.
Okay.
It's all that, you know, suggestions.
You know?
Oh no!
They climbed one mountain and it's all over.
Everybody's pretty cool.
Yeah.
I climbed one mountain and I know what I'm doing.
Like lost or something.
The show.
I know exactly what I'm doing.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, don't get away from me.
Get away from me!
What?
Those are safe.
I ate them myself.
You wanted to force feed me.
No, those are safe.
Red is good.
Okay.
Green is bad.
Yellow is good.
Okay, that's good.
Wait, for what?
For eating.
The crisperies.
Yeah, yeah.
Blue banana.
I saw that I was trying to force feed me, so I got scared.
No, I was selfishly eating it myself.
Okay, that's good.
Come on, thank you.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, hello.
I see the campfire!
Oh, I do too!
We're gonna get through this one fast.
Cause we're pros.
Oh my god, we're so good at this!
Look at us go!
You're just like bashing yourself on the rock like a ceiling.
You're freaking crazy.
Okay.
Yeah.
What do we get?
Oh, here's a chain launch here.
Min should take this antidote because she puts everything in her mouth.
Oh yeah, Min, you get the antidote.
Oh, I got the back.
Actually, yeah, I'll grab the backpack.
I want the fairy.
Oh, we have a morale boost.
What is this?
Oh?
Why'd it get all scary all of a sudden?
I got the anti-rope spoon!
Yay!
Wait, I can pick some stuff up.
Oh.
Oh, yeah, wait.
How much stuff do we got in the, in the, in the, in the backpack?
My backpack's full now.
Oh.
Oh, wait, we get two now.
No stroke.
Yeah.
What does cooking it twice do?
It makes it well done.
Oh, what does it do?
Yeah,
it must be delicious.
Let's get to, let's get to the top, guys.
I believe.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Guys, come on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
With the power of friendship.
Yeah.
Isn't there a song from High School Musical, like...
Bop, bop, bop, to the top.
Bop, bop, bop, bop, bop.
Okay, that.
Na, na, na, na, yeah.
Bop, bop, bop, bop.
Bop, bop, bop.
I feel like I'm in, like, a car ride.
Carpool karaoke.
Are you okay?
Bop, bop, bop.
So, we need to... I'm sorry!
We're sliding!
I don't know.
Yeah, we ended up too far right, so we want to circle around to the left.
Oh, okay, I dropped down.
Oh, there's a suitcase!
Look, look, look!
Yeah, we saw that before.
I'm grabbing that suitcase.
I broke my leg.
Yeah, maybe we go more to the left since the right side was like suffering last year.
Yeah, that shit was hard.
What is this?
Nice!
I broke my leg and now I can use a med kit.
Use the energy drink.
Okay.
Yeah, use it.
I'm gonna eat my marshmallow first and then I'm gonna put it in here.
And then I'm gonna eat my energy... I did!
Oh.
Yeah.
And then we go up.
I'm gonna do the thing.
Wait.
Look at us go.
I'm gonna climb it.
Snuffy's...
Snuffy!
Lima said we shouldn't climb when it's raining, but clearly she's a liar.
Okay.
Ice Scoutmaster didn't know what's up!
Guys, I think I fucked up my PC again.
Guys.
Oh my god, I'm okay.
I...
Oh my...
Oh my god, I'm okay.
Okay.
Oh...
My god, that was scary.
I didn't need to call you a bitch then.
I thought you were just refusing to help me up.
Are you good?
No, okay.
I'm okay.
Guys, my PC...
The Grunkle curse is going strong.
I think...
Honestly, I think your computer might be on the way out.
There's something along.
Oh my god.
What?
Do you have like an Intel CPU?
Are you melting away?
No, AMD.
It's AMD.
Oh my...
Guys, I think...
I think I might have to take it to the doctors later.
Yeah, maybe a little bit.
I don't know, I don't know what's going on.
Okay, I have the...
I swear I have a curse.
When it comes to PC.
I think so too.
Yeah.
I think we're too far right again.
Hold on.
I think so.
I don't know where we'd go.
Oh, it's the magic bean.
It's the magic bean.
Yeah, the magic bean.
Yeah, watch this.
Wait, it didn't grow.
Oh, there it is.
It's a grower.
Dude, it's so big.
Holy shit.
It's just getting bigger and bigger.
It just gets bigger and bigger.
I think this might have been a slight waste of it.
Yeah, Snuffy.
Why did you waste it, Snuffy?
I should have been more thoughtful about my uses.
I know.
I hope you learned your lesson.
Oh, there's apples.
Is anybody hungry?
No, we're fucked.
A little bit.
But I have trail mix.
I'm okay.
I got none of us.
We need to hang left.
We're on the edge of the map.
We can somehow.
Yeah!
We just like the edge.
Oh, there's a little...
Apparently.
Wait, there's a little shelf thing.
You get your shelf, Shroom.
Yeah.
Alright, where do I use this?
Oh, I remember this!
We went right after that, remember?
We saw this and we went right.
Yeah, I don't think we should.
No, but... We shouldn't, because that's the edge of the map.
Really?
Oh, we lived on the edge of the map.
Well, it was kind of sketchy, though.
Everyone but me died.
Yeah, but like... That was... No, I didn't die.
I lived.
We died in the ice area, remember?
Oh, wait.
No, we didn't die in the ice area.
No, you did.
You did die here.
How did I do hear that?
I don't know.
Wait, you said go left.
Yeah.
I can't see.
Well, let me nudge you out the way, then.
Alright.
Hmm.
Let's see.
Is that the right way, Scoutmaster?
Scoutmaster!
I gave you a platform.
You're welcome, Scoutmaster.
You're welcome.
Does this ever disappear?
No.
Oh, no.
We're not going this way?
We go this way?
I don't know.
We're over here.
We have...
We have several...
Doki has several ropes.
I'm just gonna say that out loud.
Um...
Yeah, I do.
Don't shame her.
Um...
I'm not shaming.
I'm just saying that.
And...
Yeah, you tattle tell her.
I'm just saying that...
You're such a tattle teller.
We have to get further that someone is hoarding the supplies.
I am not hoarding.
Anyone else can open my backpack.
It's not just a me thing.
Anyone...
Put you off.
Do it.
Live.
Live with the crimes.
I don't know what we can do anymore.
Let's just go to the left side.
Right side.
Left side.
We kind of stranded ourselves by going down.
Why are you looking at me like that?
What the hell?
I mean, if we can get over here, that is such an easy way up.
I think she's dead.
What happened?
I think she died.
Did you see what happened?
She like ricocheted.
She just jumped.
She did a flip.
What did I do?
Wait, she's alive?
She's alive, she's alive, she's alive.
Oh my god, how does she live?
Yeah, that's why something a killer would ask.
How did she live?
How did she have no stamina for that?
Send the rope.
Wait, we can use the rope down here and then go to where the ammo is.
Or you could be gamers and catch the vine.
What could possibly go wrong?
Oh, okay.
Okay, let's do it.
No, use the rope if you're scared.
Use the rope if you're scared.
Oh my god.
Did she catch it?
Uh...
Um...
Did she... did she catch it?
Did she...
Mint?
Um...
It did start raining.
Did she just like slip and die?
Okay, go, go.
Is... can we... can we check on her?
Is this enough?
Can we check on her?
Let me know if it's enough.
Is this enough?
What?
Wait, I don't think this is gonna work.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Before I do this, Snuffy, go back up.
Snuffy, before we do this, I'm gonna put the backpack down and if anything happens to me...
No!
If anything happens to me...
You still have the backpack if anything happens to me.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Just in case.
Just...
Okay.
Do a prayer.
Remember your form.
Don't forget to press me.
Wait, what happened to me?
What?
You're like...
You look like you fell on the floor.
Wait, why can't I go down?
Oh no, I'm sleepy now.
I'm...
You're sleepy?
Do something!
Oh my god, now I can.
Okay.
Okay, I'm gonna jump down.
It's left click.
It's left click to...
I know it's him, fucker.
I'm...
I'm okay.
I grabbed the dog.
I lived.
I'm okay.
Grab the bugle, grab me from my garage.
I'm not gonna grab a stupid bugle.
I'm alive.
Everyone get back up.
Everybody... Where am I?
Where am I?
Don't say that.
No!
Get stick bugged.
I'm okay.
This is all men's fault.
This is all your fault.
This is your fault, men.
I told you were alive.
This is your... Okay.
Are you okay up there?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm good.
I'm on her own.
This is all... This is all your fault, men.
You mess with my groove.
Excuse me, men.
You've thrown off Doki by the groove.
Oh, I'm not.
Sorry.
I'm crying.
Okay.
My POV was so... You did this.
You did this.
For mine, I just saw Doki fucking bounce.
It was so good.
You cursed me.
It's okay.
Snuffy has the rest of the backpack.
Is Snuffy alive?
She is.
Hi, Snuffy.
Hi.
I was like, I don't know where everybody went.
I don't know where everybody went.
I don't know how she...
I don't even know how she...
But you died.
Did you live?
How did you die?
Someone... someone cursed me to all eternity.
Someone cursed me to all eternity.
That's kind of nice, though.
That's so romantic.
I'm dead!
What do you mean?
To be fair, as soon as I saw you hit the ground, I kind of marked you as deceased.
It was, like, a pretty bad... It was a pretty bad... Yeah, it was pretty bad.
I had, like, adrenaline shock from the hit.
So, like, I didn't die right away.
Like, Dresden was taking me over to the edge.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
I'll be right back.
Alright, I'm gonna check on that.
Are you close to the... I'm waiting.
You should just get to the tap.
No, no.
If you go too far, the Scoutmaster spawns and knocks you off the mountain.
Because teamwork is important.
Wait, really?
Yeah.
He fucking spawns and kicks you?
That's fucking hardcore.
Yeah, he chases you down and, like, takes you off the mountain.
He's like, wow, you're not working as a team?
Go fuck yourself.
Wow.
Okay, so all we need is Snuffy to die, then.
Or, you know, get to me.
One or the other.
I used your Snuffy ghost.
Did you hear that?
Snuffy was like, what?
Hi, Snuffy.
It's okay.
You'll be fine.
Did you hear something?
Somebody just said something to me.
No.
Who said what?
Mint?
Oh, it must have been Mint.
I can't believe... What did she say?
Are you able to get off Snuffy?
Um... She doesn't know what to do.
I can, like... Can you get to here?
Oh, wait, sure.
You're literally right there next to her.
Oh, I got you.
I got you.
Yeah, you guys got each other.
This way.
I'm... Okay.
Just tumbling.
Hey, girl.
What's up?
Hey, what is this, like, wind?
Do you see, like, wind or something?
Yes, yeah.
I don't know what that's about.
I think it's a broken waterfall.
Yeah.
At least just no clipping.
This, honestly, this map generation seems kind of funky.
Oh, yeah, here it is.
What the fuck?
I do think getting robbed out of our, like, big luggage at the top is kind of cruel for the RNG.
I can't believe Peak is the game that's fucking destroying my PC right now.
So, do we wanna go around this way?
Or around this way?
Because it's kinda clean and nice.
Yeah.
Because my main monitor keeps flickering from black screen to the main... Oh.
Oh.
That's not good, right?
That's... No, that's usually...
Uh, it's evolving.
Can you guys relate to this picture card?
It's trying to talk to you.
I don't think that's it.
Hold on, let me... Let's check this way around.
This will...
Guys, I might need to take my PC to the doctor's tomorrow.
I haven't installed my new CPU yet, because I didn't have time to go to the...
The...
The PC people.
She went to the other side.
You should go back down.
Going down?
Yeah, she went... No, left side.
Where you came from?
She went the other way.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
Oh, whoa.
You're on the vine.
How did we...
How did we get up top?
I don't remember how we get up top.
I don't remember the way either now.
There's a good mushroom over here, but...
Maybe this way?
Wait, we could climb from there, right?
Well, that works.
Yes.
I'm back, sorry.
I was getting more tea, too.
Oh, god.
Are you good?
Yeah.
What kind of tea did you get?
Yeah, what kind of tea?
Zephi, could you give me a hand up?
Nice again, my job.
Yes, yes.
Thank you.
Look at you guys.
You're almost there.
Whoa!
Are you?
Maybe?
I think so.
We're making progress.
I believe.
Go to the water.
He he he.
You just jump out into the abyss?
Yeah.
Dang.
Watch your stock don't let it fall!
Ooh, but what if it does fall?
Every time someone in this game dies they immediately become like, I don't know the call of the void or some shit.
Oh, there's a medicinal root!
Carrot!
Do you need medicine?
No.
Oh, thank you.
Hey, you are such a feeder.
I'm just concerned.
Thank you very much.
Wow, Snuff, I didn't know you were into that.
No.
That's why she's carrying the thick mints.
Oh, extra thick.
Thank you.
Oh, this is so straightforward.
This is good.
Yeah, this is nice.
It only took two of our friends fucking dying to get over here.
But you can't climb up from there.
I wasn't.
My death could have been...
My death could have been avoided.
No, my death could have been avoided.
There's a luggage over there.
What are you talking about?
You literally caused it yourself.
There's a luggage to your left side.
Okay, just trying to find a good path.
Do you think we make this vine climb?
I...
Yeah.
I think so.
Do you have good stat?
You got any extra?
Do it.
Maybe, but...
Alright...
If you were watching...
What were you avoiding...
Oh, I love the boy.
Oh, that was close.
I broke my shins a little bit.
Oh my god, thank you.
I thought you were gone.
I think I was in shock for a second.
I saw that.
Something literally...
Something literally paused.
It's gradual damage.
Oh, I can't see because of the fog.
This sucks.
Oh, Snuffy went the wrong way.
I think we're under a tree.
No, Snuffy went the wrong way.
Come up this way.
Oh my god, Snuffy is eating.
No, the left rock!
The left rock!
No, the wrong way!
The wrong way, Snuffy!
This way, this way, this way!
No, the back rock!
She's damaging!
Oh, oh!
Oh, Snuffy is patting me!
Now, Snuffy, no!
No!
No deil!
Yes!
Croware.
Yes, Crocule dies with her!
Yes!
Crocule dies with her!
Throw Crocule off!
Throw Crocule off before you die!
No!
Yes!
Throw him on!
Throw Crocule off!
That's it!
He's sniffing.
Alright Diamond drin, it's up to you!
I think we went the wrong way.
It sucks here.
I think- I think maybe we made a wrong turn.
I think we went the wrong way... I think we should- Oh right.
Wait.
To the right.
There's still a far ways away too.
Oh gosh.
Yeah.
I think the right way was- Go on, they're so fast!
I think we were just really slow.
Yeah, we kinda like meandered around a little bit.
I think the right way was the right way.
Yeah.
No, no, you can make it.
I believe.
I think you guys should have grabbed the vine.
I grabbed it.
It was... No, look at this.
I think this is a tree.
Oh, no, no, no.
Different tree.
Never mind.
It has bees.
There's the bees.
It is a bee tree, but I think it's a different bee tree.
The environment looks different.
Oh, wait, no.
Not though, right?
Bees.
Oh, that's the same... You touched a spike in the wall.
That's pretty...
Oh, it's waning.
It's waning.
Yeah, it's waning.
It's pouring.
The old man is snoring.
He hid his head.
And something sounded something, and came up and went to the...
Yaay!
That's the story of me.
So I don't have... I don't have the same drink I had last time to make this.
This is exactly the same cliff and I don't have the drink.
It's okay, you have... Wait, don't you have drink in your backpack?
No, someone swiped it.
Who would have done such a thing?
I don't know.
Don't talk to her.
Oh, it was you, wasn't it, Min?
It was you.
You swiped it.
I didn't actually... You swiped it.
I got a water bottle, but it was in my backpack.
I would have said I did.
Uh-oh, gosh.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Careful, careful.
Alright, since we're all confessing right now, I may or may not have been the one that swiped the energy drink.
Oh my god.
The worst kept secret ever.
I mean, I kinda watched you do it.
It may or may...
She was giving you the time to confess.
It would may...
Yeah, and I did!
And I did!
And all is forgiven in the eyes of God.
Oh, okay.
You're a ghost.
There is no...
I just have some unfinished business.
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Ow, ow, ow.
Oh, oh, ow.
That's a lot of spikes!
Fucking rain, fucking rain, fucking rain, fucking rain, fucking rain.
If I have my drink, this would be so much easier.
Oh, man, I know, right?
The character looks so angry.
So, it's just unfortunate.
I wouldn't...
Oh my gosh, you're so close.
Oh, this is fucked.
There's like nothing here.
Yeah, there's a rock.
There's a rock that has a green patch.
Get to the left, that rock.
I see it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then you can climb up that.
There you go.
And then all is for Giffin.
Oh,
that was so close.
Alright.
And then you just gotta climb that.
I don't want to worry you but the fog cometh.
Yeah, but it's not Okay.
The fog cometh and the fog can take you.
So you made it!
I did take you.
You made it!
You're at the top.
Woo!
Oh my god.
We did it.
I feed Lima and she carried us.
Yeah!
We did woo!
Yay!
Oh my god.
We were all there.
Oh my god!
We were all there!
We're heroes!
Yay!
I'm back.
Welcome back, everybody.
You still have that open?
Yeah, that suitcase is still up there.
How do you get that?
I don't know.
You can't climb this, too.
I think it was just generated, like, fucked up.
Yeah.
There's a backpack here.
Corral boost!
Wait a minute.
So are you guys gonna see the capybaras this time?
Oh yeah, I wanna see a capybara!
Yeah.
Gotta go fast.
Unfortunately, I had just died, so we don't have gungle or the trumpet.
Yeah.
Oh, can I cook the herbs?
Can you?
Herbs!
I wonder where one of them went.
Hmm.
I wonder what happened to the other marshmallow, too.
Huh.
Nah.
Funny.
You guys are gonna get overtaken.
I'm climbing.
The freezing ears.
You know what?
By the time I get my... I got Invisalign in.
By the time I get those out, it's gonna feel weird to have my teeth actually be able to touch each other.
Like, I'm just gonna be uncomfortable and, like, for anything else with my own mouth.
That sounds... What's Invisalon?
It's like braces, but better.
They're, like, a retainer, like, right?
Yeah.
Huh?
It's kind of like, like, it covers your whole mouth, right?
It's cold.
It's like a little plastic tray that your teeth, like, uh...
sits around your teeth.
It's molded to the shape of your teeth.
Is it still cold?
How much to buy your yeast Invisalon?
It's a lot more expensive than regular braces, from what I've heard.
It... depends.
Like... Yeah, there's another suitcase.
Oh, there's that suit.
I remember that suitcase.
I'm heading over.
Yeah.
I don't think it's even more subtle than normal braces if they put enough attachments in, which I have.
Uh...
You get, like, sparkles and, like...
Oh, yeah, did you add, like, stickers on it or something, like...
...can you bling it?
...can you put, like, bling on it?
Like, bedazzle it?
I don't know, actually.
Yeah!
If you can bedazzle it.
I think, like, yeah.
Oh, wait, wait.
I might actually die.
Oh, I'm okay.
I'm okay!
Wait, that's a medicinal road?
Gimme!
Oh, I stubbed my toe.
When did I stub my toe?
I don't know.
It didn't feel!
Yeah!
Really?
We can go cave dive and see it through to the end!
Oh, my God!
We can finally, we can cave dive!
That's what our boys wanted!
...execute me.
Min, did you not cook your marshmallow?
It was you.
You totally didn't steal that marshmallow.
It was you!
You bastard!
I'll remember this.
I remembered already.
Why do you think it was gone?
Oh, it was just us, too.
It would be a shame if something happened.
I'll push you into the store.
Nobody will see.
Nobody will hear you die.
Nobody will hear you scream.
It's like, if a tree falls down an empty forest.
Oh,
my God.
There has to be more food somewhere.
I think we should go to the way that we were going before Snuffy and I died.
Yeah.
Oh, there's food right here.
Oh, you got some.
That's right.
I got some oranges.
Some orange eyes.
I have a marshmallow.
It's really yummy.
I don't need your stupid marshmallows.
I have nature to save me.
Oh, shoot.
Oh, no.
That's right.
You can't have it.
Take it from my dead hands.
I'm gonna fucking... I'm gonna choke you.
I'm gonna choke you and no one will know.
No one will...
That's right.
I took it.
You didn't take it.
Do you get the boost from it?
Yeah.
Okay.
Wait, where are they?
It was a science experiment.
Hello.
Wait, where... Don't forget capybars to the left.
Wait, where's the capybars?
I want to see the capybars.
I didn't get to see them.
I'm heading over.
Run.
Get there before the storm comes.
Wait, does it affect you when you're in there?
When you're in the storm?
No, it doesn't.
Yeah, as long as you're in the water, you're okay.
Oh, is that them right there?
Oh, my God.
They're so easy to get there.
Yeah.
Yeah, they're right there.
Oh, my God.
I want to... I want to be there with the capybaras.
I'm tired.
I'm so tired.
This way.
Hello, little capybaras.
I am here.
I hope they don't touch the lava.
They're awfully close to lava.
Oh, my God.
They're so cute.
Oh, eat it.
Just stay in the water.
It doesn't hurt you in here, no.
Yeah.
We're so safe.
Why is it purple?
I wish we had the blue one.
It's like a... It's a hot spring.
What the heck?
Maybe...
Maybe the pH level is changed.
Oh, yeah.
It's reflecting the clouds.
Wait.
Is green bad?
Yeah, the green...
Shut up.
The P levels are high because I was in there.
Guys, I think we should go to where Snuffy and I were at before.
Which was?
Yeah, okay.
It's over towards the left.
Yeah.
The other way seems really difficult.
It was.
What are you guys...
cackling about?
Nothing.
I think you should find my tree and tickle my bird eggs.
Alright.
You want me to feed you and satisfy your fetish?
What the?
You want me...
I'm feeding.
Yum, yum, yum, yum.
Oh, you liked watching, didn't you?
I don't know what I was watching.
I don't know what I was witnessing.
Does someone have the other heel root, perhaps?
Oh, there's...
I need it.
What happened to you?
I have this.
No?
I don't have it.
Okay.
I have this.
Is this what you wanted?
Yeah.
Could you feed it to me?
He said, please?
I fell on my butt.
Please.
Please what?
Get in!
Please feed me the root, ducky.
There you go.
Thank you.
You did it.
I don't know that he fucking fried.
Oh,
nice jump.
Whoa.
Parkour!
Parkour, stop!
Get outta my way!
Get outta my head!
This is gonna require ultimate teamwork together.
I believe.
I don't remember even where me and Min were.
Me too.
It was like... I don't remember either, actually.
Is this the right way, Scoutmaster?
Cause you're hugging.
I mean, it looks pretty good, honestly.
I have no idea.
I'd go by based on tools and vibes.
Has it been working?
I don't need a map or a compass.
I got vibes.
I got my vibes.
My body tells me this is the right way.
The wind is blowing.
I can smell it.
You go here?
Where are you going?
I have no idea.
I'm going... I'm listening to a Scoutmaster.
Whoa!
Me too.
Also, is the implication that the Scoutmaster is actually a psychopath and has put us through this trial on purpose?
Because the campfire is set up with marshmallows at the top every time?
Well, when you told me that he comes and attacks us, I was like...
Yeah, he's like... So does he have, like, anti-air or some shit that blew up our plane?
We... Yeah, we could've... We could've been saved this whole time, but...
Yeah!
Scoutmaster wants this for us.
Yeah, like, he has anti-air.
Yeah, if you... If you climb ahead of your friends, which is, uh...
While I was waiting for Snuffy on the last map, if you climb too far ahead, he spawned...
Oh my god, that means I could've died earlier when I was climbing ahead.
I was kinda waiting for it to happen, yeah.
Wait, this is safe.
We can all just leave Doki behind.
Wait, what?
Wait, I'm literally right here!
Wait...
I'm literally right here!
Being left behind doesn't make him show up.
That's it, I'm angry, I'm eating this.
I'm yum, yum, yum, yum.
I'm gonna eat my anger.
There's actually so much food on this mountain, holy crap.
You're not you when you're hungry.
Yeah.
Mmm...
Maybe I'm here.
We go left or right?
Okay.
Oh, I see a suitcase down there.
Yeah, I see a suitcase there too, but is it worth it?
I don't know.
There's nowhere to go left.
I think that, that, that much is clear.
Maybe, can we climb this tree and jump to here?
That seems kinda flushed.
Mmm, Scoutmasters, you're- Oh, there's a thuggish down, right down there.
Wait, is she dead?
Oh, she's okay, she's okay.
I don't think we can climb that.
The branches, you cannot grab, guys.
I just wanna- Okay.
You cannot grab.
There is a suitcase all over there.
Wait, so we can't touch the pretty blue crystal either?
They turn, they freeze you.
Oh.
Oh, so what do we do?
We just go down?
I mean, you can touch them briefly.
Does anyone have rope?
Like, don't we have a chaingun or something?
We have- We have- I don't think anyone grabbed the chaingun.
What?
How did nobody grab the chaingun?
I guess nobody grabbed the chaingun.
Where was the chaingun?
It was in the last map, I thought.
Nobody grabbed it.
Nobody grabbed the chaingun.
I saw it, but I thought someone with a backpack was gonna grab it.
I think that was the last one.
We're just misremembering.
Yeah, there's two people with backpacks and that's not us, Doki.
Yeah, it's not us.
It's not our fun.
We didn't have room.
I think we're gonna make like that.
I have a shelf thing.
Will that help?
Oh yeah, that should.
Maybe.
Yeah, maybe we could shelf that.
Oh, wait, wait.
Pass the shelf.
I can- Don't worry, I'm MLG.
Watch this.
Okay, okay.
I'm watching, I'm watching.
Watch this.
Ha!
Very good.
Yeah, and then we grab there and then we get over there.
Right?
Wait, that fell the chain launcher.
I thought we were going- Oh, we have a chain launcher.
Nevermind.
Oh, you found the chain launcher.
She has the chain launcher.
Okay, maybe we go to the shelf and then go there.
Either way, I think we want this.
Okay.
What do we want?
Okay, we get to the- We climb to the shelf.
Okay, okay.
Alright, who's doing- You can do it, Snuffy.
Snuffy!
What if I get this?
Really far.
Wait, I kinda- Can it work?
Hold on.
Wait, what are we doing?
I think she might.
She's experimenting.
Oh?
Yo!
Hey, don't get too hasty now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't get too confident there.
Don't get too overconfident.
The fog is coming.
Come on, the fog is coming.
We can't be- Easy.
Oh, nice.
Wait, can we make it?
I'm gonna rest a little bit before- Oh, that's such a fucking bad timing for the storm.
No, take it easy, guys!
Oh, nice.
Wait, how do I get off this thing?
You press space.
Yup.
Space.
Space bar.
Okay.
Are you coming?
You coming over too?
I kinda got fucked if I had to jump off the shelter, so I might be scared.
I tried to put it some way that like- Can we even climb up that?
No, you can climb up that?
I think I'm fucked.
Wait, no!
No, wait.
I have rope.
Okay.
That would be cool.
There's lava.
It's fine.
Imma check that suitcase.
Oh, woah, woah, woah, woah.
I'm not gonna check the suitcase.
Oh, woah, woah, woah, woah, woah.
I can, yeah.
Okay, I'm gonna put it- I'm huddled.
I'm huddled.
I'm like a penguin.
You know when a baby penguin's not huddled and it dies?
Yeah, yeah.
I hope that's enough.
Oh.
Why does the lava not keep us warm?
I think it does a little bit.
Wow.
Okay, I'm going for the suitcase.
Oh, it's a lantern.
Does the lantern keep us hot?
I don't know.
Oh, we go up.
What are those?
Oh, that's a flashbang.
Yeah, yeah, and she almost ran into the lava.
Yeah, the one where she almost ran into lava.
Oh, you can come straight up here.
Give me your hand.
There you go.
I got you.
I'm okay.
Maybe I'll climb up here.
All right.
Oh, yeah, this is how we do it.
Oh, nice.
Yeah, this run is going pretty good right now.
Is she dead?
Is she alive?
I lost all my extra energy.
Oh, no.
I'm going to check where to go after this.
Okay, there you go.
Come back up, Snuffy.
I got you.
I'm okay.
Wee.
We're going.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
And then... How did you get all the way up there?
I just climb.
Just keep climbing.
Oh, wait.
It's a little spot here.
Yeah, just keep climbing.
Okay.
Oh, by the lava.
Oh, the lava.
Don't touch the lava.
It's a little spicy.
That's what the sound of mixing.
I don't know where to go after this.
I'm going to wait for Scoutmaster Lammu.
I think we actually want to go, like, around this way.
Yeah, it's not here.
You see this little bit here?
No.
There.
Oh, that seems kind of hard.
How are you going to get there with lava?
I don't know.
How is it looking that way?
Is it okay?
It's good.
I think it's better.
It's better.
Okay.
Let's go this way, then.
I think it's a little bit easier.
Although, how do we get up that first part there?
We're climbing.
There's actually a huge jump, though.
Oh, so was it okay?
Oh.
I'll try.
I feel like this one might actually be more straightforward.
If you can get across there, and then you go up here, and then up here...
I will watch you guys...
Uh, okay.
I mean, you can maybe use the tree.
Wait, but there's a luggage over there.
Yeah.
Oh, that's a huge fucking jump.
We have another rope.
It's not that big of a jump.
I miss my lollipop.
Gamer legs, oh.
What do we do, Scoutmaster?
Um, yum, yum, yum.
Um, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum.
Who's hungry?
Anybody?
I'm all right.
Okay, thank you.
Okay.
Yay!
We go over there?
To the right side?
Wow.
Do people get made it, though?
There's no way.
Yeah, it's so far.
Where else will we go?
Wow.
Oh, my gosh, she's doing it.
Do your best.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh, Scoutmaster.
Scoutmaster did it.
Scoutmaster, she's a Scoutmaster.
It's not too bad.
You can, like, this is straight.
Just jump up.
What, jump?
I got my arm up for you.
Jump, yeah.
Wow!
Scoutmaster did it!
I'm so proud of you.
Oh, my God, I'm gaming!
Ma, get the camera!
Yeah!
You stay, you stay, you stay.
We burn it!
Yeah, we're here for the storm, I think.
Be careful, don't touch the rock.
Don't touch the rock.
It's a dangerous rock.
Wait, can we climb anywhere?
I'm touching it.
There's some food above us as well, for those who don't have stamina.
Is it a safe place?
It's red suits.
It's nice.
I'm gonna go this way.
It's like a little cave in there.
Oh, we're going the other way.
Wait, now, can you stick out your hand?
Because I might fall.
JK, I'm okay.
You're great.
You're doing wonderfully.
I'm doing so well.
Here we go after that.
There's some food in this tree if you want any.
No.
It's too far.
Please climb the trees.
Wait, where do we go after this?
Anybody need any food?
Oh, I'm okay.
I'm a king.
I'll get an extra one.
Is that the right...
Okay.
I think we had some of the pitons somewhere.
Oh, wow.
Thanks a lot.
I can put my arm out for you.
You're welcome.
Wait, that one was all me.
I'm glad I was very helpful.
Wait, why do I...
Why can't I stand?
I got you.
Oh, whoa, whoa.
I'm cold.
I feel so cold.
You're cool.
I feel cold.
Hey, no, you're so cool.
Where's Min?
Are we all fitting on you somehow?
We're here.
We're all here.
Alrighty.
Alright.
Up we go.
Clam, clam, clam.
Wait, I don't even like this.
Yeah, I don't like this either.
Wait.
Oh, not, not yeah.
Not yeah.
There.
Yes.
Oh, Jesus.
There's this bit here?
If we can jump across the lava behind Min.
Oh.
But it's still really far.
That's scary.
What about to our left?
That's like really far.
Anything over that way?
Actually, yeah.
I wonder if I eat, if I can make it up there.
Okay.
I'm gonna try.
No, you, you, I don't, I don't think so, Min.
Is that safe?
Oh.
I made it.
Come this way, Min.
We got it.
This is safe.
I'm gonna try up here.
Min, be careful.
Min, come this way.
Oh, there's a safe, there's a safe.
Oh, no.
Someone else has to, someone else has to do this.
Can you see my rope?
Do you have, what's your...
I'm good.
But if I just need an extra, just a little bit of stamina to get that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're fine.
I got it.
Okay.
Stick out.
Oh.
Okay, hold on.
Wait, don't come up yet.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I got a selfie.
I'm gonna...
I'm so cold.
Snuffy, I'm so cold.
Snuffy, I'm really cold.
I need a lantern.
Come here, come here.
Where?
Where's he there?
Where are you?
Come here.
Oh, oh, oh.
I need the lantern.
I'm so cold.
Okay, I'm good.
I'm good.
I'm okay now.
I'm still here.
I'm ready to grab you.
Okay, give me a sec.
I need to get up.
Oh, no, my lantern.
Oh.
Okay.
Okay, give me a sec.
I need to recharge my stamina.
Can you get up here?
Okay.
Alright.
Alright, I'm coming up.
I'm coming up.
She's coming up.
I'm here.
Is that... Oh, nice.
Lollipop.
Nice.
Snuffy, if you can climb up here, I got the... I'm gonna hide in here in case the blizzard comes.
Oh my god.
Is Min okay?
No.
Oh my god.
They're freaking out about something, but it's the kind of voice you'd use when you see it.
I see a cute animal, so I'm not sure what's going on over there.
Hold on, wait.
I gotta shelter for a second.
Me too.
Are you guys okay?
Are you guys okay down there?
Okay, we're here.
Try... try to come quickly, though, because we're running out of time.
Yeah, yeah, I'm here.
What's happening?
Grab my hand.
Right here, right above you.
Oh.
Grab my hand.
Thanks.
I almost didn't make it.
There you go.
Yeah, we're lowed.
We did it, guys.
We are in this tree up here.
Run, run, run, run!
Oh, hold on, hold on, hold on!
We are little penguins!
Stand here, stand here!
It doesn't hit here, too.
Yeah, it doesn't hit here, either.
I think we're dead, yeah.
Get off of us!
Oh my god!
No, you guys can crouch-boost me!
If you jump on each other's heads, you can boost jump.
What?!
Boost jump me!
Do it!
You can get that baton up there, maybe.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go!
How many people can be on a baton?
Uh, for those- those rusty ones, I don't think you can both do it.
Oh.
No.
Don't try!
Wait, I thought your energy- I thought your- I thought your energy comes back after.
I thought so, too.
Yeah.
I'm not sure about those special ones.
Oh!
That was, like, so confused.
Don- Dur, why did you hold your hand out?!
That's right, that's right, that's right!
Well, some of us- Oh my god!
Look at that bug!
Okay, I think I can- oh god- I think I can eat- and maybe lift this up.
Yeah, this doesn't... Wait, this doesn't give you energy at all.
Like the... Oh wait, it does.
Wait, this is bugged up.
Now it did.
Oh, weird.
Wait, so you're good now?
Yeah, it's good.
Okay, I'll wait.
I got you.
I swear.
I'm coming the same way as Rogi!
Oh, it collapsed.
It broke.
Oh yeah, it does that after a while.
Mad cause bad.
My hand is up here.
My hand is out.
I tried to grab you.
We're so close.
We're so close guys.
My hand...
That's not true.
I was here.
My hand was out.
Yes it is.
Look at my hand.
It's literally out.
So I didn't know she was doing that.
What did I do?
I didn't do anything!
What the fuck did I do?
What do you mean you didn't know I was doing?
What did I even do?
I don't even know what I even did.
You're doing nothing!
That's the issue!
Oh no.
Oh.
There's so much blue rock.
Wait, how did you were able to time that?
Does it freeze kill you?
I'm so tempted to touch it.
It gives you a little freeze like the snow thingy.
The same as the blizzard.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, okay, okay.
Wait, I don't understand.
I can't get on top of that.
I don't know.
How come you let her on top of it but not me?
This rock?
Right here too.
Wait.
Oh.
I'm on top.
Oh, maybe it's like just...
No, no, no!
Yeah, see?
I told you.
No, no!
I'll push you off the wheel.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
My move!
There you go.
Ah!
Oh, I'm sorry!
You took me off with you!
There's a petard here!
Wait, I don't understand.
I can't seem to... I can't seem to... I can't seem to... I can't seem to... I can't get on it.
I don't know.
Skill issue.
There you go.
I'm on it.
I'm on it now.
Yay!
Teamwork!
It makes the dream work.
Where do we go now, Scoutmaster?
I'm taking a look, hold on.
She's taking a look.
We're gonna take a look, too.
I'm taking a piss.
At this whole situation.
Wait, where did she go?
Wait, what happened?
I heard the...
Snuffy, are you okay?
Wait, what did she do?
Did you push her down?
What did you do?
I don't know what happened to her.
Wait, there's a campfire!
It's okay, if she's dead, it's okay.
There's a campfire!
She, like, ricocheted so bad.
What happened?
I'm sorry.
What did you do?
What did you do, Stuffy?
Did you commit the murder?
Did you murder?
I think Min thinks... I'm sorry, I think Snuffy thinks you committed a murder.
What did I do?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
She was saying she's so dead.
I thought she was threatening you, but I think she was talking about Mint falling.
Oh, yeah, no, she's dead.
There she is.
Yeah, I died.
How did you die?
Oh, no.
I fell.
Thank you.
I fell, and then I...
Wait, but how did you fall?
I don't think you had enough stamina.
Yeah, I didn't have enough stamina.
Alright, don't worry.
You should have said I had a little berry I would've given it to you.
Yeah, I had a lollipop.
I wouldn't have given it to you, but I had it.
Yeah, I know you... whatever.
I'll get there.
Don't worry, my arm is up here.
Okay, I got it.
There you go.
There you go, there you go.
It would've worked eventually.
Did we make it?
Oh my god, we made it!
We're gamers!
You practically are still here.
Did you have anything with you?
Yeah, so true, so true.
I was... I was.
At least we didn't have the heartbreak between using Bungle again.
Yeah, here it is.
Yeah, because we already lost him.
Yeah, we lost that guy.
Yeah, somebody dropped him.
I wonder who.
Wait, what?
I don't think it was actually me!
We did it!
We lord of the flies-ed it!
Break me back!
Somebody!
Wait, there's only two marshmallows!
Thank you!
Oh no!
I instantly grabbed the item!
Oh my god!
I'll put some stuff on.
Are you gonna take the backpack?
I don't trust you...
Put stuff in my backpack.
Yeah, well...
Did you take my marshmallow too, huh?
There was only two marshmallows.
What?
Why?
Not even for me?
Yeah.
I don't know why.
Yeah, there's only two.
Snuffy, do you need food?
I need orange bear, I suppose.
Are you sure?
Cause I'm fine.
I have- I have snacks.
Wait, Snuffy.
Look in my backpack.
I have snacks in there.
Snack pack.
I only had one snack.
That's right.
There was only one.
Okay, so this one is actually fully horizontal.
You see where the smoke is?
Yeah.
We gotta just navigate the lava.
Oh yeah.
Snack break.
Snack- At least there's no blizzard now.
It's just lava.
Yeah.
Wait, but I can see the- the fire.
Yeah, it's horizontal.
Yeah, it's- Oh, it's parkour!
It's literally parkour!
It's American Ninja Warrior.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it's- Uh, I think we go left.
Okay.
Maybe?
Well, actually, that one's kinda far.
I don't know.
No, we kinda have to go this way, I think.
This way?
Yeah, okay.
I'm already committed.
Like this way, and then across here.
Okay.
Cause I don't think- I mean, unless we take a little bit of toasty damage there.
What would you guys like to do?
I will listen to Scoutmaster Lamu.
Okay.
I'm down.
I listened.
He's already gone.
Alright.
I'm going in.
Oh shoot!
Ouch!
I'm in!
Don't forget- Oh my gosh, Mint!
Don't forget!
If you turn around- Whoa!
Whoa!
This is scary, Scoutmaster!
This is very scary!
You hurt so bad!
Oh my god, what is this pillar of flame?
Yeah, I don't like that.
These are scary.
I guess I think there's no food in this area.
Uh, there are like bird eggs around.
Oh, okay, okay.
Oh, nice.
Yeah, fuck those birds.
Um, I'm gonna- Um, I don't know.
You will sometimes take fire damage, but it like- It cools off.
Is that the right way to go?
Yes?
Weee!
Because you're not clad- It's just parkour!
Parkour!
I don't have stamina!
Ow!
Thank you!
It's okay, we'll grip you!
We'll grip you firmly!
Please carry me!
Princess, carry me!
The whole way!
Please?
Alright.
What do we do here?
Wait, I didn't see what has... the chain?
Yeah, you can climb the chain.
Just be careful.
If it's a little, you might take fire damage.
Fire damage is okay.
It'll work off.
Oh.
Ouch.
My little feetsies.
Oh.
It hurts so much.
Oh my little feetsies.
Oh no, she's burning alive.
She's burning alive.
Oh my god.
You haven't met yet.
I think Snuffy just kind of tossed her backpack into the lava.
But that's okay.
What happened to her backpack?
The backpack's gone.
Yeah.
I got everything from my backpack.
Oh, no.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's this way.
It's this way, Snuffy.
This way.
Snuffy.
Snuffy, turn around.
Snuffy, Min's on.
Wait, Min, you're okay.
Yay.
Yeah, she just burned to death and then recovered.
Does anyone have food?
Because I'm not gonna make it.
I don't have food.
Yeah, I do.
You need to get over here now.
I have food too.
Look at my nice warm toasty marshmallows.
Wait, I'm letting the
fire...
You can go first.
Oh, the lava's coming up.
This is gonna make me touch lava.
That is killing me.
Oh, my God.
I have the high ground now, Anakin.
Oh, baby.
Ouch.
Why did you... No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
Oh, my God.
Why did she do the same thing?
I didn't know.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
You could have waited.
Oh, that was a rough one.
My honor.
I'm defending my honor waiting for what?
I was literally on down here.
You could have waited for the lava to cool down.
There was a gonna cool.
Yes, it was.
It was cool.
It's like high tide.
Oh, I didn't know that.
What do you mean?
I've been dead this whole time.
Why would I know?
I didn't actually know that either.
I didn't know it goes up and down.
I saw it.
Let the lava go up and go down.
Well, how were we supposed to see it?
Use your eyes and the eyes tell you.
We'll have to wait for this one.
I think it's about to catch fire.
I'm rooting for your death, Donkey Kong.
Yeah, you wish you had this lollipop.
Oh, lollipop.
Look at this lollipop.
Mint was literally begging for anybody to feed her so she could make it.
No, I was like I was like if you make it here I can give you this lollipop this marshmallow I said that I didn't say that shit.
Yes I did it.
I was like I have this marshmallow that I can give you if you make it.
All the marshmallow that you stole?
because..
What do you mean I stole?
I got there before you!
I was dead!
Too bad, maybe you shouldn't have died.
Maybe you shouldn't have died.
No, yeah.
I'm gonna kill you again.
I'm gonna kill you.
Why are you going?
Why are you going, baby?
Cause the sticky catches on fire, so I'm making sure it doesn't.
Look how fast Limeo is gonna get pushed off the mountain.
Well, that's her fault.
If she gets pushed up.
No, she is, because you're so slow.
No, I'm waiting for it.
Look, look.
It's gonna catch off.
Oh my gosh.
Oh my god, that's gonna catch on fire.
That's because you took too long.
And the god is angry.
No, it's fine.
It's fine.
Yes, it is.
I'm gonna wait until this catches on fire and then I'll go.
I don't think it will.
Yes, it will.
Oh, wow.
That's really fun.
Yeah.
You were the chosen one.
You were my brother.
I trusted you.
Wait, how did she do this, actually?
I was not paying attention.
Okay, stop being on fire.
Okay.
I actually was not paying attention.
Oh my god.
Shut the fuck up.
I can report you for inciting deaf violence towards me.
I don't care.
I'm gonna tell them.
that you told me to the scoutmaster.
I'm gonna report you to the scoutmaster for, um, doing deaf friends towards me.
Holy shit.
Are you guys good?
And I have some fucking demon here yelling, die, die, die, in my ear.
I don't care if that's what she was shouting.
Even though her step wasn't even my fault.
She is blaming me.
I'm starving.
I needed energy and I had that.
I literally said, hey, if you make it through, if you make it, I can give you my marshmallows.
That's what I said.
I did not know.
I didn't know.
I didn't know you'd eat it before.
Information was...
You have to give her the lollipop.
She would rather die than give her the lollipop.
Nobody gets it.
You should have just waited until it receded.
How did you wait?
The lollipop went down.
No, I didn't let it.
Oh my gosh.
I don't know.
Maybe because like someone kept yelling, die, die, die, die.
That I wasn't paying attention to the lava.
That was clearly...
You shouldn't... What do you mean?
You're supposed to use your eyes and wait for it to go back down.
Oh yeah, yeah, let the guy...
You didn't know?
Die, die, die, die, die, die, die.
It worked, it worked.
You manifested the downtime of the first scout number.
I hope you get a badge.
I'm pretty sure... Is that gonna actually like catch on fire?
I don't know.
I don't know, I can't tell.
I think it's just because it's high right now.
Yeah.
Nice.
You can just climb up.
Climb, climb, climb.
Oh, now you're not gonna say die, die, die.
Die, die, die.
Yay!
It's called being a team player.
Oh yeah, you're the best team player out there.
That's for sure.
Lily, you are definitely not rooting for anybody's demise there.
No!
Wow!
I'm rooting for Limu all the way!
Yay!
Oh look, there's only three marshmallows.
No, there's four!
There, I can see them with my eyes!
Die, die.
Die, die, die, die.
Thanks!
Oh yeah!
Take all the loot before Doki eats it all!
Look at that, look what I got, guys!
Oh my god, you got it back!
Never punish!
I got my lollipop back!
Oh, I want this instead.
Wait, no lollipop.
No lollipop for you.
Look, the lollipop got res too, guys!
Oh wait, I can just do this.
Did we have any climbing items?
Nope.
Does anyone have a sports drink?
No.
Oh, I don't have sports drink.
I have food and lollipop.
That's all I have.
Oh, just kidding.
That's, that's kind of what it was.
Sorry, I meant, I meant an energy drink.
That's my bad.
I'm ready.
Let's, I'm ready.
I'm ready to go.
I'm ready.
Let's go.
Let's go into the hall where there's the gold.
Dubs of hell!
Yeah!
Yay!
I hope Scoutmaster is smiling down upon us.
I hope so too.
Scoutmaster's gonna be so proud of us.
Doot doot!
I'm already proud of myself.
Hey!
Let's go.
The hall is the gold!
Yeah!
It's like laggy as hell.
Yeah.
The hall is the gold!
What?
Yeah!
We have to pay the troll toll to get inside the boys hole!
Into the boys hole!
What?
I don't think anybody has ever said that to me, but you just said it in tandem.
You never heard of the critically acclaimed musical?
What was it just been cold?
Take neRail.
I don't know the only thing.
I don't know the only thing about our park.
Is emotions biting and wegiment?
AAAAAAA Fight champion of the sun!
He is the protector of friendship and everyone.
Oh my god, I can imagine it.
I can imagine it.
Yeah, maybe like, I won't have a fucking little demon on my left ear yelling, die.
I'll be good, I'll be good.
I'll be a good boy, I swear.
I swear.
The killin?
The killin.
You mean, killin?
Did he say that again?
What does that say?
I thought it was like, I'm killin' you.
The killin.
I don't know how it really depends.
I feel like the left looks kinda good.
What's the gimmick here?
Is it all to catch on fire?
There's rocks that hurt you.
Uh, no, it's just hard.
Like, the pathway that it gives you is hard, and sometimes, it's like, you can't really do it very well without items.
Okay.
Yeah, you can run out of items to climb this.
Yeah, so it's kinda like, more of a, did you do well the rest of the game check, which, uh...
Oh!
Oh, that scared me!
Oh ho ho ho ho ho ho!
If I die, the lollipop dies with me.
Wait, where did, where did Naimu go?
Yeah, where did Naimu go?
I don't know where she went.
I don't know what her pathway is.
Thank you!
Yep!
Okay.
Get up there.
I don't know.
Hahaha!
I'm just, I'm just going by vibes.
Oh, keep going.
Wait, Naimu, I think you might have to stop, because they're, they're pretty far down.
Oh, oh, okay.
Oh, okay.
Here, I'm here.
Nice?
Alright.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Where do we go now?
I think up here, maybe?
This way?
Okay.
We're going up, up, up, up, baby.
I'm gonna rest here a little.
It looks like it gets opening moves that we won't be able to cross.
Alright.
Yeah.
I'm here.
If you've seen a good pathway, let me know, Snuffy.
Cause you looked.
Yeah.
I don't even know a pathway.
I think it's mostly the left.
It has a lot of good laying.
But the right is just an empty darkness.
Yeah, like here, you mean?
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Well, I almost didn't make that.
We go left?
Oh, thank you.
I think so.
So the other thing is because there's no food in here, you kind of just need to like, book it a little bit.
Can we go here?
I think we need to get to here, somehow.
We're going up.
It did not work out.
It does not look good though.
Come on, I caught you.
I'm good.
Yeah, I got you.
Got you too?
Okay.
I got her more.
I'm killing him.
Here.
For stamina.
Okay.
Okay, there's a place here too?
Yeah.
I think this place...
Amplified of the stamina, my growling stomach.
Oh, you hungry?
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Little bit stuck, a little bit stuck.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa...
Whoa!
Whoa... What's going on with me?
What's going on?
Wait, what's going on, I can't...
pau ra lily!
Bailky, you need to separate from that surface a little bit, so try and drop down a little and then come back up.
You're stuck in the wall.
H- What's going on?
I don't know, that's what's going on what's going on...
What's going on?
I'm trying to figure out... I can't get out!
Someone help me!
Which one?
Is it a fully gone?
I don't know.
Am I?
Am I better now?
Guys!
What
did you do to me?
What did you do to me?
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Am I okay?
No.
Am I?
Oh, whoa, whoa!
Oh, it's tested on fire.
What did you do to me?
What did... I don't know.
Doki, have you ever seen the movie 127 Hours?
Oh, look, you fixed yourself.
I fixed myself.
I don't know if you even made it.
There's like... Is there anything up here?
So I think we're gonna have to try our best to climb on each other's heads and get up here maybe.
Or we take a very big leap over there.
Okay.
Don't trust me.
Get on my head.
That is a big one.
That is a really big one.
I'm a lollipop.
Wait, wait, why don't we just jump here?
Which one?
This way.
Oh.
That's what I said.
It is kind of big though, so it'd be kind of scary.
You'd have to like climb on this, I think, as a midway point.
Yeah.
It's hot too, so you're gonna take fire damage.
I'm scared.
I don't think I'm gonna make that.
Oh my gosh, she gained!
Wait, wait, wait.
How much stamina do you guys have?
Did you sprint for...
I did a lunge, but be careful if you don't have enough stamina.
You might be able to stand on top of this, actually, but it's hot.
Wait, I'm scared, guys.
I got you.
Should I eat my lollipop just in case?
If you just stand on top of this, just run.
The damage will fade away.
I'm gonna eat.
I got some rope too in case...
Yeah, you're good, you're good.
Just jump off and on here.
Yeah!
I have cookies.
I don't know where to go now.
Up here, I guess.
Okay.
Where's like the goal to get to?
To the top of the hole.
Oh, there is?
Yeah.
Oh.
I don't know how we're gonna get up from here, though.
No, me either.
I don't...
I really don't think there's like a way to go.
Clamming, I'm clamming.
Because we're losing stamina.
I have cookies.
I just...
I think...
There's cookies.
Oh god, this place is such a fucking bitch.
Wait, how about here?
There's two suitcases here.
Yeah, there are.
Maybe you can climb here?
We don't have any items, I assume.
Wait, if we...
If we get there, there's a suitcase and there's an item.
Maybe we can help the others.
How do you get up there?
Oh, thank you.
I got you.
Oh, nope.
You got your own.
You're all good.
Oh, I think we have to go through here.
Yeah.
If we even get up there, though, how do we get up here?
We...
I don't think we can.
That's...
Oh my god.
It's too high.
The only other place that looks...
I don't even know, actually.
You know what?
It's a class.
It's like a chain launcher.
Nothing looks feasible right now.
We...
We could...
We could go all the way around here, maybe.
But we're...
What do we do after that?
I think...
I think we need an item.
Oh, we saw something...
There's not even there, but...
Wait, doesn't the lollipop...
...make you go speedy fast over here?
It does, but only you.
Yeah, I can give it to you.
I...
I trust you.
I think I know what we could do.
What?
I think we need to use the firearms.
You should take the lollipop...
...and you should go up here.
You should use that energy to climb all the way up to this bridge...
Yeah?
...and try and get those lollipop.
Do you think it would work?
Do you think that's enough?
Alright, Limeo.
This is...
It's your time to shine, Scoutmaster.
No, no.
Hold on.
No, take this rope.
This is your lollipop.
No, wait.
No, I...
No, it's...
It's...
You should do it.
You should...
You are the most experienced.
I'm actually looking at this.
Look at this.
If we run across the hot rocks, we can actually get all the way up there.
That's what I said before.
Oh, okay.
Then we would go back?
We...
We can try that then.
Okay.
Yeah.
So, we're going back down?
I think so.
Where we came from?
Oh...
Nightman.
It's gonna hurt.
Yeah.
That's gonna hurt.
I gonna leave a mile.
Ain't much.
It's honest work.
Okay, you don't...
You only take like a tick if you're clay.
This one's...
Okay.
Gosh.
I took a lot more than a tick.
I almost died.
Be careful, guys.
Be careful.
Oh, okay.
I got it.
Yum yum yum yum.
Okay.
Thank you.
Oh!
There we go.
I'm gonna be here and give you a lift up.
Boy, this is scary.
Uh-huh.
Thank you.
Yep, woof!
Wee!
Whoa!
Okay, so across the big rock and onto the bridge, you see what I mean?
What?
Uh, you should go first.
Yeah, you should go first.
I know what you mean, but you should go first.
Oh god, this is gonna be beans, actually.
Uh...
Oh, why is the music so intense now?
I know, I know, I don't know!
I don't know!
Ooh, here?
That is... maybe?
Oh my gosh, she's gaming.
Oh my god, what does she do?
What?
What does she do?
I didn't jump, I didn't jump, I'm going back, I'm going back, I didn't jump.
Grab me, grab me, somebody grab me.
I'm scared!
I didn't jump, I didn't jump, I didn't jump, I didn't jump.
Is that enough rope?
If you can get to this bit, is that enough rope for you to get up?
Sure!
Yeah.
You can put up a little bit more.
A little bit more?
That's about as much as I can do, apparently.
No, no, no, pull it back up a little bit.
Oh, okay, push that?
A little bit... yeah, yeah.
Still more, still more, still more, up up up up.
Ok, that's it.
No, that's true.
If that saves any extra rope, I'll take it.
I have rope too, so.
Ok, stuffy, I believe.
C werd zeerical voice from helpes Wow.
No, this isn't the way... take me.... t ok that's it.
I changed my mind again.
Guys I might be coke... I don't know if I can make this jump.
Alright, I believe Mint.
How did she do that?
Oh gosh.
Oh my gosh,
I'm not gonna make it.
Oh my god.
I made it.
Do you think we go across enough or do we stay here?
I think we might stay here.
Snuffy?
Guys, Snuffy?
I don't think Snuffy.
I don't think Snuffy made it.
You need cookie, man.
Oh, can I have one?
Yeah, that's all.
Here we go.
Okay, thank you.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Hi, kids.
Up this way, I think.
Hello, I'm kid.
There was some medkits and lollipop.
And a lollipop, sorry.
Yay.
I'm a big boy now.
Hi.
I don't know if this is the way though because it gets very sheer again.
I'm wondering if we go across.
Oh.
Like, both ways suck.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, there you are, Snuffy.
What happened, Snuffy?
Hey, Snuffy.
Snuffy!
Unless I can get up this way.
It's okay.
I'm gonna wait until Lamo makes her executive.
I knew I wasn't gonna be able to do it.
Lamo, you sacrificed yourself for us.
I don't know.
It's so crazy.
You guys made it.
You didn't even go this way.
There's more luggage on the other side.
There's more luggage.
I think we can go this way, yeah.
Yeah.
You purposely didn't tell us that you were starving so we could save resources.
What are you?
I didn't think I was that low.
I don't know.
Where did we go?
We're going across.
Yeah, we're going across.
It's okay.
I took damage, but it's okay.
Oh.
I'm a little scared, guys.
Yeah, we should let Snuffy scout.
Do you think we do the hot rock or we go on the right?
I think the hot rock actually does a bit above it.
So I think we need to do the hot rock.
Snuffy should start scouting.
Wait, are you actually injured or just hot?
I'm injured.
She broke her leg.
Yeah.
Oh.
Ouchie, ouch.
Thank you.
I think you should save it.
Oh, thank you.
Ouchie.
What do we do?
It's spicy here.
I'm going to go check.
Okay, I'm going back down.
Ouch.
My spicy legs.
Doki, come down here.
No, it's fine.
I'm safe here.
Yeah.
I'm safe in this little hole.
Okay, I'm going to the hole.
Nice.
Okay.
Oh, fucky.
Yeah, you can stand.
Yeah, wherever you are.
And then you come up this hot rock here.
Ouch.
I'm burning.
I gotta wait until my feet sees.
My feet sees are too hot.
I gotta wait.
Just give me a sec.
My little feet sees.
I have a...
I have a lollipop.
Probably all the same amount of feet.
So I can rope for a mint.
Or do we try and keep it slightly higher?
Wait, how did you make this?
I...
How did I?
Uh, with...
I don't know.
With the...
There's a spot to stand on the hot rock.
Yeah, there it is.
No, it's not.
It's not it.
Oh wait, there it is.
I don't know if I can make this now though.
You just gotta catch it.
Okay.
Alright.
Wait, wait.
Oh, you can?
Okay, hold on.
I'm going to eat this.
Mint, my chat tells me that if I knock you out with a blowgun and you sleep safely, you won't be hungry anymore.
Oh, okay.
Wait, you have a blowgun?
Mint's lowest.
Come here, Mint.
Yeah, I have a lollipop.
Put yourself here.
Okay.
Knock me out!
Oh, okay.
Go to sleep.
I'll see you in a minute.
Good night.
Oh.
I thought we picked her up or something.
What if I pick her up and chuck her into the lab?
Pick her up for a little bit.
Just pick her up and hold her for a little bit.
Just in case.
I don't know if it, like, causes a problem.
What if I accidentally- What if I accidentally- Unironically play with motion blur?
What's wrong with you people?
Wait, I have motion blur on?
Did you not?
I feel like you did.
Wait, did I- Did I actually put motion blur on?
Where is it?
There's no motion blur anywhere.
What do you mean?
I'm awake!
I think I'm free!
Are you hungry anymore?
I'm not!
Oh my god!
I'm letting the Z's go away and then I'll be okay.
Okay, then you spot the next one above up here.
Also, if Doki hadn't picked me up, I would have died.
Oh.
I was just like, we were just looking at your body for the longest time.
Where do we go from here?
I don't know, I haven't looked yet.
I think another hot rock jump is in order.
This one?
Yeah, there's also this part here.
This isn't bad.
What are you doing next?
There's this whole bit here.
Let me have a look.
A-ba-ba.
A-ba-ba-ba.
Oh god.
Oh.
I'm waiting for that...
Lamu's executive decision.
Okay.
Oof.
Okay, yeah, there's lots of places to sit here.
Okay.
I didn't really...
I didn't really know what she did, but okay.
Oh, okay.
Alright.
You're okay.
You'll see it.
It's pretty straightforward, actually.
Oh, I see it.
Yeah.
And then...
The left side.
Over there.
Turn around.
Oh, here?
Oh, I see it.
There's this full-spit perception here.
Ow.
My feet sees.
You got it?
Yeah, I got it.
Wait.
Why am I...
Why am I attached to the wall?
What the heck?
Oh my god, that's skewed.
I got...
I got it.
Okay.
Yeah!
Wait, did you...
How did you make that?
Wait, how did you make that?
This way.
I'll put my arm up for you.
Okay.
I got you.
My turn.
Yeah.
Yay.
We're almost there, we're almost there.
We're almost there.
Where are we?
Almost there.
I see the light.
The light, it calls for me.
Do I go straight to the light?
Yeah.
Go to the light.
Yay.
Okay.
Okay, there's a spot to stand just below me.
You're good.
Yep, sorry.
Sorry to push you.
You're fine, you're fine.
I'm behind you, okay?
There you are.
Here?
I think so.
Oh my gosh, you guys!
I can see!
Oh my god, I see!
Okay, guys!
You're hungry!
Oh?
I'm not hungry.
I'm so hungry.
Okay, do we need- I think we need to go across the hot rock because we could go up here, but there's nowhere from there to go.
I did lose my rope, I think, from the thing.
Oh, you didn't pick that up?
I should've dropped it, yeah.
Oh!
That's okay.
I don't know if we can do this.
Let me- let me do a quick check.
Okay.
There is that loo- there is that luggage right there.
Looks like you can stand there, where you're going.
Yeah, but like where else would she go after that, though?
Oh, yeah.
That's the thing.
Is it a raft, maybe?
Oh, wait!
I don't think she's gonna make it, guys.
If you- Did she make it?
She made it.
It's not that way, so she'll come back to come down.
I made it, but I picked up through mine.
Aww.
So we have to go this way?
Maybe the left side here, these- these rocks- this formation over here.
This one?
Yeah, here.
You might be able to get more footing there, without having to go so long between your stamina.
Yeah, like- Don't cry, man.
Yeah, yeah.
Got you.
Maybe- maybe Baimu can lift you if you make it up to the second- It's fine, I'm not hurt.
I just don't have stamina.
I think- I think we go around, don't we?
I got my arm out!
I don't know if I can make it.
Cause my sa- my hunger is so bad now.
Woo!
I just made that, oh my god.
Just barely, just barely.
How about here?
Going into a ma- well, actually, you- Where's Laimo?
I don't think you have anywhere to go from there.
That's probably bad.
I'm gonna be falling, sorry, hold on.
You're fine.
Yeah.
You score all you need.
There's nowhere to go, don't go up there.
You're gonna fall and die.
It's ok, I- No!
I grabbed it.
We grabbed each other.
We grabbed each other, we're here.
There's really nowhere to go.
You'll have to see if you can grab Laimu's hand up there.
Ah.
Where is she though?
Oh, she's over there!
I'm not here but there's nowhere really up- That's the problem.
How do we get here?
No!
What do we do?
What do we do??
What about here?
Uh...
Is there anything here?
Oh, I have the lollipop, but I'm scared.
I think, Doki, I think if you took the lollipop, if you climbed up there and then took the lollipop, you could probably make it to that bridge.
But you wouldn't have to let yourself take a break at all.
You definitely go straight there.
But it'll make you tired, but your stamina will go crazy and it'll be really fast.
Do I... Okay, well, we'll let her use the lollipop first.
Yeah.
Oh my god, look her go.
She's like a little spider monkey.
Woah, she's zooming.
Yeah, look her go.
Oh my god.
Woah, woah, woah.
Woah, woah.
I think you guys are just going crazy.
Oh, she made it.
Oh, there's a chaingun.
But I don't know how...
It's actually a rope cannon.
Less good.
Less good all day.
She can still use it to make you guys get up somewhere.
Maybe, hopefully.
Oh my god, there's a little hole here that scared the shit out of me.
I could have disappeared.
How do you use the...
Dude, where do I go?
Where do I lower the rope from?
Like, where would be...
I don't even know how...
I think like...
Min and I are fucked.
I...
I mean, this is...
I see it.
Okay.
I think...
We're getting hungry.
The only place that they can reach that, I think, from where you are, is that second bottom bridge.
That's not all the way connected to the wall, but it's beneath this bridge.
They might be able to jump on that, but it would be in the...
Can you get to this, maybe?
Okay, we'll get back there.
That?
Yeah.
Let me think though.
I can't...
I can't drop, because I won't be able to get back up.
I have a lollipop.
Just for time.
I can try and get there.
Or do you want to shoot the rope first?
Well wait, hold on.
Let me try and get above you.
Do I use my lollipop now?
No?
I'm gonna do it.
Oh gosh, your eyes are going into the back end.
I'm gonna try and get above you.
She's having a vision.
I'm having a vision.
I'm gonna do it.
Watch this.
What do you see, Raven?
What do you see?
Are you ready?
I'm gonna do it.
Don't do it.
We don't know where to go here.
I'm gonna do...
Just make it to the bridge, Dogey.
Go straight for the bridge.
We have to get...
You're probably abandoning this, but...
Yes.
That's fine.
I would sound like I've helped you out or anything.
One of us has to...
Wait, do I take the lollipop and I go this way?
The right side or the left side?
The right...
You have to go right side and climb up the bridge.
That's the only way to go.
This way?
No.
Wait, wait, wait.
Can you see the road?
No.
We see it, but there was no way we're getting that road.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
So do I go...
Okay.
Snuffy, do I go this way?
Oh my god.
Wait, no, no.
You would go...
You would go this way, I think.
Either up to this ledge and then you...
Yeah.
I think you go this way.
Or you just go straight up.
Alright.
Sayonara.
How can I say it?
I'll try.
I won't stay until she goes.
I'll go.
AR energia.
Is there anywhere up there to stand?
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Can you...
Is the rope any better from here, or no good?
Oh my god.
A little bit actually.
That's not terrible.
Sayonara!
OkayAY!
MICHAELf Himselfge.
I did, but I had so little stamina that I couldn't- I couldn't go anywhere.
Oh my god, you should've given it to me.
I'm gonna burn, guys.
Wait, I see you!
Wait, wait, wait!
I can come back!
I thought the lollipop would give me a little bit of, like, food.
Wait, Min, Min, Min!
Yeah, Min, give me your hand, give me your hand, I'm like literally right below you.
I don't know.
Okay.
Come on, come on!
Yay!
Yeah, okay.
Okay, now we don't know.
We're just trapped in here.
Yeah, now we're just trapped here.
I can't believe you're still alive.
I didn't.
Nene.
With Nene.
Immunity in this game.
You keep falling.
No, we're not gonna reach that.
We're not gonna make it!
Lai-mu!
Don't scout!
Min and I are gonna jump off!
You go on without us!
Wait, we are?
We're gonna jump off.
So, the Scout Master, the Scout Master will kill her.
We have to do it for Lai-mu.
Oh, for time the Scout Master will kill you!
We're gonna do it, Lai-mu!
We're gonna sacrifice ourselves for you!
Come on!
I'm so hungry now, I don't know if I can do it.
It's all up to you, Lai-mu!
It's all up to you!
Lai-mu!
It's so close!
Oh my gosh, it's right there!
It's right there!
It's literally right there, Lai-mu!
I can't quite reach it.
Oh my gosh, she's EP!
She's EP and she's so hungry!
Use the rope gun!
Wait, there's a luggage right behind you!
There's a luggage right behind you!
I wanna go for the luggage instead, but...
Ugh!
I don't know...
I couldn't- I couldn't get up there.
And someone said drop the pool!
I don't think you- It's time, you got- you can't wait too long!
Okay.
I- I need- I can get water in my pack.
But I can't- there's nowhere to safely put the pack down.
You have to go to that bridge!
I don't think I made that.
Oh my god.
Gamer?
Oh my gosh!
She's gaming?
Oh?
Don't if I could stop them!
OK.
Nice!
Yes!
Oh my god!
Woo!
She's gaming!
What if she misses this jump?
That would be pretty funny.
Come here!
I don't see you now!
Oh my god.
I can hear birds!
Oh my god!
An energy drink!
it drop the jack bar from there!
Yeah, drop cannon in it!
Like here?
The left side looks like the...
Behind you, maybe?
There's a lot of pressure here, holy shit.
I know, my god!
Shoot it right in the little balls right there.
The phallic-looking rock formation?
You don't have time to think too much because you're hungry.
Oh, I see the balls!
I think I get what you mean, yeah.
Just don't shoot too far because of the length of the rope.
I was gonna say...
We're good, we're good.
I was gonna say, that is a very short rope.
Right on the balls.
That's exactly what I was saying.
See how it's phallic?
I'm saying this, right?
You see it?
Oh gosh.
Oh my gosh, she's literally right there.
She's so close.
I can hear, I can hear freedom.
I can hear the birds.
Do you think she'll remember us when she's up there?
I can see fresh air.
Oh my god.
It's so beautiful outside.
Whoa.
That would've been so funny.
I'm scared.
I'm so scared for her.
I can't handle this pressure.
You can't handle this pressure!
We literally couldn't take it, you jumped the.
We sacrificed ourselves for our scout master.
We had to so she could continue falling.
For our leader.
Remember us.
Make sure you have to...
There's a ledge right above you.
Yeah there's a ledge.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Make sure when...
Make sure to like visit our graves every year.
You're a pro!
You beat this game before!
Oh yeah, don't accidentally use your extra energy.
Yeah, I'm trying not to.
Oh my god, it's literally right there.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, I see the sky!
The sun!
Where's the sun?
The sun for the campfire.
Oh my god, it's like the whole world is our campfire.
This needs like some epic music, I think.
I know, it does, actually.
I can't do it!
I see it!
Wait, can you...
Oh my god!
It's literally right there!
All my days, day man!
Pop pop pop to the top!
What time it is, what time is it?
It's summer time!
It's our vacation.
We should drink your energy drink right before.
Yeah, get a little bit of zoomies before you make it.
I can't believe it, guys.
Look, our second try playing Peak and we finished the game.
We're so good at this, right?
We're so crazy good at Peak, guys.
I do think that you guys sacrificing yourselves and having that bravery would get us this win, dude.
I'm fine.
I wouldn't have left you if you hadn't jumped.
Look at us go, man.
We did it.
We contributed.
Yeah, we did it.
Oh my god, it's lava color, too.
Look at that.
Oh, the helicopter!
Help is you!
Yeah!
We did it!
Sir, please, I'm starving to death.
Eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
Yeah!
Have a friend escape the island.
Participation badge!
Oh, look.
Me and my friends.
We did it!
Wow, we did it!
Look at all the times we've died.
Yeah, yeah.
Where's our badge for dying five times?
A greater challenge?
Are you kidding me?
Oh, I got promoted!
I got tadpole scout!
I got promoted!
Oh my god.
New hat!
Sense and add modifiers that make summoning that's more difficult.
Goodbye!
I didn't get to see it.
We did it!
We did it, everyone!
We clapped Pete!
We beat Pete!
Oh my god.
Guys, we carried.
We carried, guys.
We did.
We did it.
I never want to fly again.
The only thing that we would ever go back to a fucking airport after that.
Let's go, guys.
Dogpile online move.
Yeah, you know what?
I'm happy now.
Thank you so much.
Look at that.
Now I'm happy.
Now you're happy.
Yeah.
I'm happy now.
Sadness cured.
Yes, we fixed depression.
All I have to do is touch grass and lava.
Well, I believe the snow monster was right.
And like, climbing a mountain and almost dying and actually dying would fix depression.
Let's go.
Let's go outside, clearly.
Let's go outside, everybody.
Let's go outside, not aloha.
Someone super chatted and said Waimu was the great Sherpa.
It really was Everest.
She was the... Yeah, she was the Sherpa.
We were the rich folks.
Yeah, we were the rich Sherpa.
We were the rich folks climbing Everest while the Sherpas, like, put us on their back to carry us up the mountain.
We did it, guys.
Look at me.
Now I'm so happy.
Aloha, everyone.
Aloha.
You look like you're ready to go on vacation.
Yeah, I'm ready to go.
What are you guys doing?
Why did you blow it out?
No.
You're right, Mint.
You know what?
You're right.
We did so good, Mint, for our second time playing.
Our second time ever playing.
Yeah, for our second run.
You did awesome.
Our second run, we beat the game.
Yeah, more rocks than ever finish hitting you.
Yeah.
So that was really good.
Let's go.
We did it all while sleep-depriving.
Yeah, yeah.
That's true.
And Snuffy...
I'm sleep deprived, but I also have adrenaline.
So my body is like, what the fuck am I doing?
And Snuffy for, like, sacrificing herself so she wouldn't worry us.
She was like, don't worry, guys.
We all can make it.
You guys, I was trying to motivate you.
Yeah, yeah.
You knew you were...
You knew you didn't have enough, but you didn't let us know.
So, you were like, don't worry, guys.
I'll be right behind you.
And then you sacrificed yourself.
Just don't look back.
Thank you so much, everybody.
I had an amazing time.
I had a great time, Sloppy sister.
Yeah.
We slopped a lot.
Let's go.
Let's put our hands together.
Are you continuing to stream?
Snuffy, are you still going?
I actually did the stream.
I wasn't...
You want to stream it?
Okay, okay.
Alright, guys, let's put our hands together and do...
Let's put our hands together.
I love you guys.
Thank you so much.
Yeah, Sloppy's.
You'll see what's wrong with your arm.
Sloppy's.
Yeah, and it's Sloppy's on one, three, two, one.
Good night, everybody.
Yeah, GG's, guys.
GG's.
Bye-bye.
Gee-bye.
Oh, she left the expedition.
Oh.
It's just us.
What's wrong with your arm?
What do you mean?
It's my arm!
What's wrong with it?
Wait, come look at me.
Okay, what's wrong with it?
Ever since I merged into the mountain, things have not been the same.
Yeah, mine is straight.
Wait, I don't see it.
What's wrong?
Oh, mine's a little curved.
A little?
Yeah.
Wait, no, I think it's whatever's on your screen.
It looks weird, but mine's like normal.
Wait, screenshot it.
Screenshot it, I need to see.
Aloha.
This is what it looks like to me.
Okay, I want to know what this looks like.
I'm confused.
Oh my god!
I think it's a broken arm.
I think ever since I merged with the mountain, things have not been the same for me.
Alright, GG's.
Yeah, I can't do that.
Okay, GG!
Bye bye!
Fun!
I have no idea what's wrong with my PC.
I'm sorry for...
I'm sorry for... for my PC exploding.
I have no idea what's going on.
Most likely... Most likely, I'm gonna take it to the shop tomorrow and figure...
I think it's just a monitor thing.
It's been a thing where...
But my main monitor's never died that much before.
So like, that was confusing.
But I think like...
I think like...
Yeah, I could not handle...
Yeah, I could not handle Peak for some reason.
But I'll take it to the store...
To the PC store tomorrow and see what happens.
No, it's been like a thing for my third monitor.
My...
I think it's just...
I have three monitors that might be too intensive in general.
So...
I'll go check...
I might...
I'm gonna swap my monitors...
Maybe.
And see what happens.
Cause it's been a thing for my...
Ever since I...
Um...
No, it's like been a thing for my...
Ever since I swapped my third monitor...
To another really powerful monitor.
Um...
Uh...
I...
All my cables are...
Plugged fully.
No, all my cables are fully plugged in.
So it can't be that.
Yeah, it can't be that.
I'm literally like checking the cables right now.
But that was fucking weird.
Hehehehe.
That sucks though that...
Uh...
My stream died a little bit there.
Hehehehe.
Uh...
Yeah, I have like...
It could be the power...
Supply, yeah.
Uh...
Um...
But...
It's okay.
It was...
It never had to happen though.
It was mostly from...
But...
I hope like everything else was okay.
I hope the volume was okay after...
Um, I rebooted my PC because, like I said, I didn't know if the sound-balancing...
Oh no.
Oh, that scared me.
That scared me.
I lagged a little.
Yeah, it might be frying from three monitors.
It could be that, too.
Um, it could be frying from three monitors, which could be... which is pretty bad.
But, was the volume okay?
I'll set the... yeah, that was crazy.
I hope it didn't, uh, it didn't mess with the stream too much.
I hate it.
I hate when that, you know, there's a good stream everyone's looking forward to.
And, um, and, you know, having tech issues for that.
So, I hope it wasn't, like, too intrusive for it, uh, during that time.
That's all I hope for.
I'll put the third monitor on 60hz and see if that helps.
Uh, I'll put the third monitor on 60hz and see if that fixes it.
Hmm.
It happens?
Yeah?
Was it just, like... it only mostly happened during, uh...
How... was it just lag... lag... lag... lagging when my PC died there?
Or was everything else good?
Chat.
Was it a little... was it a little choppy throughout it?
Like, a run?
Chat?
What?
Was it, like... uh...
It's just, like, laggy... three laggy times.
Okay, it was just only during when my PC died.
Okay.
So... wait, it was really bad?
Was it really... it was lagging a lot?
Oh, it just when... oh.
But I'm so confused.
Oh, only when the monitor was dying.
Okay.
Okay, that was fine.
Okay, I got worried.
I was worried.
Because I saw, like, someone said it was really bad.
So only when... and it died, like, two... three times.
So that's fine.
Oh, okay.
It was fine for except when it died.
Okay.
Okay, that's good to know.
That's good to know.
I was worried about that, though.
But I had a lot of fun.
I was fucking around a lot, but we still...
We still won!
Yay!
Apparently, I looked really cursed on other people's stream while my PC was dying.
So that must have been really funny on...
It must have been funny on other people's stream with what was going on with me.
Um...
But...
Uh, I'm gonna change my...
I'll change my third monitor...
Tomorrow.
Or later today.
And, um...
Um...
And, uh...
I'll see how it goes.
If...
If, like, after I swap my monitor...
My third monitor out...
Um...
After I swap my...
Third...
Third monitor out...
Then I'll...
Uh...
I'll...
And it still does that.
I'll go...
Go to the...
I'll go to, like, the shop to see if they can fix it.
Yeah.
I have audio delay now.
Wait, that's so...
Wait, wait, what?
Really?
My audio is delayed?
That's so weird.
Why would it be delayed?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha...
Ha ha ha ha...
Oh my god.
Like, on my end, it doesn't look delayed at all.
Yeah.
Oh, my audio is fine?
Oh my god.
Uh...
People do that?
Lie on the internet?
Ha ha ha ha...
Oh, Nimi!
Thank you for the raid!
We actually...
We just...
We just finished...
We just finished beating Peek, so we're just chilling right now.
Uh...
But thank you for the raid, Nimi!
I hope you had fun in Night Ring!
I saw you three were gonna play Night...
We're playing Night Ring.
I don't know what characters you guys picked, but I hope you had a fun time.
We just beat Peek!
It was so fun!
I hope you get to play Peek soon, Nimi.
It's actually...
It's such a fun game.
Um...
We beat it after, like, two...
Like...
In two attempts.
It was definitely...
Me...
All of us did so well.
We all lived and everything.
Definitely.
But hello, Napplings!
I hope you guys have...
Um...
A fun time watching Night Ring.
We're just really...
Uh...
Chill today.
Oh, Nimi was the mage lady.
Oh, that fits!
That fits.
Many, thank you for the one gift of ship.
Thank you, thank you.
I can see that.
Doesn't she play mage in Elder Ring?
The Royal Wii.
Hey!
It was a team game, and we beat it.
I...
Mint and I sacrificed ourselves...
For that greater good.
If Mint and I didn't sacrifice ourselves...
Lamu would not...
Would have got slapped.
Okay?
She would have got slapped by the Scoutmaster.
That's right.
So, we...
We did it all.
Kabuto, thank you for the super chat.
I was so brave.
I know.
Kabuto, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
I'll head back to work now.
It's a shame I'm gonna miss the rest of this peak gameplay.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Mr. Broken Bond, thank you for the super chat.
It's peak.
Woof, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Broken bun.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
This was the sloppy sister corporate retreat from the fast food restaurant.
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
At least I ate my lollipop.
I know I kept getting the lollipop.
Never punished.
Never punished from eating the lollipops.
Uh, next C.
Thank you, this super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
It might just be the monitor cable not being fully connected.
It tries to replace the cable or swapping it out with another monitor to test it.
Thank you, this super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Right now, my monitor's not dying.
Now, now it's fine.
I don't know what it was about Peak that was causing my main monitor to freak out.
But, like, right now, I haven't had any issues at the moment.
So, it's very weird.
It's very weird.
Uh, never punished, yeah.
Um, maybe it was FPS?
Uh, I mean, I did low- I kept lowering it, too.
Um, it was too peak.
That was fun, though.
I understand why a lot of people, like, have been spamming peak.
Um, uh, have been spamming peak a lot.
Because I feel like since the map changes every day, um, it changes every day.
And, um, um, and with different people, you can have different, like, chemistry and combinations and stuff for it.
But, like, I don't think I can, like, play it.
For me, after beating the game, I don't know- I don't know.
Maybe I could play, like, once or twice more.
But I don't know if I could, like, play a lot more of that- of the game, because after beating it, you know?
Um, it was very fun to watch.
Yeah, it was very fun to play, too.
It was definitely really fun to play with the Sloppy Sisters.
Uh, but yeah, I think it was good that, you know, Min and I didn't spoil ourselves with, like, Modric- like, with, like, playing it beforehand.
And, um, um, and, you know, um, having this as our first experience, too.
I mean, it did help a lot that Lime was a fucking gamer when it- like, she's the most competent out of all of us when it comes to, like, games that require your brain.
She is definitely the most competent person out of all of us.
Yeah, it was a good combination of blind players and experienced players.
Yeah.
Um, yeah, I had a lot of fun.
I'm glad.
Mm-hmm.
But I'm definitely gonna- yeah, I'm gonna try and swap the monitors tonight and see if anything changes.
Because I had no issues yesterday when we were streaming, uh, Eldering.
So, um, so it was very weird, um, that Peek was the one that decided to kill my PC.
I was at PC issues, too.
I don't know why.
I don't know why, like, I have, like, I actually have the PC curse.
I- every PC I touch fucking explodes in the end.
Uh, I have no idea how this happens.
Every PC, no matter how fucking good the PC is, um, it, like, there's something, something happens.
Something happens.
Um, I didn't move my cables, though.
I- I didn't touch anything regarding my cables.
Uh, Seijen, thank you for the super sticker.
Thank you, thank you.
And, uh, Matt, uh, thank you for the various super stickers.
Also...
Thank you again for the Akasupa Sajun!
Thank you, thank you!
Alright Dragoons, hold out your hands.
Um...
SimpleMinded!
Thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you!
Doki, your character reminds me of the Popeye, the Sailor Man...
And I'm angry!
Zonerman!
Thank you for the super chat!
Thank you, thank you.
Add sloppy sisters to the description.
Oh, I mean, I could in the future.
Thank you for the Super Chat, thank you, thank you.
I might make a playlist every time for all the SloppySister collabs, that helps too.
Thank you for the Super Chat with us.
Thank you, thank you.
Sage, thank you for the Super Chat, thank you, thank you.
CPU 100% and Dragoon, hold a line.
And, um, guys, thank you for the super... Thank you for the super... Thank you.
This game is so metal.
You die in game.
You die in real life.
It was so freaky.
Um, because, like, when my main monitor died, um, everything, like, slowed down.
And then, like, when it fully died, I knew, like, oh, I have to force shut my PC.
Um, all I heard was just meant laughing on repeat over and over and over again.
And I was like, oh my god, my PC is haunted.
I am truly haunted right now.
And then that's when I, like, fully shut down my PC.
Um, and came back.
Um...
No name.
Thank you for the super chat thing.
And thank you.
Uh, from ghost to toast.
Uh...
Kabuto, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you.
Hey, I'm just catching a stream.
I can tell this is going to be peak.
Thank you again for the super chat.
Thank you.
Sejan, thank you for the super sticker.
Oh, yeah.
Tomorrow.
I think it's tomorrow.
I think it's either Saturday or Sunday.
But tomorrow, I'll be on my very first podcast.
Well, I did already do the podcast.
But I'll be in my very first podcast that was hosted.
By Lily Pichu.
Lily Pichu.
And I think the podcast is... It's... Whose channel?
What channel is it?
I need to grab it real quick.
But she has a podcast series called Sweet and Sour with Lily Pichu and Pokimane.
Pokimane's not there, but I'm a guest with Lily Pichu on Lily Pichu's podcast.
I think it's gonna be out tomorrow on her... on the channel.
It's a Sweet and Sour podcast.
Yeah.
And it's a VTuber dedicated episode.
And this is my very first... It's my very first time doing a podcast.
I've never done a podcast before, but it's my very first time.
And I think it's gonna be out tomorrow.
That's what I was told.
Unless it's next week, but whatever.
At least, like, they're knowing it the earliest better, right?
And...
To, like, you know, commemorate...
This being my very first podcast...
Lily and I are gonna do a collab next week.
Um, cause we do have, like, another collab with, uh...
With, uh, Mimi and Doobie and Mint next week, too.
On Friday.
Um, where we're gonna do part two of Missionary Zero.
But, I haven't... we haven't figured out a date yet.
But, we're also gonna have another...
Another collab with Lily Pichu next week.
Where we're gonna be drunk and drawing characters from memory.
We don't know if we're gonna do Pokemon or random characters.
Cause I feel like random characters would be pretty funny.
You know?
But, it also has to be characters that we both know.
Um...
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Um, so, we're gonna...
We're gonna do drunk drawing characters from memory together.
Um...
Uh, with Lily Pichu.
Not sure the date yet.
So, yeah.
Um...
And then, the week after...
I think I have another collab the week.
Well, I know I've been...
I've been trying to schedule collabs in advance.
Um...
Let me see.
Do I have a collab next week?
Oh, no.
Oh, wait.
I...
Technically, I don't have a collab...
Hmm...
I think...
I don't remember if I...
I don't remember.
I think I have a collab on...
The week...
The week after that?
Cause I know I've been scheduling...
Cause...
Oh, no.
No.
I have a...
Tournament thing next week.
The week.
No, not next week.
Sorry.
I have a tournament in two weeks for a new game that's coming out.
Um...
That I'm gonna be sponsored for.
So, that's gonna be what that is.
You guys are like, whoa!
Tournament?
Uh, I got invited.
Um...
You guys might have seen it already.
But apparently there's a new...
Game coming out.
A new FPS...
I said FPS...
It's a new third-person shooter game that's coming out.
That's based off of anime characters.
And, um...
And I got invited by the devs to a tournament as a sponsor.
Uh...
So I get paid to be there.
So, yay!
I love being paid.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Um...
And that's...
I didn't put...
I didn't organize a sponsor.
I didn't...
Sorry, I didn't organize a collab there.
Because there's already gonna be a lot of stuff going on.
Um...
But some of you guys might have seen it already because I saw someone on Twitter at me to sign up for the tournament.
But little did they know, I was already invited by the devs.
Little do they know, I was already invited.
I have no idea who my teammates are.
What team I'm in.
As long as I'm there and I get paid.
That's all that matters.
Next C, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Playlist would be cool.
Sloppy Sisters is truly peak.
Well, again, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Yay!
I love networking.
Oh, is it networking?
I guess it is networking.
Because I've been building some really good relationships with a lot of companies and stuff.
And a lot of companies are coming back to me for sponsors and stuff like that.
Because I guess I do well on my sponsors.
So, a lot of companies are coming back to me and being like, Oh, I want to work with you again.
And work with like...
For like this new game and stuff like that.
Which is nice.
It's really nice.
Because like...
In the past, I never had some...
Like a lot of these types of opportunities before.
So, it's like really nice in general.
Um...
Because like...
Some...
I remember in the past, people thought that I reject offers or like...
Sponsors in the past.
But like...
Why the fuck would I reject free money?
Like...
I'm like...
It's like one hour of my time.
Like, why would I say no?
Like...
Why...
I remember in the past, people were like, Oh, I wonder why she doesn't like...
You know...
Um...
Wonder why...
Like...
Why doesn't she do the sponsor?
Like, why...
Oh, I wasn't...
Like...
Oh, she must have said no.
Or something.
Or like...
Or something like that.
I'm like, why would I say no?
Like...
Why...
Hello?
So, it's really nice, you know.
It's really nice that companies like me and, like, companies, you know, trust me enough to, like, you know, show their stuff.
Which is like, speaking of showing, hey, you know what's out right now?
My merch!
You can buy my merch right now at dokimerch.com.
Yay!
We have so many things in the store right now that you can order.
Yeah!
So, buy my merch.
My birthday bundle is out right now.
Four, thank you to the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Proud of you, Doki.
Thank you.
Thank you to the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Doki loves money and I love her.
Thank you to the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
Well, I like just being able to have enough money to invest back into my channel and do lots of fun things and stuff like that.
And all that stuff.
So, you know, it's nice to be able to... What can I... Oh, someone's like, what can I buy?
You can buy this!
Whoa!
Look at that!
My birthday bundle!
Whoa!
So many cool things!
Oh, shit, not that.
Alright, here we go.
Let's put it here.
Um... Um... I do want to move, though, this year.
I want to move to a bigger space.
Um... And a better office.
I hate this office.
I... I really hate this office.
I want to... I need to, like, move to, like, a bigger place, too.
That's, like, all I really want.
So I can have, like, um... A better office for my PCs, you know, my setup and everything.
And also, uh... No, I'm gonna stay... I'm gonna stay in the same city.
I might just... I'm gonna stay in the same city.
Um... Just cause, like, I don't want to make a big, big move.
Um... And I didn't want to make a too big a move just so, like, my... Uh... I can still, like, uh... Do the things I want to do without having to make too much of a big hiatus.
I think if... I think, for me, I told myself, like, the day you can, like, actually relax and chill will be after you hit a million subscribers.
And then after you hit... After I hit a million subscribers, I'll, like, focus on myself more.
That's what I told myself.
So, so... I... I had, like, a midlife crisis to my manager last week.
Cause I was, like... Oh my gosh.
Like... I mean, I spent so much time just, like, inside my room.
Um... Like, should I have been, like... Do I... Cause, like... Okay.
Cause, like, I was thinking, like...
So many people are just moving to Japan or, like... Like, I don't know... Moving to Japan or moving to a new place or whatever.
Like, LA.
Where all the content creators are.
Or, like... Um... I know, like, mid... Okay.
Midlife streamer crisis.
This is, like... You know when you're streaming for so long and you have a midlife streamer crisis?
That was me.
I was having a midlife streamer crisis.
Um...
I was, like... People are, like, experiencing the world.
Everyone is, like, experiencing the world.
Enjoying, like, new experiences and stuff like that.
And I was, like, oh my god.
Like, should I... Like... Should I, like... Try and do that, too?
Like, maybe, like, you know... I don't know if... I don't know.
I'm, like...
What do I do if I move to Japan?
I... Mostly, I just eat a lot.
Cause, like, I'll just explore the food market area.
Because, like... That's, like, the only thing I could think of.
Like, just, like, you know, go around, like, different cafes.
Or, like... Um...
Or, like, just explore the food around Japan.
You know, like, those fucking food Japan bloggers?
That... There's one that I always watch.
The Japan Eats... Is that his YouTube channel?
His shorts always pops up and it's so interesting.
Also, see, my main mod has not died once.
It has... Something about... Something about Peak has been...
Something about Peak is, like, had... Was fucking up my... My... PC.
And I don't know what it was.
Okay, let's see.
Yeah, Japan Eats.
I love Japan Eats.
And I was thinking, like, I could, like... I could, like... I could move to Japan.
And just, like, experience the different types of food.
Not become a vlogger.
I meant, like... I meant just, like...
Like, experience life more.
You know?
And I was thinking about that.
I was, like...
I was just, like, having, like, a low-key midlife streamer crisis about it to my manager.
About it.
I was like, am I throwing it all away?
Like...
What if I can't experience that?
Like, should I... Should I be, like...
Should I move to Japan?
Like...
I was like...
Do I move to Japan?
Do I move to LA?
Like...
What do I do?
And, like, you know, I'm okay now.
I'm okay.
I'm okay now.
And it's just, like...
I was just thinking, like...
But then I realized, like, you know...
I could always do that later.
You know?
I could always do that later in my life.
It doesn't...
I don't have to, like, you know...
Something that I have to do when I'm young.
Or, like, at my current age right now.
Um...
I could always do that later on in my life.
Later on in my career.
Where things are, like, less...
Or in New York City, though.
I don't know.
New York City is scary.
I feel... New York City feels a little scary right now.
Or not... I would love to just like be there for the... I love the musicals though.
I love musicals.
But yeah, I was like... But now I'm like... Maybe I'll just like... Now I enjoy the moment right now.
Just enjoy the moment.
Do like... What I... Like...
Do like... You know... Do what... I wanna do.
Um... I think also like... I do get a little jealous.
I get a little jealous of all these VTubers like traveling to see each other.
Traveling a lot.
Hang out in real life.
Cause I'm very... I'm a very... What's the word?
I'm very closed off.
And I'm a very private person in general.
Um... Oh my gosh.
I... I had an incident.
This was a while.
A long time ago.
I had an... I have a... Huge trust issues.
I have very big trust issues.
I had an incident a long time ago.
And this was why I don't like... See a lot of people in real life.
Um... Because of what happened.
But I had... This was a long time ago.
Where I... Um... Met up with some people.
And... Um... And thought it was like... A private dinner with everyone.
And then... And then like... A couple of months later...
A picture of me like... Got leaked.
Um... Like got... It was a long time.
But it got leaked on the internet.
And then... It was just my picture.
It was like a group photo of everyone.
And somebody like... Cropped my picture.
And like... Leaped it.
And then like... And then that like... Like made me so scared.
Of actually like... Meeting up with people.
Cause I was like... Who would do that?
I was so... I was like... Oh my god.
That's so fucked up.
Like, who would do that?
Yeah, it was just me, though.
Like, someone in that group really hated me or something.
Or, like, I don't know.
I thought we were all friends, too.
I thought we were, like, all friends.
And then someone in that group, like...
And it was, like, a private dinner where, like, all of us were, like...
Like, we all, like, kept to ourselves and stuff like that.
And I was like, yay!
Like, oh, it's a great experience and everything.
And everyone was so happy there.
And then, like, someone cropped, picked just me.
And then, like, leaked it.
And I was like, what the fuck?
Like, I was like, what?
Like, yeah.
But this was a long time ago.
Yeah.
And so, like, because of that also, like, really messed me up.
And I had, like, big trust issues when it comes to meeting up with people.
Because, like, I'm like...
I thought, like, all of us were cool of each other.
Like, everyone had a great time together during that dinner, too.
And, like, we're all drinking.
We all had a good time together.
And then, like, a couple of months later, like, that picture got leaked.
And then I was so confused because it was just me.
Because it was a group picture of all of us, too.
And because of that, like, I'm very hesitant of meeting with people, too, because of that.
Because, like, I'm like, what if you're not cool with me?
And I didn't know that, you know?
Like, what if, like, you're friends with someone that's not cool, like, doesn't like me?
Because I know I'm, like, a very...
Like, even, like, now, I know I'm a very...
Like, I don't know if I say controversial figure.
But, like, you know, some people like me and some people don't.
Depending on who you're friends with.
So I'm just like, oh, what if, like, I meet up with someone and they actually secretly didn't like me?
And then, like, oh my god, what if, like, stuff gets leaked?
Especially when I'm a VTuber, as a VTuber too, yeah, I'm very polarizing, yeah, and I'm like, oh man, that worries me a lot, because now I have to keep my identity extra secret too, because of, you know, because I'm a VTuber too, because I like the privacy.
That's actually a topic in the podcast, where we're talking about, like, privacy stuff, and I like being a VTuber because of having my privacy respected, and stuff like that, and that's what I like too, and so I have to be a lot more careful about things like that.
That's why, like, I'm like, like, I do like envy the VTubers that travel a lot, that travel a lot, and like, you know, meet with other people, and stuff like that, and doing things where, you know, you know, they get to meet so many people, and, you know,
doing a lot of IRL stuff together and everything.
And, and I do get a little jealous, and I think, like, obviously that's, like, a thing that I have to, a hurdle I have to get past myself, and that's preventing me from doing a lot of fun things, because of the paranoia and stuff, because of the, I guess,
like, the PTSD from that.
So, um, it is, like, a little thing that I have to learn to grow from it, because I do have, like, a bit of PTSD from that, and that's why I don't, I try not to, like, I, I don't do that in general.
Um, but I do envy the VTubers that can do that, and that do travel a lot, too, to meet up with people, and, like, do content together.
I also envy, like, you know, seeing, like, IRL streamers do that, too, when they do, like, IRL live streams of, like, um, meeting people, exploring conventions, and stuff like that.
That, that's, like, uh, I know, like, some people are like, oh, why don't you ever do, okay, personally, though, I would say, I, I personally don't do, I, I never do live streams, where I'm, like, you know, I've seen, like, people would do, like, would walk around,
um, they walk around conventions and stuff, and do, like, a stream, like, walking around conventions and stuff.
Um, I don't do that.
I, people ask, always ask, because when I go around conventions, um, with my staff team, I do it off stream, because, one, I have no idea what's gonna happen on stream.
Like, I, I, I am so, I don't, I don't like the, I don't like the, um, what's the, the risk in that?
Especially when I know I'm more of a polarizing figure, and, like, you know, I have aunties, I know that, like, I know I have aunties, and I know some people don't like me in general, so I'm, like, I, I, I don't, I don't want the uncertainty or the risk of,
like, doing stuff like that.
And then, also, um, the second thing is that, uh, the second thing is that, um, I also want to respect the privacy of other people, too.
Um, so, uh, because, you know, so maybe someone doesn't want to be on stream, you know?
Like, even if it's just, like, a glimpse or something, I feel like, for me, I feel awkward doing stuff like that, because, like, maybe someone doesn't want to be on camera, you know?
So, um, I'm worried that, you know, like, if an artist at, an artist alley doesn't want to be shown on camera and stuff like that, then, you know, I don't want to, like, make them uncomfortable.
And, uh, that's why I try, I don't, I, I personally won't do it.
But I know a lot of people, uh, a lot of people, uh, don't mind it, and it is fun, because it's, like, you know, you don't have FOMO.
You're watching a stream.
You're watching a stream, um, just so you can enjoy, like, you know, enjoy the, the environment and stuff with your favorite streamer.
And, yeah.
Um, I think, like, if I ever do something like that, it would definitely be an edited video, so I can, like, blur the faces and, uh, blur the faces and, like, cover things up just in case, you know.
Um, Oscar, welcome to the tomato farm.
Welcome, welcome.
Paladin, thank you for the super chat.
Thank you, thank you.
I've been signaled out before and cut myself off from the others.
As I am older, the best advice I can give you is not let fear prevent you from doing something.
As big as a mistake of my life.
Yeah, that's basically for me, too, like, I do have a lot of work in terms of, like, making sure I'm not scared to, like, hang out with people and stuff.
Um, I know, like, Mint travels so much and meets up with so many people, and I envy her, and I envy her for having, like, so much, I guess, like, extrovert charisma to just, uh, do all of that, um, in general.
Uh, maybe one day.
Maybe one day I'll be brave enough to do something like that.
Um, anyway, that's my, that's my life talk today.
I hope you guys had a fun time.
Um, I hope you guys all had a fun time listening to me yap and hanging out with the sloppy sisters today.
Um, tomorrow I'll be playing Elden Ring, uh, Sunday, no stream, as always, no stream on Sunday.
I don't know about Monday, we'll see, but I won't have a stream on Sunday, but tomorrow I'll be doing Elden Ring.
Uh, I'm gonna head off now, as always, everybody, stay hydrated, posture check, get up and move around to get that blood flowing, and if you stay up for me, head to bed, cause you deserve it.
I'll see you guys next time, everybody.
Uh, bye, guys.
Bye!