Yeah, technology these days.
Did you show your chat?
The tomato foogie?
Yeah, I was drawing it before.
Okay, wait, I need to show it.
Let's just take a welcoming shot, you know?
Get it out of the way.
What are you drinking?
I'm drinking sparkling sake.
Okay, I'm drinking a hard iced tea.
I was gonna buy soju, but I didn't have time.
Bye-bye.
Hard iced tea.
What is the percentage of that?
Okay, it's like...
Oh my gosh, what is the percentage of it?
Okay, there's vodka in here though, so...
Ooh!
It's hard, hard.
That's hard.
That's really hard.
Yeah, that's how hard it is.
It's 5%.
Okay, tears!
It's...
By the way, it's so hard.
It's only 5%.
5%?
Okay, mine is...
What is this?
Oh, this is delicious.
What the heck?
Oh, Lily is loud?
Okay, let me turn you down a little bit.
You are quiet for me.
I have you at 200%.
Ooh...
Maybe... okay.
Actually, I think it's okay.
Chat by the chat.
Oh yeah, I can turn myself up a little bit.
And...
It's okay now.
Okay.
Yeah, okay.
Alright, I turned Lily down a little bit too, on my end.
But hello everybody!
Sorry, we didn't really have an intro.
We just went...
We just got in the call.
But hello guys.
It's me at DokiBird.
And then we have here... I mean...
Well, people on Lily's channel will know who she is.
Uh...
I have Lily Piccio with me right now.
I like how you, like, take a shot, right?
Yeah.
That's good.
It's good.
Uh, we're gonna be...
Oh, sorry.
I'm so sorry.
No, wait, no.
You go.
Is your sparkling sake hitting hard now?
No, no.
Is it hitting?
No.
Let's...
Let's turn over.
Please.
Okay.
Hello, everyone.
My name is DokiBird.
I'm here with Lily Piccio.
Oh, yeah.
You're gonna stay.
Okay.
We're gonna draw stuff.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
It's gonna be great.
We're such professional...
We're such professionals.
We're gonna be drawing random characters from memory while drunk.
So, we'll see...
We'll see how...
How well it goes the longer we go.
Yippee!
Oh, yeah.
I want...
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
No, you go first.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You go first.
Wait.
How are we drawing?
Are we...
Okay.
Separate canvas or...
You know the canvas where we can draw together?
What are you thinking?
I feel...
No, I think it'll be funnier if we could surprise each other.
Okay.
Of what it would look.
And then we just send each other the picture.
And then we can just show it on stream.
In terms of like picking what we draw, I feel like each of us could pick from our own chats what they suggest.
And then like if we don't know it, we'll just have the chat describe or like we have each other describe it to the other person.
If we know what it is.
Oh, okay.
I caught the first three sentences.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
So, this is how I think we could do it.
We could do it where we...
Each of us take turns grabbing a suggestion from chat.
Yeah, yeah.
And then like if the other person doesn't know what the character is.
Oh, the chat describes it.
Yeah, the chat describes it.
I see.
We also...
Or if like we know what it is, we'll also describe it to each other.
Oh, one more.
One more question.
Are we doing the same thing then?
Yeah, yeah.
We're drawing the same thing.
And then we'll show each other the picture and be like...
Got it.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
So, also for those who are wondering, they're like, oh, why this sudden collab?
Well, I was on Lily's podcast earlier this week.
Yeah, we did a VTuber episode.
Yeah.
Which was really cute actually.
I really liked it.
Yeah, I love how you made Kroki like transparent.
Oh, Kroki.
Okay.
She was very disappointed because I hyped Kroki up so much.
And then I couldn't get it to work.
All she saw was like, it was just like a static, not moving Kroki.
It was the most underwhelming thing I've ever seen in my life.
I'm like, this is okay.
Should I...
I'll be nice.
Yeah.
She's like, um...
Yeah, it looks...
Yeah, that's so...
That looks so good.
Okay.
I was like, no, I swear to God.
I swear to God, it's so much funnier when it can move.
No, no, I bet.
She did show me later and it was really cool.
Yeah, it was pretty funny.
But...
Before then, it was very whelming.
Uh...
Oh wait, I wanna show my chat...
Oh wait, let me show my chat to Fuki you drew.
Alright, let me...
Oh my gosh.
Wait, let me send you...
There's a talking version.
I don't know if that one's cute or...
Don't worry, I'll use this...
I'll use it one day in the...
I'll use it tomorrow, actually.
I'll use it...
I have a collab tomorrow, so I'll use this tomorrow.
Sorry, Pharrell.
Uh...
My...
One of my fan artists actually drew me a Fugi, too.
Like, this week.
Um...
Sorry, Pharrell.
We're using this tomato one tomorrow.
Uh...
I thought...
I didn't know the collab...
I...
It's my first one.
I've never tried it.
You've never done a VTuber collab before?
I guess whenever I play with other VTubers or whatever...
We just did Fugi.
I didn't know this was a thing in this...
Oh, now you...
Yeah.
Now you do.
You can, like...
Actually, you can, like, attach stuff onto...
Uh...
Onto, like, the other...
Other, like, VTuber, too.
If you want.
I can control you.
Yeah, you can basically make me smaller, too.
If you want me to.
And you make me smaller, and then attach myself onto you.
So, like, when you're moving, I'll move, too.
Yeah.
Yeah, when you're AFK, I was smelling you.
No, I...
I...
I might have saw you, uh, trying to, like, kiss me, too, earlier.
I did.
I did do that, yeah.
I love the...
You were, like, AFK, the...
Oh, yeah.
The full circle loading thing.
That was cute.
Yeah, the buffering.
That's how I feel every day, to be fair.
Alright, let's...
Let's start draw...
Drink...
Drawing.
Oh, drinking or...
Oh, you can do both.
Okay.
Okay, I need my BGM to start.
Alright, I have my BGM playing now.
This is too delicious.
Why is it so good?
Wait, what flavor is it?
It's, like, sparkling peach.
It's just...
Sake.
That sounds nice.
It's a carbonated sake with peach flavors.
I really like it.
That sounds really nice.
Mine's just iced tea.
I could never drink, like, actual, like, hard liquor type drinks.
To be fair.
They're kind of disgusting and they smell and taste like nail polish.
I don't know how people can drink beer.
I'm sorry.
Beer is even worse.
I...
I'm sorry to all the beer lovers, but, like, I actually...
I cannot handle beer.
It's just...
I need something fruity, you know?
It sounds...
It looks good, though.
You know, like, the golden...
Oh, yeah, like...
Yeah, yeah.
The foam and everything.
Yeah.
The anime makes it look so delicious.
Yeah, and it's like...
Kanbei!
Yeah!
But, like, I can't.
I don't really like...
I don't like...
Actually, I don't even like wine, to be fair.
I don't think you like alcohol.
Well, no, it's just like...
Okay.
It's just too...
Sour?
Slash...
It's just, like, sour slash bitter for me.
So, like, I just can't handle wine, in general, as well.
Uh, just cause, like, the taste of it is just...
I just like...
I just like it when it's...
When it doesn't taste like alcohol.
Yeah.
It's all those fruity cocktails.
Yeah, like the fruity cocktails.
Yeah.
Mm-mm-mm-mm-mm-mm.
Alright.
So, my sound guy said to bring down the BGM, so I'll bring it down a little bit.
Um...
I haven't drawn...
I actually have not drawn in a very long time.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, me too.
Wait, when was the last time you, like...
Like, drawn anything?
I was thinking...
30 minutes ago.
I'm sorry.
Okay, before this collab, before we set up this...
I was drawing before!
Yeah, you have been drawing!
Oh, so you've been lying.
Yeah, but...
I just with...
Got my...
Tablet.
I have to dust it off.
The...
Drawing tablet that connects to the piece.
Cause I usually use my iPad, and it won't connect.
Yeah.
Oh...
I'll use...
Yeah, yeah, that makes sense.
Oh, guys, don't mind the circles.
I was testing out brushes.
Alright.
What program are you using?
I'm using Paint Tool Sai.
Oh, me too!
Okay.
Are you using Sai 1 or 2?
Wait, you didn't know there was a 2?
I thought there was a 2.
I don't know.
Man...
I'm just not with the time, bro.
It should say...
It should say 2 on the top left.
Top left?
Oh!
It just...
Maybe this is just 1 then.
Oh my god!
Wait, there's 2?
Yes, there's 2.
It came out 10 years ago.
Version info.
Oh my god!
I didn't see version 1.
Dude, I have...
I'm...
I'm in aura depth right now.
This is nuts.
Okay, to be fair, to be fair, everybody usually use clips...
Uh, what was it called?
Clip Studio, right?
Yeah, Clip Studio.
Everyone uses Clip Studio now.
Like, people who still use, like, Sai just refuse to, like, learn.
Um, which is me.
That's me!
Yeah, me too!
I don't wanna change.
I don't...
I don't like change.
I'm using this program.
Okay, to be fair, have you seen Clip Studio?
Find the program.
Like, use the program?
I have.
I've used it before.
It's good.
Yeah, it's good, but the...
It's so overwhelming.
Like, you know how Clip Studio, everything's just there?
Mm-hmm.
And then, um, not Clip Studio, sorry.
Paying Toe Sai, everything's just there.
And, it's like so...
Straightforward.
I like that.
Yeah, it's simple.
It's simple.
I keep it simple.
And then, I see like Clip Studio, and there's like...
Different...
There's just so many...
The overlay is just so intimidating.
And, I used it, like, one time, and I just crawled back to Sai.
I feel like if you're just used to a program... you know, you can make art out of anything, right?
Yes, true.
That's so true.
Like, people can make, like, those, like... or the Roblox ones.
Have you seen the Roblox artists?
Roblox?
Wait, you've never seen the Roblox artists?
So much art.
You can go to, like, a... there's, like, Roblox servers dedicated to, like, Roblox artists.
And they would actually draw, like, the Mona Lisa and stuff like that on Roblox.
Yeah, like, there's, like, a... I only know about it because it popped up on my Twitter...
my For You Twitter feed.
And they're like, here's, like, a... here's a three-hour time lapse of my artwork being drawn at the server.
And I was like, what the fuck?
This was done in Roblox?
I feel like good artists can draw Mona Lisa's anywhere.
Yeah, that's so true.
You know?
Like, I've seen the coffee stain art, whatever, and it was fantastic.
Oh.
Are you okay?
No, I'm great.
I'm great.
I'm just really excited to draw Pokemon.
Oh, yeah, we're gonna start with Pokemons first.
Alright.
Sure.
Sure, yeah, let's do that.
Alright.
We'll take a suggestion from Lily's chat.
Since, you know, Lily Pichu.
Oh, yeah.
I always forget about that shit.
Wait, what the fuck?
12-year-old Lily.
I could not think of anything else.
Was Pichu even your favorite Pokemon?
It was.
To be fair, it was my favorite Pokemon back then.
Because I thought, oh, it's like, it's not Pikachu and everyone loves Pikachu.
Yeah, yeah.
Wait.
12-year-old.
What's your favorite Pokemon now, then?
I like Comfy.
Comfy?
Which one's that?
It's like the circle of flowers that floats.
Oh, it's that one!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wait, I know.
She's also the...
Have you ever played...
Oh my gosh, what's the Pokemon League of Legends?
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Pokemon Unite!
Pokemon Unite?
Have you ever played Pokemon Unite?
She's the Yumi of...
Yeah, she's the cat!
She's the cat!
You don't have to do anything!
You don't do shit!
You just attack yourself to people!
I play Comfy...
No, I...
I...
I didn't...
I was not a Comfy main.
I was bored.
I like Sylveon and Pikachu.
Oh my gosh, me too.
I love Sylveon.
What's your favorite Eeveelution?
Sylveon.
Okay, one of the biggest reasons why...
I always tell this in my chat, but one of the biggest reasons why I love Sylveon is the fact that when I found out...
It's pink!
No.
Sorry, go on.
To be honest, pink is actually not my favorite color.
Uh...
But...
Um...
But one of the reasons is because when I found out that...
The...
The ribbons are actually, like, made out of his flesh.
And, like, I thought it was, like, super hardcore.
If you think about it.
Because the ribbons, when they touch you, they're feeling your emotion.
And for that to happen, it's made of, literally, flesh ribbons.
I did not know that.
Yeah.
I thought it was just ribbons.
No, no.
They use their ribbons...
To, like, touch your body.
To, like, feel what you're feeling and stuff like that.
And then I was like, oh my god.
They're literally attached to their skin.
Like...
It's...
Wow.
Wait, that...
That's cool.
Yeah.
And I was like, wait, that's so hardcore.
Like...
Alright.
What did your chat pick?
Um...
Okay, sorry.
Uh...
Beedrill.
A lot of people said Beedrill.
Oh my god.
I don't remember this at all.
But I would do my best.
Okay?
Um...
There's a reason why.
Okay.
There's a reason why your chat picked Beedrill.
Yeah.
I...
I'm assuming you're very...
You love Beedrill?
No.
No!
Do you love Beedrill?
I think...
Okay, it was...
That's fine.
I'm not judging anything.
It's fine.
This was a long time ago.
Uh-huh.
But basically, the reason why they're picking Beedrill is because...
Oh my gosh.
The fact that I actually remember how to draw Beedrill because of this.
Um...
I did something similar where I was like, oh, I'm gonna draw Pokemon from memory.
And then I was like, fuck Beedrill.
Beedrill looks so...
It's so dumb and stupid and hard to draw.
Um...
Because I was like, okay throughout it until I got to Beedrill.
And then...
And then I was like, I'm gonna skip Beedrill for the entire...
Like, I'm gonna skip Beedrill.
I don't care.
And then...
Oh.
They're like, what if we bribe you?
And I was like, you have to give me a hundred dollars if you...
Someone give you a hundred dollars.
I see.
Not just someone.
I got like...
50 plus...
50 plus donations!
To draw Beedrill?
To draw.
Because I was like, I will...
Every hundred dollars I get, I'll draw one Beedrill.
So then I got...
I drew...
I don't even remember how many Beedrills I drew.
I actually had to turn off my donations.
Like, I had to turn off my super chats.
So I didn't have to draw more Beedrills.
Wait, that's...
Honestly, bang for your buck.
I like that.
But like...
The thing is, I had to like, keep my promise.
So I spent like...
I think like eight plus hours just trying Beedrill.
Over and over and over.
And then I outsourced it too.
I outsourced it to my friends.
You outsourced it.
I would like...
I like invited my friends to join the stream and I outsourced it to the...
They didn't get paid.
They...
They were just there...
They were...
They got paid in being my company.
Yeah, in my company.
So...
Um...
So they drew...
Help me drew some Beedrills too.
Uh...
To...
To repay the debt.
The Beedrill debt.
Well, I'm drawing one right now.
So...
Get to it.
I'm drawing one too.
Oh my gosh.
Okay.
Oh my fucking...
I don't remember how to...
Okay.
I know I said I...
I remember how to draw a Beedrill.
But I actually sort of low-key...
I remember like vaguely how to draw a Beedrill.
There's a...
Oh, this is so bad.
Okay.
And then like...
There's his wings.
And...
Oh god.
It's like one of those Pokemon I just don't draw ever.
Okay.
Like I don't know what it looks like.
I...
Beedrill...
Yellow.
...stands on his two legs.
He's like an...
He has two legs?
And...
Okay.
Keep describing it.
This is kind of open.
Okay.
So he looks like a bee.
And...
Adam, you know this.
Oh my...
Drill, right.
Yeah.
And his two arms are his drills.
So...
Oh!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, no, no.
Yeah, yeah.
So...
Oh my gosh.
Okay, wait.
Is it like this?
I think it's kind of like that.
Oh my gosh.
I'm...
Okay.
So...
And then...
And then the top is...
It's just a bee head.
And then he's standing on his two legs.
He has two legs.
Okay.
Yeah.
And he has two drills.
How do his legs look?
Can you describe them?
I...
That's the one part I don't remember.
That's...
Okay, it's fine.
I'm just gonna...
I'm just gonna wait.
Is it...
Are they buff?
Are they...
Are they skinny?
Like...
I think they're skinny?
Because it's a bug?
I...
That's true.
It should be skinny because he's a bug, right?
Also, the worst part is that...
Since I haven't...
I never...
Um...
Uh...
I haven't downloaded Paint Tool Sai on this PC.
So, like...
I lost all my brushes.
So...
I was so sad.
Wait, same.
I got a new PC recently and I have lost everything.
Yeah, I was so sad.
Because, like...
I actually had, like, a custom brushes and everything.
And I had, like...
I lost it all.
Yeah.
So, I don't remember what my brushes were.
Yeah, I think I...
I think I nailed it.
I think I'm good.
I...
Wait, you're already done?
Oh, sorry, guys.
I'll...
I'll details while you're doing.
No, don't worry about it.
Take your time.
I'm just gonna add some details.
Okay, maybe I'll...
I'll do faster then.
Alright.
You know what?
Fuck it.
I'm just gonna...
The top part, I tried and then I stopped trying.
Wait, how deta...
You know what?
I'll see how detailed we're going.
Oh no, it's not detailed by it.
It's not detailed.
Let's make a change track.
I'll know.
It's not detailed.
I straighta...
I straighta gave up.
I...
We'll fix it in post.
Ready to send it?
Okay.
Wait, uh.
Alright.
Yeah, I'm ready.
I'm just gonna snip it from my OBS.
Yeah, I'm just gonna copy-paste it.
Yeah, it's gonna be from my OBS.
Okay.
Look, it's just warm-up, it's... Send yours, send yours, send yours, send yours!
I'll never be able to live up to this.
I feel like the alcohol has already hit it for you.
Oh my god.
Okay, who do you think is less accurate?
Okay.
I mean, more accurate.
Who do you think is more accurate?
I would say you, right?
I mean, I feel like it would be me because I had the experience of trying Beedrill so many times.
But... Oh, this is so cute.
Why don't you look up what Beedrill looks like?
Why don't you look it up?
Oh no, I'm gonna be so disappointed.
That's what it looks like?
I see...
That is...
Why did you give him, like, one...
Like, one black strip, like...
I thought... I knew... I knew there was a black stripe.
I just didn't know where it was.
Oh!
Yeah, it looks like he's, like, wearing a little skirt.
Like...
Next Pokemon, next play.
I mean...
Wait.
Why did you give him lips?
I gave him lips?
Oh, I thought...
Yeah, why did you...
I don't know why...
Why?
I thought Beedrill had a mouth.
It's a bee.
Bees have...
No mouth?
Stay in school, kids.
But...
But it's a...
I mean, they do have mouths, but, like, when you look at a bee, like...
Maybe I've never seen a bee up close.
To be fair, to be fair, I mean, like, I'm scared of bees, too, but...
But, like, when you look at it from, you know, like, a little bit far, you don't really see a mouth in general.
I think.
That's true.
I mean, to be fair, they're, like, super fuzzy.
The bumblebees.
All right, my turn.
All right, guys, suggest a...
Suggest a Pokemon, and then we'll pick...
It's your turn, chat.
Don't disappoint us.
We're not gonna do another bug.
We're not gonna...
There's no more bug.
They were trying to suggest a buzz swole.
Oh god, I hope it's...
First three gens, cause I'm...
The first same.
I...
I start falling apart.
I, like, stopped paying attention to Pokemon when we went to Paris.
You know the, the XY?
We went to Paris.
Like, oh, no.
They went to Paris!
Like, XY!
Pokemon XY!
They have an Eiffel Tower!
There was an Eiffel Tower!
I don't think I played XY.
I went straight to Sun and Moon.
You went...
Wait, when did you stop?
Uh...
Like, the first three gens, and then you skipped a gen?
And then you went straight to Sun and Moon?
I think so, yeah.
Okay, someone said...
Uh...
Mudkip.
Oh!
Okay, Mudkip!
Mudkip, I remember.
Yeah.
Okay, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
This is easy!
Mudkip's easy!
Yeah!
Remember those Mudkip memes?
Yeah, yeah.
Mudkip!
Yeah, that was on DeviantArt.
Yeah!
Oh, DeviantArt!
I'm sorry!
Okay, so...
I went off.
Okay, wait.
I actually sort of don't remember Mudkip.
I don't remember the Mudkip.
Yeah!
I was like, wait!
He was like...
He had like a big ass mouth.
That's his thing.
Because he was like, Mudkip!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He said Mudkip.
Yeah, and then...
Oh my god.
I have not drawn in so long.
This has been so long since I've done art.
Okay.
Accurate.
Oh, honest?
I'm kind of cooking with this one.
Oh my gosh.
I miss my brushes.
I feel so like handicapped without my usual brushes.
This one can kill me.
How does his body look?
It's like this, right?
And then he's like...
Like a little axolotl?
I don't know.
Oh yeah, because he was based off of an axolotl.
Yeah, and those are cute little guys.
And then it was like...
And then he had like little cheek things, right?
Did he have a tail?
Yeah, he did.
That one I remember.
Tail.
Okay, uh...
And then there's like...
It's like his...
His...
Oh my gosh.
His side.
I know I'm wrong somehow.
I like it.
This is good.
I know I'm wrong, but I...
I cannot be too sure how wrong I am.
I know he's like...
What is it?
Blue and orange, right?
Orange?
No.
Wait, is it not?
His body was blue.
Blue?
Yeah, but he had orange things coming out, I remember.
Was it not yellow?
Or orange?
It was like orange...
Yellow...
Ish?
And then like...
And then yellow...
Yeah, but...
Were these orange too?
Yeah, it was like that.
What?
I'm gonna just try orange.
I guess it's orange.
Yeah, it was like this.
Yeah!
I feel like I'm so wrong.
Yeah, no, no, no.
Okay!
This does not look right.
This looks...
Fantastic.
I might make stickers of this.
Nice.
Capitalism.
Mud.
Was it shiny?
Did it have a glow to it?
A glow?
Yeah, like a glow.
What?
Alright!
Are you trying to draw a shiny right now?
I'm done.
Okay, me too.
Alright.
Okay, okay.
Okay, alright.
Wanna send it at the same time?
Alright, yeah.
Three, two, one.
Wait, why did I cut the same shit?
Your straws are so cute.
And tiny.
Okay.
No, to be fair, the reason why it's tiny is because I'm just snipping it from my OBS.
That's the only way I did it so tiny.
Okay.
Oh, these are so cute.
It's like...
Oh no, yours is...
I can tell you're the artist here.
No.
Yours is the artist.
It has the same vibe of it though, you know?
Yeah, you know, like...
I'm looking up how it looks.
Yeah, me too.
Wait, are we close?
Were we close?
I...
Oh, it was orange.
Yeah.
It was.
I mean...
We got the cheek part right.
Yeah, we got the cheek part right.
And I got the tail.
I think...
Yeah, I got it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I got the tail right.
It was...
The top part.
I didn't realize the top was blue.
I forgot all about it.
I forgot.
I thought it was orange too.
Yeah, I thought it was like part...
The same color as...
You know what?
We did pretty well.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Look, see?
I mean, it's almost...
Almost looks...
I feel like if both of our artworks had a drawing, it will produce the original Mudkip.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, like, because I got the...
I got like, sort of the tail and the body right.
And then you got the face correct.
I think we did pretty good.
I think, you know what?
Feels like you were like...
For some reason, I have a feeling that you draw a lot.
No, I'm just a small-time artist.
Yeah, it's just a little hobby of yours.
You picked up a...
You just started picking up a tablet.
I see your little...
I see the sketch layer in yours.
I see it.
Yeah, I don't know.
For me, I've never really learned how...
Not...
I won't say...
Is learning the right word?
I never, like, learned how to do, like, freehand drawing.
I'm so bad at freehand.
It's just...
I always...
I had...
When I actually used to draw, which was, like, years ago...
Um...
It would take me, like, a lot of...
Like, it would take me, like, three to four hours for a finished GB in general.
Oh, I see, I see.
Yeah, because, like, I would, like, control Z all the time.
Because I wanted, like, perfect lines and everything.
Um...
So, like, it was just...
I don't know how to draw fast.
It would take me, like, hours to even draw one thing.
I think I am the opposite word.
Because I streamed myself drawing...
And chat has, like, such...
Such...
Dogshade attention span sometimes.
I have to...
I feel like I taught myself I gotta draw really fast.
Oh, yeah.
Or, like, chat would judge me.
I don't want to embarrass myself.
Oh, they're gonna yell at me.
Yeah.
I think when I used to do, like, art streams, I just, like...
I would, like, draw for, like, ten minutes and then spend the rest of the time just chatting with my stream.
So, like, nothing would be done.
All right.
All right, Lillies, chat.
Choose the next art...
Okay, chat, give me a suggestion.
It doesn't have to be Pokemon.
Oh, yeah.
Honestly, send us whatever you guys want.
Yeah, send us whatever.
Let's do whatever you want.
Some of these are not Pokemon.
Why Arbok?
Arbok's...
Oh, Arbok's Pokemon.
That's the snake.
Because it's backwards.
It's, like, it's from Ikans.
You know Ikans?
The other snake and it's snake backwards.
Yeah, and Cobra.
Oh, yeah, yeah, Arbok is Cobra backwards.
Okay, let's do Arbok then.
I remember Arbok.
He's like...
Arbok.
You know what?
And then he had, like, the little...
He had a handsome face, from what I remember.
For a snake?
Yeah, for a snake.
What does that mean?
I'm gonna try and freehand this.
He's a handsome face.
He's a snake.
And?
What is considered a handsome snake?
I just remember it being a little suave, you know?
Like, I had a bit of, like, a...
Am I misremembering?
God, I hope I'm not misremembering.
Anyway...
Oh, wait!
No, I know what you're talking about.
Not the part that, you know, that she's right that the snake was handsome.
But, like...
You like snakes.
But...
I remember exactly when you said, like...
He had, like, the type of face.
I was like, oh, I know what...
Yeah, you remember?
It was like a...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm kind of looking at you sort of way, you know?
Like a sassy face.
Yeah, yeah.
And then he had, like...
Because it was a cobra, he had the little frill thing at the top.
Oh, man.
Wait, are you a skelly?
A skelly?
You mean, like, do I, like...
Snakes?
So, like...
So, like, you know furries?
Yeah.
So, like, that's, like, the...
That's basically for, like, skellies, it's like furries.
But, like, specifically for, like, reptiles.
Oh, that's why Skara calls himself, um, his fans...
Or his viewers, skellies.
Yeah, yeah.
Because he's trying to say they're all...
They're all sexually attracted to reptiles.
I think I'd rather be a furry.
Wait, why?
Over a skelly.
A horseman.
You're a horse...
Oh, you're a ho...
Oh, yeah, you're a horse girl now.
Have you ever had...
I was...
Have you ever had a horse girl, Ari?
Never?
No, never.
Umamu Sima is, like, my entry to...
Wait, not even, like, Milo Pony?
I mean, I liked it, but I wasn't, like, super into it, you know?
Oh, so you were in, like, a...
What's it called?
A Pegasus-y.
I was not a Pegasus-y.
Who were...
Were you?
No, no, I...
I didn't watch...
I didn't...
Why did you...
Why didn't you say it like that?
No, I'm just crazy.
You had no judgment here.
I was, unfortunately, not a Pegasus-y, but I did...
I did watch the show, because, like, I actually, like...
I'm, like, a huge animation fan.
So, like, I really liked the animation for Milo Pony.
You're like Applejack!
Sorry.
Applejack?
Not Rainbow Dash?
Rainbow Dash!
But...
I only said Apple because of the blonde hair.
Oh!
Apple Dash...
Wait, the Apple Dash had a...
Oh, yeah, Apple Dash did have blonde hair.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, and then she had, like, braids and stuff, too.
But, like, you know, like...
Each episode cost, like...
I think, like, $440,000.
Holy crap.
I might be making numbers up, but it was, like...
Triple...
Like, it was, like, you know, six figures.
Basically, per, like, episode.
And, yeah, it was, like, super fucking expensive.
But, like, you know, it's Hasbro.
They have the money.
They have...
You're very knowledgeable about My Little Pony.
Well, I just, like, I, like, I have, like, anim...
I just know a lot of animation facts in general.
Because, like, I spent too much...
I was chronically online before I became a streamer.
I'm not...
And we are still chronically online.
Anyway, I'm done.
We're still chronically...
Oh, me too.
Oh, sick.
Alright.
I don't think I cooked with this one.
Me too.
Well, my...
I tried to draw a face on the...
Like, you know, like...
Because they're, like, a cobra.
Oh, my God.
You put...
Why did you put...
Why did you put so much effort on this?
I didn't know how long it was supposed to be.
But it was, like...
I'm, like, if you scroll up...
If you scroll up, like, you can see how fast you did Vigil.
And then for some reason, you're...
You're...
He's so...
Your art book is so detailed.
Like, I...
I don't...
You got the eyes on the thing.
I didn't know what those were.
Wait, what?
Oh, you mean the...
The, um...
He had a face on his chest or something, right?
Wait, he had a face on his chest?
I thought it was, like, on...
Are those not eyes?
Wait, okay, wait.
All right.
Let me look it up.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It looks like an elephant.
Yeah, I remember he had, like, evil eyes and everything.
But, like, I couldn't remember exactly what...
I knew there was red on it.
And I was like, oh, whatever.
I don't see color right now.
I...
I can only see in...
In black and white right now.
Yours looks like an elephant.
With the elephant ears on...
I feel like mine looks like an Egyptian drawing.
Oh, that's so fun.
Keep those.
All right, chat.
My chat time.
Time to give us...
Give us a...
Any character.
It doesn't have to be Pokemon.
We're not locked into Pokemon, right?
We really are.
You can suggest whatever you want.
Whatever you want, guys.
Not...
Not just Pokemon.
I like how I say that and it's still just Pokemon.
Guys, we're not gonna draw Starscream.
I don't think, like, either of us can.
I'm just kidding.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, so...
He's basically a Decepticon.
And you know what Decepticons are?
Oh, boy.
All right, let me explain the lore of Transformers.
So, in Transformers, it's...
In Transformers, it's...
You know Autobots?
Okay, so...
So, these are robots in cars.
So, they're robots in disguise.
But they're not just cars.
They can be, like, any, like, mechanical thing.
Or not mechanical thing.
Depending on if it's Beast Wars.
Because for Beast Wars, they can scan animals.
And then turn into the animals' machine...
Like, the machine's machinery animals.
But so, there's different types of Transformers.
The ones you know is Optimus Prime.
And he's an Autobot.
And an Autobot is, like, the good robot.
And then he's against Megatron, who is a bad robot.
And his crew is called Decepticons.
And then, so, it's, like...
It's, like, a millennia year-long battle.
Between the Autobots versus the Decepticons.
And so, like, Megatron's right-hand man is called Starscream.
And the reason why his name is Starscream...
Is because his voice is, like, super shrill and everything.
So, that's why his name is Starscream.
Because...
Actually, no.
It depends on which version it is.
Because in another version, his voice was normal.
But then Megatron, like, choked him.
Like, and choked him.
And he liked it.
And then his voice turned to be, like, shrillian.
And everything because of it.
Because Megatron broke his voice box.
And so, like, that's why his voice is like that now.
But anyway, Starscream is, like, the right-hand man of Megatron.
And...
Lily, are you getting all of that?
Yeah, I'm trying while you're...
Oh, okay.
I'm trying while you're talking, yeah.
Okay, so, yeah.
So, Starscream is, like, the evil right-hand man of Megatron.
And his entire...
And he wants to actually be the leader of the Septicons.
So, he's always trying to sabotage, like, Megatron's plans.
Or, like, trying to kill him and everything.
But anyway, Starscream.
Basically, he looks...
It depends on which version you're talking about in Transformers.
There's, like, various...
There's, like, various designs of Starscream.
So, there's one where he's, like...
There's called, like...
There's, like...
Oh, there's, like, Michael Bay version.
There's G1 Starscream.
There's Armada Starscream.
And there's also...
There's Beast Wars Starscream.
What does he look like?
Just curious.
I just want to...
Okay, okay.
So, sorry.
I just need to make sure that you know the whole...
His personality.
Yeah, no, I think I got it.
So, he put that into the feeling of Starscream.
Like, he put that in the feeling.
And so...
He...
Basically, he is based off a fighter jet.
So...
He's a jet.
Yeah, he's a jet.
So, untransformed.
He looks like...
Okay, it's like a robot face.
I'll give you G1.
Okay, for G1 design, it's like...
You know, okay, he's a robot.
But he has a nose.
And he has, like, evil eyes.
And then he has, like, a little helmet.
Blocky helmet thing.
You know, like, a Minecraft helmet?
A Minecraft...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
So, like...
It's his head.
The top hat...
The top of his head, it looks like he's wearing a Minecraft helmet.
Okay.
Yeah.
And then, like, his body is, like...
Like, you know, like, rock'em, sock'em robots?
Kinda, yeah.
So, like, you know, it's like a blocky...
It's like a blocky body.
And then he has, like, jet wings on his back.
Jet...
You know what?
Yeah, and then...
I think I got it.
He wears high.
His shoes are, like...
His feet is, like, high heels.
High heels.
Got it.
Yeah.
But, like, not the stilettos.
They're, like...
Like, the blocky high heels.
Blocky high heels.
Got it.
Yeah, and his color scheme is, like, gray...
Dark gray.
And, like...
Red on the wings.
So, the helmet is dark gray.
His eyes are red.
And his wings are red.
Yeah.
You got it?
I think I got it.
Yeah, helmet's red?
Yeah, no, his helmet is dark gray.
Dark gray, sorry.
Wings are red.
Yeah.
Yeah, his wings are red.
Wings are red, got it.
And then, like...
And he's very hot.
I can't get it all.
I cannot get it all.
I didn't try.
Actually, I just want to see what you drew.
As someone who's never seen stars green before.
I want to know what...
What is his body color?
His body color?
It's, um...
It's, like...
Red and white.
Red and white?
So, you know, like, a bee?
Yeah.
So, like...
Um, his, like...
His top part is red.
And then, like...
The middle is white.
And the...
Uh-huh.
The pants area is red.
And red.
Got it, got it, got it.
And his, uh...
And then, don't forget the Decepticon logo on his wing.
So, Decepticon...
Okay, yeah, no, I got it.
So, he has a Decepticon logo.
And his Decepticon logo...
Yeah.
Is on his right wing.
Right wing?
Yeah.
And so, the Decepticon logo...
It's, like...
Just draw, like, a head.
And then he has two pointy horns.
On that.
Got it.
Yeah.
And then, what about shoes?
Shoes, it's, like...
I think it's blue.
Okay.
I will stick with blue.
And I'm pretty much done, then.
Okay.
I didn't draw it.
Because I...
I just wanted to...
Make sure you portray it accurately.
I got to look up Starscream.
I'm gonna see what...
Was I close?
Oh, I wasn't close.
Oh...
Because it's a star, you know?
Because I...
I thought the star was...
I said...
I said, like, the Minecraft helmet.
Then why is it just a wrinkle in the helmet?
I...
Wait, I forgot.
He's, like, going to war.
Wow.
Hey, I think he did a great job.
I...
You know, to be fair...
Like, you got...
You got the personality of Starscream correct.
You know, I...
People were like, why did you describe the entire plot of...
Like, the entire origin?
But look, she got the personality correct.
Yeah, he's evil.
If I didn't describe his entire life story...
We wouldn't...
I don't think you could have gotten that yet.
Yeah, exactly.
It's the same picture.
He looks just like Starscream.
I don't think I'm sorry.
I don't think I just threw a star.
Oh my gosh, I almost finished my can.
I am definitely not sober.
I...
I am not...
Alright, it's your turn.
Alright, chat.
Again, it doesn't have to be Pokemon.
It could be whatever you want.
Anything you want.
Okay.
Oh god.
King from Tekken.
Okay, but like...
Which version?
What's the...
Um...
The one from Sage and Slam.
The one...
Yeah, that's the...
The default one, I guess, right?
Huh?
The default king?
Yeah, the default...
Okay, any king.
Might as well just be any king.
Okay.
Any king you want.
Yeah.
Okay, from what I could remember...
That's the one that had to play so much king.
He was like half naked, right?
Yeah, and he had a mask on.
That's a...
Oh yeah, that's like...
That's not him?
That's like...
I just thought...
I keep forgetting he's not a...
He's not like an actual...
Like...
Jaguar.
I was like...
Oh yeah, he's actually a man.
Yeah, he was like...
Shirtless and stuff, right?
A shirtless man.
That just...
Was just really, really into jaguars.
In general.
And he was like super buff and everything.
So he was like...
Yeah.
And then...
Did he have a cape?
I feel like he had a cape for some reason.
Did he?
Did he have a cape?
Am I...
I don't know what the...
I forgot what...
What a man's body looks like.
Like, the chest.
What does the chest look like?
Like, are we allowed?
Just like a really muscular...
If you draw nipples, is it still bannable on Twitch?
No, no, that's art.
That's gone, right?
No, remember when they...
Remember when they, like...
Remember when they, like, did a thing where...
Twitch did a rule where they're, like, you can draw porn...
If it's art.
And then, like...
And then the Twitch art category was just all, like, porn artists.
And then it got, like...
The rule got changed within a day.
And then, like, anyone that drew nipples or anything was bad...
Like, was, like, considered bannable.
So that's why I was like, did they fix that?
Did they fix it?
I think...
I think nipples are fine here, right?
I'm assuming...
As long as it's art, right?
Yeah, like...
Yeah, like, dots.
I was just trying dots.
Okay, yeah.
As long as it's not, like, detailed...
Yeah.
I'm not gonna draw a detailed king nipple.
Oh, that's...
Yeah.
I feel like he had a...
Cape for some reason.
Like, I'm not giving up on this idea.
Did he?
Did he have a cape?
I don't think so, but I...
I don't...
Maybe...
And he had, like, a six pack, cause he's, like, a wrestler.
He was, he was very muscular.
How do I draw six packs?
What do they...
What does that look like?
I think I just draw a line, and then, like, three lines going through it.
Cause I'm lazy.
Okay.
What...
What was he, like, leopard colored?
I don't...
Yeah, and then he...
He wore pants.
That's for sure.
I remember that.
Wait, what was...
He had pants on.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Cause he's, like...
Like a boxer?
Was it boxers?
Okay.
Oh, I have no idea.
Like a boxer...
Boxer...
Oh, whatever.
You know.
And then...
I'm gonna go with my cape idea.
I just...
Yeah, I just...
I feel like you're right.
Because he looks so...
Naked without...
Like, I mean, he was...
He is half naked.
But he looks really naked without a cape on.
So...
I feel like you're right.
This is...
The worst...
One yet.
I tried.
I'm gonna take a drink.
I think...
I think that's what he looked like.
Yeah.
Uh...
Okay, guys.
I don't remember...
What the abs look like, guys.
I don't remember.
I haven't watched a movie in so long.
Or like...
TV shows where they're...
There's half naked men.
Oh, look.
The frosty flakes guy.
Oh, God.
I think that's what he looks like.
Yeah.
Okay, wait.
Am I gonna color it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
I'm done.
You're done?
Okay.
Let me...
I'll color it a little bit, too.
I'll give it a little color.
Okay, I stopped.
I'm not gonna color it.
It does not look great.
All right.
Give me a sec.
Okay.
Ready?
Yeah.
Hey.
Oh, you got the face shape right.
What does yours look like?
It looks like a...
What does he look like?
Why does that your head looks like a cookie?
I thought that was a trap on us.
I don't know.
Oh.
Wait, did he have a cape?
Oh, wow.
He does have a cape.
Oh, we got him right!
Wait.
He has a cape.
You should look him up.
Okay.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's him.
Oh.
Oh, and he is half naked.
He did.
Yeah.
He has a mask on.
Oh, so he didn't have...
He didn't have shorts on.
It was, like, skin tight.
No, no.
I didn't know that.
I could not remember that at all.
He had, like, skin tight...
Skin tight pants on.
No.
I couldn't...
I never would have guessed skin tight pants on.
Yeah.
For some reason, I always thought he had shorts on.
It felt like he had...
Oh, cuz my king had shorts on.
Oh.
Yeah.
Custom king.
That's why.
Yeah.
I think...
Yeah, mine's, like, tic-tac-toe abs.
I...
I did not...
Did not remember what abs looked like.
No, I got the same tic-tac-toe.
Wait, no.
Yours is literally tic-tac-toe.
Mine is literally tic-tac-toe.
Do you know there's a game where you can play online multiplayer tic-tac-toe?
With, like, a group of people.
Look at him play.
Oh, my God.
There's, like, there's this one where, like, you can tic-tac-toe within a tic-tac-toe square.
So you battle...
Yeah.
That's, like, crazy.
I was like...
Cuz you can have, like...
It can be, like, four people playing tic-tac-toe at the same time.
So then, like...
You have to win the tic-tac-toe within that square.
To, like, win the square for your main tic-tac-toe.
Oh, I was just thinking of this.
Regular tic-tac-toe.
It's like...
It's like tic-tac-toe within a tic-tac-toe.
That's too much for me.
Too much tic-tac-toe.
Too much tic-tac-toe-ing... Toes.
Alright.
Oh, is the alcoholic hitting you now?
I'm almost done with this bottle.
Wait, you never told me how much percentage it had.
Oh my god, she's still going.
She's still going!
I'm sorry.
I couldn't suction the thing.
It was, like, stuck to the...
How much is it?
It's only, like... I think it's 7%.
Oh, it's not that bad.
It's not that bad, no.
I thought it'd be more because it's sake.
It's not that bad.
I would think it was, like, more because it's sake.
Isn't sake, like, more alcoholic?
I thought so, too.
Yeah.
I guess because it's sparkling.
So it diluted it a little bit because it's... They added, like, soda to it.
It's delicious.
Oh my god.
But what brand is it?
Hana Hawaka.
That's really sick.
Ooh, I would, like, try that.
I wish I had soju too, man.
Yo, have you ever had lemon soju?
Oh my god, I love lemon... I love, like, my favorite flavors are lemon soju.
Um... Peach soju.
What?
You had it already?
Yeah!
No, because, like, okay.
Um, because, like, uh... Um, when I... Um, this is a little bit, like, lore behind personal life thing, but when I was growing up, I went to international school growing up.
Mm-hmm.
Like, and then, like, one of the international schools I went to was just all...
Mostly, like, 60% Korean student body.
Yeah.
So then they would, like, teach me about, like, Korean drinking.
Okay, I didn't underage drink.
Did I?
No, I didn't.
No.
But when I turned 18, they took me, like, I met up with them in Korea and they, like, introduced me to soju.
Oh... Yeah.
Yeah, no, and then, like, it was, like... Because, like, soju is, like, so dangerous because, like, you can't taste the alcohol.
At all.
The fruit one, yes.
Yeah.
It's very dangerous.
Yes.
Yeah, because, like, that was, like, when they, like, introduced me to lemon soju, I had, like, I think, like, six to seven shots.
Whoa.
Because I was, like, oh, man, it's so good.
It tastes... It's so good.
I can't believe they only gave me so little.
Like, they gave me such a tiny little cup.
Yeah, that's just juice.
Yeah, it tastes just like juice.
And everything.
But... Don't drink, kids.
Yeah, don't drink and draw.
I'm staying in school.
Don't drink and draw.
Oh, my... If I... I don't have a car.
But if I did, I had a car on my car.
You wanted, like, a bumper sticker.
And don't drink and draw, yes.
Don't drink and draw.
Someone's gonna make that in the merch now.
Stay in school.
Like, in, like, in, like, a couple of months, Lily's store is gonna have... Don't drink and draw.
Don't drink and draw.
And I'll be like, where's my royalties?
Oh, God.
Okay, your chat now.
My chat.
Draw responsibly.
That's good.
I like that one.
Okay.
Drawing under the influence.
No.
Do you lie?
That's cute, dude.
Alright.
Give us a... It can... It can be anything.
It can be anything.
Anything.
Anything at all.
Anything that your heart desires.
I don't know.
You know?
Alright, someone suggested Zengie, but I don't want to draw another half-naked man right now.
No more, no more.
No more.
No more abs.
No more tic-tac-toe abs.
No more yipples.
Oh, Sans Undertale.
Okay.
I got this.
I love...
What's my Sans voice?
What's your Sans voice?
Oh my god, I was like...
My chat knows this, but I was like a huge Sans fan growing up.
Just Sans though.
None of the other characters.
She's a skeleton?
Yeah.
Oh god, this is so...
I don't remember.
Oh.
Skeleton.
I should just draw a skeleton and it'll look like him, probably.
And then he...
The thing is...
I love Sans so much.
I literally had like...
I had like a custom Sans doll.
And like a custom ball-jointed Sans doll as well.
Like a Sans plushie and a custom ball-jointed Sans...
Figure I bought from a Korean artist.
For some reason, Sans is incredibly popular in Korea.
Just Sans though.
Yeah, just Sans.
So like...
And they had like so much cool like custom shit from there.
Okay, uh...
Sans is a cool character.
I love Undertale.
I actually never...
I never played Undertale.
Oh!
I like...
The thing is, I watched so many playthroughs of it though.
I don't know.
Yeah.
I watched so many playthroughs of it because that...
So it's like...
I feel like me playing it...
I think I can't play it blind, you know?
That's the worst part.
Yeah, I mean, you already know what's gonna happen.
Yeah, I already know what's gonna happen, so...
I can't play it blind in general, so it's like, I felt like...
Because like, my chat would be like, Oh, when are you gonna try Undertale?
But like, I...
I can't.
You already know everything.
I know everything.
I like...
I literally...
I know every like...
Uh...
Ending possible that you can do and all the hidden secrets and everything.
So it's like...
I felt like there's no point in me playing it.
I feel like the best experience is to play it blind.
I feel like...
Was his jacket zipped up?
I don't know.
I know it was a...
He did have a jacket that looked like a winter...
Yeah, I remember that.
A winter's coat sort of thing.
Yeah.
I got that much.
And then, he...
You know, his eyes can...
Glow.
There's Hollow, right?
There's Hollow, what?
Hollow.
Hollow?
Hollow eyes, right?
Hollow eyes?
Yeah.
Yeah, because he's a skeleton.
He's a skeleton.
But he had something in it.
Remember when the...
You know the fu...
Ah, fuck.
I can't...
Remember what?
My communication skills are going down.
Wait.
The flame eyes.
Yeah, the blue flame eyes.
God damn it.
Yeah.
There's the flame eyes.
Oh, yeah.
And then...
I don't remember what's going on with his arm.
I don't think he had chicken.
No.
I don't...
Do you have pants?
Are you asking if he was...
Yes, of course he had pants on.
He had pants on?
No.
It was like shorts.
Oh!
It was shorts.
You're so right.
You are so right.
It's coming back.
It's like shorts and then...
And then he was wearing slippers.
Pink slippers.
Yes.
Nice.
Okay.
Okay, look.
When I said I had a really, really...
Deep obsession.
Yeah, you're very oddly knowledgeable about his...
Outfit.
I had a very, very deep obsession over this character.
You guys have no idea how bad it got.
It was really cool.
He was a pretty swell guy.
All right.
I'm done.
Same, same, same, same, same, same, same, same, same, same.
I'm ready.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
3...
Oh!
Okay.
I am so sorry.
Oh, you gotta smile!
Yeah, yeah!
The, the little...
The little oboe...
Steven Universe smile.
Dang.
The smile.
The only reason why I remember... Okay, this is... Okay, I don't know if I can tell this story because it's like... I don't remember how fucked up this picture is, so I... Wait, let me look it up real fast before I tell this story.
Um... Oh, okay.
Okay.
The only reason why I remember what his smile looks like... Was because there's a really fucked up picture where, like...
Okay, this is really bad.
This is really bad.
But, like... Um... You know Steven Universe, right?
Uh-huh.
So, like, people were saying that... There's, like... Sans was, like, basically... It's, like... Um... It's basically, like... There's a picture of... Oh, my gosh.
I am drunk.
There's a picture... There's a picture progression... Of Steven... Getting cancer... And his hair falling out...
And then... And then... And then he looks like Sans... And then... And then he looks like Sans... That's like... That's the only reason why... That's the only reason why... That's the only reason why I remember the smile... There's a game... There... Okay,
I'll show you the picture... Okay.
I'm sorry.
No.
I'm sorry Oh, no.
Oh my god, I can kind of see it, but no.
Because you're like, oh, the head.
The head is basically Steven's head.
Hey, what is this?
Guys, this is what... This is what Sans looks like.
Don't worry, guys.
Oh yeah, and then this is... I forgot to show Lilies.
You can tell the more drunk she is.
Don't worry, the image is starting to evolve in quality.
Is that true?
Wait, what?
No, you can... Look at your second artwork and then compare it to Sans.
Oh, this is great.
Oh god.
You can tell when the alcohol is starting to hit.
Next suggestion, please.
That's your chat.
Oh, chat.
Anything.
Oh god.
Okay, I like... Oh my god.
Oh my god.
Um...
Yeah?
What?
There's so many.
What is it?
I'm just gonna pick one.
Kirby with feet.
Did you just say curvy with feet?
Sorry, I was like the one that...
Is that your... Okay, curvy with...
I mean, we all know what curvy looks like.
Yeah, this should be easy.
But like, what type of feet?
Like the...
Feet.
But is it like the really detailed feet version?
I think artist...
I can't draw a circle.
Artist interpretation.
Okay.
I remember it.
Cause I...
There was...
There was an art...
I was like...
My staff member was...
Taking me around...
Um...
One of the artist alleys.
I think it was like...
Anime Expo or some shit.
And then like...
There's an artist that had the plushy of the...
Very realistic human feet.
Kirby.
Mmm.
And then...
I can't draw feet.
So I'm just gonna...
I think it's...
Gotta just...
Uh...
Yeah, that's...
And then...
Wait, what's the eye?
Wait, okay.
And then...
I'll do this.
This looks good.
Uh...
Wait.
Tools.
Transparent.
This should work.
Oh man.
This one's hard.
Yeah, this one's very hard.
I'll try hands.
And then...
I'll do this.
Wait, that's not transparent.
I'm going to experiment.
Here now.
Let's get the one over here.
Um...
Lower dungeon-y.
No, that doesn't work.
And then, like, blend it in.
Okay.
And then...
Oh, good.
I did the wrong one.
There you go.
Yeah, that's fine.
That's fine.
This is fine.
This works.
And then...
I figured it out.
I think this is my best drawing yet.
What about you?
No.
I...
I'm inclined to agree.
Okay.
They got this.
This definitely looks like Kirby.
You know what?
Kirby, why are you looking so fine?
I'm so proud of this.
Why are you looking so fine?
You know what?
I got...
Oh...
Kirby!
What's that?
Whoa!
Okay.
You know what?
You're right.
I'm gonna shade too.
I'm going to give you what you want.
I'm giving the people what they want.
But...
You know what?
I'm shading too.
For the people.
Gonna add some details too.
This is the most detailed drawing I've done so far.
Me too.
I agree.
Okay, okay.
I'm down to spend a little bit more time on it.
Me too, yeah.
Cause I just don't think I can rush this kind of art.
You're right.
You're so right.
Like...
I feel like...
I could sell this.
Oh yeah.
I gotta zoom in on that.
And then...
You know what?
I'm gonna do the background too.
Oh my god.
You're going hard.
Yeah.
I'm going hard.
I'm gonna go.
Oh.
Okay.
This is...
Alright.
Oh.
What's that, Kirby?
You want nail polish?
Are you giving him eyelashes?
I'll do what you want, Kirby.
Anything you want, baby girl.
Anything.
Are you...
Are you pimping out, Kirby?
No.
My eyes are watery.
Are you pimping out, Kirby?
Axe those poles, Kirby.
My eyes are just really watery.
I'm gonna...
Ow, it's burning.
Drink.
Don't worry.
Wash my face.
Okay.
He said...
He's just having a good time.
Hang out.
And then there's the sun.
I'm so sorry.
Oh yeah, I forgot.
I forgot.
I forgot to...
Make sure the feet's red.
Give me a sec.
Don't worry.
I got you guys.
I think it's God's way of telling me to stop.
I got it.
I won't...
Wait, but no.
It should be pink.
Yes.
I remember.
It's like pinkish too.
I am demoted.
Make it more pinkish.
Ooh.
That's actually better.
Cause it's like more...
To...
It fits to skin tone more.
There you go.
I'm ready.
A little bush.
Okay.
Are you ready?
Give me a sec.
Let me...
Let me snip this for you.
Two.
Okay, ready.
Okay.
Here we go.
Alright.
Three...
Oh, okay.
Oh, sorry.
Oh my god.
Okay.
She went literal.
Dude, where did you find those feet?
I googled...
Bare feet...
PNG.
Oh...
Oh my god.
Did you...
Thank you.
You gave her fishnets?
You gave...
Yeah, she was...
She wanted it.
Holy shit.
Alright, guys.
This is...
Have you ever seen that picture though?
The bare feet curvy?
Bare feet curvy...
Let me...
I think I did.
Hold on.
Oh yeah, I've seen this.
Yeah, yeah.
It is.
There's a plushie of this?
Are you serious?
Yes, I saw...
I saw someone have...
Like, put that plushie in at Artist Alley.
And I wanted to buy it so badly.
Oh my god.
Wait.
You're...
You're bare feet curvy?
Oh my god.
I wonder if I...
Okay.
I drew something very similar to this.
It's...
Okay.
I don't know if I...
Okay, let me see.
It's...
Okay, let me see if I can find it.
Guys, is it still on my Twitter?
Is it...
That's the question.
Is it still on my Twitter?
But...
I will look for...
Doki Bird...
Bare Feet.
No!
Wait a minute!
No, don't...
Don't look!
Don't look at that!
Doki, what is this?
No!
No, no, no!
No, stop!
Stop!
I didn't mean it like that!
I didn't mean it...
Okay.
This was...
I said stop!
You didn't stop!
That is your fault!
I said stop!
I'm so many more!
There's so many more!
Wait!
Are you on that?
Okay, this is...
Okay, can I...
Okay, I'm gonna say it.
I have an excuse.
Are you on...
You know that website where it's like live streamers...
Twitch live streamers...
Feet dick like...
Feet Thesaurus or whatever?
Where it's just...
Oh, you mean wiki feet?
Yeah, wiki feet?
Are you...
Are you asking if I'm on wiki?
I...
I don't wanna know.
If I am...
I think I am.
I don't wanna know.
You don't wanna...
I don't know.
I don't even have...
Okay, honest...
I don't think I have like...
Nice looking feet in particular.
Yeah.
So I always wear socks and stuff.
And like...
I don't know.
I think my big toe is a little too big.
Big toe!
A little too big!
God.
Okay.
Oh.
Wait.
Okay.
Okay, wait.
I need to find...
Okay.
I...
Apparently...
This particular artwork that I drew...
Is still on my Twitter account.
But...
I don't remember...
I can't...
Like...
I have...
I found the sketch of it.
But...
I think...
I found the sketch.
But I colored it...
Like I actually drew...
Colored it and finished it up a long time ago.
But I don't remember where it went.
I...
It's okay.
This was...
Five years ago.
Oh!
Oh my god, is that...
Is that...
Is...
What's the...
Two hanging...
It's the blobfish.
So...
I drew this...
Um...
Five years ago.
Let's see it.
When I used to draw.
When I...
What is that?
It could...
It could be anything, really.
It could be.
It's like Curbio with feet.
Wow, it's beautiful.
Thank you.
See, you can tell when I stopped drawing and what happened to me.
I love this.
This is beautiful.
This should be a sticker.
I love it.
No, I did sell it as a sticker.
That's the thing.
Oh my god.
Sell it again.
This is... I don't know where it is.
It's... Okay, maybe... Maybe I can find this.
Wait, okay.
Let me scroll down my Twitter.
I think I can find this.
I did not tweet a lot.
I'm pretty sure.
There's... Okay, I'm scrolling.
I'm scrolling.
I think I sold it as a... No, I did.
I did.
I remember selling it because I used to do Artist Alley stuff.
Oh, Artist Alley.
Yeah.
Oh, you did art... I remember you did Artist Alley too at TwitchCon.
I'm trying it out.
It's cute and fun.
You make little cute stuff.
Oh... Also, guys... I can't... I forgot that since Twitter became X, you can't scroll past a certain point.
Oh my god, you're right.
I forgot about it.
Wait, guys.
Surely somebody remembers the blobfish... The blobfish... Sexy blobfish art I drew.
And someone can, like, find that tweet and then at me.
It's my own tweet, but it's not just at me.
So it'll be back off my search history.
Oh, yeah.
I deleted my search history.
A little bad idea.
I told you to stop.
I don't know what I was thinking, man.
I just thought, you know.
I mean, I guess... Typing in Doki...
That was not the smartest...
I don't know what I was thinking.
No, I liked...
I liked old...
Old Doki's...
Brushes and...
Oh, man, I missed...
I missed this brush.
That was such a good brush.
That was my go-to brush for sketching.
I mean, I'm just...
Did you only draw in, uh, Paint Tool Sai?
Yeah, I only draw in Paint Tool Sai.
Mmm.
It was my...
It was my safe place.
I'm gonna steal my...
I'm gonna steal Old Doki's, like, color palette.
I'm gonna delete this.
Ha ha ha.
Delete Kirby.
It has to be undone.
Goodbye, Kirby!
Alright,
guys.
Suggest...
It's my turn.
Suggest me... Oh, wait, they found it.
That was... No, no, not the sketch, guys.
The finished one.
The finished version where it's fully colored and everything.
And he's pink.
And fully shaded.
Because I remembered it was fully colored.
Okay.
My turn.
Suggesting... Suggesting...
Uh... Give me... Give us... Give us a character.
Any character.
Oh, someone's... Oh, since you're playing a horse game.
We should do... Gold shit.
Gold... Oh, god.
Off the top of my head's gonna be hard.
Okay.
Yeah, me too.
Wait.
Guys, describe gold shit for us.
Actually, don't.
I don't even play the game.
I don't... I've seen it all over.
I've seen it all over.
Twitter.
Oh, gold shit.
Okay.
Gold shit.
Oh, I found... They found... They found it.
They found the colored version.
Okay.
Wait.
I need to show you this before.
They found it.
That's... Wow, that's cursed.
That's cursed.
You're gonna say that's cute or something?
No, that's just cursed.
You're like rubbing it up.
You're... Oh, wait.
I can put it on top of your head.
You don't get... Okay.
Wait.
I can pin this on you.
Okay.
You don't gotta do that.
You don't gotta... How is this worse?
Yes.
How is this worse?
Like no other said.
This is... If I stopped... If I didn't stop being in our... Like... If I didn't stop driving...
And became a VTuber... I... I basically... You know, I wasted my talents.
I... I can't believe... I can't believe... I stopped... You know, no.
I stopped at the right time.
This was my peak art.
This was actually peak right there.
I could never replicate this again.
Is that the best thing you've ever drawn?
Yeah.
This is honestly the best thing I've ever drawn.
Honestly, this is... I feel like... I feel like I could never do anything better than this.
You know, I'm retweeting this.
I'm... This artwork deserved more than 100 likes back then.
Um... I honestly... Honestly... I retweeted it.
Retweeted it.
I retweeted it.
Nine.
Five years ago, Doki would be so proud to see this artwork get attention it deserves.
All right.
Five... Five years ago, Doki would have been so proud of me.
Using my... Using my current fame to advertise my old art.
Okay, wait.
Oh, yeah.
It's pretty good.
I would... I would get a sticker of this.
It's... I liked it a lot.
I did.
I did make stickers out of this.
I would... I would resell this.
Okay, guys.
You should.
If I put this on my merch store, would you guys buy...
Of course they'd buy it.
A Doki Fruit original?
All right.
I'll tell Gamer... GamerSubs to put this as a sticker.
I... I'll tell... I'll tell GamerSubs to put this as a sticker.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Please.
When you do... Can you send me one?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I'll send... Will you... Wait.
Will you... Where will you stick it?
Oh, God.
I got... You gotta let me think about...
Would you stick it in the back of your phone?
No, I would put it in Michael's garage.
But somewhere where he'll come across it one day.
Oh, my God.
Yes, you should.
Didn't you do like a... What was... I saw a video like where you painted...
Babies?
The... The... Sorry.
No.
The... The... What?
No, no, no.
It's good.
No, no.
Can I explain?
What about the babies?
No.
I... I... I bought tiny little babies from Amazon.
And hit them everywhere.
Dude.
Oh, my God.
Contact.
Holy shit.
Okay.
The babies?
That was close.
I was gonna say like...
Like... You're... You're... The mural you did on this garage.
Oh, my God.
I was gonna talk about that.
Not... That is bad.
Not the big babies.
Yeah, no, no.
Big babies.
Yeah, I'll send... I'll send you like...
Like... Like...
Like... You know, like a fistful...
Of stickers so that he can put it everywhere.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And that's where I can put it.
Yeah, and then like... You know, like...
Where like Michael would like open a random drawer and then it'll just be there.
He's gonna hate it.
Maybe like... Like... Like...
Five years later, he's still trying... He's still finding you.
That's the dream.
That's the dream, baby.
Okay.
Wait.
What were... Oh, my gold ship.
I was the one that suggested it.
Um...
Wait.
Can you describe gold ship to me?
Okay.
Gold ship...
Wait.
Look it up.
Alright.
Finish drying your...
Wait.
She's a tall girl horse.
She has...
White silver hair.
Front bangs.
Ponytail.
Horse ears.
Okay.
She kicks a lot.
Um...
Okay.
And she's...
Wait.
What is her hairstyle?
Front bangs, I think.
And she has a high pony...
I think...
Oh, but like...
Front...
High...
Oh, so it's a ponytail.
Okay.
Yeah.
Wait.
No.
Is it a ponytail?
Wait.
It's not a ponytail.
It's like down.
She has a hat.
Oh, it's not...
Wait.
Hold on.
I'm gonna think...
Am I thinking of the wrong character, guys?
Chad, does she have a ponytail?
Please tell me.
I can't think right now.
Wait.
What does the hat look like?
The hat is like...
A tiny...
It's like...
What does...
What does the hat look like?
It's between her ears!
What does that mean?
Yeah!
No ponytail.
She does not have a ponytail.
Okay.
Um...
What else?
She has an earmuff things, I remember.
Oh, yeah.
She has ear muffs.
Okay.
So like...
That connects to the hat.
Which connects to the hat?
That goes in the middle of her ears.
Yeah.
And her ears just come out of her hair, kinda, you know?
And her hat is like a box or something.
I don't know.
I don't remember.
And then, like, what's the hair?
Like, if she doesn't have a ponytail, then what does she have?
I think it's just long hair.
Like, really long hair.
And it's, like, silvery, like, very pale pale silver lavender sort of thing.
Yeah, okay.
And what about, like, the body?
Well...
Yeah?
What does the body look like?
I don't remember.
Oh, she's building muscular?
So does she show her?
She is muscular, yeah.
So does she show her belly?
Um, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, give her a hat.
Okay.
Okay, what about the... Does she wear pants or... But she has huge assets?
Or does she... Um... Does she?
No, I would say it's pretty normal.
Is it flat or medium or huge?
I think it's medium.
It's pretty medium.
Okay, it's too late.
I think she has a red dress.
She's very fit.
Like, muscular and fit, though, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
It's a long dress or short dress?
Short, I think.
Oh, God.
It's crazy how little I remember.
Yeah, it's how you play the horse game all the time.
I never use gold ship, though, you know?
Wait, what do you use?
Um... Does she have a tail?
She does have a tail, yeah.
All the horse girls have tails.
Okay.
Okay, and then... Alright, I think... She's a little hard to use in the game because she does random shit and then it fucks your entire run.
Oh, yeah, because it's like... It's like based off of the real horse.
Yes, she's a troll.
Yeah, yeah.
So I don't really use her that much because it's so hard to use her.
Yeah, because... Don't worry, I got her silver hair, guys.
Don't worry.
I think I got her correctly.
I think this is accurate.
Make sure you got her tail.
She has... Wait, she has buff legs, right?
She's pretty fit, I would say, yeah.
Yeah, because she does a lot of kicking.
Okay.
She does.
She kicks a lot.
She dropkicks.
Okay, so I knew I fucked up somewhere.
I gave her sick legs.
Don't worry, guys.
I'm redeeming myself.
Okay.
There we go.
Actually, no.
I can redeem myself even more.
Okay, I think I'm pretty... That's pretty good.
Alright.
I did it.
Oh, I didn't even color.
I have not been coloring.
I did not color this.
Okay.
I'm ready whenever.
Uh, yeah.
You know what?
Let's just go for it.
Let's go for it.
Here, you're not gonna...
Yeah, mine is not that great.
Alright.
Ready?
Yeah.
Honestly...
Um...
Am I close?
Honestly?
Honestly, Koki?
Yeah?
Did I...
No, no.
No, I...
You see the vision?
It's a cool image.
Where are we?
I see the vision.
You see the vision?
Okay, let me...
Yeah, the neck is really long.
Why is it... I see it, guys.
I look at Google Goldship and I actually get the real horse.
I get the... Yeah, he's still doing it today.
He's still doing great.
Yeah, he's still alive, guys.
He is.
Thank God.
He's like... So many horse stories.
Yeah, he gets like $2,000 to like...
Have that horse.
Breed?
Yeah.
Oh.
Like, have that horse fuck your horse.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is it $2,000 or two... Is it $2,000 per...
Per... Per... But like, the thing is... Is it per session or like...
Just for the day?
Yeah, how does it work?
Is it like...
Per session?
I'm gonna ask... At Drock.
How does... 2 million yen.
Wait, how much is that in USD?
It's... Wait, that's more than $2,000?
Is it for a session?
A day?
Like, what's the...
The process?
What's the whole process?
How... How the horses... How the horses do it?
20K?
Oh, 180 session.
That's insane.
That's like...
That's like... That's like...
One and done?
Let's see.
Per session.
Oh my God.
Wait, Stucky.
20K?
30 to 35K?
30... Wait, he got a raise?
Like...
It's gotten a more expensive?
Oh!
I... I... It's cause like, he's getting older.
So it's like, tick tock.
You know?
They're like, get your...
Your mini... Mini ships before it's gone.
Pit, you're paying per breeding session.
The fee covers one mating attempt.
So what if you're like...
So what if he, like, misses?
What if he misses?
Yeah, what if he...
Yeah, what if...
Or something.
I don't know.
Like, what if he falls out?
How do you mean misses?
Like, does he...
Oh, I don't know.
Like, um...
He doesn't miss.
Oh, Bailey doesn't miss!
He...
He stays in!
He doesn't...
He has a...
He has a 95% accuracy!
Oh!
Okay, so...
You don't pay for another stat fee if the contract includes a live fold guarantee.
Oh!
Damn!
So like, if it...
Okay, but...
Yeah.
So like, if it didn't work...
Like, if it doesn't work...
They're like, the next one's free.
What?
But...
Goldchip is apparently...
Like, his breeding rate is super freaking high.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Everyone just gets pregnant.
Pregnant.
Pregnant?
Oh, wow!
What a fertile horse!
Yeah, it's 99% rate.
Oh, my God!
That's crazy!
Do I feel like...
Do they...
Okay, do they do like...
What is it called?
You know, like when people can't have kids?
They do like the...
Like the...
The outside thing, and then they implant the person with the egg.
What is that called?
The IVF thing?
Is that IVF?
Oh, you think when he gets older, they're just gonna store like...
His horse sperm?
They're gonna store...
Can they?
Because if they really like gold chip, right?
Can you just store horse sperm?
Yeah!
Can you store it at...
I mean, you can do it for humans, you should be able to do it for like horses, right?
Yeah, that's so true.
You gotta clean your Google history after this.
Yeah, it can be stored, yeah.
Involves freezing it in liquid nitrogen.
Bro, they're gonna milk him!
No, they're literally gonna milk him!
My search history spot.
Bro, they're gonna...
They have to keep him alive!
Gold ship alive!
Yeah!
This has gone too far!
We're just thinking, cause like...
We gotta keep his bloodline secure!
You want more gold...
Oh, yeah!
Yeah, do not want his...
Do...
Do you not want his bloodline insecure?
Procedures for handling fresh stallions!
That's great.
That's good.
I like that.
This bit has gone too far!
We need to move on.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Your chat...
It's your chat's turn.
Okay, okay, okay.
Next one.
Oh, God.
Stop saying we...
You're the people that want me to play horse game!
I'm just trying to understand the horse lore!
I'm in my...
Of course!
Okay, chat...
Alright, chat, give us...
Give us a suggestion.
You know what labooboos are?
Yes!
My 24-carat girls labooboo!
Let's do a labooboo.
Let's do a labooboo!
Labooboo!
Okay, I'll...
Labooboo, do you have a labooboo?
No!
I...
I used to!
Wait, what happened?
What did you do to it?
Okay, one story short, I was in an aquarium and a little girl saw my LeBooBoo and she said, Oh my God, I like your LeBooBoo.
And then my friend turned on her camera and said, Oh my God, Lily, you should give her your LeBooBoo.
She turned on your camera?
I'm just gonna vlog it.
I'm like, oh, and I'm like, okay, I guess I'll just give her my LeBooBoo.
Because she made it sound like, Lily, this is probably like her first LeBooBoo and she really wants it.
And I gave her my LeBooBoo.
And the girl was like, thanks.
And she looks at it.
And then she looks at me and she goes, this is my second one.
And then she fucking picks it and leaves.
She's like, I don't have one anymore.
Fucking cutie.
You got fleece.
She owes me a new one.
You got fucking fleece.
I bet you you're not even the first one.
I bet you it was some fucking LeBooBoo scam where like they recruit little girls to go up to random strangers, get their LeBooBoo's, and then like, and then scalp it.
Scalp it on the internet.
On the TikTok marketplace.
She didn't even look that like excited.
Oh, thanks.
It's like my second one or something.
I'm like, oh.
I can't say like, I can't say like, can I have it back?
You know, it's like rude, you know?
I'm not gonna do that.
I can't believe it.
Well, you got scammed.
Like, I...
You got scammed.
It was a pink one.
You know, like this.
Wait, was it the...
Okay, wait, do you remember which version?
Was it the sitting with you and the LeBooBoo?
Or is it...
It's the...
What was it?
Energy LeBooBooBoo?
Oh, it's the...
I don't know that one.
I just know that...
Mood?
I don't remember.
Oh, it's the newest one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They're all past...
I heard about it.
I've been having, like, so many, like, LeBooBoo-related videos on my YouTube.
And I was watching this video from this YouTuber that was, like, opening every mystery box from Popmart.
And I got so invested in, like, LeBooBoo, like, history.
Because they're like, it was so hard to grab this box of LeBooBoo's.
Like, I had to...
I had to refresh the marketplace, like, for three days straight to buy it.
I was like, holy fuck.
There's so many, like, TikTok lives.
Or they're just, like, unboxing, like, Popmart stuff.
Yeah, yeah.
I remember part...
I'm drawing a...
Yeah?
Oh, sorry.
No, no, no.
I'm drawing a...
Doki LeBooBoo.
Draw...
Oh, you know, I'll draw a...
Lily LeBooBoo.
LeBooBoo.
I love doing words.
I'll draw a Lily LeBooBoo then.
And then...
Dude, did you see that people give their LeBooBoo's, like, outfits and, like, hats and stuff?
Oh, my God, yes!
They, like, can buy, like, clothes for them and everything.
Yeah, and, like, glasses, accessories, and everything.
Okay, did you see the one where, like, you can buy, like, a LeBooBoo case?
What?
Where you can, like, imprison them in a little acrylic, like, jar?
Wait, wait, LeBooBoo case.
It's, like, okay, it's, like, crazy.
I saw...
Oh, my God, it looks like this.
It looks like they're, like, they, like, trapped it in a fucking prison.
That's shaped, like, LeBooBoo's.
Oh, no, I've seen that, I've seen that.
That's so sad.
I know, I was, like, that's so fucking sad.
Look at him.
Look at this chat.
Wait, this is what it looks like.
Like, he's got...
It's, like, that Star Wars thing with Han Solo.
It's just encased there forever.
Permanently.
Okay.
I miss my little boo-boo.
You never trust children.
No.
Never trust children.
Okay.
I need to color it.
I need to color it pink.
I'm gonna color it.
What?
Oh, you're, like, what color is she?
Or...
Yellow, orange.
You can literally look at the screen.
What do you mean?
What were you saying?
Maybe, maybe, I don't want to...
You know what?
I'm not calling you that anymore.
I'm taking the color.
What?
You're, like, you don't deserve it anymore.
You don't...
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna shade you, too.
Because I'm a good person.
Give me a little color.
Yeah, I'm gonna give you the clothes you're wearing right now.
All right.
I'm just making you pink.
Oh, wait.
I should give you...
Yeah, you know what?
I'll give you the clothes that you're wearing.
You know what?
I'll even shade...
I'm so nice.
I'll even shade you.
Wow, thank you so much.
Thank you.
All right.
You get to be shaded.
Wow, look at the opportunity.
What an honor, you know?
Okay, now I'll give you your ribbon.
Ah, ah.
Oops, sorry.
I hit my...
You okay?
Oops.
Okay, I'm good.
Okay, there you go.
I got...
The boo-boo is done.
What's your favorite number?
Why are you laughing?
That's so out of nowhere.
Um...
What is my favorite number?
69.
Okay.
That's my favorite number.
Why would there be numbers?
All right, I'm ready.
I'm ready.
All right.
Oh, you didn't link the loboop.
I could've just looked that way.
Whoop.
All right.
Double channeled over here.
A little gremlin letting me there.
I was like, I'm gonna kill you.
Don't give her too much alcohol, guys.
Do you have a loboopoo?
I actually don't have a loboopoo.
I never bought a loboopoo.
They're so cute, though.
I know they're just a trend thingy, but I like them.
They've been around for so long.
It's crazy that they just blew up this year.
I've seen them around for the longest time.
Wow.
Whoever made it is pretty happy right now, I bet.
Yeah.
I heard that the reason why it blew up was because it started in K-pop, actually.
Because a K-pop star held a loboopoo on her...
She had a loboopoo on her bag, and she was talking about it.
And then the K-pop fandom was like, I want to be just like her.
And then it spread.
Wait, that's why?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's how it spread into the Western audience.
Yeah, someone said it was Lisa from Blackpink had a loboopoo.
That makes sense.
And then...
That's why now we have loboopoos everywhere.
Oh my god.
Loboopoos are everywhere.
I'm the $69 loboopoo.
You cost $69.
Yeah, I cost $69.
Oh man, you heard like the counterfeit version of loboopoo?
Oh my god, I love loboopoos.
Wait, why do you love loboopoos?
They're so janky, man.
I want to get one for Michael.
I just think he would love...
You should...
You should get a customized loboopoo that looks like him.
Loboopoo.
You should get one that looks like him.
You can commission that.
I'm pretty sure you can commission it.
Why do you custom loboopoo?
Custom.
Or loboopoo for loboopoo.
Loboopoo.
That would be so cute.
There is!
There's one on Etsy.
Wait, that's so cute.
Wait, look at this.
Look at this.
That is actually so cute.
Oh my god.
That is horrible.
You should...
If you use your clout, they'll do it for you.
They'll accept your commission.
No, like...
He's like...
Hello, I'm...
I'm Lily Pichu.
Can I...
Give me a microwave.
Yeah, I need...
Please, I need it.
I need to commission you, please.
Okay.
She's accepting commissions!
Wait!
She's actually accepting commissions.
She says...
It's like, DM for inquiries.
Let's see...
It's time.
Oh my god, these are crazy.
Yeah, I know!
Hers are insane, though.
Wow.
Oh my god, they're so good.
They are good, though.
Yeah, they're all really pretty.
Okay, I'll show you guys which one I linked.
I mean...
I did give Michael a regular little boo-boo.
And I watched him as he...
You know, attached it to his bag.
Yeah.
And then I watched him again as...
When we went out.
I just think he's embarrassed.
And he put it back in his bag.
I'm like, you shithead.
You little f- Are you serious?
Wait.
Are you ashamed?
Are you embarrassed?
He'll put it on if it's like a custom painted one.
And you tell him how much it costs.
He's embarrassed.
He didn't want to be seen with that around.
Oh.
Oh my god.
No, if you make him...
If you get him a custom la-foo-foo.
Or la-boo-boo.
He'll have to put it on.
Yeah, if I customize it.
Yeah.
Put my whole heart and soul into it.
Yeah, and then be...
And then like, you'd be like, I did this for you.
But you don't tell him that you mean lies.
And like, you paid someone else to do it.
He'll assume you did it yourself.
But then like...
If you omit the information...
He'll have to put it on his bag.
I bet I can try to do it.
Like, I just get like tufts of like...
Fake brown hair.
Oh, that's true.
His hair?
It looks so bad.
It's like voodoo dolls.
You get a voodoo doll.
That'd be kind of funny though.
A voodoo...
You should do it on stream.
Make a Michael...
Yeah, make a Michael la-boo-boo.
That's a cute idea.
That is.
I might do that.
And then they get like a matching one.
And be like, we can match.
We can put it on...
So like, I'll put it on my bag.
Oh my god.
And then someone was like, la-boo-doo.
La-boo-doo?
That's so good.
Wait, that's so good.
Copy.
Wait.
Someone padded that.
I don't padded it.
Someone la-la-la voodoo.
Let's get out.
You can...
And you can use his actual hair.
Oh my god.
Okay.
I should get him when he's sleeping, huh?
But it needs to be like a place where he won't notice.
Yeah, you can, like... You can, like, he's sleeping and you cut a bit of his hair, and then, like, you can... It doesn't have to be, like, his entire... It could be, like, um... Like, you glue it.
Yeah, yeah, time it and glue it onto the... Oh, my God.
It would mean so much more because I'm using his actual hair.
That's so true.
Oh, my God.
That's so smart.
You should do it on stream.
Not the cutting his hair part, but...
I'm blaming you.
Am I the asshole?
I cut off a bit of my body.
Hair grows back.
It's not... Hair grows back.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Maybe, like, the back of his... Yeah, do his back of the head because he won't look... Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He won't look at it.
You should do the back of his head.
That is the best idea you've had all night.
I had so many ideas.
So many, but this tops all of them for some reason.
And then... And then... And then we had a voodoo doll.
And so if Michael... And so if Michael pisses you off...
Should I gather his fingernails, too, while I'm at it?
Yeah, you should.
You did not sound convinced.
You're like, yeah, you should.
All right.
We'll stop at the hair.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it's fine.
But all I'm saying is that if he ever pisses you off...
You know what to do with the la voodoo doll.
I beat the shit.
I'm joking, I'm joking.
You dropped the la voodoo doll from like...
From like a building.
And you'd be like...
No!
Don't piss me off.
I would take good care of it.
Didn't you like...
I was watching a stream before I started a stream.
When Michael came into your room, didn't you say you were gonna beat the shit out of him?
It's a...
No, it's because there's a meme that I beat him.
And like, obviously, don't beat him, right?
Right?
Sure.
Don't fucking wait.
No, I'm actually gonna beat him.
We don't believe it.
No, we don't.
We don't.
I swear we don't.
So, you know, sometimes I make you little jokes about it.
How many times you made this little joke, Lily?
I just think it a lot.
God damn it.
I don't beat Michael.
He's a good boy.
He's just in his garage.
Wait, is Michael here right now?
He's in his garage downstairs.
Should we ask him?
No, let me slizz on stream.
Please stop hitting me.
And I'm like, can you not?
It's so hard.
To go against these allegations.
I don't see what you think.
I need a lawyer.
My chat turned.
My chat suggests.
So much.
I was like, Michael, blink if you are in danger.
Okay.
Give us a character.
Give us a character, guys.
Oh, my God.
I'm not sober anymore.
I am.
So, what's it from Michael?
Because I don't remember what Michael looks like.
I would love to see a rendition of Michael.
You know how, like, Michael doesn't upload videos a lot?
Oh, my God.
I'll have you know, he uploaded a short recently.
I can't believe that.
I
don't know.
It's been so long for me.
Well, video five months, yes.
But, shorts was like, oh, my God.
What do you mean?
He has two shorts.
So, I don't even...
Wait.
Okay, so, Michael?
Okay, Mike.
Okay.
How...
When was the last time...
Wait, you never finished...
When was the last time he uploaded a short?
I think, like, a month ago, right?
Is that true?
At chat.
I'm trying to...
Where does it stay?
Three weeks ago.
Three weeks.
I haven't watched that short.
Wait.
I haven't watched that short yet.
Okay.
It's so true.
Oh, thank God.
When chat was like, draw him with a black...
I'm not gonna draw him with a black eye, guys.
No.
No, no.
I don't actually beat me.
I don't beat everything.
I don't beat Michael.
I don't beat my dogs.
She only does it in Minecraft, guys.
And that...
Only in Minecraft.
But that makes it okay, apparently.
That makes it...
No, Minecraft is better.
Because, like...
You can't leave your dog in Minecraft.
And, you know, log in again.
And they're probably still waiting for you.
That's so true.
So, Michael...
Michael...
You have, like, a Michael doll right there waiting for you every time you're angry.
I don't think he makes me angry.
As much as, uh...
As much as what?
Wait, what does Michael look like?
Can you describe him?
Okay, uh...
Okay, okay.
I'm gonna do my best.
Okay.
Guy.
Five three and a half.
Is that...
Half Filipino, half white.
Is that taller or...
Or...
Shorter.
Shorter than you.
Same height.
Oh, same height.
Wait, what's his nose?
Uh...
Okay, um...
Do you know Daniel Radcliffe?
Yeah.
In his Harry Potter form?
So, just give him brown hair.
What the heck?
I said nose!
Wait, what?
Filipino Harry Potter!
Just go for it.
Filipino Harry...
Filipino Harry Potter!
They probably could have been a bad thing.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Filipino...
Guys...
How do I draw Filipino Harry Potter?
Harry...
Is that like...
What makes...
What makes Harry Potter Filipino?
You're...
You're a Filipino Harry.
I'm a what?
Wait, what does he wear?
I don't...
Okay, so...
Wait, that makes his forehead...
He's smart.
He's like...
A coder.
So, like, his forehead is fine.
There you go.
And then...
Wait, okay.
What does his...
Yeah, I mean, he's a coder, right?
So he has to be, like, super smart.
He did that thing with the fish in the stock market.
And then he lost money.
But, like, that doesn't...
That's not the point.
He made that.
What does he wear?
Guys, what does he wear?
Does he just wear a t-shirt?
Okay.
Okay, what does...
Oh, does he wear flip-flops?
Does he get it?
Does he wear flip-flops?
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Yes, he does.
Okay.
He does.
What about long...
Shorts or pants?
Shorts.
Okay.
A yellow t-shirt and, like, brown shorts.
Does he have buff legs or skinny legs?
Um, they're skinnier than his arms.
His arms are super buff, though.
Oh, okay.
I messed that one up.
Don't worry.
I'll fix it.
No problem.
Okay.
It's okay.
He's just like Sans.
I'm just drawing Sans again.
And then make sure...
His eyes are, like, um...
They're pretty, like, boba balls.
I call them sometimes.
Boba balls?
They're round...
Okay.
Like, a bit of a crazed glint to it, almost.
I got this.
Mm-hmm.
Make sure to draw him really buff, though.
Wait, but you said he has skinny legs.
Oh, like, his arms, I mean.
Okay.
It's, like, buff as in, like, rip the shirt buff type arms that will rip the shirt off?
Alright.
That's enough information for me.
Okay.
Alright.
Okay, what color is the shirt?
Uh, yellow.
Yellow, yellow.
Okay.
Um...
And then he likes to ride motorcycles.
I remember that.
He does.
He loves motorcycles.
And yet, he used to have a goldfish.
He died already.
I don't remember what motorcycles look like, so I think this is...
I think it's almost...
Motorcycles have one wheel.
Two wheels, right?
Two wheels, yes.
Okay.
Like a bicycle, except not really.
Yeah, yeah.
There you go.
There's his motorcycle.
And then...
Uh...
Oh, and his goldfish.
His dead goldfish.
Yeah, then...
Rest in peace, Frederick.
Here we go.
I think...
I think I got it, right?
Yeah?
Wait.
Wait, did I spell Filipino right?
I hope I'm...
I'm really bad.
I'm really bad at spelling.
Wait, I forgot another L.
There you go.
Wait.
No, it's P. Two Ps.
Whoops.
Okay.
Filipino.
There we go.
It's okay.
I have one.
All right.
And then I'll color it.
That's the only thing I'll color.
Yeah.
This is my fault.
Okay.
Maybe we can look...
Wait.
People don't...
Oh my God.
My chat doesn't even know how to spell Filipino.
Like, they keep giving me wrong at me.
They're like, no.
Stop.
I'm like, I was just listening to chat.
So I did spell it right.
I spelled it right.
Okay.
You ready?
Give me a sec.
Let me...
Okay.
Let me snip this real quick before...
I'm just snipping it real quick.
I'm just trying to snip it.
All right, I'm ready.
Okay.
Hey.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
You're a Filipina, Harry.
I'm a what?
Oh my God.
You're so smart.
You put like his dead fish on his shirt.
Oh yeah.
That's a fish.
Yep.
Can I ask about your neck?
Oh, my neck?
Oh yeah.
They're just...
They're all so long, you know?
Yeah, because it's like...
It's to hold up the head better.
You know?
Makes sense.
You know how he's like...
He's like smart.
And everything.
So like he needs a proper support structure.
Massive brain.
Yeah, to support...
Yeah.
You know, support the five head.
Got it.
He said his hair is like Harry Potter.
It's Filipino.
No, no.
That was...
No, it's Filipino, Harry Potter.
That's all I got.
God, you said Filipino, Harry Potter.
You did great.
You did wonderful.
That's all I can remember.
Don't worry.
That's great.
All right.
Okay.
Your chat's turn.
All right.
Um.
I like how you gave him leg hair.
That's a good...
That's...
That's great attention to detail.
If you told me he had leg hair...
I think...
I would have done it too.
If I knew.
Ask Doki for a neck toggle.
Oh my God.
Wait, no.
I showed it to you, didn't I?
During the podcast?
Didn't I show it to you during the podcast?
A neck toggle?
Yeah.
This one.
Wait, is it this one?
Yeah.
Did I show...
I thought I did.
Did you show...
I don't remember it.
There's so many.
I don't remember you showing me this.
So many things happened within that hour.
Wow.
You...
You got such a long...
Oh, wow.
That's really good.
Really good neck.
Yeah.
You see, you know like artists draw from real life experiences?
All right.
Your chat's turn.
Oh, yes.
Chat.
Give me something.
To blow my nose.
Come on, chat.
Okay, let's see.
Sorry, there's some.
Okay.
I'm seeing like Garfield, Giraffe, Shrek.
Like...
Pick your heart's desire.
Should I open a second can?
Garfield.
Let's do Garfield.
Garfield?
Oh, man.
That's my Oshie right there.
That's my Oshie.
That's a great Oshie.
I am.
Okay, Garfield.
I...
He's orange.
Yeah, yeah.
You need help.
He's orange.
If you need help, don't worry.
I got you.
He has...
Eyes that are...
He's like...
His eyes are like...
It's like when his eyes looks like when...
You know, like...
The half-biddled eyes.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
Because he's like...
And then...
Oh, my gosh.
I'm not sober.
I can tell.
Oh, my...
I don't...
I don't know how to...
It's just a chill...
Okay, you know, I'm just gonna do my interpretation.
He's just a chill...
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
I can tell I'm not sober anymore.
And then...
He's just like...
I'm sorry, John.
Oh, I'm sorry, John.
I used to love that subreddit.
And he has like...
Is he still active?
Hmm?
Yeah, it's like a stomach because he's fat.
Sorry, he's big bone.
Okay, and then...
He likes lasagna.
Yeah, he does.
The lasagna.
Where's the lasagna, John?
Where is it?
Okay.
And he has like big paws.
Big paws?
Yeah.
Oh, God.
I don't remember.
Okay.
And...
Uh...
He has...
He has like...
He's like a little...
He's like a tablet.
Tabby with the black...
The black stuff on him.
He has like black stripes everywhere.
Okay, he is strange.
Because he's a tabby.
And then...
It's like a Pikachu, you know?
With the black stripes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Lots of black stripes.
Like a tiger.
Like...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No worries.
Does he have...
Does he have eyebrows?
I don't remember.
Does he?
Just gonna draw...
I don't remember he has eyebrows.
Guys, does he have eyebrows?
Fake fan.
Guys, the eyebrows is the last thing I remember.
Yes.
Oh yeah, he has bushy straw.
Oh my God, you're right.
I remember now.
It's like that.
And then he's like...
Fuck...
Odie...
Where's the lasagna, John?
Where's the lasagna?
Okay.
And then...
It's like...
Oopsies.
Big belly.
Alright, I think...
This Garfield looks big.
He looks so tired, he is.
You know what?
You're right.
My Garfield looks so tired, too.
Okay, Garfield is like, what?
30 already?
No, he's like 40, right?
Look, he's middle age.
He's middle age right now.
He's a middle age man.
He's been through a lot.
He has a 9 to 5.
You're right.
He does.
Let me give him a suitcase.
He's off to work.
He's got...
It looks like it's Monday's.
He's on status.
It's Monday's for Garfield right now.
There you go.
He's ready to go to his 9 to 5.
Alright.
I'm done.
What about you?
Oh, I'm...
Yeah, I'm done.
I'm done.
Alright.
Okay.
Well, you went completely different.
Yours just looked like a regular cat.
What made it?
I'm gonna look up Garfield.
I just...
I just ruined his eyes.
Oh...
Oh my God.
Wow, I could not have gotten that.
Oh my god, you guys lied to me about the eyebrows!
This is Garfield?
Okay, I was... it was very close.
He's so shapely.
I told you, he's, like, fat.
I mean, like, all he does is eat lasagna.
That's true.
That's all he does.
Oh, I got the big feet, right?
See, I remember feet.
The eyeball.
I remember feet.
Oh, I'm hungry.
I want lasagna.
Oh, you should... oh, I did not eat while I was, like, before I drank.
Oh, that looks so good.
Yeah, you should order lasagna.
Do it.
I might actually order lasagna.
What's stopping you?
You're, like, the devil on my shoulder.
Cut it from the back of his head.
He'll never notice.
He might.
Why would he notice?
No one looks at the back of his head.
What if you run your hair through...
Like, wouldn't you notice, like, a top of hair missing if you run your hand through your hair?
But does he do that?
Yeah, exactly.
You're Scott.
And I'm pretty sure there's no way he's gonna be looking through your vids.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't... I think he's super busy right now.
Yeah, there's no way.
Yeah.
You're, like, in the clear.
I mean...
Are you sure I should...
It would be such a...
It would be such a good stream idea.
Think about it.
Oh, I guess when you put it that way...
Yeah.
It could be really funny content, huh?
Exactly.
Yeah, yeah.
Just, like, do it as, like...
And then, like, give it to him on his birthday.
On your birthday, too.
Oh, yeah, my god.
You should give him...
Yeah, give him a voodoo doll first.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
There you go, honey.
There you go.
I made you a little...
Don't piss me off.
I have a second one.
I have to cut out so much hair.
I can make another one if you piss me off.
Oh, Garrett, what's a loopy doll?
Oh, god.
Oh, my god, that's so nice.
Yeah?
No, you know the loopy doll, right?
What's a loopy doll?
Oh, my god.
The fucking...
Girls who look like this have permission to ruin my life thing.
Here, I'm gonna place it on there.
Wait, what?
Oh, this one.
The one that looks like you.
Shut up.
Oh, my god.
You should...
It's tagged.
I get tagged every time.
You should...
You make the little voodoo doll.
The voodoo doll.
You should put it next to the...
That doll.
Yeah, the loopy doll.
The loopy doll.
Oh, my god.
It would be so...
And then you can have a little...
You can do like a little photo shoot with them.
Actually, that's such a cute idea.
Oh, god.
Oh, my god.
And this one, they...
I didn't notice.
They gave her eyelashes, too.
Wait.
That's crazy.
Wait, I drew a sexy bee?
When did I...
When did I do that?
Holy shit.
I think...
Wait, look at this.
Like...
An art...
I was like...
I was looking at my Twitter notification.
And...
One of like...
The art...
A Korean artist I follow...
Um...
Like...
Liked...
One of my old artwork.
And I was like...
How did she find...
How did she find this?
Wait.
This is what it looks like.
Oh.
She's extra sick.
Whoa.
What happened to me?
I used to...
This is really good.
Yeah.
I was like...
Wait.
I can draw...
Oh, my...
I drew this?
Wait.
What happened to me?
It's really sexy.
Yeah.
What happened to me?
You start practice again.
I do not remember me being able to draw stuff like that.
Yeah.
I...
I drew this, guys.
I'm gonna make this for you.
Look at...
My...
My sexy bee.
My thick, sexy bee.
Next to my Garfield.
Doki, what happened?
No, it's because we're doing it so fast right now, you know?
That's so true.
I think if you take your time, you can actually like...
You can draw something really, really good.
Why don't we...
Okay.
What about for our last one?
Yeah.
Like, we just spend more time on it.
Okay.
Yeah.
That's a good art piece.
That's a good idea.
Alright.
We'll have...
Okay.
We'll have the...
Okay, yeah.
Yeah.
Who do we pick it from?
Your chat or my chat?
Why don't we do each other?
We'll draw each other?
Okay.
Wait, but it's not for memory because I literally see you.
Yeah.
Oh.
Yeah, yeah.
It's just an art thing.
Okay.
Alright, I can do this.
Wait, what outfit though?
Should we swap out?
No, hold on.
Should we do a swap out?
Let me think, let me think.
Wait.
What do we do?
Design you a new outfit.
You can design me a new outfit?
I can't do that.
I'm too drunk for that.
I'm like...
I'm like pleasantly tipsy.
You know, I'm not like drunk drunk.
I'm good.
I'm at a good...
I'm trying to remember what was my old art style.
I think it was this?
I think so.
Oh my god.
I haven't drawn in so long.
I don't even remember what my old art style was like.
How did I draw her out?
I'm gonna change the resolution of this.
Just in case.
And then...
Okay.
Tomato?
Mm-mm.
Crow?
Mm.
And then...
I'm just looking at your model.
I'm gonna cheat.
I'm looking at yours too, Jesse.
I'm looking...
Big eye.
Oh no.
Oh my god.
I missed my sketch brush.
I want my brushes back.
You're just using the default...
Side brushes too.
Okay.
I'm just gonna draw a GV.
Probably...
Oh, you're doing chibi?
Yeah.
I don't remember how to draw real pictures.
I don't remember how to draw like...
Not...
Sorry.
Chibi is also real, guys.
Chibi's...
Chibi's real.
I meant...
I don't remember how to draw like...
In a non-chibi format.
Wait.
Is yours a dress?
I'm just gonna...
It's gonna be a dress.
It's a dress.
Okay.
I didn't...
I didn't pay for full buy.
I just did bust up.
Cause I wanted to save money.
I mean, that's smart though.
That's so smart.
So I don't have a...
I don't have a body, okay?
Yeah.
We cut our legs off.
It was so much cheaper though.
Oh my god.
No, it is.
But like people don't see like...
They don't see it anyways.
Yeah.
It's so true.
They don't see it.
Hmm.
Let's see what kind of hair...
Wait.
Okay.
I'm gonna...
You know what?
Wait.
I remember...
What?
Nothing, nothing, nothing.
Wait.
What did you do?
Did you look up...
Ooh.
I'm gonna try and...
Find my old art style.
Maybe I can like...
Copy myself.
I'll trace myself.
It's not tracing if it's from myself.
Five years ago.
Oh my god.
You still got it.
How did I draw like this before?
What the fuck?
You probably had so much more practice and stuff.
Oh my god.
I used to actually...
Be an artist.
Wow.
Hey, look at this.
I drew this.
Oh my god.
This is so cute, Doki.
This was...
This was not just six years ago, Doki.
You could sell this at a convention and I would try it.
I did too!
Yeah, it looks like a cute pin art.
Yeah, I sold this as a sticker.
Look at it.
You can still...
I know you can still draw.
You just got...
You're rusty, but if you keep drawing...
That's really good.
You don't just forget things like that.
Yeah, it's like riding a bicycle.
This was...
It really is!
Six years ago, Doki.
Right there.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna trace myself.
That's a princess.
Okay.
And then...
Alright.
Am I doing it?
I'm doing it, guys.
I think I'm doing it.
I don't know how to draw...
Oh, I gotta look up references or something.
Um...
I don't remember how I did the eyes and stuff.
I don't know.
Looking for like...
Oh, I remember.
I would cheat.
I just draw one eye and then I like copy and paste it and then did perspective.
And then I did the...
Work smarter, not harder.
These are kinda cool.
And then...
Oh, these are too hard.
Oh.
I did this, guys.
This was my cheat method.
Cause I don't remember how to draw...
I don't know how to draw the other eye.
I do this.
And then...
I did this.
Okay.
And I'd be like, I did it.
I drew.
That's right.
Oh my god.
I did that.
Yeah, Princess Doki.
Princess Doki?
Princess Doki.
Whoa!
I'm gonna draw you like a...
I'm gonna...
I'm trying to draw the face now.
Oh my gosh, mate.
God, I hate drawing arms.
I'm just gonna draw it by the side.
That's fine.
You know what, that's...
That's...
We're not looking for perfection here.
Just draw this.
Eat your lasagna.
Lasagna.
Okay.
Alright.
And then...
Whoa.
How do I do hair?
That?
That's how I do hair?
And then...
I remember my style was I like to do this.
With my line art, because I thought it was cute.
Oh my god.
I hate your hair.
This is like silent.
I feel like...
I don't know how do I do this.
I didn't know how I did.
You got it!
Your old art is so good, man.
It would happen to me.
You just stopped drawing.
I don't know what happened to me.
That's all that happened.
You just gotta draw again.
No!
It's so hard though.
Drawing is so hard.
But it's so fun.
I'm washed.
I'm washed in gaming and...
Oh my god.
That's it.
I'm fucking fixing my...
Rusty Doki.
It's okay.
There's my flip.
I was like, where the fuck is my...
Oh my god.
You know when you flip an artwork?
You flip your artwork and you're like, this does not look okay.
Dude, I do it all the time.
I flip it so much.
And people are always like...
If they don't draw or something, it's confusing.
Because I'm like, why do they keep...
Why do you always keep flipping?
I'm like, it helps so much.
It's...
So useful.
It's so useful.
It's so very useful.
Mhm.
Okay.
Life is not daijoubu right now.
It's not daijoubu.
It's gonna be daijoubu.
Like...
I don't feel daijoubu right now.
Believe in yourself.
I don't.
You're crazy, man.
I don't know what to tell you anyway.
What do I do when I don't believe myself, Lily?
What do I do?
Who's gonna believe?
I don't believe.
You'll believe in me?
Yeah.
That's a dumb thing to do.
I'm expecting great things.
Fucked up.
What color is...
What am I saying?
It's just gonna be pink anyway.
I don't know.
You suck.
Yeah.
Are you okay, man?
Not okay.
She's not okay.
Alright.
She hates pink.
What's your favorite color?
Yellow.
That's why I'm blonde.
Of course, I should've... I should've guessed that one, sorry.
Okay, um, I sort of gave up at the bottom part.
Wait, why is it brown?
I actually used brown liner, when did that happen?
What is homage?
I know I'm cheating for this.
Alright, I learned this a long time ago.
Like, if you can't draw circles, just...
Get a brush.
Make a long-ass circular blot.
And then get a smaller brush and then...
Eraser?
Yeah, or eraser.
I did it too.
Yeah, I learned that on Tumblr.
You should draw on an iPad.
I feel like you like it a lot.
I tried to.
Really?
It is weird, I feel.
I feel weird drawing on an iPad.
It's a sense.
I think it's a sensitivity.
This feels weird to me.
Tablet.
I think it's because I draw...
I used to draw on a tablet for so long.
That like, it was just hard to...
What tablet this is?
Um...
A Wacom?
Yeah.
Yeah, Wacom Wacom.
Wacom Wacom.
Wacom.
And...
Oh yeah, I would make layers for like, everything I...
Not everything, but like...
For a lot of like...
Um...
For...
Like, each line art, I guess.
Mhm.
Like, or each body part.
So if I fuck up, I don't have to erase everything.
That's pretty smart.
Just very tedious.
Yeah, it's more so...
Because it's like, you know, if I fuck up or something, I can just change it on that piece in general.
I don't have to worry about...
Redraw it.
Like, I don't have to worry about like, affecting other pieces of the artwork.
I'm lazy.
How so?
Oh, layer management stuff?
Oh, me too.
Don't worry.
And then I just merge everything together after.
Yeah, I do that too.
But I keep the original just in case.
Like, duplicate the file maybe.
Cool.
Yeah, that's smart.
Mhm.
Did I do that?
I don't remember.
I don't...
I don't remember if I did that.
How's your hair?
Oh, it's like this.
Is that how hair works?
I can't remember.
What is that?
Is this...
Is this how hair works again, guys?
I like your...
Commentary difference for a lot.
Oh no.
Alright.
And then...
And then I'm gonna cheat and like, your other hand is like, behind your back.
Cause I can't be bothered.
I will do that all the time.
Yeah.
I don't wanna draw two hands, bro.
Sometimes I don't even wanna draw one.
So both hands are behind the back.
And it gives like, this cute mirror.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, it's fine.
It's fine.
Actually, I lied.
I didn't put your hands behind your back.
Okay, nevermind.
Okay.
What layer is this?
It's this layer.
And then...
I'm gonna cheat and grab this hand.
Copy and paste.
Move it here.
And then move it here.
That's so funny.
Yeah.
And it's like...
It's like I drew two different hands.
But I didn't.
Okay, not Princess Doki no more.
Princess Kroki now.
Princess Kroki?
What did you do?
There you go.
Yeah.
It should have like this thing.
And I really feel like it should have like...
Yeah.
Like a hint.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, baby.
Uh...
Yeah.
Oh my god.
It's literally just your hair.
You're stupid.
What?
I mean, your beautiful hair.
Yeah.
Princess Kroki.
I need to sketch this out before I have to do this.
I'm gonna give her pink eyes.
Or like...
Red eyes.
Seems like a darker version, you know?
So...
Or like red eyes?
It's not evil.
Just...
Just what?
Mischievous.
Just...
She's the type of girl who'll just tell to your face.
Exactly.
Like what I tell you.
To cut the hair of someone.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
To make a Buddha doll off them.
To order lasagna, even though you're on a diet.
You know, stuff like that.
Little stuff like that.
Do you order lasagna?
No, my phone's too...
My phone's been being used for VTube studio, so I can't...
I can't.
Just pause it for a little bit.
No, I gotta...
What?
I gotta finish this first.
But you want lasagna, though?
I don't deserve dinner until I finish this, alright?
Oh, that's so true, though.
Yeah, reward yourself.
Mm-hmm.
For a good job done.
Exactly.
Like, what did I do?
Nothing.
Exactly.
Did you draw, like, Michael?
Is that not a reward enough?
No.
But Prince is croaky?
Hell yeah.
Oh, true, true.
And then...
There's something wrong with your head, but I can't be bothered.
In your life or the trying?
The trying, right?
Sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't worry, I can fix this in post.
Okay.
Oh, I know what to do.
There you go.
It's cramping.
So much coloring.
So much art.
Princess Croaky hails from the Croaky Kingdom.
She's taking over several neighboring nations.
Ooh.
I like how you're, like, making a whole story behind it.
No, there's a story here for sure.
Yeah.
And now I cannot do this.
People have tried to catch her.
But she just turns into a crow and flies away anyway, so there's no point.
Yeah, there's no point.
Just die.
No point.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Accept your fate.
Oh, I have a good idea.
I think I'm gonna give her a little bit of makeup here.
Makeup?
Whoa!
You're gonna give me eyeshadow?
I'm evil, you will.
You are evil.
No, you're not evil.
It's like mischievous, you know?
Oh, true, true, true.
I always like a bit of pink eyeshadow around it.
I just...
Yeah.
I think I'm gonna change the part too.
I mean, it's super messy, but it's okay.
There are no mistakes.
In art.
Only happy little accidents.
Exactly.
For a little...
Yeah, I'm gonna do too.
Actually, no.
Okay, my hands are too cramped.
Okay, I'm just gonna give her a little...
Yeah, like a little...
Crosshatch for no reason.
Because sometimes it just makes it look cool, you know?
Yeah.
It hides the little mistakes.
Like, it distracts everybody.
Yeah, I'm gonna cheat for this one.
I think I've heard that.
I think I've heard you say this.
I think I'm gonna cheat for this.
Yeah, I'm gonna cheat for this.
I hate her hair.
It'll make it look better, I swear to God.
Look, art is all about finding all these neat cool tricks that you can do to make things easier for yourself.
That is so true.
Shortcuts everywhere.
Yeah.
Literally, that's like how I...
How I survived.
How I survived in art.
And...
The croaky jewel.
Oh.
Alright.
Don't worry.
I can...
I've realized I forgot the most important part.
You're...
The flower.
I'll color that in later.
How's your...
Oh.
Right.
Don't worry, I'll just color that later, guys.
It's five.
Alright.
Yay.
You done?
No.
I'm just coloring your hair right now.
Yay.
Ehhh.
Hmm.
Are you done?
I'm just doing, like, details until you finish.
Okay.
But can I wait a second?
Sweet.
Cause I am definitely not done.
Do not worry.
Hmm.
Alright.
Let's do this.
Oh.
Like, the song that's playing right now.
What?
I have, like, a little playlist of, like, BGMs.
That's copyright free.
Oh.
I like the tune that's playing at the moment.
Your song?
Yeah.
It's on my stream.
Oh.
Speaking of...
What?
Oh, nothing.
Oh, yeah.
Original song, guys.
How's it going?
Don't wash anything.
Don't worry.
I'm practicing it.
Okay, okay, okay.
Just so you know.
Don't forget about it.
TJ and I will die.
Yeah, yeah.
Guys, guys, for those who don't know, who haven't watched the podcast yet.
Uh...
Lily and I have an original song that's in the works, right now.
Well, they're just waiting on me, but...
Just waiting on me, but it's in the works, guys.
It's in the works, guys.
It's beautiful.
I think she'll sound really pretty.
As soon as she records it, it's gonna be awesome.
Don't worry.
It will happen.
Yeah.
Don't worry.
Believe in them.
And me too, because it's all up to me.
To be fair, it's all up to me.
So, believe in me, actually.
I think that's better.
Believe in me to make sure we record it.
I believe.
I believe too.
Someone has to.
And then...
How did I do this?
What?
Okay, I'm gonna steal old Doki's skin color.
Alright.
Don't mind the feet, guys.
I just copy and pasting.
Alright.
I'm stealing old Doki's color palette.
Wait, was it that?
Was it actually?
I've been...
I've had it once.
Oh, maybe it's...
This area.
Something lighter.
I need something here.
Yours is gonna be, like, super detailed, and then you'll see me...
No, no, no, no, no!
I can tell, though, that... it's been so long.
You know, like, for me, when it's so long, my hands are not as stable as before.
When it comes to... You just gotta de-rust, you know?
Yeah.
But definitely I can tell my hands are not stable when it...
...comes to line art and stuff.
Cause I...
I was... I had, like, super...
...super smooth line art back then.
Oh my god.
It was only five years, man!
You can do it!
Oh, that's a long time!
Five years on the internet is a very long time.
A lot can change in five years.
No.
I don't know.
Thank you, Pastoki, for letting me steal my own color palette.
I really appreciate it.
Super pretty, though.
Okay.
I am...
...done, I think.
Are you done?
Oh, shit.
Yeah, but you can take your time.
Don't worry about it.
Okay, cool.
Cause I just have your...
...flower and your dress left.
And then I'm not gonna...
...try on the other parts.
Actually, I'm not even gonna try on your dress.
Let me...
Don't worry about it, man.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you're done...
If you're done, it's time...
...to speed run it.
Oh, I'm just... I'm just chillin'.
Do not worry.
I'm gonna order lasagna after.
Oh my god.
A good stream, you know?
A good stream?
A good stream with some good ideas.
You do drive a hard bargain, yeah.
Exactly.
Should I get breadsticks too?
You should.
Oh my god, mozzarella breadsticks.
Oh god, okay.
But just to like, even it out, should I get like a Caesar salad or something?
Okay, but like, I don't know if it's gonna be good Caesar salad, no, that's the thing.
It might not be really good Caesar salad, so I don't know.
Yeah.
But I agree on the breadsticks, though.
I think breadsticks is a very good idea.
Good job, Doki.
I like bread when it's like, slightly chewy.
I don't know how to board it.
Oh, that's so true.
There it is.
Alright.
Wait, what's the bottom half look like?
It really is, like... I never really fully...
Like, what color is it?
Finished it?
Yeah.
So...
I don't got a body.
Like, my bad.
Are you wearing...
Okay, I'm gonna give it black pants, then.
I'm like, what color is the bottom, though?
That's fine.
Alright.
And then...
I've definitely sobered up, though, while we're doing this.
I think I'm sobered up, too.
I'm not just hungry.
I definitely feel...
I feel very sober.
Well, not very sober, but, like, I'm definitely...
I can't believe an hour ago we were talking about horse...
Horses, and...
Dude, I remember...
I had so much conversation about...
Horses team.
We got IPM horses.
We...
I can't believe...
I can't...
That's not what happens.
That was a long...
The conversation was too long.
Oh, my God.
And I Google image your feet.
You did.
Bad.
That's bad.
And then we talked about wiki feet.
Not that your feet are bad, but just...
How was it?
How was the feet?
It was...
Delectable.
Is that the word?
Is that...
Is that the word you want to stick with?
Uh...
Succulent?
I don't know.
Excuse me?
Nice.
Are you sure you're sober?
I'm...
You got good grippers.
I have a feeling you are maybe not that sober as you think you are.
I am.
I'm very sober.
I...
I do appreciate feet though, you know?
Like...
Wait, really?
Like, Jury's feet.
Have you seen Jury's feet?
Wait, what?
Who's Jury?
Jury from Street Fighter.
Oh, Jury!
I was like...
Jury!
Oh...
Yeah, I know what...
I know who you're talking about.
Yeah.
So you understand.
I don't, but like I know who you're talking about.
I know who you're talking about.
I thought we were on the same page, my bad.
No, we were definitely...
As a person who is...
Who does not...
Who does not enjoy feet...
I...
I think you lie.
Sure.
Sure, sure.
But like, you know...
I do not kink shame.
Yeah?
Are you okay?
Are you...
Every time I sniff, I put my V2 model behind you?
Not the feet?
You can like pull my...
My skin suit up a little bit and...
Oh!
You have feet?
Damn!
Are you doing that now?
She has a whole fucking...
She has a whole freaking outfit.
Wow, that guy...
I can't even show myself.
Look, I like end right there.
Yeah.
I float.
Whoa.
How do I do glasses?
Don't...
You're not wearing glasses anymore.
And then...
You don't figure out like this.
I'll give you tiny glasses.
Okay.
You're not wearing glasses anymore.
I can't be bothered.
Alright, I'm done.
Alright.
Ready, ready, ready, ready.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm done.
Yeah.
You're not wearing glasses, though.
I'm not wearing glasses?
Yeah, unfortunately.
Do not worry.
I think I have a thing with glasses.
There we go.
Actually, no.
I can do something for it.
Glasses, PNG.
Don't worry.
I can't... That's where I draw the line.
That's where I get... That's where I've given up.
Okay, circle, circle, glass.
Circle glasses.
Wait, I'm almost done.
I just need to do circle glasses.
Transparent.
Oh, there you go.
Oh, this is nice.
Those are cute.
Ready to show?
Um, let me give you glasses first.
Let me give you glasses.
And then I'll be ready to show.
Okay, wait.
I need to pull it up in my files.
Pull up in my file.
I love this collaboration thing.
It makes me want to do more VTuber collabs.
It's so freaking cute.
Oh, my God.
It's so, like, convenient, too, right?
I can go to your right.
I can go to your left.
That's so cool.
I believe... Oh, but you haven't done a lot of VTuber collabs, right?
Mm-mm, mm-mm, mm-mm.
Oh, yeah, so it's, like, museum.
This is really cool, though.
I love it.
Why can't I save this as a .jpeg?
Oh, there you go.
.jpeg.
I had to save it as a .jpeg.
Can I make myself huge?
Oh, my God.
That's creaky.
All right.
Oh, it wasn't transparent.
That's fine.
Let's do this.
Oh.
Big.
I'm like a titan.
What are you doing?
So cool.
Oh, my God.
Never mind.
Why didn't they give me a PNG?
Sorry, I'm, like, suffering here because I'm trying to find the perfect...
I'm trying to find the perfect PNG glasses for you.
Oh, okay.
Oh, I found a good one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wait.
Oh, I have to pay for this?
Don't pay for it.
Just draw the circle, man.
No, no!
You can do it.
I know you can do it.
I can't.
I'm not.
Just draw the circle.
I'm not strong enough.
You can do it.
No.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
I'm not.
I can't.
It's just two circles.
Yeah, it's just too much.
It's too much work.
Is it?
Really not?
Yes, you don't understand.
It doesn't have to be perfect.
It does, though.
No, it doesn't.
Yes, it does.
If it's not perfect.
Okay, I found it.
Web P to PNG.
I just need to convert it.
And then, and then, every...
No, you don't understand.
I swear to God.
It would be like...
It would be so worth it.
I swear to God.
I believe you.
It's not like the croaky thing where it wasn't worth the wait.
But like...
Yeah, that was funny.
Good times.
Yeah, yeah.
Exactly.
Princess croaky.
Okay.
Save.
Did it save?
It did.
Yippee.
Okay, guys.
We got glasses.
All right.
We actually got glasses now.
It's Ray-Bans.
Oh my God.
That's even better.
You gave me Ray-Bans?
Yeah, I gave you Ray-Bans.
Thank you.
Thank you, Toki.
Okay, maybe I should have just drawn circles.
But like...
But it's too late.
It's too late.
It still works.
I took off my glasses, though.
So I didn't know if you...
Okay, I'm gonna put them back on.
It's like...
It's not that noticeable.
But like...
You have glasses.
Okay.
Oopsie.
Oh my God.
Oopsie, oopsie.
Okay.
I'll show you that you're not glasses one.
And then you're glasses one.
All right.
This is you with glasses.
This is you without glasses.
Did you send anything?
No.
Did you send me a pencil?
Okay.
Now I sent it.
Oh my God.
This is so cute, Toki.
You like your Ray-Bans?
I love them.
Hold on.
I'm gonna show my chat.
Oh, I'll show you the glasses I gave you.
So cute.
How cute.
Look at your Ray-Bans.
It's like a little me character.
I love it.
Guys, I'll show you the Ray-Bans chat.
Don't worry.
It's so cute.
I gave her these glasses.
I look by a little figurine of this.
So cute.
All right.
Your turn.
Thank you.
I think I accidentally flipped it.
There you go.
I'll get rid of it.
I'll give Ray-Bans to the real Lily, too.
Oh, how do I flip it?
How do I flip it?
Oh!
Wait, what happened?
I'm just learning how to flip.
Because I flipped it.
So it was like flipped already.
You know?
Oh!
Yeah, I messed up.
So I have to flip it again.
Oh!
Wait, that's so cute, too!
Princess Kroki.
You know, when you're talking about like burning stuff.
I thought you were actually like drawing like a burning building and stuff behind me.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
But I can imagine it.
I can imagine her burning buildings.
You would.
You would burn down the neighboring nations.
And they would ask her to keep the tree or something.
Yeah, I would commit more crimes.
And you would burn down the tree.
Oh, no, no.
Fuck trees.
No, I actually hate trees.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Then you'd burn down everything.
Look at that.
Princess Kroki.
Guys, I don't actually...
Okay, I don't actually hate trees.
But I hate tree-adjacent characters.
Oh, so I said treaties?
Treaties?
Yeah.
Wait, did you mean treaties or trees?
Wait, you...
I don't understand anymore.
She hates trees?
We'll never know.
It's so cute.
That's really cute.
I love this.
I love your suit.
Yeah.
Alright, it's like...
I was thinking about Animal Crossing and Mii's.
Yeah, it reminds me of it.
The glasses give it like a secretary look.
Oh, that's true.
You're like Isabelle.
Princess Kroki.
Yeah, Princess Kroki.
Do we proceed?
No, I'm the secretary.
You're the princess Kroki.
Yeah.
And I'm like...
And I ask you like...
Are you sure you want to burn down our neighboring countries?
And I'll be like...
Why are you asking me?
I'm so sorry.
Why are you hesitating?
I'm sorry.
You still feel for them?
Do you not care about our nation?
I do.
You're right.
Of course.
Please don't hurt my dogs.
Please don't beat up Michael.
Like Michael is in the dungeon.
And like bring him out of the dungeon.
And I was like...
Do you have a voodoo doll?
Lily here tells me that she is hesitant about burning the neighboring countries.
Yeah, I'll be like...
Stop.
I'll be like...
You want to hesitate again, Lily?
No, I am so sorry.
I will go ahead and press the button.
That's right.
Or you'll have to beat up Michael.
Then I'll have to stage a coup.
You're going to stage a coup?
Oh, it's called?
Yeah, a coup.
Yeah, yeah.
To like an uprising.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like viva...
I want to do it.
Like viva la fra...
Viva la vida.
What?
Wait.
That's a cold place.
God damn it.
Stay in school case.
Don't you?
Viva la vida.
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
Isn't that song from Shrek?
Viva la vida.
Wait, viva la vida?
No, viva la vida loca.
Oh, we are not...
Wait, we're not thinking the same song.
We are not...
Wait, Coldplay?
No, I wasn't saying Coldplay was Viva...
I was saying...
I thought I was like...
Coldplay?
Is that song from Shrek?
Viva la vida loca.
I hear Jerusalem bells.
I can't believe it.
Fuck this shit.
Well...
Wait, is that Coldplay too?
Viva la loca?
Viva la...
No, that's...
That's another...
That's...
That's Ricky Martin.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
That's the...
Oh.
Yeah, my song is from Ricky Martin.
Not Cold...
I don't even know who the fuck Ricky Martin is.
I'm just at...
I was like, that's Ricky Martin.
Who's Ricky Martin?
I just know he's...
I just know the song is from Shrek.
I thought we were talking about Viva la vida from Coldplay.
I was talking about...
I thought we were...
You know that viral clip of the Coldplay concert?
Oh yeah, the one where they held each other and stuff.
That was so funny.
That blew up everywhere.
Oh my god.
You know...
People are like meeting it.
Yeah, you know they just didn't do anything.
Nobody would have like, clipped the video at all.
Put myself...
Yeah, it was Streisand Effect.
That's...
Yeah, the Streisand Effect.
That was crazy.
Yeah, and then like...
Yeah, the crazy part is, it was like, from the HR lady.
Yeah.
Yeah, it was like, when your HR lady is...
Is like, having an inter-office relationship.
Like, the head of HR.
Affair in front of all those people.
Like, it's just...
That's true.
Wow.
Yeah.
And then...
Yeah, and the fact that like, you know, they both had affairs too.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
And he was like...
Yeah, he's the CEO.
And she was...
She was head CEO...
Head HR and head CEO too.
I heard they both resigned though.
Wait, she still kept the position?
Wait, the HR lady is still the HR lady?
The CEO resigned though, didn't he?
Yeah, the CEO resigned.
But like, the fact that the HR lady, like, is still the HR lady?
After committing the worst HR...
Not the worst, obviously.
But like, one of like, the top offenses in HR.
She resigned today.
Oh!
Okay.
Good for her.
Good for the...
Good for the company.
I'm gonna...
Bring me lasagna?
And eat food and stuff.
Yeah, me too.
But I had a great time, Lily.
That was really fun.
Yeah, that was such a fun collab.
We talked a lot about random.
My favorite conversation is...
You convincing me to chop off hair off of Michael and make a voodoo doll.
That was my favorite conversation, too!
I love that voodoo!
And don't drink and...
If I make the doll, I'll let you know.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh my god, you have to let me know.
I want to watch that stream when you do it.
I need to watch that stream.
I love voodoo.
Love voodoo.
Making my voodoo doll.
I can... I can see it.
You okay?
You feeling saliva gets stuck in your throat?
Oh, yeah, I hate that.
Yeah.
Oh...
Yeah, hack it all out like a cat.
I have to mute my mic.
I was like...
Are you okay?
I'm gonna be a topic right now.
Well, it was fun hanging out today, Lily.
I had a great time.
Yeah, thanks for...
I'm dying.
Don't die.
If you die, you can't make your love voodoo.
It was nice talking to you.
Yeah!
It was great talking to you too, Lily.
I'm fine.
I hope you die.
I hope you don't die.
I hope you die?
What?
I hope you...
No, I said I hope you don't die.
I...
It's like...
Collabs over.
I hope you die now.
Good night.
Good night, Lily.
Thanks for joining me.
Oh my god, that was so fun.
I had a...
I had a fun time hanging out with Lily today.
That was definitely a great collab idea.
Uh, I had with her.
Uh, I'd love to do more of these, I feel like.
Like...
Um, I was like thinking about it.
It's like, oh, if I...
What if I make this like a series where I drink with someone and we just draw random stuff together.
Um, and everything.
I felt like I was such...
That would be such a cute idea.
But I don't know.
I have so many things.
I already have so many things to do.
Uh...
But...
I definitely had a great time with Lily.
Talking to her.
While drinking.
Um...
And...
It was definitely, like, fun.
Just like...
You know, just trying to draw random things out of memory.
And like giving each other...
Describing what things look like.
And we're all trying to draw it from memory.
He he he he he he he he he.
He he he he he.
Um...
I hope you guys had a lot of fun too watching us.
Oh my gosh.
Whoa, fuck.
I definitely sobered up though.
When I was trying to do this artwork.
I...
I definitely sobered up.
But...
Um...
But I definitely enjoyed all the conversations I had.
Even the really cursed ones.
There were some...
There were some fun conversations.
But...
Like I said.
I hope you guys had a lot of fun too.
For this collab.
Um...
Please check out the podcast that I did with Lily.
That was posted on the Sweet and Sour channel.
On YouTube.
And...
Uh...
Yeah.
I'm really looking forward to releasing a song with her.
Uh...
Well...
She wrote...
Like...
Well, she's not singing it.
I'm singing it.
But you know, she wrote the entire song with her producer.
Uh...
So I'm really looking forward to actually getting that done.
Um...
Either this month.
Not...
Not like the music video done then.
But like...
Me recording the song done.
Either this month or next month.
So...
I'm really looking forward to that.
Anyway guys!
I'm gonna call it here.
Now...
But I hope you guys had a fun time watching.
As always everybody.
Stay hydrated.
Posture check.
Get up and move around.
To get that blood flowing.
And if you...
So for me...
Head to bed.
Cause...
You deserve it.
I'll see you guys next time everybody.
Bye guys!
Bye!
Also it was nice to dry again.
It's been a very long time.
Since I've lost the art.
Uh...
But yeah.
Bye bye guys!
Bye!