I can't do it anymore.
I can't listen to this song anymore.
I can't do it.
I can't listen to this anymore.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't.
I can't do this anymore.
Please.
Oh my god.
It's just been beep, beep, beep.
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
I can't do it anymore.
Okay, have you guys enjoyed the title screen and up?
Yay!
Oh, good evening, asaiyama-e-go-sijin-sama, ojo-sama.
Hello, everybody.
Oh, quiet.
Peace and quiet.
Oh.
I had to turn this.
sound down so low genuine tip for feeling sick rub a little
rubbing alcohol around your nostrils also face bump your cat
guaranteed treatment for any illness no I don't know I I I
ate and then I was like I like I don't know it's just like
my head started hurting weird but speaking of my cat um
yesterday i took him to the vet and he got poked and he got
he got prodded and he like do you guys like the new e-boats
or so you guys are just spamming it i'm glad that you guys
like it
um so good i'm glad you guys like it i'm glad yes yes yes
um here may please consider playing strong bad's cool game
for attractive people this summer you fit the demographic
crap fully um let me tell the story about my cat and then
we'll talk more about strong bad but um uh uh i took him to
the vet yesterday and i got him a bunch of tests done um not
really a bunch just like an overall well it was like a big
test for senior cats because i um last time i mentioned him
i was like i smelled his little head and it smelled sweet
and i was scared because cats smelling sweet is sometimes a
sign of of diabetes I was like oh no and I took him and they
were like wow he's down two pounds which they were a little
concerned about um but uh I I have him on a diet because
last time the time before I took him they were like he needs
to lose weight so you know he's down a little bit um it's
scary when pets lose
like the doctor checked him yesterday and was just like i
don't know i don't see anything wrong with it i don't or
rather i don't hear anything i don't notice anything so
we'll send the tests in and we'll give you we'll give you
the results tomorrow i also had to reach into his litter box
and take some poop so i've had a pretty shitty day uh no i'm
just kidding um you get it that's what happens when you when
you when you have a pet but literally yeah literally but
when i went and got um his lab results the doctor there she
was like oh my gosh your cat is like first of all every time
i take him to the vet the vet like the the vet and like the
technicians and everyone everyone is like, he is so good.
He's like the best cat I've ever worked with.
Like he just stands there and lets you do anything.
Like he doesn't, he doesn't fight.
Like he is so good.
He doesn't bite.
He doesn't scratch.
He doesn't, he's so sweet.
And I was like, yeah, I know everybody tells me that.
He is my good boy.
But he's pregnant.
Close.
Oh my gosh, so close.
Um, uh, today the doctor was we were ooing and eyeing at
your cat's results he is like the pinnacle of healthy for a
cat his age he is so healthy like every there was like no
nothing with diabetes not even a worry like he is my vet
called my cat an unholy terror yeah so they were like His
heart is good, his kidneys are good, his everything is good.
We just have to look at his poop and make sure there's
nothing wrong there.
But he passed.
Yeah!
He is healthy!
Yippee!
So I felt so much relief after that.
Especially because she was so enthusiastic about it.
She was like, he is so healthy.
And I was like, well, he's a bit of a butthole, but that's
okay.
Did he pass gas?
You know, he's been, like, farting a lot recently.
It's, you know, he's just, you know, ghost cats are a little
gassier than others, I suppose.
But, um...
Can we get a Butaro...
A Butaro emo.
I'll think about making one, maybe.
maybe but yeah anyway sorry that's just a side I know it's
like I'm talking in absolute silence right now I just
couldn't keep them gaming that opening music on any longer
um hope you feel better man thank you based on the title
though and which of these should I watch next outlaws to the
ends of the earth super dark times the mimic oh I think the
mimic sounds interesting or to the ends of the earth the but
i like the mimic um so you're awesome thank you your cat won
at cat here is cat money for the cat is victor thank you you
know yoko your your your donos makes so much more sense than
they used to dear midman how do you type with your sleeves
over your hands your super chatter, Charo 666.
Well, Charo, this is how I type.
And then I punch the screen.
Super awesome punching.
That's my impression of Strongbun.
Delete it.
Strongbun.
And Drigos, thanks for the deck gifted.
And KM, thank you so much for the ping.
Oh, wait, you asked to your strong mid.
How do you type with those big dorking sleeves over your
hands?
Stingfully yours.
Ben Dover, deleted.
A teen girl squad.
Cheerleader.
Sew itself.
What's her face?
They ugly.
How do I make a voice that sounds like strong bad trying to
talk like a teenage girl?
No.
So as a kid, I watched so much Homestar Runner.
Oh my goodness.
I watched way so much Homestar Runner.
And I played this game quite a bit.
I don't remember at all how to beat it.
But I would like to try and get, like, I think with 150
points, I would like to try and get every little drop out of
this game.
that we can get.
Thank you for the memberships.
Thank you.
Kanky, thank you.
Glad to hear he's all right.
I wanted to let you know that Streamer Life Simulator is
free on Fanatical right now in case you needed any more
games.
Streamer Life Simulator?
I mean, I'm afterlife.
Like, I'm dead, so if I do a life sim...
It is...
I mean, so...
If I...
Um...
Oh, I don't get it.
Come on.
Wait, I...
Wait.
That's another reference, isn't it?
I...
remember.
But I don't remember at the same time.
Your impression of Strong Bad doing a teen girl voice is so
good.
so good and he keep it up so well dear strongman i love you
i think i once wrote into the strong bad emails i think i
once did um but it never got chosen i'm so sad i wonder if
he still accepts them can i write oh my gosh thank you for
that pink and neither king thank you for the pink strong bad
has the cheat strong maid has the chat
gonna lie to you.
I'm a super chat from the 60s.
But here's a few things I remember from Strong Bad Emails.
I remember the one when he makes an anime about himself.
He gives him the awesome blue hair.
I remember the the system is down.
The system is down.
Stinko Man!
Oh my gosh.
Legitimate business.
Yes, he has the rave that when he makes the song.
Dear Strongbent, what would you look like as a Japanese
cartoon?
And what would it be about?
Well, if I was a Japanese cartoon, I would be super
booby-licious with a bubble bite.
And I remember the song about the cheat.
The cheat.
the gene strong what's strong arm strong no stop please
metal gear and home star runner how can one ghost be so
cultured stop tunes games email why is this so ingrained in
my brain oh my gosh downloads why is it so ingrained into my
brain oh no mint you've always made my day better life
without you was ghastly but now that you're back i feel like
i'm in mint condition love you ah thanks limousine or sloshy
i
don't remember the original brain rot oh my gosh it was so
much fun i i would have like front like um actually i think
i i tried to get my friends in a homestar runner but i got
into homestar runner from when I was a kid.
And so he and I would like do the emails and like try to
find all the little hidden clickies in it.
So that was a lot of fun.
I heard my name.
Well, if it is, it's Saucy Maidman.
Oh my gosh, it's an actual Armstrong.
Hello, Senator.
Oh, shoot.
I just realized something.
But it should be okay.
until after stream.
I am constantly quoting Strong Bad anytime I see a
protagonist with blue hair.
But yeah, so Homestar Runner was a huge part of my ghostly
childhood.
And so was Peasant's Quest.
So we're gonna play it.
Here's how things work around here.
Tips for not morons, beginners.
Look around by typing stuff like look tree or just plain
look.
Talk to folks by typing stuff like man take items by typing
get item use items by typing use item you can also give item
throw item or some other action words type in to see your
inventory type save to save your game and load to load one
what you can save and load games to save games your browser
must have cookies enabled press plus and minus to speed up
or slow down your character okay wait no Wait, hold on.
Hold on, can I turn off the music?
No!
No, I'm not even reading it!
Hold on!
No, I can't do this anymore, please!
No!
No, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
No, no!
I can't do this anymore!
Please, maybe it...
Hold on.
I will.
You could start playing it in a second.
Here.
Maybe it doesn't play the whole game, right?
Go for it.
Oh!
Yes!
Okay, I'm going to restart that.
I'm going to restart that so we can...
I'll read it to you guys.
I never felt so young until now.
Oh!
Tongue looks like a thong?
Oh my god, now that you say that, it really does kind of
look like a thong.
No, I didn't want it to be that.
I didn't want it to be that sexy.
Okay, here we go.
okay okay okay all right let me read now this hey didn't
thank you so much for the 10 gifts thank you you are rather
dashing oh thank you a humble peasant living in the peasant
kingdom of peasantry you return home from a vacation on
scalding lake only to find that shrug door the burninator
has burninated your thatched cottage roof cottage along with
all your goods and services is that what i said with nothing
less left to lose.
You swear to get revenge on the wingling dragon in the name
of Burnin... You head east towards the mountain atop which
Tronkdor lives.
That's a nice looking lake.
You can start playing in a second here.
Oh, my thatched roof cottages.
Thatched roof cottages!
Hello, sir.
Oh, talk.
You explain your situation to the knight.
The Trogdor burn it in your cottage, and you've sworn
revenge.
You ask for passage to the mountain to settle your score.
Hang on there, Trogdorkilla, says the knight.
I can only allow actual peasants up the mountain past to
face Trogdor, and you clearly are not one.
Look, Dragonheart.
Fine, thanks for the tiny captain, thank you.
You don't stink like a peasant.
You don't dress like a peasant.
Actually, I feel like I do dress like a peasant.
And you are definitely not on fire like a peasant.
Once there are those three things, come back and maybe we
can talk.
Be sure to look around lots, talk to everyone you see, and
ask about stuff.
Type help if you get confused in inventory to see your
worldly stuff.
Load your game, duh.
If I just walk, I don't stop.
Look at me, I'm so dashing.
Do I need to put on some BGM for this game?
Actually, I don't know why I thought there might be BGM, but
here I go.
I'm walking here.
I can't stop walking.
Actually, is there...
Oh, there is a way to stop.
I'm going in.
I'm going down.
Man!
Look.
Why, it's half a lake with a fisherman in it.
fishing yell oh talk you holler at the old man about trogdor
but he just grumbles about the fish not biting must be the
wrong I must be using the wrong bait he says oh sorry must
be using the wrong bait he says suggestively can I fish fish
swim damn How do you say that suggestively?
Okay, I'm going to put on a little bit of BGM real quick.
Because it's kind of quiet.
Unless you guys don't have...
It's basically a podcast at this point.
Or I can sing the song again.
Oh, the press and minus.
Thank you.
Oh.
Oh, we're so fast.
Nice.
Um.
Where's my music?
Oh, here we go.
What do you guys want to listen to?
Let's listen to some chill music.
This doesn't really fit the vibe, but just pretend it's like
after school and you're on your like Windows 98.
Actually, I don't know when this game came out.
I don't know if it's older or newer.
And you're playing, and it's old.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, yeah, we're speedy now.
Wait, is this my house?
Eat.
Take, take berries.
You probably wish you could get that.
Oh, dang.
Okay.
What's here?
Knock?
It's open.
Oh, sorry.
It's open, says a female voice from inside.
Um, it's not open.
But you get her drift.
You open her up and head on in.
Oh, she's got a baby.
Talk.
Hello, I'm, you start, but the lady cuts you off.
Okay, here's why I let you in here, she explains.
My husband got squished by Trogdoor.
And to make matters worse, insurance riches I got were just
stolen by the Janka.
Go steal them back for us and I'll give you something great.
ViviCorps thinks you're the gifted.
I never thought I'd see you play Baldur's Gate 3.
Yeah, I think we're gonna go see Asterion.
Take.
No, talk.
Oh, okay.
It's a say.
Take.
Grab.
Look.
What a depletion.
pressing little cottage.
It reeks of single parent.
I mean, oh my gosh.
They said he is rather dashing, but they never said he is
rather classy.
Dang.
Oh my gosh.
A lady rocks her baby in a chair.
A mostly empty shelf sits against one wall.
Mm-hmm.
Rather savage.
For real.
um what's this can i sleep that's probably how the first
baby got here forget it what do you mean by that i i mean oh
yeah oh
my gosh um take what can i say again um look to oh where
where Where am I?
Where?
You're hanging out in the in baby lady cottage.
Can I take baby?
Take baby.
You want to be part of this family?
Go get us those riches!
She shrieks.
Dang.
What is this though?
Take, take feed?
Oh, you used to eat this stuff like crazy when you were a
kid and your parents weren't watching.
Which was all too often.
You grabbed several large handfuls.
Oh, we got a point, we got a point!
we have a chicken feed all right nice wait can I take okay
take pillow you don't have anywhere to use it and it is
rather bulky so you leave it
okay the baby lady calls after you why don't you calling her
the baby lady instead of like mom the mom calls after you
know the baby lady well actually we don't know if she's the
mom we have no idea hey you're on some quest right well the
little squirt here lost something of mine in the yard the
other day it's yours if you can find it oh okay let's look
in the bush then check bush uh look bush you suspect they
might be crunch berry bushes take berry okay uh look bush
look bush uh search bush oh oh you reach into the bush to
snag you some berries but they all just squish in your hand
okay here we go search search i really like the last podcast
episode and did that personality quiz and i ended up with
the same result as you great minds think alike right search
bush Oh, nothing in this bush, but squished berries either.
Let's check this one.
You guys are so smart at saying search, yes.
Search bush.
Too bad you don't want any squished berries.
Because, hey, jackpot.
Maybe I shouldn't be so aggressive.
Like, search bush.
You reach into the bush to snag you some berries, but
instead find a super trinket.
Get ye flask.
these things are awesome you have a sneaking suspicion that
someone in this game will need this thing we're at three
points already feed oh oh you cannot get e flask you can't
get e flask but you can't get e flask what do you guys mean
you can't get e flask what what Oh, what's our shirt look
like?
I bet it's like a boy band or something.
Oh, it's so cute!
This has got to be your favorite t-shirt ever.
Oh, the times you had at Scalding Lake.
Canoeing, fishing, stoning heathens.
What a blast!
What is this thing?
This super trinket is weird.
It looks like it could either kill you or make you the hit
of your Christmas party.
whoa gold nuggets oh wait this is just chicken feed crap
this game is so dumb this game is so
silly sorry
what what was that
what in the world was that getting ye flask?
I could not get ye flask.
I tried and I tried and I tried and you want to know what
happened?
That's right.
I became ghost.
What is the flask?
Oh, sorry if you can see my mouse.
Okay, we'll go this way instead.
Brushing river.
Black and white.
Yellow tree.
Huh?
What?
Brushing river.
for the river okay for the river dang i miss oregon trail
backed with between everyone's giving me everyone's giving
me different answers p in the river p in river doesn't
understand your strange request wait if i go over is it
gonna be that guy again oh look there's a really generic
well here oh and apparently it's autumn on this screen well
well well i gotta go for now men but i hope you have a
wonderful day and a wonderful stream take care thank you so
much thank you use you I don't need to use that now.
Crank that soldier boy.
Dang.
Okay.
Don't go that way either.
Wait.
Wasn't it up though?
What if I look at?
Oh.
Hold on.
Look.
It's the Carrick, you moron.
Get out of here.
Peep-pe-pe-pe-pe-peep.
Um.
This is a really creepy screen.
Why does it look like this?
Crank that hog.
Um, look.
Nothing special.
Ah!
Nothing special here except for that weird wavy tree!
Who is that?
Look!
Man!
Talk!
You startle him and he disappears!
Oh, God!
Oh my gosh!
What a suspicious...
What a suspicious man!
I remember this part!
I remember this because look!
Move rock!
That!
I remember that.
You slide the stone over to reveal a little hole.
If only you could cut off your arms, legs, and head, you
might be able to squeeze through.
Yippee!
I remember that one.
much of anything else though knock you can knock until your
knuckles bleed nobody's home i'm a ghost i can fit through
you know who could fit through the baby oh talk your
attempts at conversation are met with horse grunts and tail
flaps which is better than you do then it's just which is
better than Can you do a conversation with most people?
Pet horse.
Oh, that's sweet.
Poor Gary tries in vain to bite your arm off.
Thank you for the dog.
That's a horse?
What is this?
Oh, wait.
Look.
There's a rotten old horse.
It's a horse.
He doesn't look so good, though.
Take Gary.
Oh my goodness.
You probably wish you could.
Eat flies.
Oh, there's the flies.
Hmm.
How hungry.
He looks pretty.
You're hanging out in poor Gary's Glen.
Why is he?
Why does someone take care of Gary so he's not so poor
anymore?
Please don't get kicked.
Oh, what's in here?
Search head.
Sorry, sometimes my fingers work in really mysterious ways,
you guys.
Sometimes my fingers work in really, really mysterious ways,
and I don't know why.
That's after stream.
Dang it.
You'll probably see me making crazy mistakes all the time,
this whole stream.
Did you find the rainbow?
Did you find anything?
Just some edible glitter.
It's your sleeves.
Exactly.
Also the G and the H are right next to each other.
Okay.
You search and search through the haystack.
Nope.
No needles.
Someone had a good idea.
Take hay.
What do you think you are?
Some kind of thigh dungeon man?
You don't need any hay.
Okay.
What about for the horse?
Can I climb this tree?
Climb tree.
But then all your hands will get all sappy.
Hmm.
oh what's this read note it says sacred oh scared of carrick
go away jay okay where am i where you're hanging out in junk
oh this is where janka is we need to talk to him knock a
gravely voice inside yells just us chickens Oh, okay, we're
back here.
Love the podcast on Thursday.
Love to hear more about your music taste.
My music...
Oh, maybe we could do a music episode.
That'd be fun.
Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh.
Um...
Look.
You have chicken feed.
Wait, what do you mean the chicken feed?
For us chickens?
there's a dried out mud puddle it's all cake it's all caked
up and cracked like the kind like the kind that rock stars
are always standing on what i don't i don't get it okay here
um what do i do with this chicken feed um throw chicken feed
um use chicken feed You don't need to use that now.
Hmm.
My house!
The remains of your thatched roof cottage lie burdenated
before you.
You swear revenge against Trogdor.
You're hanging out in your burdenated cottage.
Mint, if this is how you wanted to come out to us, this is
really complicated.
I'll put it in it.
Stop!
One of my manga shelves broke down yesterday, and a lot of
the manga on that one had black covers, so the damage is
really noticeable.
Pain!
No!
Oh my gosh, I'm so scared of that day.
That, like, my shelf just decides to break.
I hope never.
I have so many dojin.
Oh, can I take the berries here?
Take berries.
No!
man geez why not there's definitely half a lake here with a
sandy shore there's some rocks here though take rocks you
grab a handful of fairly substantial pebbles you make sure
to get an even mix of sedentary igneous and um surreptitious
rocks yeah wait oh I know what to do with the chicken feed I
just the guy fishing the guy fishing said that nothing was
biting if we throw the chicken feed here right throw chicken
feed you toss the feed into the lake you shed a tear for
each one goodbye Monty
goodbye Delga Rasputin farewell combo done that's so forth
ho ho Whoa!
That crotchety old man just caught a pant load of fish.
Now I can get back to running the inn, he says, and rose to
shore and hauls his boat out and cleans guts and flays all
the fish and a bunch of other stuff we didn't animate.
Yippee!
Oh my gosh, we're making awesome time.
Oh, the inn was right here the whole time.
There's a giant inn here.
Takes up, like, the entire screen.
Just open it, man.
Open.
Open the door and step inside the inn.
Oh, he's back.
I'm going in here, too, then.
Open.
Look.
What a dump.
Only one bed and no mini-bar.
The innkeeper stands behind a desk, and there's a door
that's closed.
Open door.
That's the pantry, says the innkeeper.
Employees only.
It's wild how much Skyrim ripped off this game.
I...
Right!
Like...
Like, this game is so innovative.
To every game following it has just taken everything from
it.
Peasants' quest walks so Baldur's Gate 3 could run.
Could we get a job here?
I don't know.
Sleep?
You probably ought to talk to that stinky old guy over there
about that.
Okay.
Hello, sir.
I would like to inquire about a job.
If you're interested in staying the night, just type get a
room.
Get a room.
I only serve peasants here, fancy pants.
Bark's the old guy.
Where's your robe?
Why are they so mean to me?
Oh.
What is this?
A single...
A signal lantern of some kind hangs from a severely
bernanated tree.
Where am I?
I'm at the burninated trees.
Okay.
Um, this is nice.
There's a beautiful magical waterfall cascading down the
cliffside.
I'm gonna swim.
That waterfall would probably turn you into one of those
weight gain protein smoothies.
So sad.
Burninated?
Oh yeah.
That's what Tragdor does.
He burninates the countryside.
He burninates all the people.
He's burninating all the thatch roof cottages.
Okay, so I need to figure out a way to kill this guy.
Oh, not here.
Where is he?
What?
Is he a down one?
Oh!
Hello!
Oh, hi.
I'm Mendelev, says the archer.
a shooting range here with my brother Dongolev but we don't
talk so much anymore I haven't seen him in a dronka's age if
you ever run into him tell him I said Haldoh you mean hello
you ask um no shut up I said Haldoh and I met Haldoh tell
him I said Haldoh dang can I play play game the gallery's
not open and you got no bow or arrows Cupid Holdo,
everybody.
And I said what I said.
Not much to see.
River's got a rock in it.
Take rock.
For what?
Now you're just making up puzzles to solve.
Sorry.
Wait, if I go back here, then I go up.
Okay, we're here.
This map makes no sense.
Holdo, everybody.
Does this lead to Janka?
No, it leads to mud.
Then this leads to Janka.
No, it leads to hay.
Can you swim here?
I don't know.
I still use Holdo to say hello to my friends.
So crazy.
This game is too influential.
Wait, how do I get him out?
Wait!
Maybe the super trinket.
Or...
Can I throw the pebbles at...
Maybe the...
Maybe I can stone that guy to death.
Whatever his name is.
Ow!
Talk to Janka?
Okay.
Rock and stone.
I thought I tried to talk to him.
Did I not?
Talk.
Talk to...
How do I spell his name?
So glad to see my favorite ghost playing such a great game!
Thanks Black Knight!
Thank you for the pink!
Thank you!
Wait, how do I... Talk to... How do I spell his name?
Oh, there we go.
It's sad when you have to make up people to talk to!
Man.
Person in my chat yelling in all caps.
Talk to talk!
You're wrong!
Is this it?
Okay, um...
Okay, hold on.
Throw pebbles.
Stone him.
Death him.
Kill.
Will I die here if I, uh...
Oh, where am I?
Oh, there I am.
I will die?
Slash kill.
Hmm.
I think the guy he'll want this.
Okay, is there anywhere...
Map?
Is there a map?
We are neither confirming nor denying the presence of a map
in this game, but...
Irregardless.
You don't have one.
Save?
Okay.
Oh.
Oh, it does auto-save, you guys.
I think we're okay.
But I'll save anyway.
Okay, go away.
Thank you.
What have...
This one?
Use.
What else can I type here?
Earward disregardless.
Doctor, welcome to membership.
Thank you.
Turn crank.
It won't budge.
Maybe if there was something heavy in that bucket.
Take bucket.
You can't.
It's tied to a rope and you're terrible with nuts.
Jump in?
Dang.
Can you imagine?
Like there's this area here.
Great game choice.
Love home star runner stuff.
Do you think Strong Bad is a V-Tuber?
I think so.
He just used email instead of chat.
Wasn't there a strong bad VTuber that was made, though?
Like, actually?
Or am I going crazy?
What's above the inn?
Ah, wait, what's up here, then?
Ah.
Now we're on the other side.
Oh.
The world is so small and confusing.
Burger buns, welcome to membership, and Leanne, welcome to
membership thing.
Thank you.
Hmm.
Try make friends or buy Karak a cold one.
I don't think I even have a place where can I even buy a
cold one.
The inn is useless.
Okay, I need a robe.
We need to, I think, okay, we need to figure out how we're
going to kill this guy.
The Karak.
But we also need to talk to his brother.
Okay.
Did you just prove this world is round and small?
So very small.
Call me Galileo.
Magnifico.
Mento, toe, toe, toe, toe, toe, toe.
Mama mia, mama mia.
Did you try to seduce him?
Seduce him.
Uh, kiss, kiss archer.
Um.
Can I take this?
Take arrow.
They have range printed on them, so it would be kind of
embarrassing to have to shoot around with them.
Also, that guy over there is giving you the evil eye.
Okay.
Exodized, welcome to membership.
Thank you.
See, I think the bucket is used for this, right?
bucket full of water and maybe that's what we need to do but
it won't it won't move or it won't yeah we can't get it out
um use the pebbles oh in the bucket i think you're a genius
where is it what
here oh oh i'm trapped okay game is very specific oh here we
go here we go here we go use pebbles i'm not supposed to use
them for death for stoning i'm supposed to use them for for
life what do you propose to do with them discuss oh put
pebbles in bucket you plunk all your pebbles into the bucket
the weight causes it to descend to the bottom of the well
with a quickness crank level level level uh get to bucket um
raise bucket oh here we go what is that the crank seems to
have loosened and you will haul the bucket back up What's
this?
Why is there a monster mascus in there?
No doubt left over from some pagan ritual.
Silly pagans.
You grab up the scary monster mascus.
Man, this thing could scare a horse!
Wear mask.
Not on this screen.
You've got to image...
Wait, you've got your... You've got your image to think
about.
Oh, actually, you might want to start deliberating on that
right now.
to the horse to old Gary stinky Gary Gary's gonna be really
sad about this though I think sorry I can't read you guys
okay it's very hard with ghost eyes okay I died with poor
vision okay where mask.
You slip on the hideous monster mask.
Oh wait!
I wanted to see the description of it first.
Oh!
You scared the crap out of poor Gary!
He broke on through to the other side.
Oh my god, it's terrifying.
Man, those pagans sure can make a freaky looking mask when
they want to.
It's like those theater masks.
Uncle, evil uncle or something.
Yeah, basically.
When I was...
This did not happen to me.
But it happened to my sister.
Um...
Hold on.
My...
This brother!
Wait, can I?
My grandpa went to go pick up my sister.
And...
It was when she was in kindergarten.
Okay.
And he decided to wear a scary mask and barge into the
kindergarten going And he got banned from doing that he
Wasn't allowed to pick up my sister anymore
Save save What if oh Hopefully this guy will have some sense
and not shoot you.
Oh.
That guy has no sense.
He shot you.
Dumb, dumb, dumb.
Nice one, William Tell.
You dead.
Thanks for playing.
Yippee!
Okay.
That was fun.
That was a good little...
Okay.
Now we say Haldo.
Archer stops arching, arching, and turns to you.
My brother told you to tell me, Haldoh, he must want to
start the old business backup.
Yeah, Mortis.
Oh my gosh.
I love that game.
How'd you know?
Take arrow.
You pick out a really good one and yank it from the tree.
Hooray!
Now you have an arrow.
all right now we're getting somewhere you guys now we go
back to the archer right I want to see how they're doing our
favorite brothers look at them they're so happy talk Haldoh
says the brothers test your skill give us the right super
item from your inventory and you can give it as many tries
as you need we have a Give trinket.
That'll work, says Mendeleev.
Just hit three bulls' eyes, and you win the super time fun
bow TM.
The arrow keys aim left and right on the space bar operates
the bow.
You'll need to press it a couple of times to get a nice shot
off.
But we don't give lessons, so you're on your own.
Okay.
I think we'll get it first try
Oh I knew how it worked
Close Oh my gosh, wait, there's wind too So we need to go
over this way, right?
Like as As Oh Oh Oh Oh Did you guys see that?
That was professional gaming?
Oh!
Professional gaming?
I mean, I told you so.
I told you guys.
I told you guys I would get it first try.
Pro gamer.
I know.
I told you.
I told.
You said you weren't an FPS player.
I just, you know.
I learned from the best.
Me.
Obviously.
Nice shooting.
Three hits, says Mendeleev.
Here's your prize.
You got the Supertime Funbow TM.
We don't sell ammo, so you'll have to find your own arrows
for it.
Now we can go kill that guy.
Wait, right, wait.
Ooh, oh, we see it?
We have an arrow.
Boy, you sure know how to pick them.
This arrow's kind of pointy even.
This is a pretty fancy bow.
You're surprised those shady archers give away such decent
prizes.
You have expected goldfish in a bag.
Let's go.
Steel arrows.
Wait, you can do that?
Hold on.
I gotta save real quick.
I can't stop coughing today.
I'm so sorry.
Um.
Dead eye ghost girl.
Who's the big boss now?
Me!
What do you mean?
Steel arrow.
Oh, steel arrow.
Yeah.
Oh, no, they're still watching me.
Pollen?
I think it is pollen.
I think I have a bad allergy.
Coughing tuscaru.
Now...
Hi, Tech.
Welcome to membership.
Thank you!
Let's take some arrows here, I guess.
Do I need any more?
I think I can one-shot him.
Take Arrow.
You're pretty much all set on the arrow front.
They are kind of cool, though.
We're confident, you guys.
Have confidence.
We're gonna kill this guy.
We're gonna kill him dead.
Shoot Arrow.
Here goes nothing, kid Icarus.
Whoa!
Erode.
Nice shot.
You smote to the Carrick.
He lay there stinking.
Just like my cat.
Oh!
A light rain heralds the washing free of the Carrick's grip
on the land.
You're feeling pretty good, though.
So the artless symbolism doesn't bug you.
I'm going to take my arrow back.
Take arrow.
Ew, no way.
That thing's got some serious Carrick brand cooties on it
now.
Not the cooties.
Terrible day for rain.
Cry for Carrick.
What's his name?
Carrick.
Look.
There are large hoof prints in the grass here.
There's a large Carrick shaped mound on the grass.
Cry for Carrick.
This guy has no empathy.
Take his belt.
Strip.
Take everything.
Steal.
Rob him.
Loot him.
Take everything he's got.
Rob him for all he's worth.
Steal his fortune.
search search carrick I think we have exhausted everything
oh
now you've done it you're covered in sticky albeit fine
smelling mud your scalding lake t-shirt is all soiled too
you just washed it last harvest what am I supposed to do
looking like looking like I look like, oh my gosh, this is
literally the Bigfoot over here.
Like, I look like Bigfoot right now.
Type cheat.
What happens if I type that?
Cheat.
Meh.
I look like Bigfoot over here.
Okay, this guy should now be...
Oh, yes, there is.
he is.
Talk.
The Carrick is dead, he cries and hops around some more.
You wonder how someone this primitive could have made that
much dough.
Um.
Hello?
Talk?
Uh.
Take gold.
The Janka will see you and rip out your jugular with his
teeth or something equally horrible.
Hmm.
Steel.
Treasure.
Wait.
I still, I just, let's go, let's just go get another arrow.
Let's just go get another arrow.
We can solve all of our problems.
Oh.
Take arrow.
You grab yet another arrow from the tree hoping to get some
bonus points.
Okay, let's go kill him.
Let's go kill the jonka.
Yeah, we're gonna go kill him.
Shoot.
Shoot jonka.
Shoot bow.
Fire.
Kill jonka.
No way, jonkas are born scrappers.
He may be a little, but he'll crawl you.
Oh.
Oh, shoot arrow.
The game is not letting me choose violence.
Hmm.
So we need to distract him somehow.
What do I have?
Uh, oh, the monster mask.
Maybe he'll be afraid of me.
Wear mask.
Tell him a joke.
Hmm.
No violence?
What else can we do?
Wait, I'm kind of stinky now, right?
So maybe the innkeeper will let us in?
Lily Straight Shin, welcome to membership.
Thank you!
Brib.
Do I have anything?
My t-shirt?
shirt he wants my t-shirt maybe here
we go to the end we're gonna say open um get a room i only
serve peasants here fancy pants where's your robe can't you
see that i'm quite peasantly looking how am i not a real
peasant i wonder hi perdude man welcome to you manbishop
thank you Master 117.
Welcome to membership.
Thank you.
Mmm, baby lady.
We haven't seen her in a while.
Um.
No, she says the same thing.
This place is dead anyway.
Dang!
Is there a muing commit?
Is that actual muing emo?
What?
Oh my god, not the Lorax.
He speaks for the trees.
Welcome to the Peasantship.
Also,
the hay.
I'm trying to think of what else.
Okay, so we killed him.
We scared Gary.
There's the hay.
Hey.
Search.
No needles.
There's nothing else because we got the fart or the fissure.
Roll in hay.
No.
Eat.
I did it again.
Um.
I did it again It means eat happy you guys Eat happy By the
way What are you playing this on?
Is it a recent re-release?
I'm on the homestarrunner.com website Actually Find needle
No It's how some people say jump in hay You've not known
much better than a roll in the hay alone.
What?
Wait, that was right!
You leap in the hay like a two-year-old boy.
Uh-oh, the hay sticks to your muddy body.
You're a walking hay bale, just like that one guy from that
one show.
Oh my god!
I'm just hay!
Oh, the winds are heavy and all, but a couple of key
screens...
Looks like you're no longer in stealth mode
Okay, okay We got it going to stealth mode Jump in hey Yeah,
he looks so excited to get in there, you know, hey nice
disguise the jonka doesn't seem to notice you
Steel gold I wanted to say that I've been enjoying all your
streams since you came back you can't wait to watch more
also since you started streaming again you've become one of
my favorite youtubers to watch oh my gosh what no way little
old me thank you so much mr.
Mike Tyson's butt
oh oh a stiff breeze blew all the hay and surprisingly the
mud off of you You take my riches, grouse the jonka.
Run?
Go run?
What?
Uh, run.
Just answer him.
Oh, yes or no?
You fool?
Oh, no.
Okay.
Let me know if you see riches anywhere.
Huh?
Just a hay.
He grunts and goes back to his hopping.
You smooth talker, you.
All right, let's go to the baby lady.
Fooled.
Oh, no, our mud is gone.
That was so easy.
We're going to be a peasant in no time, you guys.
Except we've done 41 things and we don't even stink.
We don't even anything.
How are we supposed to become a peasant?
Okay, lady.
uh oh
these riches though riches dude riches that peasant lady
totally has to share some of this with you right at least
that shiny clawed scepter thing she will she's a good lady
she's a good mom she's been raising her baby all by herself
she's a good lady she's nice she's going to she's going
she's she's a good good lady give riches my riches she
screams and snatches up every last gold coin thanks sucker
here you go she shoves the baby into your hands and bolts
out the door you later learn that she does this all the time
and is wanted throughout the countryside those riches
probably were the junkas and who knows whose baby that is
well it's yours now I got scammed I got scammed is there a
baby in my inventory now baby it's a beautiful blue-eyed
baby oh peasant babies are adorable no wonder they fetch
such a pretty penny on the Black Market.
Yeah, we're gonna throw this baby.
Ooh, it's kind of creepy.
Hell, the rocking chair is still rocking.
There...
It reeks of single parrot.
It's such a...
Savage line.
Mint is cute.
Stop!
Stop it!
Stop it.
Stave it.
There is one of those self-rocking chairs.
Mostly empty shelves.
It's okay.
Oh, it's a self-rocking chair.
She was even too...
Boner!
Thanks for the super chat.
Baby acquired.
Now we're playing peasant stranding.
Wait, why can't I move?
Oh, there we go.
I'm gonna go to the lake and throw the baby into the lake
for the gods.
Oh, here we go.
Throw baby!
You've already fed the fish.
Let's get moving here, people.
Oh, dang.
Okay, the other...
The fish on the other side!
Throw that baby!
Throw baby!
again from the center of the lake.
Looks deeper there.
Throw that baby.
Where's the center?
Oh, throw baby.
Hmm, maybe try someplace else.
Throw that baby.
I accidentally clipped into their table for a second.
Throw baby.
Hmm.
Where else can we throw the baby?
The waterfall!
Oh my gosh, the waterfall throw that baby throw that baby oh
down the well throw baby throw it where throw baby down well
take put baby in bucket you're not that keen a shot try
standing a little closer I'm as close as it can be.
Baby in bucket.
Throw that baby.
Wait, how do I get to the center of the lake?
I forgot about this guy!
I'll give him the baby.
You're on the right track, Mint.
Hey, Cafe, what did Mint do in stream today?
She threw that baby!
Actually I have to or else I'm gonna be a liar.
Where is he?
Did he go home?
Throw baby.
give baby talk how do we not startle him
is this guy okay I've kind of feel bad now the carrick is
dead oh yeah that's right can I go into his house knock open
no dang wave wave we give him a big hearty wave okay what do
we have um arrow baby bow mask we gotta use the baby we
gotta throw the baby somewhere i think it's the waterfall
throw that baby give baby you think he wants the baby give
baby no how close are you to getting your own thatched roof
cottage um i don't think i want one because trog if i get
one trog door is going to come and burninate it that would
be really unfortunate and i'd have to go on some my own
quest i'd also have to become a peasant i'm already a maid
can i get any lower than this like come on i'm already a
servant essentially give baby don't need nothing from no
filthy peasants is I'm not he said I'm a peasant for real
you are but you get paid I
forgot about this room wait a second is this where you use
baby Deploying cue baby
No baby come back Baby come back No my baby My baby Way to
go baby It got the cottage door open and headed off to a new
life Baby It becomes valedictorian of his graduating class
Goes to scalding lake state Get a degree in advanced
peasantry And lands a drop a thatch pro building better
cottages for a better tomorrow my baby you grow apart and
the letters from him become fewer and fewer he develops a
severe mead problem and blames you for never being there
wait did I read is that mead or med like head or read what
is What is Mead?
What is that?
Oh, I got more points!
Oh,
it's alcohol.
Like reed.
Okay, okay, okay.
So what is Mead?
He gets a alcohol addiction!
Oh my gosh, my baby.
You went to Skalding Lake State.
The pressure was too hard on you.
Normal plant.
Welcome to membership.
Thank you!
An alcohol made from honey!
Honey wine!
Wait, is it good?
Mead is a type of alcohol made with fermented honey.
How can you ferment honey?
Open.
A search drawer.
Search?
Look!
This place could use some serious sprucing of the up
variety.
There's a dresser over there and a broom kind of silhouetted
all mysterious like.
Open, or no, search dresser.
Uh, huh?
I'm in mysterious cottage.
What can I say?
Uh, open dresser?
Oh, there we go.
There's a vintage peasant robe in there!
Just like grandpa used to wear.
Wear robe!
You don't have anything but you're scolding lake t-shirt and
pants forgot to mention the pants um take robe yeah get that
robe where robe you slip into the vintage robe it smells
like grandpa's ew grandpa's lap now you're looking like a
serious peasant mince got oops sorry i don't mean to kick my
mic mince got that baby fever I want baby back.
You guys were a peasant!
We're a peasant!
Let's go to the inn!
Let's go to the inn.
Yeah, yeah, to the inn.
Boop, boop.
We're gonna catch ourselves on fire eventually.
Back to the inn.
Boop, boop, boop.
We have to catch ourselves on fire here, I'm assuming,
right?
Hello, sir.
Get a room.
Okay, youngster, says the decrepit old person.
Just bed on down for the night, and I'm sure I'll remember
to collect the fee come morning.
Good night, everybody.
A night falls like a bad PowerPoint presentation.
Welcome to Mambusha.
Thank you!
Whoa,
it's night.
What an uncomfortable bed.
You sleep for maybe 20 minutes before the extreme pain and
your spine forces you to get up.
He left the pantry open.
What can we take?
Take candle.
Seems like you should be able to do that, doesn't it?
Sorry, no dice.
A small hint of brilliance.
but she can wear clothes right she can still be a peasant
because it's not her on fire but the robe yeah so true the
brilliance is magnificent still dark out the grimy old
innkeeper is gone and he's left the pantry open search
pantry look pantry shelves and shelves of something called
old man rub I want my baby baby baby baby baby baby baby
baby baby baby baby baby back jillies baby back ribs what is
this yes
old man rub old man rub the only thing of interest is a big
black pot of horse grease up on the top shelf.
Take horse grease.
You reach way up to the top shelf.
Oh, great.
Now you can't see a thing and your head is covered in highly
flammable horse grease.
You better get out of here before that disgusting old man
comes back.
Oh, oh no.
Oh, my keys are all messed up.
Wait, okay.
This way?
This way.
Oh, oh, I was close.
Phew.
Momo-chan!
Thank you for the really big Akadono.
Hey.
Hi.
Thank you.
Oh, my gosh.
Thank you so much.
I really appreciate it.
ARIGATO ARIGATO Chew
ARIGATO Special SpongeBob Don't know For that Thank you You
You discard the big black pie And wipe the horse grease from
your eyes The hood of your robe is still covered in highly
flammable horse grease Oh my gosh We're gonna catch on fire
like Soon Soon soon Wait Can I take that candle now or open?
Take candle.
Light candle?
Eat candle.
Save?
Okay.
You guys are so, so big about me saving.
Rolling for two.
Oh, it's on.
It's on.
Okay, here we go.
Ah!
whoa the horse grease on your robe caught fire you're a four
real peasant now wait but i'm still not stinky enough right
or am i i mean it said it smelled like my grandpa so man
screens sure get light fast around here yeah i'm just having
your normal peasant day i'm on fire i'm you know do there's
a lot of stuff that I don't have this there's a lot of stuff
hmm what else am I missing besides the the guy behind the
tree looked naked talk go away said donglev we're arguing
about who's hotter as Mendeleev okay I can I can settle
this.
Well, I can see that Dengalev has a very pronounced chin.
That's already the signs of a Chad.
And he also speaks with confidence.
Where Mendeleev is, you know, he's just kind of Eeyore.
He's like, I'm so king.
side.
Mendeleev is hotter for sure.
What?
I'm where do you...
What are your credentials?
Peasant day.
Peasant time.
Stop.
Not the lane reference.
And you don't seem to understand.
I have a confidence.
Whoa.
I'm walking on top.
I'm walking in my heart.
Whoa, whoa.
Thatched roof.
Sorry, my thatched roof.
Cottage.
Whoa, whoa.
What am I missing?
Talk.
We're on fire.
Set on fire.
I can set anything.
I can light anything on fire now, you guys.
Ugh.
level hmm is there anything I can take look large hoof print
no carrick mound take shoes take what is this is this a
pants take pants take he doesn't have a shirt on oh it's a
belt oh oh you strap the carrick's belt buckle around your
waist oh boy you sure stink now oh my gosh we smell we smell
oh we got the carrick belt oh this thing stinks like oh get
out why couldn't the carrick have carrick have kidnapped a
hot wench or something that you could have saved so true
give me the hot wench i'm a peasant and i'm gonna go kill
trogdor and i'm gonna get a hot wench for me myself only i'm
a peasant but there's still so much that i don't have before
we go face him face trogdor and also okay hold on i have an
idea because i do it's now that i have the robe on maybe i
can give the shirt to that guy a proper peasant robe it
smells freshly washed and the initials nn sewn onto the tag
nn is there anyone in home star that has those initials
home star oh wait uh look hey come on now buddy oh no no no
no
oh talk how do i make him not disappear I was once possibly,
maybe, perhaps a chicken nugget.
Thank you.
Nice boaty profile pick.
Oh,
give shirt instead.
What's wrong with end?
And give shirt.
You don't need to give that now.
Give robe.
Give shirt.
Throw shirt.
gift shirt hide behind the tree give shirt drop shirt talk
maybe I'm missing something does he need pants also let's go
back to the inn because it's daytime now let's go Go back.
Beep.
Open.
Hello, mister.
If you're interested in seeing the night, just say, get a
room.
Get.
Uh.
It might have crashed.
It popped right back up as I refreshed.
No way.
Oh my goodness.
Skip.
Load.
We have to go back just a little bit.
little bit oh wait actually load oh here we go load that's
better the auto save is better sorry guys so so so sorry for
the inconvenience also this screen has nothing we could have
thrown the baby in here not here too no we went to college
do you have the belt uh Yes.
Yes, I do.
Oh, open.
I don't know why I typed inventory.
Ord of Peasant Health says I can't serve any folk that's on
fire.
Nothing personal.
Well, I mean, I don't like you much anyway.
Because I'm on fire, you're discriminating against me.
It's a pre-existing condition.
You can't do this to me.
Please.
sleep so it's very personal yeah can I swim now I don't know
how to give that guy the shirt hmm let's go talk to the
night here too the one that's gatekeeping us but I don't
exactly want to go we only have a score of 92 Talk.
Looking good, Mr. Peasant.
Good luck with old beefy arm up there.
This is it.
You can finally get revenge on Trogdor.
Nice work so far, stupid.
Okay.
But we have to get that guy.
Nah, welcome the membership.
Thank you.
Hmm.
How can we give it to him?
How can we...
I want to give it to him.
Now I'm gonna give it to him.
Hmm...
I love that they call you stupid all the time.
Uh...
Hi, Mint.
This is Trevor from Hampton, Maine.
And I was wondering if you could teach me to be as awesome
as you.
Ah!
Sorry, you scared me.
I am a vampire and...
Huh?
And what?
Mellon, welcome to membership.
Thank you!
What do I do?
What do I...
Maybe I hide behind...
Hide behind tree.
I'm just gonna say hide.
Hide.
Um...
Can you whisper?
Whisper.
Hmm...
Check my inventory.
I feel like the hay would have been a good thing here.
Take off shirt.
No.
This guy needs my shirt.
His nipples are so prominent.
Look at them.
I thought they were eyeballs at first.
Maybe this is not a human.
Maybe this is actually a creature.
These are his eyes.
And this is like a...
A cyst or something.
You know?
What do you mean another Mipple Hater?
I'm not hating.
I'm just saying.
Wear.
Mask.
No.
I can't tell what to do here.
What can, what to do here?
Oh!
He's gone.
We scared him.
What?
There are large hoof prints in the grass here.
Looks like someone left their spare bones here.
Take bones.
No!
No.
Oh, I want the bones.
I want the bones.
What?
Does anyone actually have a good, like, I was going to say
an actual good idea, but does anyone, like, if you remember
the game, want to give a hint?
I can't remember.
Talk tree.
Trees can't talk, but a breeze picks up.
And you swear the leaves whisper in the words Naked Ned
Naked Ned Hey Ned Holdo Oh That's totally not Dongolev And
And The trees are on something
dead i missed a lot with the baby oh no really wait like
points that's so sad you have his robe i know but take off
robe give robe i have your robe try talking to him i'll show
you what happens
Hmm.
Wavy.
Oh.
Talk to Naked Ned.
Never speak of this meeting, says the nudie and he
disappears.
Huh.
Oh, talk naked Ned gives a different day?
Sure, it doesn't do anything.
Game facts.
What the?
Okay, we'll do talk naked Ned instead of talk to.
Okay, talk naked Ned.
Nope.
Same thing.
Ah, what the?
Maybe I miss something.
Hmm.
Maybe I'll miss something.
He gave us hints for the robe.
useless oh baby had two other tasks oh
oh the baby had two other tasks wait where were they guess
we gotta go beat trogd door now then oh here I come here I
go please insert floppy disk Two, it's a drive B and press
enter.
Snake, you have to change the disc.
There we go.
Let's go.
Climb.
With a new determination, you dig your fingers into the
cliff face and begin to haul yourself up the mountain like
you were in a sports drink commercial.
The mountain starts rumbling and big loose boulders start to
move.
tumbling down you'd best avoid them's okay oh oh oh goodness
gracious you cannot go up and also you have to like you
cannot go up and sideways at the same time okay we're just
gonna go this way all right i'm gonna go scoot over a little
maybe here we go everybody we're gonna We're going to go
beat Trogdor!
Oh, nice job climbing the cliff.
You have a real way with those arrow keys.
What a thrill.
Oh, you do keep getting more points.
Oh my gosh.
What's this?
Oh, oh.
Foolish peasant, how dare you enter this fairly sacred
chamber?
You explain that you are here to smote Trogdor.
And if he doesn't get out of your way, him too.
I love coached Z.
Great job.
You cannot vanquish Trogdor.
Only the three keepers of Trogdor hold the tools with which
to destroy the burninator.
The Trog shield, the Trog helmet, and the Trog sword.
And the only way we'll give them up is if you answer the
three Trog trivia questions correctly.
Oh, right here goes, what does Mendeleev have you tell
Dongle.
Hello, everybody?
I mean, not hello.
Everybody?
Let's all say it together.
America ya!
Happy!
No, I'm just kidding.
It's A.
Oh, crap.
You're right.
Here, take this stupid trog shield.
America ya!
Hold, peasant.
You must answer the second dreaded trog trivia.
question listen careful now what was the innkeeper's pantry
full of I remember not Epson printers old man rub that's
right oh this sucks because I have to give you this trog
helmet dang and last oh but not least I thought they were
all going to be color-coded like their fancy dangles here
old man rub think you're pretty hot stuff hey let's see you
answer the deadly and pretty impossible third trog trivial
question riddle me this which way does the river that runs
through peasantry flow
north east to southwest
I think, wait, I'm thinking of the, um, no, I'm thinking of
the, what's the word?
I'm thinking of the waterfall.
Wait, see you think?
I think it's C, right?
Yeah, maybe I am right.
Pick number C, my lord.
Pick number C, mint.
Okay, let's try C.
Oh, oh, uh-oh, you got it right.
Trogdor's gonna kill me.
Okay, you can have the Trogsword.
Just promise not to kill any Trogdor's with it, okay?
You just stare at the keeper blankly.
Okay, fine.
You can have the dumb thing anyway.
Trogdor's through the beaded curtain over there.
The fabled Trogsword is yours.
Now you have the means to strike down Trogdor.
Good luck, peasant.
Yeah!
Look at me!
We are still missing three things!
Oh, four!
Four things!
How curious.
Let's check out the Trog helmet.
The Trog helmet is not screwing around.
It's a serious helmet.
It also protects against harmful UV rays!
Are you Team Yukari Sensei or Team Namo?
We need to No.
Uh.
As a kid, I was always more Team Yukari Sensei.
Behold the Trog Shield.
No, seriously, behold it.
There's no way Trogdor's fire breath can penetrate this
thing.
Yeah.
The Trog Sword is for real.
Hands down, the coolest item in this whole game.
You can't wait to lop off that beefy arm of Trogdor's with
this guy.
Oh my gosh.
Oh my gosh, you guys.
do it we're gonna go we're going to go defeat Toronto this
is it this is it actually I don't remember what the is there
a minigame or I actually don't remember what happens so
let's go
my ears the beaded curtain slams shut behind you there's no
turning back no Save?
Oh.
No turning back now, you guys.
Oh, save.
Be boop.
Maybe I should have had like a thing before I did the baby,
you know?
Be boop.
Oh my god, we're so small!
Throw sword!
This is it!
You hurl the trog sword with all your might at the sleeping
burninator!
Oh!
Wow, it's beefy.
It looks like a cigarette.
You shouldn't be smoking, Trogdor.
Now you've done it.
Trogdor's awake and the Trogsword doesn't seem to be doing a
whole lot.
Oh, no.
Your legs lock in fear.
Your eyes glaze over and you wish for some de-peasant...
de-peasant adult undergarments.
But you think you hear Trogdor whimpering.
Oh, crap.
That's you whimpering.
At least your voice still works, I guess.
Uh, oh, talk.
You scream that your name is rather dashing, and that
Trogdor burninated your cottage, and you're here for
revenge.
I really appreciate you making the effort to become all the
way up here and thank you, Mr. M.
Hector.
But I'm kind of indestructible.
Mortis!
I will say that again for anybody who did not understand.
Sup, mortal.
Boomstrogdor.
I really appreciate you making all the effort to come all
the way up here and vanquish me and all, but I'm kind of
indestructible.
Yeah, I can't be cute.
I'm surprised nobody mentioned that to you.
I let me through.
terrifying rain of spiders yeah I can't be killed I'm
surprised nobody mentioned that to you I'll admit though
you've gotten farther than anybody else has I bet they'll
make a statue or something in honor of you somewheres
Rain of Trogdor's.
I can honestly say it'll be a pleasure and an honor to
burninate you, rather dashing.
Oh, that sure was nice of him.
And I've been burninated.
You've won!
No one can kill Trogdor, but you came closer than anybody
ever.
Way to go!
No!
I wanted to 100% it.
He's eating him.
Then he's gonna eat me!
Oh my gosh, it's our statue!
Nice work on winning and everything.
Oh!
Scalding Lake!
134 out of 150 is so okay that's it oh it's so frustrating
though ah it's so frustrating not to get 150.
the end yippee what a game look at how rather dashing we are
yeah Here, this statue is in honor of rather dashing.
I expected him to have a bit more of like a far quad kind of
haircut from his little sprite.
You know, he seemed to have like a bit of a, a bit of a bob.
A bob.
Yeah.
Hmm.
How can AAA games compare?
I think I found my new brain rot.
I think I found my new brain rot with this.
I'm kind of a fan.
Is this an old game or a new game made retro style?
It's pretty old.
It's not like as old as it seems though.
It's like mid-2000s game.
Right?
Circa 2004.
That's what I meant.
2010 right wait 2000 to 2010 so 2004 is almost in the middle
so 20 years yeah yeah 20 20 years old this game is but it
seems like it's supposed to be like 40 years old you know
it's an old parody of an even older genre exactly oh my gosh
tractor Thank you for the trip down memory lane track.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Sorry, when I say not too old, I mean compared to the style
of game that it's emulating or that it's parodying.
You know what I mean?
It's not from the 80s or 90s or anything.
explode.
Yeah, that was so fun.
What a trip down memory lane.
I almost want to speedrun it to try and get the baby extra
stuff, but I'm kind of tired.
I'll be honest.
Today and yesterday were a couple of busy days with me
haunting all over the place.
Yeah, Spider-Man.
Oh, sorry.
I wish you were but welcome the membership thank you
burninating the countryside burninating the people look you
guys metal gear solid is older than this I think zoom beat
is also older than this so cap fourth a leg is like a house
without a bonnet has to find the bill key to pen blue door
Oh my gosh, that's the yokel felon king I know and remember.
It's crazy how back then they just copied how old DOS games
and nowadays we get styles copying the PS1 wobble.
What a time we live in.
I know, right?
So funny.
Though there are some games that copy styles like this too
sometimes.
You know, indie game Dave the Diver.
No, I'm just kidding.
um mortis what what is uh faith faith is faith is pretty you
know
uh and i don't i don't think it's a very i don't i can't
think of anything else though i don't know undertale
not really though it's just like a pixel game right movie
time what do you mean movie time what's the movie time how
do i get out of this
help quit done thanks for bringing clarity to me for a rep
to me for a reference that i never got to experience but
only heard about it second hand also cute made ghost is cute
Thanks, Black Knight!
I'm glad that there's a Peasants Quest movie!
Wait, actually?
Hold on, I'm looking it up.
Peasants Quest movie.
Also, don't Google Peasants Quest because there's apparently
another game called Peasants Quest that does not.
Hmm.
It, uh...
It does not look friendly.
Hold on.
Oh, movie trailer.
It began.
Oh, I think we can watch this.
It's, hold on.
Give me a second.
How can I do this real quick?
I'm going to hide the peasant's quest.
I'm going to do this.
Wait, can I put it here?
Oh, no.
I can't.
Here we go.
The Peasant's Quest.
And then I can scoot it over.
Like that.
Okay.
We're watching.
We're going to watch ye old YouTube.
We're watching ye old YouTube, everybody.
Oh, it's a little cut off.
Hold on.
Turn it down some too.
I hope I don't get copyright struck like before.
There we go.
Okay.
It began as the best-selling video computer TV game of all
time.
But not really.
But still.
A simple peasant wearing short pants.
I was him.
way into the heart of a nation now for his greatest
adventure yet he will quest into theaters oh see that's what
I imagined him to look like where's my cottage oh no I got
oh my god whoa whoa who's he fighting I don't remember that
part it's not with the baby we have coexisted with the bird
of nature Who is that?
This is from 14 years ago, you guys.
Oh, he's got his golden leg.
From the sort of people who brought you Trogdor and
Litigation Jackson.
Is that a real horse?
Easy now, Gary.
I'm just going to wear a mask.
Is that a real horse?
Show me your real man, rather dashing.
Through baby!
How do you?
I'm Mendelov.
I'm Donglev.
Ah!
Rather dashing.
More like rather homely.
Whoa!
High dog!
A trog venture for the whole trog family!
Oh, they said they don't do lessons.
They just hate me, I guess.
Oh, I love Blue.
for night.
I'm just so mad at Trogdor.
Access to Trogdor is strictly for peasants.
Oh, yep.
Why is it wiggling down here?
You don't smell like a peasant.
Ah!
Oh my god!
I killed that guy!
Yeah.
Good thing we didn't watch this.
It's spoilers.
I don't remember this part.
Maybe I should have attacked him.
fire like a peasant the quest for adventure oh my god quest
for revenge oh what is that a quest for a peasant peasants
quest oh oh my eyes in the in the moon and the trombone
comes in the Not tonight, he doesn't.
Yeah.
Come in the night.
Trogdor.
Yeah.
Peasant's quest.
I think I get it more now, I think.
I think.
The maid is grounded.
bad there was so much love in that video i think the people
that made homestar probably had a lot of fun you know they
seemed like they just were goofy goofy people all all around
goofy people you know what i mean oh you can see i'm on the
homestar website that that's that's it That's it, everybody.
I really wanted to 100% it, but oh well.
I'm glad we watched the video.
I'm going to go to the bathroom real quick.
I'm going to go to the little ghosty's room.
So you guys also get some something to drink and stretch or
go to the bathroom.
I'll be right back.
I'll put on music at least.
I
will be right back.
I'm back, baby.
From the dead.
Give me one second.
I made a cafe and yeah I can talk.
Okairi.
Tanaima!
I went and I saw my cat and he was laying on his back and
looked really cute so I went on his tummy.
And then I kind of kissed him and I said, who's a healthy
boy?
Who's a healthy boy?
Him.
He's a healthy boy.
boy have i ever mentioned you have a pen chant for a
pleasantly peasant quest for a pheasant a what i don't i
didn't understand a single word you said
i've been busy at work so little late no worries glad to
hear your kitty's healthy how old is a little guy my kitty
is 17 but you would never guess looking at him but he is
definitely stinky my cat's about like 13 so definitely not
17 of stink 17 age of stink penchant oh a penchant like that
I was thinking like a chant like water game oops that's what
idle brain does to you I suppose thank you guys for all the
donos while I was going party thank you thank you thank you
thank you Penchant A penchant I was just like Let's here
let's Okay I'm gonna make a penchant right now Fall Pen
Quill Fibo Wipe Inkie Inkie Inkie, inkie, inkie Inkie Hmm
What's, um, what's like the different sizes of a, you know,
um, pen size, like millimeter, you know, um, fine, medium,
bold, fine, medium, bold, yeah, we can do that.
Fine, medium, bold, fine, medium, bold, um, fine, point,
quick, drying, clap.
Rubber grip Okay, let's try it real quick Wait, maybe I
should change the 5OIPA part though, right?
Ball pen quill 5OIPA Inky, inky, inky, inky Fine, medium,
both Fine, medium, both Five point quick drying Rubber grip
0.7 millimeter It kind of works Okay I think I tripped over
my words a little bit towards the end though.
Fine point click drawing.
Rubber grip.
0.5.
0.5.7.
Rubber grip hits hard.
It's a first draft.
I think it's perfect the way it is.
It's okay, but it's not your best work, boss.
Wow, we have some real criticizers in the chat.
It's okay, I get it.
I get it.
What if I go to Homestar Runner today?
Their website?
Wait, the main website is like...
Oh, come on in.
Wait, can I actually... What is Ruffle?
Oh, at the bottom it says, what's this big play button, you
ask?
Well, Flash is all kinds of dead.
but the amazing ruffle project helps our cartoons live on.
Not every cartoon in game works perfectly just yet, so be
patient and expect some jankiness here and there while we
keep working.
That's so cute!
Tough crowd, for real.
It's not easy making chance up, we've got a good knack for
it.
Thanks!
Wait.
Hold on real quick.
I want to make sure I say the right thing.
Hold on.
One second.
Will you ever be playing the Danger-esque Point and Click
game also on the Homestar Runner website?
I don't know.
I don't remember playing.
This one I played because I played it a lot as a kid too.
But I don't really remember.
the other ones so I don't know if they work either like they
said not all their games work but
my heart felt that chat
did you beat it back then I don't remember beating it
because I didn't I feel like I feel like Trogdor's voice
would have traumatized me as a kid and I don't remember that
i don't remember that at all i was like but i probably would
have remembered that right i don't know i don't know
oh i'm so sleepy you guys i've i yesterday i worked i did a
ton essentially I like had a I made a um what's the word I
made like a big calendar for Matara and I to work on um
future podcast episodes and scheduling them out and
scheduling some trips and scheduling some other events and
scheduling things like that and uh um so I worked on a bunch
of that I worked on messaging some people for commissions on
things
Oh, nice.
Yeah, I was so organized.
She loves to schedule.
Yeah.
We have things we're cooking.
I'm so glad you're indie.
I mean.
I guess it is, I guess there is more freedom with it, right?
So, did you message Henya?
I messaged her!
I said, I said, I said, I said to her, I said, I first, she,
she sent me a waving emoji, emoji, and I sent a waving
emoji, and she said, hi, people, people, shy, and I said,
hi, I'm a big fan of you, Dayo.
I said, I'm a big fan of you, Dayo.
Is it P-Po-Shai?
I don't know, actually.
What's a P-P-Po?
I don't know which ones they are.
Hold on.
P-Po-Shai.
Yeah, she said the P-Po-Shai.
This one.
Hold on.
It's literally me.
Me, people shy.
Yep, gotta hit her with the...
I don't know.
Can I stick out my tongue to her?
Would that be considered weird?
Or...
I don't know.
What if I...
What if I just always talk with my tongue out?
What if I always talk with my tongue out?
And I...
Wait, what a stream like this all the time?
What do you think?
We're gonna, but if you keep watching, it's like, it makes
the stream like this.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna try to stream and like turn
it out of town.
It's a sign of intimidation.
sticking out your tongue for the no no they're not pants
it's in my tongue wish I got to experience the early
internet some more.
No.
I think the early internet...
I don't even know.
There's definitely some weird stuff going on.
I mean, there's always weird stuff, right?
But...
Home Star Runner was very pure, which is the best part about
it.
People...
Oh, Pepe and his son...
Pepe?
Is Pepe's son?
Do you guys know that?
Like, Pepe is so popular in Japan.
There's a whole section in Village Vanguard for Pepe, Pepe,
Pepe, Pepe.
For him.
Look, they sell, they sell a bunch of merch.
Hold on.
It's like this.
I got a picture.
Like this.
Pepe the frog.
Pepe's a frog.
What is a Pepe the frog?
Who is Pepe the frog?
Demonic normals!
Thank you so much for that!
Fifty!
Thank you!
Thank you so so much!
Shouse!
Hey, Mint is my birthday today!
Just wanted to send some love and appreciation to the
silliest, goobiest...
Wait, hold on, let me get this out of my face.
Ghost...
If it's not too much to ask for, could I get a birthday
tongue?
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, dear Charlotte.
Happy birthday!
Yay!
Happy birthday.
I'm assuming that's what you meant.
I sure hope so.
Now lick the candles.
This was fun, guys.
Sorry that I feel like this week I don't have so much
planned.
It's only like my second week back.
But, um, and I'm already just like, I'm tired.
But, you know, I'm already, but since I kind of came back,
the day after I came back was when we announced the podcast.
there was a lot of stuff that I needed to take care of and I
was like okay I should probably take care of some of this
stuff before I before I get too deep into things a little
bit a little so um yeah but it's okay like I just just some
like housekeeping you know housekeeping hmm hmm you kind of
dropped on us from heaven i know yeah that's what i'm saying
but i'm still planning lots of stuff and uh yeah um we can
have fun uh with the podcast happening too yippee it's only
been two weeks i know right it feels like so much longer for
even me but i was okay all right time to make my schedule
yesterday and then when i was posting it the post that i
made before was like first schedule and i was like first
schedule what do you mean i'm only making my second schedule
professional mid house keeping yeah yeah podcast is super
fun i've been loving every episode i think um we well last
night when i was doing the planning i think i decided or
what rather i decided maybe a good day to end the podcast um
but i still need to talk about it with matara which is
already so sad to think i don't want to think about it
because yeah even though well the podcast for me also it
feels different than how do i say like for me like obviously
it's different than normal streaming but like it's weird
because when i stream i don't know i feel like maybe half of
my brain is turned off when i stream but with the podcast i
feel like my brain has to be like totally on hear me out
what if you don't end it no we gotta end it's you know it's
a summer podcast you guys it's a summer podcast
but that's okay you'll have you'll have um you'll have lots
of lots and lots of more episodes so um stream nerve but
yeah since my brain is like on for like a hundred percent or
what at least it feels like it's supposed to be a hundred
percent um during it like it it actually does kind of like
wear me out a little bit more which i didn't expect i was
like oh my gosh it's just talking for like a couple hours
like no biggie but um maybe i'm just because you know uh
it's been so long since i've streamed i have no stamina
anymore i have no stamina anymore will you still collab with
In the future with Matara?
Yeah, yeah, of course.
So, podcast turns into collab.
Hey.
Y'all are very, on very high grade YAP mode.
It's got to end someday so that we get the fall and winter
Matara.
Mintara podcast?
No!
But, but I think...
because i'm just like oh my gosh this is like kind of
wearing me out maybe also because like matara is such an
extrovert and for me like when i talk to you guys like i
still can feel like i'm an introvert because i just see you
guys's text but with her i have to have an actual
conversation so my battery just goes so quickly it's
something that i've like kind of been like self-aware of
with the podcast i'm like oh my gosh by the end i start to
like i feel like i start to get kind of tired i need to i
need to work on that for future episodes so i want to say
lately i've been um trying collecting more ace combat merch
although the shipping is kind of expensive because they're
mostly in japan shipping from japan is so expensive but good
luck podcast in winter because it's summer down south that's
true that's true
yeah but it's not that i um i'm still definitely of course
having fun with it it's just a different experience for me
something that i didn't expect because i thought it would be
so easy but not that i'm complaining or anything oh my gosh
being a content creator is so difficult you'll just you
peasants you just never understand now go go and destroy
truck door
yeah special aussie episode
socially battery depleted my battery maybe that's what's
making me so tired all the time no i had a bad dream last
night oh my gosh oh I think it's because I fell asleep
listening to listening to like one of those ghost hunting
YouTube channels or whatever there's this one that I there's
like I love the ones that are so dramatic about everything
because it just is so funny where first of all it's just
like oh my gosh you're doing that to a ghost Like, a ghost
is never going to respond to that, you know?
But, um...
But, uh, you know, as a ghost, of course, I would know.
But, yeah, they're always so goofy.
They're just like...
Yeah, I don't know.
What's the one that I... What is their name?
They had a TV show.
I saw Metal Gear Facts to Fall Asleep 2 video I was going to
try tonight You should I have a person For the past couple
of nights I haven't been able to sleep well I was trying to
Fall asleep to like head scratching ASMR But it just wasn't
working I fall asleep so much better to like Just mundane
person talking videos I with Shane and Ryan no I love them I
love Shane and Ryan ghost adventures no it's a it's a it's a
it's a YouTube channel project fear I remembered it project
fear they are if you want some like trash TV esque ghost
hunting YouTube content they are it's one of those like like
every video they'll be like this is the craziest night we
have ever had history channels are my sleep channels do you
dream of aliens do you dream of getting probed wow have you
tried rambling videos what's a ram what do you mean just
people rambling about stuff
are you a shaniac or a bugara i'm a shaniac all the way even
though Even though I'm a ghost and I appreciate that.
That.
Oh gosh.
What's that?
That Ryan believes in ghosts and Shane doesn't believe in
me.
And that's okay.
You know.
It's not like if someone.
If someone doesn't believe in me.
It's not like I'm going to die again.
You know.
Or cease to exist.
I'm not like other creatures.
Where like.
If someone doesn't believe in you.
Like they like fade out of existence.
You know what I mean.
But.
So for me it doesn't matter.
If Shane doesn't believe in ghosts, I just think he's funny.
Go team Shaneiac.
Shaneiac hype.
Yeah!
Hmm.
Wait, you exist?
Do what?
Hmm.
You mean like a fairy?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Those things are so weak.
What?
Two people don't believe.
in you and you can't fly anymore so come on get you need to
adopt a better a better policy about your existence you know
it's okay we believe in you i don't care if you do or don't
doesn't mean anything to me the weakest the weakest the
weakest hey one of my former ooshis was a fairy Sorry.
I don't mean to Oshi slander.
My bad.
Sorry.
I apologize.
Not to your Oshi.
To you.
Yeah.
Get wrecked chat.
Also, you don't need wings to fly as a ghost.
Speaking of, well it's not flying, it's more like floating,
but I got a new desk.
I got a standing desk.
But I've been calling it a floating desk.
I got a floating desk for myself.
Oh my gosh, I'm going to be so healthy.
So you're saying you could beat up a ferry.
Yeah, probably.
Why not?
Yeah.
I've been trying to.
Because because um can I mention this you know what she
mentions things all the time it's probably fine if I mention
this actually I think it was already mentioned before so
because I know that Matara is wanting to come visit yeah we
mentioned it because we talked I asked if she wanted to play
my patchy slot machine because Matara is planning on
visiting me I'm like been reorganizing the maid's cafe a
little bit I was just like like oh gosh maybe this doesn't
look like so awesome maybe i gotta like reorganize just just
just a little just a little bit
so i've been kind of that was part of what i've been doing
this week but also i've been cleaning and reorganizing for
another reason good day mint good day first thing you need
to get to go with your standing desk is a tall chair It's
the purpose!
No!
It's so soon?
I'm not gonna say what!
Don't say it.
She needs to hide her lewd snake dockies.
Hey, if you can show me where to get those, then I will need
to hide them.
3D stream?
No.
No, no, no.
Not anything like that.
I... I... I... I...
Don't even know how long I'll be around for, you know?
So, um...
3D stream... We'll see, we'll see.
We'll see, we'll see.
I'd like to though It'd be really fun To What are you guys
saying?
Is that what you want?
Oh my gosh Luud you could do the funniest thing right now
Luud Luud you could do The funniest thing right now If you
make just one I'll buy it out off cut if you make just one
i'll roll up to you in my little robot tablet and i'll buy
it from your booth just one
i know that's not how orders work i know it's like oh my
gosh i have to order 50 for it to be even worth it but a
higher price tag on it i'll still buy it i know they're like
i've seen ones exist but imagine my own personal one that'd
be crazy
yes mine me mine mine mine gonna cost 300 dollars
worth maybe just order one sample louvoude you can do.
Oh, you're so big brain.
Just order it as a sample.
Exactly.
It doesn't need to be perfect.
Just order the sample.
That's so genius.
Oh my gosh.
That's so smart.
Of course, of course the vendors would all have all the
knowledge.
Yeah, it's just a sample.
It's not for sale.
Except to me.
This is my official commission.
Okay.
See you at...
At...
Off-Kai.
Yes.
Hacking the system.
Big boss on my...
one side and solid on the other no double pliskin double
pliskin can't wait for all the mint fan merch it's so like I
see people like posting like oh I made a mint keychain or I
saw I saw like a mock-up of a mint plushie and I'm just like
it's crazy It's actually crazy.
I never would have thunk.
I never would have thought, you know?
Wow, thank you.
Ma'am, Lady Ghost Made Mince, please keep the tongue in
check.
You can't just have it out in the world flopping out like
that.
Actually messed up.
Oh, God, it's okay.
And I get it.
I know.
It's a power that I must handle responsibly.
you're a suit thank you it's always summer down here so it
never ends right right
you're a bit of a celebrity boss no no no i'm just little
old me must have been backlogged i think some of them are
backlogged a little bit yeah Well, I have to change the
notives because I can't read them.
Look how tiny.
The text is for ants.
I can't read it at all.
Can't read it at all.
Alicia, you're famous, though.
You think too little of yourself.
You're bigger than Elvis.
You ain't nothing but a hound, dog.
Crying all down
Hmm Was that a Zoolander reference?
So famous she gets banned in chats.
Look.
I don't know.
I don't know what you mean.
I've never been banned.
And I've always been honest.
I've always been like If I go into a chat I don't know I
I don't know what you mean I don't know what you mean
Hold on I'm gonna do something real quick
Is it a bro I can't tell.
So you two are broken?
I can't tell anymore.
Bustin?
Thank you, thank you.
Since I saw someone donate about Ace Combat a couple days
ago, begging you to play Ace Combat?
I just want to say as much as I love Ace Combat, me and most
Ace Combat fans don't want to demand you to play them if you
don't want to.
Don't worry, don't worry.
Yes, it is broken.
It's breaking.
It's like not loading for me right now.
Hold on.
I'm gonna try.
Yeah, I think it's broken.
I think it's broken.
Thanks!
Oh gosh, now my chat is actually...
Oh, oh, oh!
50 people are watching?
This is just like old times!
This is just like before I left!
This is... this is nothing new!
This is literally...
How... how it is for...
Oh my god, my chat's not even loading anymore.
Oh my gosh, we're back to normal, you guys.
This is just like how it was before I left.
Yippee!
Neil fears how much people love you.
No, I actually, I just went and saw if, I don't know, things
are not loading properly.
YouTube is being very slow.
And I'm seeing it's happening on other channels too, so...
You know what?
It's fine.
Small indie company for small indie VTuber.
Andrigos, thanks for the 10 gifted!
Oh, why is nothing...
Oh, gosh, it's so frustrating.
Can't see anything.
Time war back to 2020.
Oh, YouTube.
Please.
Hold on, I can't reach it anymore.
I'm sorry.
I just opened up that back end of YouTube and I got a
comment that was like, WTF, why do you sing so well?
I don't know.
Why?
WTF.
Well, guys.
Oh, oh, chat is just like old times.
WTF.
YouTuber, why?
Why do you sing so well, YouTuber?
Huh?
Why do you have a voice on YouTube, YouTuber?
Um, I can't sing.
Oh my gosh.
That reminds me of, oh my gosh.
Okay, so sorry, I was gonna say, I was, I was gonna say
like, why can't I sing as well as you, YouTuber?
And that reminded me, it was last night.
No, it was this morning.
This morning I was, okay, so there was this issue on TikTok
where I don't actually know if it's just a TikTok issue or
if it's like a general like young people on the internet
issue now.
But it started on TikTok or rather it blew up on TikTok
where someone made a bean soup, right?
They were like, okay, here is a recipe for bean soup.
If you want to have this bean soup.
And they were getting comments like, well, what if I don't
like beans?
Okay.
Don't make the bean soup.
And they were like, what if I can't have that ingredient?
Okay.
Just don't add it then.
You know?
Like just...
Like there was this weird thing where like people are like
starting to...
watch videos and that's this is why I think it's like
younger like younger audiences because they'll be like
they'll take they'll watch a video and take it very
personally like well what if I can't do this thing okay then
you can't do it that's okay and so I experienced it
firsthand this morning when I was watching a TikTok and it
was about this like crazy grocery store that's in Ohio and
they were like you should go it was like it's like a real
grocery store that like has like animatronics in it and it's
only in Ohio yes jungle gyms jungle gyms yes yes yes yes yes
it's called jungle gyms and it has like monorails like it is
crazy it's super like there's a movie theater in it to teach
you about jungle gym like but anyway so the video was like
if you are in Ohio you gotta go check out jungle gyms like
it's a really crazy grocery store go check it out awesome
cool thanks for the recommendation guy like if I'm ever in
Ohio I'm gonna go to jungle gyms but there was a comment
that was just like hey you should check out Omega Mart which
if you don't know what Omega Mart is it's like a it's it's
an it's really an art an art exhibit it's like they have
like rooms behind like doors like like you open up the thing
to think you're getting milk but it's actually a secret room
um yeah it's like an art installation yeah that's a better
art installation not exhibit um a playground for adults yeah
like it's not a real grocery store right it's just like an
art exhibit and so someone was just like you should check
out Omega Mart and the creator who posted the original video
about jungle gyms was like oh well Omega Mart's different
because it's an art installation this is an actual grocery
store so it's kind of different and then there's one other
person comments below and says yeah well you know um I can't
go to Ohio.
It's too far away from me.
Actually, Vegas is closer to me, so I'm going to go to Omega
Mart.
That's like, okay.
I mean, then don't go.
That's like, and people were like, people were like, I mean,
it depends on where you live.
For some people, Ohio is pretty close, you know.
You can, some people can just go.
And they were like, yeah, but I'm not.
I can't.
Vegas is closer to me, so I'm going to Omega Mart.
I'm like, okay, have fun.
But, like, I don't know why kids take these videos so, like,
so personally now.
Like, kids are, like, they'll watch something and be like,
if this doesn't relate, like, they take for you page
extremely seriously.
They're just like, this page is supposed to be for me.
everything should be catered to me you know what i mean i
think that's what it is i don't know it's so strange this is
what happens when you're raised by an ipad i don't it's so
maybe it is just an entitlement thing right i if it isn't
for me it's against me
oh the algorithm has failed me and it's your fault I don't
know I just never would I just I don't know if this is a new
thing or what because you know when I was a kid when I was a
kid like I would never watch a video and be like oh but they
didn't think about my needs it's a new generation thing so
crazy it's very interesting I mean it's not good maybe but I
just I just was so shocked that I experienced it firsthand,
you know?
People being isolated at home, not socializing in person for
a while, probably did a whole lot of something.
That's so true.
Oh, we need to get these kids on Homestar Runner.
Get off the skibbity toilet.
Get them on Homestar Runner.
Have them reading.
Have them sending in strong bad emails.
But yeah, marzipan.
But yeah, this was fun.
Hope you guys enjoyed being a little peasant.
Well, we weren't a peasant.
And then we became a peasant.
And, okay, I want your opinion.
Would a maid be above a peasant or below a peasant?
Like what if I, you know, what if I'm like a royal maid, you
know, like what if I'm working at like a...
Above?
Above, above, above, above, above?
Same level, equal, above?
Same league?
Depends on who you made for, I think.
Above?
Above, above?
Okay.
I I was above the peasant
You are pet Wait if you're peasants then I can't be your
maid Hmm Okay you're not peasants You're all royalty You're
all royalty I'm a rich peasant You're Thank you, Churul.
No dice, nanoplasm.
Sorry.
Take this king.
What happened to it?
Okaerina-seima-se-se-o-jo-sama?
I said it at the beginning.
I said, Okaerina-seima-se-go-shinima-o-jo-sama.
I always say it.
What do you mean?
I said it.
Yeah!
Mint my kami peasant ocean.
Thanks.
Oh no, I meant how can we be Ojo-sama and also peasant?
Oh!
That's why I said you're not a peasant.
You are above even the peasant.
You are big peasant!
I'm just murdering Merchant, sell, sell, sell.
What are you buying?
What are you selling?
What are you...
Yeah, what are you selling?
What are you selling, merchant?
What are your wares?
What's that?
Royals have noble maids.
Nobles have peasant maids.
Takedo!
Thanks for the five gifting.
Thank you!
stream win you guys besides Resident Evil 1 I've never
played a Resident Evil game before I've always wanted to
play but I'm kind of scared aren't maid cafes made for us
peasants to experience maids no well but when you go in you
are not the peasant you will transform magical moai magic
mm-hmm
Resident 4 is a resident 4.
Resident 4.
Ray Mack, thanks for the 5 gifted.
Merry music, moth.
Welcome to Membuship.
Hakurei Mima.
Oof.
Mima posting in 2024.
Welcome to Membuship.
Ducky, thanks for the 5 gifted.
Alvin, thank you for the 5 gifted.
Thank you guys.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
residents.
Not the 50 drop.
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Thank you, Mima.
Natsuki, thank you for the five gifted.
Well, LPR, thank you for the five gifted.
Why is everybody suddenly gifting?
Shaman Maru.
RE4 is more action than scary.
You're way scarier.
See, that's why, that's actually partially why I've never
played Resident Evil because I always thought the games were
more action and scary, but just to me and my boy.
Stop!
No!
Because they were more action than scary, and I always was
like, well, I like scary games more.
But then 7 came out, and I was like, they're so scary now.
But they're also, like, so goofy.
I want to see Leon and Kat Does he actually wear cat ears or
is that just a meme?
Oh my gosh you guys!
YAMERAO!
J, thank you for the five!
Thank you for the akasufa!
Tongo cat!
Welcome to my book's ship!
Niels, thank you for the five gifted!
Dogs drinks, thank you for the five gifted!
Spank, thank you for the five gifted!
TV table tray, 10, thank you for the five gifted!
Paperbacks, thank you for the five gifted!
Takeoff and yanyan, thank you for the five gifted!
Bloodlust, thank you for the 10 gifting.
No theater, thank you for the 5 gifting.
Stupid shark.
Thank you for the 20 gifting.
Hey, that's not a shark.
That looks like a bird.
Your profile picture.
Fake neat things for the 5 gifting.
Thank you.
Akurosu.
Thank you for the 5 gifting.
Thank you.
Okay.
What were we talking about?
Leon Kennedy's.
cat ears
s8 10 ritual thank you for the amazing gift thank you thank
you so much
cat ear leon is it real does he actually wear cat ears or to
answer your question the cat ears are after you beat the
game no
hard i was gonna say it's hard living but i don't it's hard
after living we're giving you money so that you can go above
a regular peasant stop the horror game that you're looking
for is system shock 2.
what is that system shock 2.
did you guys hear me gulping say no
no no yeah Oh wait.
Actually, I can't.
I can't tell.
Found the tofu very soon funny myself.
Tofu?
System Shock 2 is a classic.
System...
I was thinking recently that I was like, oh my gosh.
I've been wanting to play Blade Runner for so long.
I was thinking of playing it on Sunday.
I'm not sure yet, though.
Tofu is an RE2 thing.
And I didn't, when I played RE, like, when I played Resident
Evil 1, I didn't even beat it.
I only played, like, a little bit of it, so.
Blade Runner.
Yeah, I really wanted to play, they have, like, the,
actually, I know they have it on GOG I think it's also on
the Blade Runner is it on Steam yeah they also have it on
Steam actually I can't remember oh the reviews are kind of
mixed on it though oh thank you thanks for reminding me of
Trog door love your streams thank you maybe I should do the
GOG one get the GOG one for the functional one okay okay
yeah maybe we'll play that on sunday i haven't decided yet
but i've been wanting to play it so blade runner
the re-release is buggy the steam one maybe it has some
positive reviews recently i don't know if they oh it says
fix now December 30th, 2023.
Seems like Night Dive has largely fixed the issues the
remaster had at launch.
Do yourself a favor and just play the enhanced edition.
Oh!
Oh nice!
There we go then.
You heard it here folks.
According to Agent Smith on Steam, they said that it is
fixed as of December 30th, 2023.
That is really recent.
That's It's really recent.
If anything, it's only $10.
So, you know.
Oh my gosh, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna go... Oh my gosh.
I'm like looking at it right now and it's so nostalgic.
Are there boobies in this game?
Or am I safe?
Hmm.
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
Sage, thanks for the 10 gifted!
Yes!
boobies oh yeah it was the 90s so anything is possible I
don't know when this what this game came out 1998 hmm anyway
I don't know yet I might save it for another time
there's soft nudity don't get mad at me YouTube don't get
mad at me it's art it's art it's it's it's not real it's
fake it's fake it's fake it's art I see belly button but you
guys want to see my belly button can't see it's covered by
apron you'll never know You'll never know.
For free?
Played like a fiddle.
I mean, you can see, well, you can, the frills kind of block
my armpits a little bit.
It's, it's, I have to be, I have to be nice and breezy so
that when I'm working, you know.
It's got to be nice and breezy.
It's on the summer art, so ha!
You're right.
Gotta take it down.
Time to take it down.
Get wrecked.
Mass recall.
Cancel the project.
Cancel it.
Shut it down.
There's like a big red button in front of me.
And I'm like.
I forgot it was on the summertime merch.
No.
I thought I was safe.
Don't look, you guys.
Don't.
Don't...
Don't look at my belly button.
As goes through, thank you for the tag gifted.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Who's the fiddle now, Mentor?
Why are we here?
Just to suffer.
I perceive.
You better stop it.
You better stop perceiving.
Right now.
If one...
Wait, if you...
If you get ghost busted, do pieces of your outfit get ripped
off like it?
What is this?
What is this question?
that could apply to anyone right like i don't think that's
an akibas trip reference i think that's just like you know
how yeah like senran kagura you know like with there's there
and there's like a lot of games like that when there's when
characters take damage they lose like their clothes just
tear apart that's why if you're going into battle just don't
wear clothes because if they're gonna tear apart anyway it
would be it would be oh a waste to lose them that's big
brain just don't wear them ah don't look where
to put the sand pocket sand meep I'm gifted!
I thought this emote looked like Pansu.
You and everybody else thought so, okay?
But when you put them all together, it looks fine.
Boob.
Okay, guys.
I'm gonna go.
I'm gonna leave.
I'm gonna head out.
Tomorrow, no stream.
I got some stuff to do, but also recording.
like the thing i'm recording so we are recording for the
podcast um
thank you guys again for watching today thank you for
hanging out with me as always i really really really
appreciate it yeah thank you for that 20 gifted thank you
thank you so much thank you mint oh thank you guys for
always hanging out with me this is fun peasants quest was so
silly and uh it was it was a good time yeah i don't know i
feel so awkward all this at it i don't know why why do i
feel so awkward i'm just gonna i'm just gonna go like this
way i'll see you guys um when i see when i see Maybe I'll go
this way.
Or this way.
This way.
I'm gonna.
Okay.
You guys can see ourselves out, right?
Good luck with your recording tomorrow.
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you.
Thanks for the super chat.
Conqueror.
Actually, I am gonna go.
Okay, wait.
You guys decide.
Are you gonna go out this way or that way?
Are you gonna go out?
Well.
Let's just say it's to the left or to the right.
Which way are you going?
Oh.
Up?
No, you can't go up.
What are you living?
The rafters?
That's where the rats live.
That's my grandma.
Through the window.
Just show us the door.
No!
I'm gonna go this way.
I changed my mind.
wait someone someone said someone said right okay hold on
I'm going this way then I'm going to the left okay okay
don't follow me you guys said to the right so I'm gonna go
to the left okay can't follow me how do I get out I'm stuck
here now that's how I became a ghost so not really wouldn't
that be crazy If you also got stuck in a maid cafe and then
became a ghost
Yeah, they're gone Uh-huh No, I told them to go to the right
Because, you know, that's the way to the fire pit They'll
never know No, no, no, I covered it really well They'll
just, whoop, fall right in, you know Yes Yes Yes?
No.
No, I forgot.
No, I forgot the... No, well, it's not that I forgot the
piranhas, it's that they just didn't do very well in the
fire.
You know what I mean?
It's, you know.
Okay, I will put in an order for robotic piranhas next time.
I'm very sorry.
Mm-hmm.
No, they should be...
I'm listening.
I'm going to hear their screams.
Any second now.
Hold on.
Oh.
One second.
You guys, you didn't go to the right.
Come on.
Okay, I'll lead you to the exit.
I'll lead you to the exit.
Okay, come on, come on, come on.
Why are you screaming?
Come on, no, no.
No need to scream right now.
Come on.
This way.
Yep.
Just keep going straight.
Okay, well, okay, bye!
Okay, they're walking there now.
Yes, I told them to...
Oh, actually, don't forget to go through the third door.
That's the correct one.
The one all the way on the right, the third door.
I told them to go through.
the third door even though the exit is actually through the
first door yes the second door the second door doesn't lead
to anything it leads to like it's like a wily coyote it's
you know it's just a painted road but the third one leads to
the fire pit that they are about to fall in second now yeah
I'm gonna hear their screams on listening I'm listening oh
by the way mr.
president you're gonna want to go through door number one
yes yes door Door number one, Mr. President.
Otsuminto!
Bye bye!
Thank you for watching and hanging out with me.
See you later.
Don't be a stranger.
Bye bye!
Otsuminto!