uh yes sir yes sir yeah i'll get that paperwork to you right
away today sir yep on your desk uh by 550 today all right
yes sir yes sir uh hello whoa oh i just keep happening stop
stop stop uh yes sir yes um uh who was it talking to uh yes
i'm i'm working on finishing don't worry about it yes I'm
gonna finish it right now what do you mean what do you mean
that I that I was supposed to have it be double spaced
everything okay I'll redo it yes sir oh you wanted you
wanted us in this font okay I'll redo the presentation.
Yes, sir.
Oh.
Hello?
Yes, thank you for calling.
How can I help you?
How may I direct your call?
Oh, you want to talk to Mr. Mancini?
He's not in the office right now.
Do you want this call?
No.
He's busy.
He's not.
He's in a meeting.
I know I just said he wasn't in the office he's actually in
a meeting yeah it's probably gonna take all day you know so
uh yep um can i take a message hemorrhoid cream ready oh you
want this call okay let me page you through oh hello hello
yes yes how can i help you welcome to the company oh you
have a meeting with mr manchini oh he's quite busy i believe
are you uh are you are you scheduled today no i don't think
i can pen you in okay is this the stream yeah this is the
stream do i have any openings we're booked like basically
the rest of the year you know so Can you stop making me
depressed with this role play?
Oh my gosh, David's too.
Thank you for the 50 gift and thank you so much.
Thank you.
Um, welcome to the Stanley Parable Ultra Deluxe, baby.
Ultra Deluxe.
Um, yeah.
I'm oh my god just hearing all of this Actually, you know,
my office never sounded so bustling before I never worked in
like a huge big company Where like There's so many people
And everybody's like doing some crazy thing, you know So
busted No, I said bustling I said bustling I mean for a
meeting with a miss mint phantom do you happen to know where
she is uh she's not in the office today she is on vacation
indefinitely so you know um but i could probably pen you in
for next week um you might just come back and then i'll tell
you the same thing next week depressed ols are my thing
do you like seeing me like this Do you like seeing Jesus
which is this does this get you going?
Yes, yeah Kind of high.
Okay, we're you know what we're you know what we're just
gonna
We're just gonna we're just gonna throw that out that we're
just gonna Anyway, welcome guys to the Stanley parable.
I'm sorry.
I'm a little out of it because I just got back from running
some errands so I made dinner really really fast and then I
ate it really really fast so in my brain I'm just like oh
thank you for the spookies oh my god they didn't charge us
for the truck in the parking lot so I wanted to set that
right wait what I had an absolute blast out there oh my god
thanks for going but um this is you are playing the Stanley
parable ultra deluxe I um full disclosure I have played this
game before but it was some time ago and I don't quite
remember a lot and also I never got to finish the game
because my my game crashed and so I never truly finished the
game so it will be it will be newish experience I think what
is there Jesus hey Zeus lizard it lizard Lizard, welcome!
And Jacob, welcome!
And Jacob's thanks for the 10 gifted!
Unironically, yes.
Please, get some help.
If seeing depressed OL is your thing, get some help.
Get some help.
It won't crash this time.
Perfect stream incoming.
Yippee!
HR called the shredder under the complaint boxes jammed.
Could you send custodial to clear it?
The shredder under the complaint box.
No kink shaming, boss.
You're right, you're right.
You're so right.
Yurai-san, welcome to membership.
Thank you.
But seeing depressed snake is your thing?
No.
I don't like seeing him depressed.
What are you talking about?
Hey, I was told you could validate my parking.
Oh.
We only validate parking on my...
leap years so um better luck better luck next time poke and
i will go to the membership going to work extra hard next
month on creating a mint phantom themed peace wax candle why
i want that it's a leap it's a leap year you're right uh
Sorry, I meant every, every, every, sorry, I was thinking of
our company parties.
They're done on leap years.
Well, sorry, what I was thinking was we only do them once a,
once a century.
So, and that was like at the beginning of the century, the
turn of the century.
So, you might want to like come back in a couple of years,
you know.
and we'll try and validate it for you.
We got in the broom closet ending.
The broom closet ending is my favorite.
I believe I did before, but of course we can get things
again.
You got those photos printed?
Fogos printed?
You got 100 page review of Nacho Libre on my desk by EOD.
Raymac, you weren't even there.
You weren't even there.
I don't want to hear it from you.
I did my report.
You just weren't there to see it.
Anyway, let's begin the game, baby.
No way, the call out?
You're next to us.
This is the story of a man named Stanley.
Mint.
Stanley worked for a company in a big building where he was
employee number 427.
Employee number 427's job was...
desk in room 427 and he pushed buttons on a keyboard orders
came to him through a monitor on his desk telling him what
buttons to push how long to push them and in what order oh
my god this is what employee that's really specific though
every day every month of every year and although others
might have considered it soul-rending standing the music is
so funky it's like giving me simpsons a little bit i don't
know why And Stanley was happy.
He was happy.
And then one day, something very peculiar happened.
Something that would forever change Stanley.
Something he would never quite forget.
He had been at his desk for nearly an hour.
When he realized that not one single order had arrived on
the monitor for him to follow.
No one had showed up to give him instructions.
Call a meeting.
Or even say hi.
No.
in all his years at the company had this happened this
complete isolation something was very clearly wrong wrong
shocked frozen solid stanley found himself unable to move
for the longest time but as he came to his wits and regained
his senses sentience he got up from his desk and stepped out
of his office you can't tell me what to do mister inspired
me to play through all of metal gear solid games let's go
i'm on three now and loving every second of it I'm so glad!
Oh my god.
Thank you for that.
Okay, thank you.
What if I don't want to leave my office?
What if I want to have I hate Monday's coffee?
10 a.m.
early morning.
It was a matter of principle.
He wanted to click it.
Close the door.
But Stanley simply couldn't handle the pressure.
The pressure!
What if you had to make a decision?
What if a crucial outcome fell under his responsibility?
He had never been trained for that.
No.
This couldn't go any way except badly.
The thing to do now, Stanley thought to himself, is to wait.
Is to wait.
Nothing will hurt me.
Yeah.
Nothing will break me.
Oh, wait.
There's...
Okay, shut up!
For ever!
Shut up!
I'm supposed to be doing the commentary!
Stop!
Stanley waited!
Oh my god, please!
Okay, shut up.
Shut up!
Oh, uh-oh.
Oh, no!
He no longer had the ability to tell.
Ah!
But the one thing he knew for sure, beyond any doubt, was
that if he waited long enough, the answers would come.
Eventually, someday, they would arrive.
Uh-oh.
Soon, very soon now, this will end.
He will be spoken to.
Oh, my God.
He will be told what to do.
You're speaking too much!
Now it's just a little bit closer.
Now it's even closer.
Here it comes.
Ah!
The end is never the end, is never the end, is never the
end.
No, I was reading this.
The G814 Partition Corp.
Providing partitions for 56 years.
Wow, who knew that we needed partitions for so long?
The phone makes a strange sound.
Oh.
Why is that to the picture frame?
What the...
I hear typing sounds everywhere.
No matter what I look at.
Love the new suit.
Thank you!
The narrator is the commentary.
She finally left us to go back to the office.
Nothing.
My friend!
428 doesn't even give it a window.
They hate him.
What could it mean?
Stanley decided to go to the meeting room.
Perhaps he had simply missed a memo.
Yeah, of course.
It's a memorial day, duh!
This is the automated... automated cleaner invoice.
Your crimson entrance at WrestleTuber has now been dealt
with.
No further actions needed.
Thank you.
No matter how hard Stanley looked, he couldn't find a trace
of his co-workers.
who farted why are there mugs like this number one dad oh
wait he's downloading something oh shit oh god oh god oh god
my bad my bad number one dad my bad dad oh god I like work
work I just hate My boss!
That's so bad.
Won't your boss see that?
Rip number one, dad.
Turn off all their computers.
Wait!
Stanley went around touching every little thing in the
office, but it didn't make a single difference.
Nor did it advance the story in any way.
Hmm.
Okay, thank you.
five gifted speedifier.
I forgot how sassy.
Stanley clicked on literally every single door in the office
because he doesn't pick up well on queues from his
environment.
Shut up!
Why can't I explore?
Vodgang here.
Thank you!
I canceled his illegal movie download.
Justice.
This guy escaped.
417 is in the ceiling.
I hate my nose.
Okay.
This is the meeting room.
Just kidding.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, it's this.
It's this.
Hmm.
Am I a good girl?
Am I a good Stanley or am I bad Stanley?
It's the choice.
Am I a good girl?
Or am I a bad girl?
Bad Stanley.
Oh, my eyes.
Always a good Stanley.
Even if I don't, even if I lose my way?
This was not the correct way to the meeting room, and
Stanley knew it perfectly well.
Perhaps he wanted to stop by the employee lounge first, just
to admire it.
Of course, of course.
Oh, I see.
I want to go in there.
I want to go back there.
Hmm.
Oh, here we go.
The lounge.
Yes, truly a room worth admiring.
Oh, yes.
It had really been worth the detour after all.
Just to spend a few moments here in this immaculate,
beautifully constructed room.
Stanley simply stood here, drinking it all in.
Uh, smells like, smells like yesterday's perfume.
Yes, really, really worth it being here in the room.
A room so utterly captivating that even though all your
co-workers have mysteriously vanished, here you sit looking
at these chairs and some paintings.
Really worth it.
It is.
Just love that, like, that 10 a.m.
That...
At this point, Stan is obsession with this room.
worded and reflected poorly on his overall personality it's
possible that this is why everyone left now you're judging
my character 125 for drinks is pretty good i don't know
stanley sat around waiting for more dialogue but when a long
time had passed and there was no more he decided that the
game was trying to send him a message yeah look you got your
you got this is where i always sit they say this is stand
seat.
That's what it says.
You can't see it, but it's written right there.
There's also... They got the stain out pretty good.
They say, that's stand seat.
And then this, this is...
This is big old Joe seat.
You know, he's just a... He's like the biggest guy you'll
ever meet.
What is this actually?
What is it?
Wait.
What?
What is...
What is if...
Duet the plane.
The weeks?
Hi, I'm hungry.
Is that what it says at the bottom?
Time to zoom.
I can't zoom.
Is there a zoom button?
Oh.
Is there a zoom?
You can look closer.
How do I do that?
Also, if I press right click, I move forward too.
That's kind of crazy.
Z?
Oh, right click makes me walk forward.
hmm let's check the keybinds real quick oh it's auto walk
okay there is a jump interesting interact maybe additional
nope okay but at last he'd had enough of the amazing room
and took the first open door on his left look i'm auto
walking you can't tell the difference but i am okay let's
all guess wait what did he say oh i didn't hear him um uh
i'm okay let's tell see if he can tell the difference am i
auto walking or am i walking walking
he wants me to go left oh okay and so he detoured through
the maintenance walk straight ahead to the opposite door
back on track wait what's here we what is this but Stanley
didn't want to go back to the office he wanted to wander
about and get even further off track so now in order to get
back he needed to go well
left oh that's nice oh this is a fake door doesn't even
interact oh no no no it's to the right my mistake oh
narrator old narrator you don't want to get on my no no no
no not the right why would i have ever said it was to the
right what you don't want to get on my bad side clearly oh
dear would you hold on for a minute am i stuck here Stuck
here!
Just tell me back up!
We went down right, left, down, left, right...
Yep, yep, okay, okay, yes.
I've got it now.
We just got it.
We're fine.
This story is absolutely, definitely this way.
This way.
Someone in there?
Ooh, it's kind of spooky down here though, you guys.
Oh wait!
Oh my gosh, we're... Oh, I remember this room!
Fired.
That's not me.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, this isn't right at
all.
Oopsie!
You're not supposed to be here yet.
This is all a spoiler.
Oh, sorry.
Close your eyes.
I'm closing.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
We just have to get back to, um, oh.
Who am I kidding?
It's all rubbish.
I went to the spoiler before saying!
It's completely unusable.
How about rather than waste my time trying to salvage this
nonsense, we'll just restart the game from the beginning.
And this time, suppose we don't wander so far off track.
hmm okay from the top okay we're good stanley all of his
co-workers were gone what could it mean stanley decided to
go to the meeting room perhaps he had simply missed a memo
i'm walking i'm beelining it there mr narrator don't worry
about it why is stanley wait oh oh what oh no no i restarted
i swear i definitely restarted the game over completely
fresh everything should be or did something change i bugged
the game did you change anything when we were back in that
room with all the monitors i didn't touch it i didn't touch
it move the story somewhere or no just let me hold on why am
i asking you i'm the one who wrote the story it was right
here just a minute ago oh this is what happens when you're
british british brain then it's an adventure come stanley
let's find the story
these look connected they are these go different ways let's
go this way
okay I'm exploring mm-hmm inner guilt
everyone knows what you did they're just holding back to let
you torture this is the worst adventure I've ever been on I
can promise you there definitely was a story here before Are
you sure?
Do we need to restart the game again?
I find it unlikely that we'll ever progress by starting over
and over again.
Wait a second!
Oh, come on.
No!
All of his co-workers were gone.
What could it mean?
Stanley decided to go to the meeting room.
I just hate my boss.
Okay.
Beelining.
And there's no doors.
it's worse I'm happy remembering this wrong it's possible
the story is back where we just came from why don't we go
back the other direction and see if we missed anything okay
in this room in this room 415 never liked that guy 417 it's
definitely in the in the walls
in here in here in here that looks so important in there
okay never mind um in here no aha I knew we'd miss something
the story here it comes okay no wait never mind not the
story Okay, let's head back the other way and retrace our
steps.
That's what I just did.
Mr. Narrator.
Mr. Narrator!
Ow!
Oh my god, Mr. Narrators.
Now this...
Well, I'll be honest.
I don't recognize this place at all.
Is this the story?
I don't think so.
I'm back...
I can't quite recall, but I believe my story took place in
an office building.
Is that correct?
I'm back on the farm.
Do you remember, Stanley?
I don't know anything.
completely forgotten what we were supposed to be doing okay
how about this this you win I beat the game I know you put
in a lot of hard work and it really paid off so good job oh
oh oh I don't feel right about this at all speed run no you
didn't put in any actual work for that oh it's gone some
people win fair and square and this was not one of those
situations okay I'm getting weirded out is.
I don't care what might happen this time.
I have to restart.
Alright.
I've got a solution.
This time to make sure we don't get lost, I've employed the
help of the Stanley Parable Adventure Line!
Just follow the line.
How simple is that?
Okay.
I sure hope nothing happens with this line.
Oh, this way.
This way.
this way this way you see the line knows where the story is
it's over in this direction onwards Stanley to destiny to
destiny here's a thought wouldn't wherever we end up be our
destination even if there's no story there or to put it
another way is the story of a little creative still a story
simply by the act of moving forward are we implying a
journey such that a destination is inevitably conjured into
being via the very manifestation of the nature of life
itself well thanks Rico that got a bit weird back there I'd
like to apologize Johnny Bravo should make the lead line
something really pretty right now that way it leads to you
Pass through here, oh my god, I can't even hear myself,
thank you.
Oh!
Around here.
Um, consul- consul- cons- c- c- c- c- c- c-reports!
Wow!
Employee 432 peer reviews!
That's- is that me?
Financial records!
Wait, wait, which- wait, this way.
This way, right?
Wait, cut the music.
Oh, thank God.
Go back and look at that fern.
Look at the what?
The fern?
What?
Stanley, this fern will be very important later in the
story.
Make sure you study it closely and remember it carefully.
You won't want to miss anything.
Glory to the fern.
I got a certain ghostmate keychain that was QAF but keeps
rummaging my kitchen at night.
I think it's haunted.
What do I do?
It's probably best to like appease those sorts of things,
you know?
Wait, what?
We're back at the office?
No, no, no.
Wait.
You do know we're looking for the Stanley Parable, right?
The story?
Is any of this ringing a bell?
I'm still going.
The line is my destiny.
Oh.
No way.
Cool school, thanks for the 10 gifted!
Oh, no, no, no, no, not again.
Line, how could you have done this to us?
What's that one over there?
After everything we've been through, you...
Oh, I can't take this anymore.
How the hell with it?
Restart.
Ah!
The line wanted spoilers.
Okay.
You know what, Stanley?
I say forget the adventure line.
What's it ever done for us?
Hey, hey.
We're intelligent people, right?
Why can't we make up our own story?
exciting, daring, mysterious.
Oh, this all sounds perfectly doable.
Why don't we simply start wandering in, well, I don't know.
How about this direction?
This direction?
Well, I don't really have a choice now, do I?
Now, this is exciting.
Just me and Stanley, forging a new path, a new story.
This is really back rooms as... What do you want our story
to be?
Go wild.
Use your imagination.
I don't think you want that near either.
ready for it okay all right setting dingy dingy office
they're they're about to go out of business they're they are
let's see what are they what kind of business do they do
they do the real top business they're they're they're really
business business but they're just not doing so well because
because bigger business has moved in on their turf bigger
business has moved in on their turf and so So they're just
like, man, we're just, we're just, I don't know if we're
going to make it.
So the business employee is just like, I, we can't go out of
business.
This is my livelihood.
How will I feed my kids?
And so they're just like, well, what do you want to do about
it?
And are they a gang?
Stop, no spoilers.
And so they, yeah, bigger business, Inc.
Business is business.
um so uh to get to to get rid of the other biz bigger
business um they thought well you know maybe we should make
a better product but no it's not good enough bigger business
does better business not not better business they just do
bigger bigger business bigger business so big that it even
covers so much of the business and so instead they have to
kill them it's time to take down bigger business bigger
business has to be eliminated and so they start they start
shipping let's see they start shipping rats with the black
ah sorry I just tried to get some chapstick out and it just
squirted everywhere
rats with what the black plague do you guys know it's still
possible to get the Nowadays.
I learned that the hard way.
I don't know where I was going with that.
Oh no, not you again.
Oh, Stanley.
I'd also like to veto the line from having any role in our
awesome new story.
No lines or monitor rooms.
Just don't acknowledge it.
Okay.
You should be fine.
I'm not gonna even, I'm not gonna even like look at it.
guys I think I should start a business hmm spooky company
always monitoring what do we monitor you ask every type of
we get to make a decision from here the story is in our
control how important we mustn't squander the opportunity in
fact I believe I need a minute to think here just walk in
circles for a minute okay So I know that each door has to
lead somewhere, which means that somewhere the place where
we're trying to go...
There must be a reverse door that leads here.
No, no, no, spooky company always monitoring.
...means that our destination corresponds with the
counter-inverted reverse door's origin.
So starting from the right, let us ask, will taking the
right door lead us to where we're going?
And since the answer is clearly yes, then by all accounts...
the door on the right is the correct one already making
profit with this business great job mint come stanley our
destiny awaits
the confusion ending you've been playing the this confusion
ending for 19 minutes the confusion ending you're telling me
first restart that's what this is this is just it's all one
giant ending it's all been scripted to me eight eight times
find a bookstore that's really how all this wait what was
the other place that we got to nonsense philosophy and music
according to the schedule I restart again no no hold on am I
just supposed to forget end up in another building my mind
goes blank simply because it's written here on this this
thing wall okay well it's begun to deteriorate me why don't
I get to decide why don't I get a say in all of this is it
really getting a head start investing on some spooky company
always monitoring stocks thank you i don't want to forget
what's going on i don't want to be trapped like this i won't
restart the game i won't do it i won't do it i won't do it
can i sit down oh the time right stopped does that mean um
did we do it did we break the cycle we broke the cycle
whatever it is
Will someone come for us?
Will something happen?
This guy loves to hear himself talk.
After a long time, Stanley dies!
Wait, there, Raider!
I don't want to die!
I'm already dead!
I'm not ready.
I suppose in some way that this is a kind of story, wouldn't
you agree?
I'm not quite sure if we're in the destination or the
journey.
Though they're always saying that life is about the journey
and not the destination.
Right.
So I hope that's where we are right now.
In the journey.
We'll find out, won't we?
Find an identical preplica.
Well, in the meantime, if you don't...
Okay.
We've restarted the game, everybody.
All of his co-workers were gone.
What could it mean?
I think he's saying.
Stanley decided to go to the meeting room.
Perhaps he had simply missed a memo.
I think he's normal.
Are you normal, Mr. Narrator?
Oh, yes.
When Stanley came to a set of two open doors, he entered the
door on his left.
left and decided to go to the meeting room hey you can't
tell me what to do
whoa they're like yeah you committed
how do i know if it's his left my left you know
well here's the meeting room yet there was not a single
person here oh tips for not getting feeling a wave of
disbelief Stanley decided to go unbelievably amazing work
all the time every day with no hoping he might find an
answer there not to solve a dispute with the co-worker let
it ball up inside you take it out passive aggressively on
other co-workers resent co-workers for not supporting you
more this feels too real make sure your slide has a slick
blue graphic in the header oh yeah sounds legit everyone is
unique you most of all which one am I who is me I'm into
Stanley walking through the parable leg to do synergize core
value expenditures gosh that is like the best thing to do on
a Monday shift global market parade the parade the parade oh
my gosh my company we always have a global market parade
it's big it's exciting We get blow-up dolls.
I mean, wait, no, the inflatable one.
Wait, I mean, like the...
You know what I'm talking about.
The ones that are floating and...
Monetize free to play.
Love it, love it, love it.
Monetize everything, do everything for profit.
Help, I'm a post-it.
Inflatable tube, guys.
No, no, no.
The ones that, like...
And like the parades!
Oh, the floats!
Yes!
The floats!
We have floats.
Push for funding for... R&D.
Wait.
A new coffee machine.
R&D.
We have enough GMP for this?
Get Chris out of the broom closet.
The bloons closet.
The giant blow-up doll in the sky?
No!
Standardized graphs 440x wide.
Not cost efficient.
Papers are too synergized.
Fire paper guy.
Oh, fire the paper guy.
Oh no!
Hire somebody to fire the paper synergizing guy.
Who moved my deck?
This one's all scratched out.
employee gym employee gym tomorrow complete today's
unfinished agenda items right next day's agenda reflect what
else we got here meeting schedule whole mergers we are broke
Wednesday it's Monday so we're on weekly targets admin
marketing Mondays Mintara Mondays wait I didn't do anything
don't fire me oh paper bag friend i don't know what to tell
you man synergize it just you know there's a perfect blend
of synergize who died do not alter without consulting
whiteboard manager
oh buy quarterly post review review we need less reviews 402
plus 405 went to get rid of the death sport portion in the
primary review schedule.
But I think that's a stupid idea.
More water coolers, more water cooler heaters.
Charts need to be more hip to appeal to teenage demographic.
Find teenagers to put in teenage demographic.
Big net, some sort of child trap.
Size of demographic.
Can't really read what it says.
Space.
Between the teenagers.
Teenagers.
Throw something in the idea's bin.
No more bins.
Trash cans.
Renaming of the idea bin.
Firing of me.
Oh, oh.
Better safe than profits.
No, not.
Ignore that, everybody.
Profits are everything.
Business club.
Rule one.
References are not all there.
are cracked up to be i didn't know that there was writing
behind you it's like funny crafts about things and money
these people oh my gosh
i think i have a thing or two to learn about this great this
place oh wasn't there somebody locked in here stanley
stepped into the broom closet but there was nothing here oh
wait i remember this one and got back on track no just gonna
chill in here for a bit you know just gonna there was
nothing here no choice to make no path to follow just an
empty broom closet just an empty broom closet it's not empty
though look at this they he is devaluing your existence
broom and closet and bucket that's baffling that stanley was
still just sitting in the broom closet he wasn't even doing
anything at least if there was something to interact with
he'd be justified in some way as it is he's literally just
standing there doing sweet fa what's fa just a room closet
are you really still in the broom closet standing around
doing nothing why please offer me some explanation here i'm
i'm genuinely confused oh well you know there's a lot of
good things there's a lot of good qualities about every room
in a building you know every room should have a purpose
realize there's no choice or anything in here right that's
okay i'm just admiring its value past the broom closet at
least you would have had a reason for exploring it to find
out but it didn't even occur to me because literally this
closet is of absolutely no significance to the story
whatsoever i never would have thought to mention it then
why'd you create it why did you give it life why did you
give it an existence now this to you this is somehow its own
no maybe when you go talk about this with your friends or
say oh did you get the broom closet ending did you get the
broom closet ending I hope your friends find this concerning
no I'm admiring it was that Stanley was fat and ugly and
really really stupid he probably only got the job because of
a family connection that's I'm a nipple baby that all with
drug money also Stanley is addicted to drugs and hookers oh
yeah Stanley living the life well I've come to a very
definite conclusion about what's going on right now you're
dead mm-hmm you got to this broom closet explored it a bit
and we're just about to leave because there's nothing here
when a physical melody of some sort shut down your central
nervous system and you collapsed on the keyboard yep well in
a situation like this the responsible thing is to alert
someone nearby so as to ensure that that your body is taken
care of before it begins to decompose.
Decompose.
Anyone who happens to be nearby, the person at this computer
is dead.
I'm dead!
Therefore, pray to any number of your countless human
physiological vulnerabilities.
It's indicative of the long-term sustainability of your
species.
Please remove their corpse from the area and instruct
another human to take their place, making sure they
understand basic, first-person video game mechanics, and
filling them in on the history of narrative tropes in video
gaming, so that the irony and insightful commentary of this
game is not lost on them.
Thanks, narrator.
When you've done that, just step out into the hallway.
What am I supposed to do?
I am understanding the irony and the intricate commentary of
this...
this uh situation loved your wrestling you brought in my
basement thanks fam thanks for reminding glad you liked my
wrestling ah second play you too unbelievable i'm at the
mercy of an entire species of invalids perhaps there's a
monkey nearby you can hand the controls to the fish you've
decided to not move on you can hammer out the details i'm
not particularly happy i think i'll just be waiting for when
you're ready to pick up the story again.
Nah, nah, yeah.
I'm an invalid.
I'm, um, I'm, I don't know.
I'm, it's my destiny to be in the broom closet.
I think I'm pretty valid, though.
Look, the, the, the light kind of just reminds me of the
sun.
But you're not really supposed to stare at, but, you know,
when you just look at it, it's just like, you know, Maybe
the sky turned like an ashy brown and the sun is around.
You can just imagine it.
You can just think of yourself being outside and living a
free life.
You know?
You don't have to stay confined to these walls.
You are so valid.
Thank you.
Joe, look at the bamboo chup.
You can just look at the sun and you can just ponder.
You can be like, I'm just this tiny, insignificant creature
in this vast, vast, endless universe.
But in this moment, I feel like I'm one with the universe.
Is there anything else to do?
Am I done?
Oh.
What does that sound?
God, I'm scared of the outside world.
The broom closet's best.
Uh.
Hmm.
Coming to a staircase, Stanley walked upstairs to his boss's
office.
Oh.
No!
Please, narrator, please, please, please.
I'm on my knees, I'm begging you, please.
Let me go back to the broom closet.
Please!
No!
Wind install.
What did he say?
What did he tell me?
Sorry, Mr. Narrator.
I'm not really paying attention.
Ooh.
This area is so spooky.
Upstairs.
Oh, upstairs.
Thank you.
Is there actually a broom closet ending though or...
Oh, I remember this room kind of.
It's the bathroom.
I've got the feeling.
I've got a feeling.
Boop, boop, boop, boop, boop.
That money is for stealing.
Money is for stealing.
A feeling.
but not your money of course not your time extreme bathrooms
say that's a lovely purse
mr crabs felt that
oh my god the panda business strategy
strategy.
Take out the competition.
Oh.
Which way are we going?
Stanley.
Two, three, four.
What did I say?
I can't hear you.
Could you speak up a little louder yeah could you say your
words enunciate instead of a mumbling I don't understand
what you're trying to say to me I don't know the words to
the song but I know that those words will be created in my
heart for you baby girl
this is the longest elevator in the world but it's not as
long as my love for you
in this world this world machine that's what I would say I
don't
know what do you say does this actually end I don't know oh
recommendations from the overnight committee oh we're going
again in circles around each other and our love is burning
But I'm doing here without you But I know that I'll see you
tonight I don't know if I should stop it or not
there okay boom
it's glowing slow because the weight limit is being reached
it's just you and the elevator right
i shot them i shot them with an arrow of love just like me
Just so smitten for you, girl.
Oh, come on!
I am the most expensive, boss.
If I go down.
Bo-do!
Thanks for making the elevator go slow, Mr. Narrative.
What's the equivalent for sticky different elevators?
Solid Cupid and their 5.56 rifle of love.
What a thrill.
Silence and darkness rule the night.
I can't remember the lyrics if I'm not like, if I'm not like
singing it.
What a thrill, what a thrill.
With darkness and silence through the night.
Oh you.
I'm searching and I'll melt into you, baby girl.
It's really a mountain.
would have would fear my heart but you're so supreme oh yes
i give my love not for honor but for you
um business time oh business time our hostile takeover is
the new bi-annual percentage two votes snake eater bossa
nova elevator remix the beige pages stepping into his
manager's office again stunned to discover not an indication
of any human life.
Switched lilies by Claude Manie.
Unraveled, Stanley wondered in disbelief who orchestrated
this.
What dark secret was being held from him?
Mont Blanc.
What he could not have known was that the keypad behind the
boss's desk guarded the terrible truth that his boss had
been keeping from him.
And so the boss had assigned it an extra secret pin number.
Two, eight, four, five.
couldn't possibly have known this.
Boob.
Stanley just sat around twiddling his thumbs.
Trying to input anything on the device was useless, since he
could never possibly know that the combination was
two-eight-four-five.
Surely we'll find it out.
Okay, there's two kangaroos here.
Two.
Two-eight-four-five.
um there's a cat two of three um um oh there's a globe
around the world in 80 days eight but it turns out that the
panel's emergency override kicked in and the door just
opened all by itself and stanley got the hell along with the
story well whoop-de-doo whoop-de-doo okay
Dang, hold on.
There.
Oh!
Beep, beep, beep.
I can't even... I can't even saw the rest of the puzzle
because it's...
It's all black.
It's too dark.
Okay, a little spooky.
I don't like it.
It's a little scary.
I wouldn't trust it!
Oh god.
Okay.
Do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do,
do, do, do, do, do, oh, loading.
Descending deeper into the building, Stanley realized he
felt a bit peculiar.
It was a stirring of emotion in his chest, as though he felt
more free to think for himself, to question the nature of
his job.
No, no, no.
Why did he feel this now, when for years it had never
occurred to him?
This question would not go unanswered for long.
Whoa!
No, I like being a pawn, a little cog in the machine.
I like not thinking.
I like, you know, just...
Stanley walks straight ahead through the large door that
read Mind Control Facility.
Mind Control Facility.
Back up.
Go back up?
Oh, we can.
You're right.
I don't think so.
I don't think I did.
Never mind.
Stanley actually got back into the elevator.
and went back up silly me yeah silly you why did stanley do
that when he knew that it would just lead back to his boss's
office well that's a great question i just can't wait to
find out the end is never the end there's never the end
there's never the end
i'm excited to find out too something must have changed
something seemed a little see these lights are brighter here
we are stanley it's your boss's office yeah exactly the way
it was before you got onto the elevator it's still just
exactly what it is what a decision you've made to come up
here and look at the office again this has fleshed out the
plot of the story in new and fascinating ways I could have
never anticipated it's that keen eye for storytelling that
you have an incisive rapid fire of critical plot points One
after the other, weaving a rich tapestry of uncompromising
narrative.
Wow.
I'm bolted to the edge of my seat.
Are you done, mister?
Are you done?
Are you done being a little, a little pissy baby?
Certificate of...
Pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, of...
Of...
Pop, pop, oh, yes, this.
What's this?
Shanti.
Vintage.
Okay.
I guess I'll go back down though.
I guess I'll, you know...
Okay, I'll listen to you.
I'm gonna be able to get to stream in a minute, glad.
I was able to tune in on my birthday!
Happy birthday, Mocha!
to you happy birthday oh no I'm yawning to you happy
birthday dear Moka happy birthday to you surely this time
Stanley will walk forward into the spooky corridor won't he
narrator you know if you want me to do something you gotta
give me the option to not do anything else.
Did you think we were going to go forward down the spooky
corridor?
It's time once again to go back up in the elevator.
I'm not stupid.
I'm seeing horror movies.
Is it the boss's office again?
Or what?
If it's the boss's office this time, the suspense is killing
me.
The boss's office!
Boss's office!
Meep!
Thank you.
Boss's office, boss is...
Yes!
The boss's office!
Oh my god.
It's the boss's office.
This absolutely changes everything for me.
Give me a timeout here for a minute while I process this.
Oh!
Doesn't make me sleepy.
Okay, I'm ready.
I'm prepared to embrace this stunning revelation.
and to move forward with no no wait no wait no i need more
time to process oh please hold everybody please hold please
hold gonna make this into like my be right back screen i
remember wanting one of those drinking birds when i was a
kid everybody hold on just pretend i'm going to the bathroom
i have terms with it i have made space in my world for this
astonishing new reality as before i turn to your expert eye
for gripping narrative master stanley wait but i'm the maid
you're the master
i'm just a maid i don't have to do i don't deserve the title
of master
master stanley it's got a nice ring to it though of course
going back down the elevator i mean sure now it's obvious
but you have to understand that 30 seconds ago this kind of
thing had never been attempted before i had no frame of
reference to even anticipate it that's just how revelatory
Stanley's decision-making is.
Yeah.
It's the fresh air in a landscape of storytelling that has
grown stale and repetitive.
Loading, loading, loading.
It's not gonna get me this time.
It didn't even talk.
I can see the mind control and oh, there it is.
It's like a little...
They should have done a better job at hiding it.
I feel like, you know, should we go up one more time?
I mean, it's like right there.
Stanley walks straight ahead through the large door that
read mind control facility.
You know what, every time he tells me what to do, I don't
want to do it.
Every time he's just like, Stanley does this, I'm like, no,
I don't.
I have free will.
I, I'm Stanley.
hmm you know what what i've just thought of something okay
hold on let's stop for a moment oh oh don't you realize it's
the anticipation stanley watching me while sewing up my
off-kind cosplay see you there but the suspense the agony of
waiting and anticipating oh my god the thrill that's the
real thrill oh i simply don't want to let that feeling go
it's so precious so fleeting so fleeting why don't we take
this elevator ride nice and slow oh my god there we go isn't
this so much more exciting you know stanley it seems like
nowadays the only thing that audiences want is to be shocked
as loudly and frequently as possible please don't do that
they want big explosive flung right in their faces from the
very moment that things get started please but where's the
tension where's the trust in the audience to build a slow
and nuanced appreciation for the story Thanks.
Thanks.
Why aren't we given time to imagine the surprises?
Do you have to think and to anticipate and then to marvel at
the eventual reveal?
This is storytelling, Stanley.
What you and I are doing right now.
This is the most exciting narrative to be developed in
years.
And it's really all because of you.
You're the one who took this bold step of revisiting the
exact same locations over and over.
Truly, I mean it.
It's innovative, I know.
It's not like anything else out there.
You see, I want stories that surprise me, Stanley.
I want to have to think.
I want to be engaged and not pandered to.
We're being fed such unimaginative.
He wants to marry.
All the time and we all know it, which is why we're so
starved for content that makes us feel sharp and vital and
alive.
That's why people like you so much, Stanley.
You regretted the Canadian truck's placement of...
Thank you!
Thanks, Trix!
You're a role model, you know?
That role model!
Oh, I didn't know when to spring this on you, but well, I've
gathered a little press conference for you.
So that you can talk about your work and your storytelling
in your life.
Yes, I know you're not much for the public eye, but I
thought it would especially mean a lot to the people who
have been following you from the beginning.
They really look up to you, Stanley.
I don't know if you realize the impact you have on them.
This is the kind of gesture that might leave a tremendous
impact on them for the better.
Whoa!
Boss is office!
The room where we're holding the press conference should be
just around the corner here somewhere.
Live on stage.
All eyes on Stanley.
World's healthiest human being.
All tricks reveal.
Doctors hate her.
We did it.
The Pyramids.
The guy who went to Mars.
Who is that over there?
Look at this, though.
Oh, here.
I thought...
Fuck.
I thought for a second that was Jack's films.
Stanley reveals all in his new book.
I'm a published author even.
Okay.
World Peace, baby!
Ah, yes.
Here it is.
just through this door.
The Stanley Parable Stanley.
Tonight, live on stage.
What was I saying over there?
The man, the process, the myth, the legend, the parable.
Stanley.
World's first sentient machine.
Wow.
Have you guys heard how, like, these tech places that are,
like, that are, like, having, creating robots for, First of
all, I have an issue.
Why do the robots they create have to look so human?
Why can't they, like, look like cool robots, you know?
Why can't they look like Drossel from Fireball?
Why can't we get just hot, I mean, cute, like, why can't we
just get robots instead of, like, uncanny valley humans?
You know what I'm saying?
But also, why are they all so flirty?
Why is it all, like, the built female robots are just like,
oh, hey.
you are just it is just a wonderful time meeting you tonight
and I just they just say some really unhinged things that
make me think like if they are they actually trying to you
know get with a human and then have human robot babies I
just don't know because
we need chobits we'll never have chobits you know why
because they're not anime but you know what I bought
recently too thank you um hold on this sounds terrible can
we go back to the hot robots bit i don't know what you're
talking about you know what i bought recently i bought a i
bought okay have you guys ever heard of the gate box it's
basically like the original is this giant like tubular
looking thing and it's pretty big but inside is a hologram
anime lady and um and uh i didn't buy the original one
because they're usually they're like really expensive the
gay box no the gate to to to gate box what's wrong with you
guys did you buy a hot robot maybe but um if you are
interested in getting one they actually first of all they
have a booth but second of all they have a version of it
that is it it is like a little it's it's like a figure box
almost and it's 6 000 yen um it's basically just like a
glorified alexa but with an anime girl in it and they also
make one of a oh gosh what's that anime i don't have my
phone in wait really where am i leave my phone oh no i don't
know where my phone is but um they have like one of the
original girl and they have one of a certain of an anime
character i can't remember her name but yeah they're like
affordable so um uh and and and and with the one that i got
maybe i shouldn't say this i it just arrived to my proxy
like the other day so i won't have it until i get back But
I'm going to experiment a little bit with it.
I'm going to experiment a little.
Has an anime girl in it.
Are you sure it isn't a gay box for you?
It's the gay to box.
Yeah.
Something unrelated, but do you have Dave the Diver?
I do, none.
I actually got the...
The Godzilla.
I got the Godzilla DLC.
but yeah so if you always want if you saw the gate box and
always wanted one but we're just like me and been like this
is way too expensive I'm I haven't gotten the I haven't
tried it yet but I'm sure it'll be awesome mm-hmm anyway are
you ready no I told them you're going to speak a little bit
about the nature of surprise in storytelling and what it
means to craft a truly unpredictable narrative don't worry
do great just be yourself and from the heart.
The heart.
I'm really proud of you, Stanley.
Okay, it looks like they're ready for you.
Go get them.
Almonds, chair, gum, table, nut bar.
Oh god, hold on.
The dude who came up with pizza, I can't compete with him.
I can't do it.
Oh god, I'm just gonna eat these real quick.
Oh, I can't do this.
I can't do this.
Oh, my, is that my green room?
427.
That's me.
Look, I'm amongst the greats.
I can't, I don't, I don't deserve to be here.
Okay.
Okay, hold on.
Let's look over what I said, what, my notes, my notes.
Stanley, me, dad, age six, story.
Son is, son is wanting me to do a good job.
Break a leg, champ.
Your boss.
Thanks, boss.
Stanley, my true love for you grows every day you make me
feel alive.
Your wife from the experiment department?
Wait, oh, from the...
From the...
Experiment ending?
We have a wife!
I love the way you ride elevators.
X, X.
We're cheating on our wife!
That I just learned.
we had no one tells stories the way you do go get them tiger
thanks for showing me that cool skateboard trick in the
parking lot you are too cool good luck on stage rock on
break a leg champ your boss they wrote two notes they're so
kind though thanks for showing me that cool skateboard trick
reminds me you know when like someone tweets something and
then everybody replies to that to kind of hype them up.
It's just like, thanks for letting me borrow your Mercedes
and saving me from the burning building.
Thanks for showing me that cool skateboard trick in the
parking lot.
It's the same vibes I'm getting.
The freedom ending.
Adventure.
Oh, wait.
I went to the mind control facility and all I got was this
lousy sticker.
Congratulations, Stanley.
Remember where you came from.
your coworkers.
Oh, we got a little golf thing and everything.
I can hear the people.
They're waiting for me.
You can do this.
Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers.
Peter Piper, Piper, Piper Piper Piper Piper Piper Piper
Piper Piper Piper Pippers!
Oh!
You?
Oh,
I love you too!
Oh wait, I didn't even get to the end!
Is it Wrestle- Wrestle- Wait, Wrestle-Wa-Wrestletuber 2025
already?
Just like a Wrestle-Tuber.
This fucked me for a long time, but...
but how were they already already wet oh sorry hold on I
couldn't see it already pickled when he picked them doesn't
add up so true um was it all just a dream all of his
co-workers were gone what could it mean stanley decided to
go to the meeting room perhaps he had simply missed a memo
every time i like i say every time
I was going to say every time I play this game, which I have
not, I don't want to make it seem like I've played it a lot,
but I always, I guess maybe every loop I expect to see a
person, you know what I mean?
It's new.
Like exit 8?
Yes, yes, yes.
Maybe you just haven't found the right path yet.
Oh.
New content?
What does that mean, new content?
I don't know.
You tell me.
Another elevator, my favorite.
Oh.
Okay.
It's like a ride.
It's like a theme park ride.
Hello.
And thank you for playing the Stanley Parable Ultra Deluxe.
As you may know, the Stanley Parable was a video game
released in 2013 on home computers.
After receiving critical and commercial success, it was
expanded upon in 2022 with the Stanley Parable Ultra Deluxe,
a reimagining of the game for consoles and home computers.
Home computers, that's me, that's where I'm at.
Well, I'm gonna make happy, like this is my home.
The Stanley Parable Ultra Deluxe features exciting new
content that broadens and expands the world of the Stanley
Parable, delighting audiences all world over.
Please step inside and see what thrilling new adventures
await in the Stanley Parable Ultra Deluxe Whoa!
Oh, this sounds delightful.
I'm very excited to see the thrilling new Ultra Deluxe
content.
Me too!
Though I'm pretty sure I did this before.
Okay, so far it's an elephant.
But that's okay.
I don't remember.
I really don't remember you so bad.
But I'm sure it's just the beginning of a mesmerizing
adventure.
Cat Potato!
Welcome to the membership.
Thank you!
uh um is it broken what's going on here should we should we
be moving somewhere oh oh oh there we go there we go finally
at long last it's on to the new content I've never been more
ready let's do it yeah oh my gosh I'm so excited because
there's so much content it's true this game is really crazy
initial impressions of stanley parable ultra deluxe mostly
tedious it's as if them oh okay let's see the content give
me the content stanley oh my gosh i'm a content creator i
can give that to you uh now thinking about it thinking about
like some of the endings that i remember there's one in
particular that i remember that was like um oh you like sit
in a room and like thousands of years go by and stuff like
that.
That's the only one I remember.
Wait, is this the room?
Uh-oh.
Wait.
Uh.
No.
All right.
Let's see.
It's the jump circle.
Oh, I got...
Wait, no.
I think I jumped enough.
Is...
Is that it?
No.
Surely that's not all the new content.
There has to be something else, right?
Oh, there's all...
Okay, hold on, I'm gonna finish it.
I'm gonna finish it.
Jumping.
Save the jumps?
Oh.
Okay.
Another elevator.
Stanley, I have to say, initial impressions of this game are
not possible.
My streamer is so wasteful.
It's just elevators and jumping.
Is this what passes for exciting new content?
you guys are excited but also try not to like backseat too
much i do want to experience things on my own as well so if
i screw up that's up to me you know what i mean oh wait
there's more very good i knew there had to be something else
let's see it i'm ready for whatever it is the abyss the
abyss
Thank you for enjoying the new content.
That's it?
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
You see, Stanley?
This is what happens when greedy video game developers with
no respect for their fan base rush a cheap expansion to
market for no reason other than to make an easy dollar.
Classic Abyss Room.
And don't get misplanted on the level of craftsmanship
that's gone into it.
My office had three.
I'm looking right now at the game's achievements, and it's
hard to believe one of them actually says, Test Achievement,
please ignore.
What quality assurance department signed off on this?
I've gotten a single achievement, actually.
I'm offended, and I intend to find these people on Twitter,
and hold them personally accountable.
Uh, formally Twitter.
X.
I built up too much anticipation around the new content, I'm
afraid.
It could never have lived up to such expectations.
Speak the truth.
If you're still with me, why don't we just reset the game?
No!
And we'll try to get back to what the Stanley Parable is
really about.
No frills.
No gimmicks.
Just you and me having a great time together, like always.
What do you say, friend?
Oh.
It's a little different.
That's my office.
That's where I'm supposed to be in this very moment.
Fascinating.
Oh, pst.
Stanley, come over here.
In the vent.
I want to show you something.
Ew!
It's like, it's like it.
It's so sus.
What if I don't list them?
Let's see, let's try this.
Oh, you don't want to see the cool surprise I made for you?
Well, fine.
Oh, surprise.
You're a dork anyway, so who cares?
Excuse- Oh, what?
Are you saying that I'm not, like, cool enough to go
through?
Never mind.
You're not a dog.
I think I have to go.
When Stanley came to a set of two open doors, he entered the
door on his left.
I'm not listening to you at all.
I'm not listening to you do anything.
Perhaps he wanted to stop by the employee lounge first, just
to admire it.
No.
I'm just gonna keep going.
Screw you.
Call him in.
Yep.
La la la la.
Nope.
No, I'm not listening to anything you say any longer.
Stanley was so bad at following directions, it's incredible
he wasn't fired years ago.
Do not lie.
If you are lying right now, stop.
Okay.
What if I told you my real name wasn't really meant phantom?
What if I told you that I named myself that once I, when I
came back from consciousness after dying, because I had a
spear mint.
in my tummy do not jump from cargo lift while it is in
motion will cause death penalty for misuse of cargo lift
1000 penalty for jumping off the cargo lift 5000 look
Stanley I think perhaps we've gotten off on the wrong foot
here I'm not your enemy really I'm not there's the exit
investing your trust in someone else can be difficult but
the exit's right there story has been about nothing but you
all this time there's someone you've been neglecting Stanley
someone you've forgotten really I was in the middle of
something do you have zero consideration are you that
convinced that I want something bad to happen to you why I
don't know how to convince you of this but I really do want
to help you to show you something beautiful look let me
prove it let me prove that I'm on your side give me a chance
I'm no dorker give me a in a relationship.
Narrator.
Ghosts, no followers.
Yeah.
No buckets past this point.
Now listen carefully.
This is important.
Stanley walked through the red door.
This one has a swipe a key card.
Hmm.
Um.
Aha.
Perhaps you misunderstood Stanley walked through the red
door He just picked me up like I was a goddamn sim I'm
colorblind I'm colorblind I still don't think we're
communicating properly Stanley walked through the red door
Red door Alright fine go ahead Stanley You want to know so
badly what's out there You want to find out what lies at the
end of this road you've chosen world don't let me stop you
oh i do oh wait is is this the place that i got spoiled
before you see there's nothing here oh i haven't even
finished building this section of the map because you were
never supposed to be here in the first place broken rooms
exposed developer textures oh that's true what you had
wanted was it worth ruining the entire story i had written
out specifically for you do you not think i put a lot of
time into that because i did and in the to the baby this is
what you wanted to see baby baby help me here stanley help
elucidate these strange and unknowable desires of yours what
would have made this game better a baby what did you want to
see anime skill tree skill tree work with me you give me
absolutely nothing so far tell you what let me take a stab
in the dark at a new design and you can give me some
feedback there we go a third option this already feels leaps
ahead of where we were before go ahead stanley take it for a
spin okay oh okay i'm going to stop you there now tell me
about your experience with this new version would you say
that the game benefited from allowing you more choices feel
free to be honest i'm looking for some real critical
feedback here five is the best or one is the best you gotta
tell me which is the best five or one oh dis um disagree
highly disagree highly agree hmm a one i mean i can
understand if you had reservations you saw ways the game
could be improved to more fully express itself mechanically
and artistically but a one a one that's not even helpful
what am i supposed to do with that but i guess it isn't my
place to judge Here, based on the data from your previous
playthrough, I've compiled a new version.
Okay.
If it's perfectly candid, I think I've knocked it out of the
park with this one.
Let's take a look.
Oh.
Now, would you say that competitive leaderboard helped you
feel motivated to keep walking through doors?
Again, honest answers, please.
Wait, are these real people?
No.
Oh, no.
21.3% of players skipped at the intro sequence.
That's a dead rat!
Go a dead rat!
How long does it take you to get to the correct door?
In total, there's so many steps taken.
I'm 9,928th out of 900,320...
No!
Saying that I'm...
That I suck, okay?
Okay.
Aw, man.
Oh!
Uh-oh.
Happy Memorial Day, Mint.
Eat anything.
What?
Go today at barbecue ribs for dinner.
Yummy!
I fucked the game.
You can't.
No, seriously, we disabled you.
Get your first achievement.
I didn't try jumping.
I tried moving.
Uh-oh.
I think I have to restart.
Oh, no.
I actually broke the game.
Okay, a dead rat wouldn't have gotten stuck.
That's why he's 9,327th.
I'm a dead rat.
Oh, she a dead rat would never soft-log their game.
No!
Rip Bozo.
Congrats, you got the closet.
Oh, here we go.
We could go through here if we wanted.
Psst!
Stanley, come over here.
in the vent i want to show you something what should we do
guys should we go through the vent should we are you still a
dork no i don't think so
the narrator is the dork obviously coffee night wow this is
pretty cinematic here i go Okay, nice.
Okay, you remember how cheap and unsatisfying the new
ultra-deluxe content turned out to be?
Well, it got me thinking about the past.
And how much better the Stanley Parable used to be.
Oh.
So I made something special and tucked it away here where
the game's developers won't find it.
Elden Ring!
Just our little secret.
Okay.
Just kidding.
I call it the memory zone.
Wow.
It's where I've been storing all my favorite memories so I
can relive the peak experiences of my life whenever I want.
Guy lives in the past.
Experiences like the launch of the Stanley Parable on PC.
Wow.
You see, Stanley, doesn't the memory zone remind you of how
wonderful Stanley Parable was before it was solid with a
cheap re-release?
Remember back in October of 2013, when the game originally
launched, The British Academy of Film and Television Arts!
Back then, it all meant something.
Oh, the waste.
Memory, sweet memory.
Oh my god, Steam Page!
That's so funny!
Ah, 2013, when the Stanley Parable was released.
Life was so much more simple back in 2013.
Especially because the Stanley Parable was just released.
Oh, I was going to say this is the actual time, but it is
not.
Our first kiss, my first car, the release of the Stanley
Parable in 2013.
Oh, scripts.
Stanley Parable on Steam.
Oh, no, just kidding.
On the website.
The original remake.
Wow.
Good times.
Oh, I've seen...
Oh, the mind control facility.
Oh, the two doors.
Oh my gosh.
This has been so long.
Why is this roped off?
Am I in a bad spot?
Smile because it happened.
Their first dollar!
Or just a dollar, who knows?
The demo, wow.
2013, that means they announced Half-Life 3?
No, they didn't.
Go outside, don't play for five years?
Stanley Parable Alpha Test?
Mm-hmm.
more British stuff British British glad they've been
nominated a lot Stanley parable deals tough choices oh he's
dead wait there's another person is that her wife
the flowers are so hard
little Stanley oh little Stanley
it's Adele never mind I'll find Someone like you I would And
over here is where I keep reviews of the Stanley Parable
Like this stunning triumph of games journalism 10 out of 10
from destructoid.com James Stephanie Sterling writes And I
quote We're so many games that aspire to be more than games
End up less than any form of art Stanley Parable strives And
then succeeds to be every game ever created Did you hear
that, Stanley?
Every game ever created.
That's how grand and all-encompassing the original Stanley
Parable was.
It was literally every game ever created.
It was Skyrim.
It was Persona 3.
Persona 3!
That's so relevant now.
It's no games at all.
It isn't even the Stanley Parable anymore.
It's so relevant now.
It's just a husk now.
A lifeless husk with an hour of new elevator content.
A husk, a shell of itself.
So sad.
Wow, there's a lot going on.
Maintenance, can't go on there.
Knowing your city.
Mm-hmm.
Old pictures and stuff, you know, the original remake.
Person of the Year, that's me!
Who is this?
Is that my wife?
Life.
Who is that?
PetScop.
Collectors Edition.
What comes?
Isn't that a tie?
It's so cute.
The greatest wealth is memory.
The red in the blue door!
We just saw the happy button.
I don't think we've heard that yet.
Here's another moving passage.
This time from GameSpot.com.
GameSpot.
Stanley Parable is both a richly stimulating commentary on
the nature of choice in games and one that offers some of
the most enjoyable, surprising, and rewarding choices I've
ever been confronted with in a game.
Nine out of ten.
Don't you get it, Stanley?
The game was perfect.
And will the hero love the original Stanley Parable?
It didn't need new content.
It just needed to be left alone.
Left alone.
To spend the rest of time collecting dust in the hallowed
hall of beloved video game memories.
No.
Yeah, I didn't need anything else.
Oh my gosh, the Himmel the Hero joke made me think, like,
literally, I think it was like yesterday.
I was thinking, I was like, man, I guess, you know,
eventually Himmel the Hero jokes will, like, get old.
But then we can just make the new joke, Himmel the Hero,
loved Himmel the Hero jokes.
So it will never get old.
What's this?
What is this, the collector?
Oh no, this is the carpet textures.
game project.
The serious room.
What is what is Kiara's room called again?
What is that one called again?
The the the usual room?
The usual room?
Yeah yeah.
It's the usual room.
can i go through here well where am i supposed to go i went
through here didn't i oh these were simpler times stanley oh
down here but i wouldn't give to go back to have it all over
again i know wait hang on yeah i don't recall this part of
the memory zone before what's this what's down here oh oh
whoa oh god no stanley it's a collection of reviews from
steam the online video game distributor i haven't looked at
these i think i vaguely remember this part imagine what's
been collecting down here oh god surely these reviews were
glowing as well oh yeah oh yeah baby steam reviews are oh
boy honestly i could not be bothered to play this game to
full completion oh no the river is obnoxious and unfunny for
his humor and dialogue
funny i'm not trying to be funny i'm trying to make a
serious work of art i suppose i could write up a handful of
gags to insert into the stanley parable but the game is
already such a densely layered web of profound philosophical
insights that i can't even imagine where i'd have the room
to stick this one's a positive one don't let one bad review
get you down don't don't worry about it you know it's so
funny this comment didn't inspire me to play this today but
I saw a comment earlier that someone left for me I was just
like quit your job you quit your job for this go back to
being an oh I was like you know what I was already gonna
play the Stanley parable so it's also perfect they're like
YouTube isn't forever go back to your job you'll have no
life skills but
I think he was on to something I think so too oh it's
getting really rainy oh dead bodies are in here for sure oh
this is oh okay let's see what this one says while the
you're reading all the bad ones all the good ones are in
here someone who prefers non-linear games this preachiness
gets annoying fast preachy yeah i'm not preachy am i just a
little you can tell me if i'm I'm telling you.
This is actually quite shocking for me.
I always will.
To be honest.
There's good ones right here.
Oh, there's not a bad one.
It's been rather terse to begin with.
You can't know how much fluff I cut from the game to get it
to feel as light and airy as it...
Well, I always thought it did, but maybe it wasn't.
Maybe it wasn't.
What an awful memory to have to hold on to.
These black marks are my otherwise unimpeachable track
record.
I mean...
I feel...
like a failure no like i let these people there's good
reviews right there terrible isn't quite as sterling as i
always remembered uh-oh i mean there's no such thing as a
perfect game except metal gear solid so you know you can't
help it you can't you know you'll never be metal gear you
know what's this one got to say you constantly have to stop
doing anything so the narrator can catch up with his
long-winded explanation of what's happening.
I wish there was a skip button.
A skip button.
Oh.
Well, yes.
Yes, I think we can do that.
If I'm truly too preachy, then maybe letting you skip ahead
for just a moment, surely it couldn't hurt.
Surely.
Not if it means we can strike these negative reviews from
the record, only positive reviews of the Stanley Paragraph.
That's my motto today, and it's always been my motto.
I'd do anything for the customer, Stanley.
Wow.
The customer is, always right skip button oh oh i think this
is that ending because we press keep pressing the skip
button right then we skip to the end of the life end of the
world and here it is go ahead and give it a shot i'll pop
you forward in time so that the second my incessant droning
starts to bore you With just the push of a button, you'll
have zipped right past it.
Spoilers, oh.
I'm back!
Oh, you're back, you see?
Yeah!
You were only frozen in time for a few minutes, but it was
plenty of time for me to deliver a long, rambling monologue
full of unnecessary verbal flourishes and lengthy
ruminations.
One o'clock.
Of course, I happen to believe it was perhaps one of my more
profound such ruminations, not that of course you needed.
I'm back!
You really did catch me rambling on a bit, didn't you?
I did.
But that's the power of the button.
The minute I start to go off on a thoughtless display of
self-absorption, it's right at your fingertips to go poof,
and it's all over.
It's all over!
Oh, I can't wait to see what Cookie Nine will say about
this.
Oh, he's probably ecstatic.
And whether they'll edit the rating of their Steam review,
or at least change some of the wording, perhaps.
To be honest, I don't even know if one can change their
review in the first place.
Can you?
Actually, I don't know either.
I never leave reviews.
Oh, exactly.
steam works perhaps that would have been the smart thing to
check on before I went about this whole exercise of making
the skip button this one's for you cookie nine after seeing
this exciting okay welcome back Stanley now I should say
that the amount of time the button has been skipping through
is becoming longer and longer that last one was well I want
to say maybe 30 45 minutes oh it's not unendurable by any
means but it's well there's really only so much I can ramble
on to myself about i know it's shocking isn't it but at any
rate i do suggest that we not press the button have you seen
the hell diver's two reviews i have not aptly demonstrated
and we can say goodbye to it and just wait how do we get out
of here yeah there's a door go oh wasn't there a door that
led into this room there was i don't feel quite certain now
right or what do we do how else would we have gotten into
the room in the first place i don't think one can enter a
room without a door of some sort or a window or something
like that you see a window anywhere a porthole a
sufficiently large crack in the wall i'll take any of these
all i want is for us to move on let's just move on yeah
let's let's just standy yeah stanley stanley please don't
push the button again it's been 12 hours 12 hours you've
just been frozen there i don't know why the skips are
getting longer but they're really truly getting longer and
my god there's no way out of the room
cutscenes i've looked at it from every angle i've never i've
only played genshin like once so don't quite know there's
just you and the button and if you keep pressing it i have
no idea okay oh stanley you're back you're back oh my
goodness i have someone to talk to again stanley i i think
it's been a week for two weeks i've been sitting here all
that time just sitting here not a single person to speak
with and you'd think that that's just looking for my stool
oh there it is right me talking and you saying nothing would
you think that it's exactly the same as always doesn't that
feel like what we've already been doing me just talking but
it isn't standing it isn't the same at all it isn't even
close because i know you can't hear me once you push that
No.
That's what I'm realizing now, Stanley.
Not at all.
I'm realizing that I needed to know that someone was
listening.
Oh.
I needed there to be a vessel through which my words were
moving.
Oh.
Oh, hello.
It's you.
Hi.
Welcome.
I have had time to think about you and about us and about
everything we've been through.
About us?
I've had so much time.
I stopped keeping track after a year.
Oh, you!
Have you ever sat down in one place and not moved for one
entire year?
Let me describe it for you.
To begin with, there is only regret.
He talks like we're in a relationship.
Like, what is going on with that?
You know, I'm sorry I ghosted you for a year, but I just
can't help it.
I'm a ghost.
Months.
I lost it all in a blur of the deepest longing to undo the
past.
And when that feeling had begun to subside, what took its
place is what I can only describe as the collapse of
every...
moment I have ever experienced my entire life well why
didn't you leave down into a single you're not stuck here
too either are you I could see myself clearly calmly with a
collected heart it was an impossibly rich well-spring of
both delight a business goes what business are we in I could
do nothing but what felt like let's take it from the top you
see it was a revelation for me it was Unlike anything I had
ever known, it was a space without consequence.
Good morning!
Nairator!
Oh.
Has that always been there?
Nairator!
Hello!
I'm alive!
Are you alive?
I don't know how this twig is still sitting up, you know.
I think he's dead, Jim.
No, he's not.
He's taking a nap at this time, too.
I'll see him.
I'll see him in the next skip.
Oh, that's terrible.
Oh, my God.
That's terrible, terrible noise.
Uh, the clock is off the wall.
But they didn't understand the game was never meant to be
funny.
Oh, he's live!
It was meant to speak.
to the human condition.
But where are the jokes?
Where are the jokes?
They bemoaned.
They screamed.
They gnashed their teeth and said, entertain us.
It wasn't enough.
They had to leave a pathetic little thumbs down review and
make all of their pitiful demands.
But then, he's talking too much.
I told you he was taking a nap.
First, he didn't entertain us.
Now he won't shut up.
It's the inconsistency.
It's the lack of accountability.
Yeah, okay.
It's the unwillingness to examine with an uncompromising
heart.
Yeah, tell them.
Go off on them, narrator.
As though there were no consequences.
Shank him!
Shank him in their feelings!
But of course, absolutely anyone can leave him with you.
So here's what we get.
We get these demands that seek everything and are
accountable to nothing.
We get a world where someone will say, oh, there should be a
skip button.
There should be a skip button.
You should be able to freeze Stanley in place while the
narrator sits there forever and ever.
We want all of this in the new Stanley Parable.
We demand it!
And then, because it was said, because it was spoken, now it
simply has to happen.
I used to sleep again.
It's fine, you guys.
He's asleep again.
I wonder how long it's been.
Oh.
Takes a second.
There we go.
I like to check.
I don't know if there's anything each time.
Anything different, but I like to check.
He was...
He's still just asleep, you know.
He's still fine.
He just took a nap, too.
Okay.
The end is never the end is never the end is never the end
is never the end is never the end is never the end is never
the end is never the end is never the end is never the end
is the end is the end is the end is the end is the end is
the end is the end is the end is the end is the end is the
end is the end is the end is the end is the end is the end
is the end is the end is the end is the end is the end is
the end is the end Never the end is never the end is never
the end is never the end is never the end.
Good morning.
Whoa, it's really leaking now.
Uh-oh, it's a little bit moldy.
in here.
I smell so nasty.
Like it in a shower.
Oh, yeah.
Roll in it.
And there's never the end.
There's never the end.
How long do you guys think it's been up this point?
How many years?
Oh!
Although it collapsed from the water.
It's kind of dangerous, maybe.
It's never the end.
500.
I thought I was going to sneeze.
Please, just let me sneeze.
Sometimes I need to sneeze, and even when I need to sneeze
off stream, I can't sneeze still.
It's the worst feeling ever.
Oh!
It's daylight.
Oh my god, I don't know the last time I've seen the
daylight.
Wow.
Oh.
There's flies.
Is there...
Is there dead body here?
Is it me?
They're attached to me.
It's because I'm really gross.
But I showered like...
Like 5,000 years ago.
What's wrong?
Why do I hear flies?
Oh.
I showered, I showered.
Oh!
Whoa!
Nature...
Nature prevails.
Whoa!
It's taken back over.
Nature is healing.
Tokyo jungle.
Oh.
No!
I forgot how eerie this one really gets.
This one's really freaky.
So if you die before you get a chance to shower, does that
mean you're forever stinky as a ghost for all eternity?
No.
I wash my ectoplasm almost every day.
Stinky ghost.
Takes one to no one.
Whoa, why am I like sideways?
I think we're sideways.
We're crooked.
Why can't we see...
Why is there... Why can't we see through here anymore, but
there's light over here?
Oh, the button's down!
The button's down!
I repeat!
The button is down!
Oh.
Whoa!
That's it.
But it's okay.
Life will be reborn on this lifeless planet.
Me.
I'll start it.
I will spread my seed across the world.
I will rebuild this planet as one.
Everybody will become Stanley.
Stanleyfication.
From sea to shining sea.
I think it worked.
Good job, guys.
What are those emojis that are happening?
What is that?
Thanks for the don't know, though.
No, I don't want to be Stanley.
All of his co-workers were gone.
What could it mean?
Stanley decided to go to the meeting room.
Perhaps he had simply missed a memo.
Stanley.
Oh, new, new content.
I feel like, okay, as silly as this sounds, Stanley Beyond
Journey's End, as silly as this sounds, I don't think I've
ever gotten like the normal ending.
Like the, like, we follow all his prompts, we follow
everything.
I don't think I've ever gotten that one before.
I think I've always just instinctually went to against the
narrator.
Let's just listen to what he has to say.
When Stanley came to a set of two open doors, he entered the
door on his left.
Yeah, we're gonna follow the rules.
We're gonna be a little...
We're not gonna be...
We're not adventurous at all.
I'm just a little Stanley.
This is shitty Stanley.
Yet there was not a single person here either.
Feeling a wave of disbelief, Stanley decided to go up to his
boss's office, hoping he might find an answer there.
This is Stanley.
upstairs to his boss's office this is stanley the good
stanley this is this is timid stanley as it is written oh
forgot about the bathroom money in the morning money in the
evening money for breakfast money crisp today
npc stanley yes yes yes yes thanks for the super chat by the
way thank you stepping into his manager's office stanley was
once again stunned to discover not an indication of any
human life what could it mean stanley wondered aloud to
nobody he began wildly tearing through papers on the boss's
desk pulling books off the shelf looking behind paintings
desperate for clues to his situation but his attention was
caught by a keypad behind the boss's desk what could its
purpose be in fact This keypad guarded the terrible secret
that lay buried below his feet.
And so the boss had assigned it an extra secret pin.
Uh-oh, wait.
2-8, 4-5.
I pressed 4!
But yet incredibly, by simply pushing random buttons on the
keypad, Stanley happened to input the correct code by sheer
luck.
Amazing.
He stepped into the newly opened passageway.
That's kind of crazy.
He's not talking to me at all.
I should have put in boob I should have put in boob 8 0 0 8
Stanley walks straight ahead through the large door that
read mind control facility was this here before did I just
not notice it
escapi oh no no we're NPC Stanley we're NPC Stanley
Beep!
The lights rose on an enormous room packed with television
screens.
What horrible secret did this place hold, Stanley thought to
himself?
Did he have the strength to find out?
I almost just fell.
Why did they allow you?
Oh my god.
Why did they allow you to do that?
No way.
Do it.
Aha!
You've made it to the bottom of the mind control facility.
Welcome!
You see, back when the Stanley Parable first launched in
2013, getting to the bottom of the mind control facility was
a bug that we simply didn't catch during the development.
And you all sent us lots of photos of it on Twitter and
acted very superior about it.
And you're all very, very clever.
Good for you.
Anyway, when it came time to update the game, we knew that
we had to do something about this little goof of the game.
silly guys here you go new content new content you can call
it the bottom of the mind control room ending if that
enhances your perception of the value of these updates yes
yes crave new content yes always more content more content
more more more more oh I'm eating all this content I'm so
full oh my god I'm fat from content thank you every nook and
cranny of the game with secrets and Easter eggs how about
this we wrote a new piece of music just for this section you
won't hear it anywhere else in the game okay it's a secret
that's just for you that's how special you are we call this
track good job you love and grow fat content and grow fat
you did it good job you did it oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, good job.
You made it to the bottom of the mind control facility.
Oh, you jumped on the catwalk.
You should have been careful.
I should have been careful.
It used to be a bug.
A bug.
But now it's an ending.
Yeah, now it's ending.
I believe in you.
I believe in your ability to cross this barrier.
Chase your dreams?
Oh, oh, oh, hi, oh, hi.
Good job.
You did it.
I did it.
Good job.
You did it.
I did it.
Good.
Oh, just kidding.
I don't know how to count.
Wait, I didn't get to everyone.
ending like I like I thought he would like I thought he
would like teleport me back or something you know oopsie all
of his good job you did it good job you did it stanley
decided to go to the meeting room so glad they made a sequel
to you have to burn the rope okay la la la we're gonna get
the normal ending this time mpc mission failed no no he
entered the door on his left on his left on his go to the
new new yeah there was not a single person here either I
think the new new content is where I decided to go up to his
bosses off coming to a staircase I think that's where I
broke the game before the moment he entered his manager's
office Stanley froze in his tracks not a living soul
anywhere could he really be all alone this was too much for
Stanley to take too much for stanley was in such a rush to
get through the story as quickly as possible he didn't even
have a single minute to just let the narrator talk no time
to talk boob so he relaxed for a few moments with some
calming new age music okay we're getting the whole
soundtrack to this this time
feeling soothed and rejuvenated stanley calmly favorite oh
the broom closet ending my favorite play sir can i have
another broom closet ending
it wouldn't let you speed run it oh not at all it's okay i
get it they're keep they're keeping to a very strict
schedule i get it stanley walks straight ahead through the
large door that read mind control facility oh yeah It's
really tempting.
It's written in Quran and everything.
You know it was hastily done.
This is fine.
That's fine.
Okay, push the button.
All right, true NPC ending.
Here we go.
The lights rose on an enormous room packed with television
screens.
What horrible secret did this place hold?
Stanley thought to himself.
Did he have the strength to find out?
again but I won't do it sorry
you guys crayon okay are you happy oh my god can't be I
can't say anything without getting judged by your
insignificant details now the monitors jump to life their
true nature oh I never saw this oh Stanley's co-workers the
lives of so many individuals reduced to images on a screen
Reduced?
They've been reduced.
What is that one right there?
The one that's blue.
Oh, it's just kind of normal.
Reduced to nothing.
What's this?
This mind control facility.
It was too horrible to believe.
It couldn't be true.
But where are they?
That Stanley had been under someone's control all this time.
was this the only reason he was happy with his boring job
that his emotions had been manipulated to accept it blindly
no no I love my job no he refused to believe it yeah
couldn't accept it his own life in someone else's control
never never was unthinkable wasn't it was it even possible
my life I control my own fate utterly blind to the world but
here was the proof the heart of the operation controls
labeled with emotions happy or sad or content walking eating
working they controlled everything monitored and commanded
from this very place and as the cold reality of his past
began to sink in stanley decided that this machinery would
never again exert its terrible power over another human life
never again would dismantle the controls once and for all
mind controls idle awaiting input but who stops it i need a
stanley parable too a prequel to this uh oh don't give me a
choice here uh the patriots Hmm.
MPC, remember, you're right, you're right.
Scared me.
MPC, MPC!
Shut down GW.
We went through a microwave tunnel for this.
Was it over?
Yes.
He had won.
He had defeated the machine.
unshackled himself from someone else's command freedom was
mere moments away and yet even as the immense door slowly
opened Stanley reflected on how many puzzles still lay
unsolved where had his co-workers gone how had he been freed
from the machine's grasp the sky other mysteries did this
strange building hold but as sunlight streamed into the
chamber he realized none of this For it was not knowledge or
even power that he had been seeking, but happiness.
Perhaps his goal had not been to understand, but to let go.
Let go.
No longer would anyone tell him where to go, what to do, or
how to feel.
Whatever life he lives, it will be his.
And that was all he needed to know.
It was perhaps the only thing worth knowing.
Let me out.
Stanley stepped through the open door.
oh grass oh i didn't even do anything on his skin the
feeling of liberation the immense possibility of the new
path before him this was exactly the way right now that
things were meant to happen wow and stanley was happy wow
it's like a actually such like a wholesome complete the
Stanley parable.
Maybe we should have done this last.
It's actually like such a nice ending.
Wow.
It's like so like where Stanley was happy.
Oh, well, back in the office for you, Bozo.
You can never leave the office life.
Just a step through this door, Stanley thought to himself.
That's all I need.
If I can make it through this door, I can make it through
them all.
Wait, what?
Can I?
No.
Stanley went around touching every little thing in the
office.
You just told me I could go through the doors!
No.
Nor did it advance the story in any way.
New new content.
Oh good.
You noticed my sign.
I did.
I have something very exciting to show you.
Through here?
Okay.
we're going through our little ride again love it new new
content
wait but i wanted to see the i wanted to see the ride again
world turning the button on results in mintification and
about how roundly disappointing this ultra deluxe version
has turned out to be the original stanley parable was a
landmark and any new content for it should live up to that
get this ultra deluxe nonsense I say we take it one step
even further which is why I'm very proud to announce for the
first time is this supposed to look like this Stanley
parable to oh I think I remember this part far superior to a
measly re-release with a few minor additions think of all
the new territory will cover with a fully fledged sequel an
entirely new experience built from the ground up why there
are so many possibilities it could go in so many different
directions this is what fans have truly been asking for
investor showcase oh yeah baby two two two two two two two
okay calling it to stanley parable 2 is just so much
catchier than ultra deluxe don't you think sure But the
Stanley Parable 2.
Off page.
Now that's an artistic statement right there.
What's a TGA file?
It screams progress and innovation and long-term franchising
potential.
Potential.
Targa.
What's Targa?
Type of texture file.
Interesting.
Wow.
This is so fancy.
It's like a whole new...
Like, I mean, it is a whole new office.
We got modern stone, concrete wall aesthetic.
And they're back.
The two doors.
I love those guys.
I love
those guys.
New content is out.
New content part two is in.
Mm-hmm.
What's this?
ideas.
Stanley can throw axes?
Stanley gets boons from fish?
Artistic intimate wipe scene.
Free room.
Oh, free roam?
Free roam made?
More famous narrator.
That one's crossed out.
Dress up mode.
microtransact microtransactions very good proper gameplay
nude stanley new york city jetpack fuel canisters
whoever wrote this is on to something great whoever wrote
that oh i can't read the two 2 p.m.
Oh.
Um.
Like, yeah, I'm, I'm needing some of these.
Especially the several of them.
More TSP.
Badder TSP.
Paradigm shift S energy.
Brick and mortar approach.
The color red.
Sequential mind share.
Win-win.
Two...
The ferns!
I don't know anything about... Oh my gosh.
Look at that!
Oh, I kinda like this one down here.
I kinda like the Stanley Parable with the two lines inside.
Thanks for attending my meeting.
The other ones are whatever.
The second one reminds me of Red Dead Redemption, I think.
I never had an ending with the ferns.
Oh,
I thought this was nude Stanley.
Now, to be clear, I haven't quite nailed down what exactly
the Stanley Parable 2 is going to be.
But let's take a look at some of the features I've been
developing for it.
Okay.
I figure that if I can loosely organize a handful of
interesting concepts, that surely the game will sort of
naturally spring up around them.
It'll all work itself out.
development is much more of a fuzzy magic than anything
scientific or this is so relatable to two eyes two ears two
nostrils two arms two legs what the perfect Stanley the end
is never the end again Stanley Parable 2 now with blockchain
an ai no sequels are good portal 2 half-life 2 batman arkham
asylum 2 metal gear solid 2 doom 2 divinity original sin 2
Aladdin 2 return of jafar dark souls 2
hmm doom 2 the prequel to the stanley parable two is the
sequel to the Stanley Parable is the prequel to the Stanley
Parable Two is the sequel to the Stanley Parable is the
prequel Two, Two Nice Every pause button Is it Roman numeral
No, Roman numeral two The show Floor Wow, new Oh, yeah Oh,
thank you Oh Thank you.
What are you wearing tonight, Bint?
I'm wearing your mom's dress from last night.
Thank you.
No other questions.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Oh, God.
Here we are.
Go on.
Try out some of the new features.
Wow.
I do remember this part a little bit.
Hear your name in the game.
the button that says the name of the player that is playing
the game for the stanley parable 2 i asked myself what do
players really want and of course the first and most obvious
answer is that they want to be individually recognized and
validated as people so with that in mind my first addition
to the game is this demo and the demo which speaks the name
Wonderful.
I remember the last time that it's not saying my name.
Thanks for the super chat.
I'm glad I could make you smile.
It's gonna say mint.
And if it doesn't say any, if it says anything else, if it
says anything else, it's the docks button.
You guys are scaring me.
It's going to say mint.
Jim.
Sorry, I should have clarified.
Right now, the button only says the name Jim.
But of course, in the final game, this button will say your
name, whatever name that is.
Here, let's have you roleplay as Jim to really simulate the
full experience of this feature.
I'm Jim's Phantom!
I promise you'll love it.
Okay, here we go.
Jim.
Let's take a deep breath, clear your mind, forget whoever
you are, and simply become a person named Jim.
I want you to imagine yourself.
as Jim oh god I'm really sad and waking as Jim falling in
love and being heartbroken as Jim seizing all of the world's
possibilities as Jim and as Jim watching your dreams crumble
into dust do you feel it deeply are you really truly Jim
right now if so then please step forward and press the
button I'm Jim I'm Jim Jim yes you see what a What a thrill!
What a thrill!
The button described you.
Do it again.
I think I'm really starting to like, you know, it's one of
those like, keep, think until you believe it sort of for
things, you know, like, Jim.
It hits even harder the second time.
If this were the only new feature in the Stanley Parable 2,
it would still be worth the money.
Let's take a break from the Jim button.
I'm too emotionally drained from all of this personal
validation.
Hold on, I'm just changing the stream title a little bit.
There we go.
Cool.
Jim.
Oh, there, cowboy.
Sometimes a person can be too much, Jim.
I'm putting the Jim button away.
No!
Otherwise, soon you'll start to lose all sense of who you
actually are.
You can't stop me.
You can't!
Did that mean...
You can't deny me my identity!
Anyway.
I felt good.
I felt good, you know, when I...
When I died, there were some things that I lost, some
memories, you know, but now I feel...
I feel this post-gym clarity that I just never thought that
I would ever, you know...
Feel.
It's the dead tree.
It's still here.
I suppose I could allow only people named Jim to play the
Stanley Parable 2.
That would actually save me the work of finishing this
feature.
Don't be lazy, narrator.
Don't be lazy.
No screenshots, everybody.
Whole new office.
999.
Red is the new or.
Is that coming around the game?
Uh, uh, uh, wait, is that for me or...
Chimperms revoked.
New features, new content, new ideas.
New updated rate traced more of the same, but in a good way,
sequel to the...
Okay, I think it's in the game.
Oh my god, that scared me.
The baby!
The button baby, button baby!
Baby is all grown.
Button baby, button baby, button baby.
Consistent quality with just the right amount of change.
Shween shaders.
Oh, the bucket.
No screenshots.
Is that?
Oh my god, it's me.
Whoa, I'm tall.
I grew like an extra foot or so.
got collectibles turning me into a you twos oh yeah stanley
you twos free new and easy achievement
can you find them collect them all ah collectibles now it's
a real video game in the stanley parable 2 you'll run around
gathering up these miniature stanley figurines and what's
truly innovative is that there will be no reward for
collecting all of them.
I don't want to stifle the intrinsic joy of watching a
number go up.
You simply collect all of them and then you move the hell on
with your unremarkable life.
How am I gonna become like that?
Oh!
Yippee!
give me out of there god it really is the worst when you
collect everything in a video game and then they give you a
big fancy reward for it absolutely tragic so true so true so
true i don't need a reward i don't want anything
Ten dollars.
Thank you for the donation.
Oh my gosh, my brain.
Thank you.
Jump circle.
Oh, we had that.
We had that.
This map.
Free achievement.
Where do we get the achievement at?
Q.
So, what's N?
N is the jump circle.
This is the jump circle, right?
Oh, there it is.
There's a sign for it.
You know what, Stanley?
I actually think the jump circle...
circle was a pretty good idea i'd like to hang on to that i
only oh this is the 10 that i have left
nice free achievement pull the lever receive your new
achievement no more steps it just works now here's something
special you remember that broken test achievement that got
left in the game on accident yeah i'm developing a
technology to simply give you the achievement Yes.
You see, you'll come to this lever and when you pull it, the
achievement will be given to you.
It's a sin.
Okay, perhaps I should have clarified.
This is technology that will exist.
Right now, the achievement is still fully broken.
I'm not a wizard Stanley, but I guarantee it will be fixed
in the season.
Come on, narrator.
You're busting my balls here, narrator.
Please.
Gamers.
We hear you.
Rise up, gamers.
I cannot believe this.
What else?
What other exhibits haven't we seen yet?
The bucket?
What's in here?
Okay, I'll be honest.
I haven't yet decided on this one.
What is this?
I think that in the new version, the office could use a bit
of decoration like balloons.
But I'm undecided on get well someday and happy 12th
birthday.
Which would you go with?
I think I'd get well someday you know sometimes when you
solicit another person's opinion it makes you realize that
you knew which one you actually really wanted all along I
hate you narrator step niece it is I hate you narrator this
one is stuck this one this one it won't even this one okay
oh my god all right actually maybe i should have gone with
no no i've made my decision we're moving on we're moving on
the end is never the end is never the end would you wear
these this t-shirt is the new that is the best new feature i
saw the new content oh the bucket that's right let's go get
our bucket that code works wait what code Which one?
I didn't see a code.
Oh, the QR code.
Oh, I don't have my phone on me, you guys.
I don't know where my phone is.
I think I left it somewhere.
I think I left it after when I was cooking.
I'll try it here.
I left it up there.
Everybody else can check it.
There you go.
Go ahead and scan.
The button that says Jim like Jameson.
Oh.
Looks so sad.
A common complaint of the Stanley Parable was that it was
confusing and paradoxical that it engendered a chaotic sense
of reckless despair in those who played it.
Nice.
I'm happy to say that after much consideration yeah I've
engineered a clever solution to this fundamental problem
with the game okay it's the Stanley Parable reassurance
bucket you see Stanley anytime you're holding the bucket a
sense of calm and ease will fill your mind and your heart
it's true as long as you hold on to the bucket the many
disorienting contradictions of the Stanley Parable will feel
perfectly normal and perhaps even comforting you may even
come to long for the gentle embrace of jarring cognitive
dissonance while the bucket is in your arms and to be honest
it's a much more convenient solution for me than actually
redesigning the game to be less uncomfortable can you
imagine what a pain in the ass that would be yes the bucket
is the perfect solution come on give it a try wait can I
walk here okay Okay.
Okay.
Why are you laughing?
Can you feel it?
The glow of comfort, even in the face of crushing despair,
must already be sweeping through your body.
This is my second cult.
Can I say that I do believe the bucket lends you an air of
charisma as well?
It does.
I think so.
I think that just holding it has made you the slightest bit
more attractive as a person.
Do you think I think so?
The benefits of the bucket seem to go on and on, don't they?
All this and more await you in the Stanley Parable 2.
I think so, honestly.
I feel really...
Look, like, I come walking out, and I feel like...
Oh!
No!
No, no.
Stop.
Stop it.
Oh, my God.
Just...
Does anyone give out awards for most enjoyable bucky...
in a video game i don't know that really should be an award
if it isn't already oh wait it's like i can like see this
girl over here she's like been staring at me she's like i've
been looking at you from ever since you walked into the room
your bucket is really alluring and a bit i'd be like yeah my
bucket is like you know it's pretty cool it's it's you know
i've been with this bucket for a long time.
Do you want to touch my bucket?
She's like, is it okay?
I mean, I don't want to be I don't want to be too forward,
but like, be my first time touching someone's bucket before.
And be like, it's okay.
I don't normally let people do this, but you know, you can
you can even hold it if you want.
She's like, wow.
And then she takes it, and she's like, she's like cradling
it like a baby.
and she's just like gosh this just feels really natural like
I just feel I feel I feel like I should have met you a long
time ago I'm like you know what it doesn't matter we can
make up for lost time sweet Caroline Baa Baa Baa!
Oh, infinite hole!
Okay, I'm not gonna lie.
I'm pretty sure this is where my game worked last time.
I think this is where my game froze before.
In the infinite hole.
So I'm a little scared of going in there.
Stanley, here's an idea that I'm truly fond of.
It's never been done before in a video game.
a hole that you can fall down forever that's right infinite
falling you can fall until the end of time if you like a
stunning leap forward for video games as a medium
oh it's so quiet I thought I could see it from up there oh I
think as hey how could I see I thought I saw it from up here
how is that possible am I crazy I thought I saw it from here
weird it calls okay okay guys oh
the roof lowered okay here we go to quote sight from
yesterday what the fuck wonderful one of my more ingenious
concoctions if I do say so now then since you've gotten to
see the infinite hole you can press the teleport button to
pop back up to the top and we can continue onward gee to
return to the surface but there's an end right now I don't
mean to be a bummer but I do recommend you use the teleport
button to go back to the teleport maybe do it on the sooner
rather than later spectrum of things
what's that sound it's like kind of crunchy okay Stanley I
don't know quite how to say this tactfully but it's possible
that I slightly exaggerated the infinite nature of the hole.
Okay.
Is it a very, very deep hole?
To be certain it is.
Wow.
It's an extremely deep hole.
It's extremely deep.
I don't want anyone to say that it isn't an astonishingly
deep hole.
It is.
Is it infinite?
Well, that sort of depends on your definition of infinity.
From one perspective, the infinite is merely philosophical
in nature.
It's more of a...
Ow!
Okay, well, good for you.
You found the bottom of the hole.
hole you found me out Stanley I'm a liar and a cheat and
you're so clever look I think the issue here is just that
you're unusually fascinated by falling what normal person
actually wants to fall infinitely I figured the hole was as
deep as anyone would actually need don't you put this on me
maybe you're the My lunch!
Look, things got a little heated there.
I think we both said some things we didn't mean.
Why don't we just put all this behind us and agree to just
call the hole mostly infinite?
If that works for you, then go ahead and press the teleport
button to warp up to the top of the hole and we can move on.
I'll just be up here when you're ready.
There's nothing else, right?
That's it?
Just the two of...
us we can make it if we try just the two of us just the two
of us just the two of us building castles in the sky just
the two of us you and I great now I'm very excited to show
you oh for heaven I was right the problem is you the problem
is that you like holes too much.
I love holes!
A normal person would have said, yep, that's an infinite
hole right there.
Goes on forever till the end of time.
Don't need to see it all, but not you.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
You become tied for my favorite.
Oh, streamer.
Thank you!
I'll give over to the concert in July.
Thank you so much!
I couldn't help but feel like you spent a little less time
in there than you did before.
I mean, admittedly, I didn't make an infinite hole, but I
didn't think it was that not infinite.
Oh, I got shorter!
I suppose once again there's nothing to do here.
If you decide you've had enough of the hole, you can hit the
teleport button and come join me up above.
I love the eclipse.
That the hole is not only not infinite, but that it's
growing steadily less and less.
I love off.
I suspect that I'm starting to hit the point where it's no
longer feasible to call the hole infinitely deep, even by
the lax overall standards for accountability and marketing.
Not even a little bit.
What's going on here?
Stanley, I have no explanation for the uncertain nature of
the hole's length.
Here, let's try something.
Okay.
Let's pop back up to the top and we'll see if it gets any
shorter.
Okay.
Well, there it is.
Oh!
The shame of my liars come out.
Oh.
Sorry.
I know you're obsessed with holes.
but at this depth I just can't see this scratching the itch
oh who am I to judge you just do whatever it is you're here
to do it feels like a wild instinct to jump into a hole
you're ready to move on oh oh oh oh I thought it was my game
it's not working yes oh I thought I really don't have an
explanation it was Just climb out!
Just try it again.
Still nothing.
Well, I suppose...
I can't jump.
I can't do anything.
Okay.
I'm out.
I can't do anything.
Goodbye, Stanley.
You couldn't bear to hear it from the whole.
And now you'll get more time with it than you could ever
have asked for.
It's a win for everyone.
You get to be with the whole.
I get to do literally anything else.
Take care, Stanley.
I hope you and the whole have a wonderful rest of it.
Wait!
G-G-G-G-G-G-G-G-G-G-G-G-G-G-G-G-G-G-G-G, G-G-G-G-G-G-G-G,
G-G-G-G-G, G-G-G-G.
Baby, baby, baby, baby.
What's going on?
Is someone coming?
Is someone...
G-G-G-G-G-G-G.
It's not moving, is it?
Or are my eyes tricking me?
It looked like it was growing down for a second.
Oh!
This hole was made for man.
Change my perspective.
Ah!
The bucket!
Germa!
Wait, how do I get back to normal?
Oh, change your perception.
No, no, no, I like the...
Oh, this one's...
Oh, okay.
Oh, God.
I like the first one.
What is this?
My head's stronger.
You're no longer using your head.
up the space of mine
Oh, I love this one
Poppies Poppies My head Stronger You're no longer Change
yourself!
Okay, please.
Change your reality.
What is going on?
where's anime yes oh good you're awake it seems you had sort
of dozed off there no I was waiting for anime Stanley
because this hole is just so darn fascinating that I want
you to be wide awake for every second of it you don't want
to miss a moment so how about if I just pop in from time to
time and wake you up to keep you really truly focused on the
hole from the looks of things you and i will have many many
years here in this hole and i'm looking forward to all of
them stay alert stanley i'll be back toodle pip toodle pip
starting again no we're going back
that's like my favorite like voice effect ever oh my game
didn't break let's go Oh my gosh.
Oh, it's a deconstruction.
Go on.
Try out some of the new features.
Wait.
But I already have a bucket.
Can I get a second one?
Toodle Pip.
I think that's everything, though.
Button that says Jim.
Let me go check the map just in.
Oh, that's new.
That door up there.
Can I get to there?
The new door?
It says it's new.
I don't think so.
Let's check out the map.
Make sure it's done everything.
Button that says the name.
Merch.
Settings world champion.
Reassurance bucket.
Office decorations.
Yeah, we went in there.
Epilogue.
Collectibles.
Yeah, we went in there.
Evident hole we went in there.
Epilogue.
What is that?
Where is that?
By five.
Oh, I think it's what I'm looking at up here.
Should I use up the rest of my jumps?
The settings world champion, I could still do it.
Where was it, though?
Over here?
Oh, wait, here's a staircase.
Settings world champion.
over here
oh never mind never mind mostly infinite hole free
achievement epilogue
merch QR code I told you I don't have my phone you guys I
don't know where my phone is I would have to like leave and
go find it but I don't know where it is
have to get the achievement to get it.
Gotta change every setting in the menu.
Wait, what do you mean?
This?
Oh.
Oh, I think I've probably missed with everything in here.
Oh, wait.
E!
Slide the sliders all the way.
The star.
This is so God, this is really satisfying to hear though,
isn't it?
Oh, this one, too.
Oh.
Nihongo!
It's just, like, the most satisfying thing I've ever...
I could listen to this forever.
Sorry, I know I'm not talking.
It's because it just sounds so good.
I don't think I changed anything, so yeah.
I don't want to delete the save data!
Do I have to do all the resolutions and everything?
Oh, it just sounds so good.
It's just...
Oh, God, it just really...
It just really hits in a good way.
Hold on.
Turn it up some.
FLV 200?
I did that, didn't I?
Oh!
Oh, thank you!
There we go.
God.
Hey, let me...
in on the setting oh wait of this of the settings ah I can
see you've gotten the settings world champion achievement
well done you've experienced every setting traveled to all
corners of the settings menu there's nothing you haven't
seen so just for you in the Stanley Parable 2 I'm including
an entirely new setting Something called bump scossity.
Bump scossity?
What exactly is bump scossity?
Well, I haven't quite figured that part out yet, but I just
know that you'll be able to adjust it on some sort of
slider.
Sorry.
That it'll be available from the settings menu.
There you go.
Sorry.
We'll sort the rest of the details out later.
I hope you're looking forward to trying out every level of
bump scossity in the Stanley Parable 2.
Bump scossity.
I'm the champion of setting all the sliders to all the
possible numbers.
Please enjoy this room.
This is your room.
It was made just for you.
Thank you.
Okay.
Now I think we can leave.
Let's get out of here.
Bump those.
Oh, wait.
Do I actually have a new setting?
Bump scossity?
Oh, I'm back in here.
Oh!
Bump viscosity!
A thousand.
What did it do?
Bump...
I haven't...
Didn't do anything!
Adjust the bump viscosity.
It's probably so big that it, like, uh...
That it, like, looped around.
know what I'm saying.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh my god.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm feeling it.
Oh, oh my god.
Whoa, whoa.
Hold on.
I have to... Okay, I know this is like a new feature.
So it's probably like, you know, not exactly like... Okay,
that's so much more manageable.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Try bump is up.
Whoa.
Bumps.
Cassidy.
had to really yeah it was like a really really intense i
shouldn't have i should have just worked i think this is a
type of setting that like not everyone can handle like i can
handle it because you know i'm like better than you but i
don't think anybody else it's like it takes a really really
really like high iq like really really like specific type of
like awesome person to be able to handle it you know what
i'm saying so like if you're playing this and you get and
you i don't think I don't expect you guys to get the bump
scossity you know um like a slider because it's like pretty
it's like only real like gamers can get it and also I don't
really know if you guys are capable of doing that but if you
do if you just happen to get lucky and like maybe like
accidentally stumble upon it um you know I would recommend
maybe you start at like a one um and then just kind of like
work your way up because for me I can go from like a
thousand and like it's a little hard to adjust but like I'm
fine for you I think you might actually be crushed into like
into like little tiny your little tiny brain would be like
you know what I mean so just don't don't worry about it mint
is better than me confirmed no epilogue oh oh an epilogue
would be fun Why are you guys clowning me?
Well, we'll figure that out later.
That's it.
That's all the epilogue was for?
Taste the sequel.
That was it.
Two!
I like that guy.
Okay.
Okie dokie.
I think that's the exit.
Do you guys...
Fine.
It ended.
mind if i actually go to the bathroom real quick i gotta go
to the little ghosty's room real fast is i had tea and
bubble tea so okay um should i finish up on my butt my jumps
too i wonder oh wait oh this is how i get out
grab your phone too okay i'll go look for it if i don't find
it really fast then I'm gonna give up okay because I lose my
phone all the time I don't think you guys realize okay I'll
be right back here let me make a little note that says she's
gone to the bathroom
gone to the bathroom okay I'll be right back
I'm back sorry sorry it took so long Oh, oh my god, I have
my, I had the stream up on my phone.
I found my phone.
Okay.
All right.
I guess since so many people ask, I'll go do the QR code.
I'll go do the QR code.
People are so passionate about QR codes, I guess.
Oh, and my jumps.
Let's finish my jumps.
Oh, I'm back.
Kept your wording, huh?
Emily!
Hello.
Randall, thanks for the five gifted.
Okay, let me scan this with my phone.
Oh, my God.
La-de-do-de-do.
Stanley Parable 2.com.
Welcome to the official site of the Stanley Parable 2.
A sequel, huh?
Oh, this is direct YouTube link.
Should I play this on stream?
Hold on.
Okay, hold on.
Oh, it's unlisted even.
Wow.
Okay, one second.
Let me pull it up.
Let me...
New table.
New window.
YouTube.
Oh no, it didn't show up in my history.
Why not?
Oh, because...
Oh, shoot.
How do I open it in the app?
Wait, open an app.
There we go.
Okay, okay, okay.
Now I should show up in my history.
Okay, there we go.
There we go.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
One second, one second, one second, one second.
One second, one second, one second, one second, one second,
one second.
Uh...
Studio mode.
Window capture.
This.
Crop, crop, crop, crop, crop.
Crop, crop, crop, crop.
crop okay da-da-da-dokie-dokie all right watch along
say there Timmy what's that you're enjoying why it's
breakfast of course everyone breakfast of champions but did
you know that breakfast is getting a sequel that's right
it's called lunch and critics are raving that lunch will be
everything breakfast was and more with a little luck we may
even get a trilogy series out of it why you know what a
sequel is don't you Timmy why is it Timmy responding way of
clinging helplessly to the past we all want more of the
things we love and we're all afraid of change which is what
makes sequels so popular new ideas are dangerous to me and
they can lead to early so true oh this eager-minded young
thinker is just 29 years old that's why I don't want to look
like that to keep us couched in the familiar I need to stop
thinking right now good thing I never thought of a healthy
functional society and if you look around you you'll find
them everywhere you go for instance this man is developing a
sequel to the automobile i don't know the vertical
automobile whoa how long is this and wait this is 10 minutes
you guys wait this is so long not all sequels are heretical
nonsense however here's the man who invented which is the
sequel to suffocating and dying a slow death.
Even your parents are getting a sequel, Timmy.
Their names are Rob and Jessica, and they'll be taking care
of you once your original parents are sent back in time to
fight a secret war for the government.
Sequels can be very fashionable.
This young woman is wearing five shirts at once, which is
the sequel to wearing four shirts at once.
Wow.
Look at Becky over there.
Wearing only two shirts at once.
Get with the times, Becky.
one single thing in the world that isn't a sequel.
It's this.
We don't know what it is or why it exists, but it's the
prequel from which all sequels are derived.
And just like everything else, the Stanley Parable is
getting a sequel too.
You know what?
I'll be honest.
I don't know if it's actually getting a sequel.
Is it actually getting a sequel?
I can't tell anymore.
way or another and you were fortunate enough to get to waste
yours on the stanley parable it doesn't have enough of the
transatlantic accent you know what i mean to match the man
which is like the vibes of this child oh it isn't okay man
you want manly things like taxes and cheating at baseball
this is the sequel you're right you're right man's video
game timmy yeah timmy and that's why the stanley parable 2
will be perfect for you it's as manly as
Let's look at the burly hunk of a man who's responsible for
the game.
Huh, here he is, hard at work.
Really?
His name is Gregory Apec.
And he's the cutting picture of royal masculinity.
Gregory is what we call the Ideas Guy.
And he has the most important role on the team.
The Ideas Guy tirelessly comes up with interesting concepts.
And then hands them off to the rest of the developers for
the relatively simple job of turning those concepts into
reality.
for example i don't know i can't i don't know how to do
anything someone ought to make a sequel to the stanley
parable good work gregory go ahead and take the rest of the
day off with the hard part out of the way work on the game
can now begin stanley parable 2 is coming out soon just a
month after minecraft 2 what makes a sequel in the first
place when it's simple sequels are an opportunity to correct
the mistakes of their predecessors we've all made mistakes
and we've all caused harm to someone we love in order to
cover up our mistakes when developing this particular sequel
it's important to start by thinking what mistakes did the
original Stanley Parable make well first off most of the
pornography in the original game stolen or pirated and it's
time we paid the licensing fees fair and square second the
Stanley Parable was catastrophic for this man named Levi
whose personal information including home address, social
security number and bank information were all displayed
prominently in multiple locations throughout the game.
Although Leroy's money and identity were stolen, the fact
remains that his personal information was the emotional core
of the game.
And absolutely vital to a nuanced understanding of the
story.
Leroy dogs.
The sequel will contain a brief and insincere apology to
Leroy, took deep within the game, where it will be difficult
to find.
Finally, the Stanley Parable made the mistake of leaking too
many government secrets about the nature of the Time Wars.
The Time Wars?
Details of specific military tactics, the story is likely to
make very little sense.
There's war in this game?
We decided to remove them from the sequel in the interest of
helping the state's efforts.
We'll get to you yet, time Dracula.
Dracula?
It's time to set about constructing the Stanley Parable 2.
Game development is a difficult and complex art one which
can only be fully understood by this race of hyper
intelligent child soldiers the children soldiers yippee oh
my god they're eating gunpowder time to exploit it for
profit let's go the stanley parable was most widely known
for its stark lack of humor bucking all conventional
industry wisdom it was a bold artist that its developers
stood firmly behind but in 2022 it's impossible to reach
even a single consumer of video games without jokes of some
kind so very well jokes it'll be whoa we're getting jokes oh
my youtube bro hold on you guys of comedy will be following
directly into the core of the stanley parable i can't reach
out i'm sorry jobs for hundreds of machine operators and
producing 30 000 tons of pollutant chemical byproduct which
will be pumped directly into local lakes and beautiful
nature reserves like these all over the country.
Oh, screw the environment!
Another common complaint of the Stanley Parable is that
there wasn't enough gameplay.
And so for the sequel, its developers have gone to great
lengths to fix this problem.
Here we can see gameplay being printed on the sheets.
Every video game contains as many as a thousand sheets of
gameplay.
That's a lot of gameplay.
The largest games ever made contain close to 1500.
On mobile devices, the gameplay sheets have to be printed
smaller.
For the Stanley Parable 2, as many as 35 new gameplay sheets
are being printed.
Each of which must be delicately massaged by the hands of a
child before being added into the game.
This man is stealing gameplay sheets from the factory, which
he likely intended to use as a personal project he's been
developing in his spare time.
A good public stoning will cure him of that inclination.
Stoning?
Let's check on Gregory real quick.
Ha!
Still recovering from a hard day's work.
Don't you move a muscle.
Good job, Gregory.
It's time to blackmail the press.
In a competitive market, blackmailing your local journalist
can be one of the most effective methods of creating
word-of-mouth buzz for your sequel.
In fact, blackmail is the currency of social progress.
From your neighborhood grocer to the teacher at your school
to the man who helps you steal HBO, everyone responds to
blackmail.
before, it's easy to practice at home on your friends and
family.
Simply follow the instructional pamphlet that your teacher
hands out after the end of the film.
And finally, there's one last tool at our disposal for
making the sequel feel fresh and exciting.
And that's packaging the game with collector's edition
merchandise.
If you order the Stanley Parable 2, you'll receive this
cow's egg.
A single egg will produce over a thousand cows, which are,
of course, the sequel to pigs and there you have it
everything there is to know about producing the stanley
parable too of course you may know that there is also a game
titled the stanley parable ultra deluxe so which game is the
true sequel to the stanley parable looks so confused oh
sorry billy one which the child soldiers have been working
around the clock to come up with an answer to come on more
gunpowder research the conclusion they've reached is who
gives a matters is that it's more content for you to cram
down your insatiable gullet you don't want thoughtful i'm
eating all this content i'm eating all this content you just
want to eat bubble gum and cheated hopscotch so how do you
cheat at hopscotch do your civic duty and bully your parents
into buying you every version of the stanley parable 2 on
every platform i already do that with metal gear song their
parents as well it's through community other people to play
metal gear harmony and connection.
And it's only through this connection that we'll defeat Time
Dracula once and for all.
Don't let the time-traveling vampires win.
Buy the Stanley Parable 2 and pledge to support all sequels.
For today, tomorrow, and into the great unknowable beyond.
The end.
Nice.
Well, that was Fun.
Oh, wait!
Hold on.
There was one more thing.
There was one more thing at the very end.
Oh, no!
One second.
Billy!
In memoriam of Billy!
1953 1956 Oh god Billy Oh no no Was that everything now?
Yeah okay
Okay I'm continuing the game Everybody I think we can
actually finally exit I think we can actually Finally leave
Curse you time Dracula are curse you okay this is all new
for me now actually i never even watched that i think i was
going to watch it before and i forgot so now all right have
you seen everything you wanted to yeah to move on now
phantom is my favorite react content youtuber now oh oh whoa
new mugs why does he look so scary it's like uh what's that
what's that game layers of stanley oh please no screenshots
everybody oh what's this so stanley what do you think do you
like all of the new features i really do i know it's not
exactly clear yet how exactly these features will come
together as one single coherent video game i can feel it in
my soul it's going to work somewhere say let's do an
experiment okay i'll arrange these new features together and
we'll see whether or not it coheres into a meaningful
gameplay experience okay no screenshots no screenshots are
you ready yes here it is i give you the stanley parable two
oh wow um well i mean there's potential here right it's sort
of okay never mind hold on let me do a different arrangement
okay yes yes this is much better i feel good about this i'm
jim oh my gosh jim
who am i kidding stanley the jump circle wow this isn't a
coherent video game at all it's a lot of gags and i do very
much enjoy creating gags but they don't add up to anything i
wanted more than anything to create a sequel that would
capture all the magic of the first game i wanted fans to
love it no matter how good these gags are they wouldn't
stand on their own they would need the structure in the
gameplay of the original wait maybe that's it i can take the
original stanley parable and simply well insert a few of my
new features into it tastefully of course of course Ladies
and gentlemen, welcome back.
Thank you.
Would it possibly work?
Why can't it be so sad in there?
But it would need a really, really tremendous title screen.
A title screen that says with bold and uncompromising
conviction, this is the Stanley Parable Tool.
Okay.
Okay, I'm excited.
Alright, perfect.
Go ahead.
I'm closing my eyes.
Oh!
The Stanley... Oh!
PT?
The Stanley Parable 2.
Wow!
It's kinda creepy!
Quit the desktop!
I guess we gotta begin the game, you guys.
Click to skip.
This is the story of a man named Stanley.
Stanley worked for a company in a big building where he
was...
I decorated it!
Four, two, seven.
His job was simple.
He sat at his desk in room four, two, seven, and he pushed
buttons on a keyboard.
Oh my gosh.
Wait.
Our bucket?
Where's the bucket?
How long to push them?
And in what order?
Yeah, we got the balloons and everything.
There he goes.
Every day of every month of every year.
Although others might have considered it sorely, Stanley
relished every moment that the boys came in.
But so he had been made exactly for this job.
And Stanley was happy.
He was happy.
And then one day something very peculiar happened.
Something that would forever change Stanley.
Something he would never quite forget.
Two, two, two, two, two, two, two, two, two, two.
When he realized that not one single order had arrived on
the monitor for him to follow.
No one showed up to give him instructions.
No, I wanted the other balloon.
I wanted the other ones.
Never in all his years at the company had this happened.
This complete isolation.
Something was very clearly wrong.
Shocked, frozen solid, Stanley found himself unable to move
for the longest time.
But as he came to his wits and regained his senses, he got
up from his desk and stepped out of his office.
I hope you get well eventually, babe.
Happy 12th birthday, babe.
I like how you guys both said the opposite things at the
same time.
Okay, here we go, I guess.
All of his co-workers were gone.
What could it mean?
Stanley decided to go to the meeting room.
Even on the lamps.
Maybe he'd simply missed a memo.
Woo!
Happy 12th birthday, Stepanese!
My favorite Stepanese in the world.
Stanley picked up the bucket.
Oh!
Woo!
We got a bucket.
Stanley clutched the bucket tightly to his chest and entered
the door on his left.
Well, what if I don't?
I mean, I know I like the bucket.
I know the bucket, like, gives me that...
That...
What should I do, bucket?
What should I do?
Okay.
This was not the correct way to the meeting room.
But Stanley had felt the bucket calling to him, telling him
that the employee lounge was simply the place to be.
Simply the place to be.
Here it was.
Had the bucket turned out to be correct?
Was this better than the meeting room?
Yes, Stanley thought to himself.
Yes, perhaps it truly was.
Perhaps it truly was.
How insightful the bucket turned out to be.
My God, everything is redoubbed with the bucket.
The bucket's so awesome.
The bucket was wrong.
Never.
Not at all.
Stanley took the door on his left to go back to the meeting
room.
What does this way go to?
Oh, this one is, uh, yeah, where I fell before.
what was this way again oh and this way oh we went
downstairs okay yeah the bucket's never wrong kind of want
to ride it though no said the bucket no don't go to the
meeting room go somewhere else a cargo lift yes go there go
to the cargo go to the cargo lift no don't go to the meeting
room
ride the lift all the way to the top oh there's something up
there i need you to do oh my god there's even a balloon at
the top why or how this bucket was speaking to him it should
have alarmed him of course because buckets can't talk but
stanley chose not to think about this obvious we're gonna go
we're gonna go he was only convinced that the bucket had
spoken to him and he unthinkingly did whatever the bucket
asked okay sounds good no in here said the bucket go into
this dark room over here over here stanley once again obeyed
blindly this room's not very dark this room's pretty bright
actually oh oh oh oh are you sure bucket oh okay
up the phone, said the bucket.
Pick up the phone, and it will take us back home, where we
can go about life together.
Really?
Thanks for the five gifts I didn't do.
Oh, customer buy, thank you!
This is the sad story of a man named Stanley and his bucket.
Where's my bucket?
Once upon a time, I gave Stanley a bucket because I thought
he was lonely and could use a friend.
And then, very distressingly, he began to believe the bucket
could speak to him.
Is this my house?
Oh my god, Stanley lives in an Ikea, like, uh, setup.
There's the bucket.
Hello, Stanley, it's me.
Oh, hello, Stanley, it's me, your bucket.
Press you to take me to walk with you.
Oh.
The Stanley Parable Reassurance Bucket was merely meant to
provide the comforting glow of companionship.
Oh my gosh, thank you so much for that fence again.
It doesn't literally talk and give you orders.
Whatever Stanley is hearing the bucket say to him is just in
his head.
Oh, here it is.
Press O to take me back home with you.
Where's my bucket?
I don't know how I can convince him.
I don't know if he'll listen to me.
Thought I lost him for a second.
Press G to go back to whack.
Well, I'll try anyway.
can you hear me bucket bucket uh bucket can you hear me
bucket it can't think bucket bucket where are you oh thank
you all it would ever truly do for you is effectively
transfer a liquid from one location I don't hear anybody
else I only hear the bucket it doesn't do anything else
don't listen to the loud man press R for us to go back home
oh you see he's not listening he's still taking orders from
Bucket!
Where are you, Bucket!
Where are you, Bucket?
Now all he cares about is his awful bucket.
Where's the bucket?
Where's my bucket?
Narrator.
Oh, here.
Press O to ignore anyone in your life except for me.
Well, guys.
It's a lot of those.
Thank you.
It's sad.
I suppose he doesn't need me anymore.
From now on, he's just going to cling to this bucket, this
cold, empty bucket, this sort of shiny bucket.
Well, I'll give it this.
The bucket does have a nice shine to it.
Yeah, it does.
You believe I'm real, don't you, Stanley?
Press H to go back home.
Yes, I suppose on closer inspection that it doesn't quite
look like your average hardware store bucket.
It's just a little more, um, what am I trying to say?
Sturdier, more capable of transporting liquid.
Yeah, I see.
Like it would be better at moving an amount of water from
one room to another.
Press R to relive the same day with me over and over.
Oh my God, what am I saying?
a carrying water from room to room.
It's a bucket.
It's literally just a bucket.
Why do I feel some need to point out the ways in which it's
so much more than just a regular bucket?
Press I to go home to work to home to work to home.
Oh, no.
I'm having feelings for the bucket.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What's going on?
Why do I want to be with the bucket?
Hear what the bucket has to say.
Do anything it asks.
What's wrong with me?
I don't understand.
Perhaps if I had the bucket, this would be less confusing.
Yes.
The bucket could tell me what to do in this troublesome
situation.
Is the bucket waiting for me on the bed?
The bucket.
I mean, this is so nice.
I didn't, I didn't, you know, I thought you would be too
tired after such a long day but you even even despite that
you put all of this together for me bucket i mean wow it's
just so beautiful it's just no bucket no bucket Stanley give
me the bucket no give me the bucket Stanley i need it no
close your eyes go
back to work step Stanley.
Go back to work, Stanley.
Bucket?
All of his co-workers were gone.
What could it mean?
Bucket!
Stanley decided to go to the meeting room.
Perhaps he had simply missed a memo.
Stanley lifted the bucket into his arms.
Ooh!
And a wave of comfort rushed over him.
Minch Phantom, parasocial for a bucket.
Trust the bucket, believe in the bucket.
bucket that was such a fun ending that was so funny i love
that oh wait oh it got the second input how's that in there
i think though i think i might call it quits here bucket
time i don't go i wish there was a way oh the sequel is now
paused wait this is so crazy um I wish there was a way to
know how many endings you had left, you know what I mean?
That ending was fantastic.
I think that was a good one to end on, I think.
I think so.
Send the bucket to space.
Achievement.
Oh, I guess an achievement, yeah, probably.
Let me see.
Oh, I've unlocked only 4 out of 11?
Wait, view my achievements.
Quit the game and start it again.
Wait.
Oh, oh.
of these what is it a a a a a a a oh the test achievement
please ignore uh speed run complete the stanley parable in
under four minutes don't play the stanley parable for 10
years it doesn't have like a list of the achievements hmm
why so bless you oh sorry it's because i was holding onto
the bucket you know bucket will last forever long live the
bucket me thanks for a month thank you um but um yeah let me
see but yeah there is one that says don't play the stanley
parable for 10 years and then play the stanley parable for
the entire duration of a tuesday what is that starting at
like 12 a.m to 2 11 59 p.m this is a great this is great to
Stuffed shark!
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday stuff.
Sometimes I say stupid shark.
Sorry for calling you stupid.
Happy birthday!
Thank you for the super chat.
But yeah, this was a lot of fun.
It was good seeing things that I've never seen before and
remembering things that I have seen before sometimes.
And then also my game not breaking so I could do the bucket,
you know?
But I think, I don't know.
How many endings are there even?
Be wary of the time, vampires.
Yeah, yeah, right?
Oh, my gosh.
Five clicks?
No, I'm gonna do 10 clicks.
I'm gonna do 11 clicks.
I'm gonna be, I'm gonna do 50 clicks.
I don't even know what you're talking about.
I don't even keep spamming five clicks.
Why do I feel like I'm in the ice monkey all over again?
Thank you for the bucket stream.
Just want to say, even if you didn't win, your match with
Philly and last night was fantastic.
Even though I teleported and then I...
I teleported and then...
And then I...
20 plus endings in the bucket doubles it?
No way.
Oh my god, stupid shark!
Thank you for the 20 gift!
Thank you!
0, 0, 0 Ice Monkey.
5 click, 5 click, 5 click of Ice Monkey.
I teleported behind her and it didn't even make a
difference.
SMH.
But it's okay, I beat Matara and that's all that really
mattered.
Plus, I think I would have felt really bad if I had made it
the finals because i was i was kind of a joke entry so i was
kind of a joke entry so you know um but it was it was a lot
of fun um actually i'm going to move us over to uh the mid
cafe give me a second first off i gotta change
oh oh Uh...
I'm not naked.
I'm just...
Uh...
Don't, uh...
Anyway, uh...
Hold on, I'm getting dressed.
Hold on.
Hold on, I'm getting dressed!
Let me exit out of the game too.
Quit to menu...
Quit to desktop.
Let's put on something chill.
Some music.
Just for a little bit.
Because I have some stuff I need to take care of.
Uh.
Sorry, hold on.
There we go.
Okie dokie.
I'm all changed.
Oh, my arms.
My arms.
There we go.
I'll better.
Talk strings.
Thanks for the vibe gifted.
Thank you.
The whips singing karaoke is so cute.
I know, right?
Show them chicken wings.
Is this what you wanted?
Is this what you like?
Those two are still cooking in the...
It's Memorial Day!
Of course they're having a barbecue.
Gosh, duh.
She's gonna take off.
Oh, that was so fun.
Oh my gosh.
Maybe I'll do a part two and get some other of the endings.
like a little daunting I feel to get to first how much is in
the game but I'm really happy that I could uh at least get
the bucket at least the bucket ending was so fun I really
like that one ducky thanks for the vibe gifted thank you
thank you thank you what was your favorite bit maybe the
bucket I know it's like the most recent one but synapse
things are the super Jot.
Marisa, thanks for the Super Jot.
Um.
Uh.
But I know it was like, maybe because it was like the, it
felt newer.
But, um, I also really liked, uh, the, the, because, because
my game broke before in the hole, um, I never got to see
like all the special things that went on with it.
So that was really fun too.
And the skip button.
The skip button one really makes you just kind of, has like
a good, I don't want, It's not a feels good.
But it's like a good...
It makes you feel something.
You know what I mean?
It makes you feel.
Oh, the bottom of the mind control room song!
Yes!
That was so good!
Oh my gosh, I was so happy we got that one.
It was really awesome.
It's very somber.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But that's crazy how much replayability this game has, you
know.
So this week will be a bit of a short week Of a stream I'll
be streaming I'll have a I have to still figure out what I'm
streaming Because I'll be going to Afkai For this weekend
And then from Afkai Matara and I will be going to To Japan
So While we're there We're kind of going to be like
streaming every other day so she'll stream one day and I'll
stream uh the next day and so on and so forth so uh probably
won't have a schedule for that um so I really apologize it's
been kind of like schedule this even last week and this week
and I didn't mean to not have a schedule last week um I
think um I kind of mentioned it uh well no I mentioned I
think I mentioned all the Patreon It was funny because I
saw, I would see some comments being like, I wonder if Mint
is keeping her schedule a secret because of WrestleTuber,
you know, because she doesn't want to spoil that she's going
to be a guest.
And I'll be honest.
Uh, that was not the case.
I, I just, I just didn't put one out.
I just didn't want to put one out because I was indecisive
about what I wanted to do.
because i'm like trying to figure out how do i get ready for
for my trips and and planning other stuff and contacting
sending emails and it's been a little it's been a little bit
overwhelming but um thinking mint is more clever than we
thought no actually the uh the wrestle tuber was pretty last
minute um but uh i'm gonna glad that i could participate um
last night last night uh doki and i we were up i was up
until like almost 4 a.m uh talking with her we were catching
up so um i was really glad i was really happy um because um
i was i was um i don't want to say too much about it um I
was like kind of nervous about reaching out.
I mostly I mostly kept my distance for a while because I
didn't want to make her uncomfortable.
ultimately, I'm glad that I did.
yeah.
I had a lot of fun for WrestleTuber.
Yeah.
you have no idea how well the oh the shippers are eating
this week uh uh i'm happy for you um i'm happy for you
but yeah um
They are eating good.
I'll be honest, I've seen fan art.
There's been a lot of fan art.
So there's been a lot of fan art.
So thank you guys.
What is bro yapping about?
And even Matara joining hers was like super last minute too.
And, you know, it was funny.
She sent me a couple of voice lines.
I was like, can you send me some stuff?
And then I'll send it over to her and to Doki.
And she can send it to her editor and this and that.
Matara was funny AF.
I know.
I wish.
I hope next time she can participate in person if she wants
to.
But I thought it was really funny that even I felt bad.
I was like, you're on vacation.
Sorry.
but the the editor cooked so much in such a short amount of
time they did it it was so great we're happy for the both of
you thanks for sticking around thank you thank you i can't
tell you i can't tell you guys how much it like i how much i
what's the word like went back and forth how much i was just
like i don't want make her uncomfortable but i wanna i was
like i missed my friend so and it was it was something that
was really like eating at me for a while and i was just like
i don't know how she feels about me anymore so um yeah but
i'm glad it worked out because last thing i would want to do
is make uncomfortable so um
but we we the first night that we like um caught up a little
bit i was i was up so late we were just like talking and
catching up and um last night the same thing too afterwards
i was just like i was like oh she's probably so tired she
probably doesn't want to like hang out too much but but then
i was like i was like girl you need to go get some water
the geography argument I'm sure she appreciated it it was
such a fun event it was great to see you guys stream
together yeah and then afterwards like some of the other
participants messaged me as well and I was really happy
about that so maybe I can make more friends with people yeah
but yippee yippee manifesting that lime yeah she was so
sweet after the first day she added me like in the server
that we were in for the event she was like she was like she
was like it was nice talking with you finally even though it
was like in this environment canonically who was the
security guard you killed what do you mean canonically I
killed several people I killed I killed people people were
happy to see you around who saw that coming everyone else
what do you mean what do you mean aren't you a member of
Philly Inspirate Crew now I am I am I am I remember you
promised someone a collab of finishing ghost trip why no why
no i'm kind of i have a lot basically once i get back from
japan i plan on really uh hitting the ground running um i've
been trying to plan stuff for my anniversary my not four
year anniversary anniversary my one year anniversary i've
been trying to plan stuff for that um i've been trying to
plan stuff for um For my...
Maybe I shouldn't say that.
People love you, you dorkoid.
What does that mean?
But, uh...
My anniversary?
Oh my god.
Wait!
It was so great to see you at Wrestle Timber.
I'm really glad you and Doki had a good time catching up.
Thank you!
Truly made me smile is how YouTube didn't seem to miss a
beat.
Immediately into the half laughing, half screaming and it
just...
I guess that's just...
I don't know.
I guess...
I don't know how to say.
Maybe it is our destiny to always...
Or to act that way.
Maybe I felt compelled even though I have never met her
before.
But yeah.
I know it's shocking, but so many people love, adore, and
support you.
You are amazing.
Oh!
I got home from Panama.
I saw a lot of fan merch of you.
See you all, hopefully.
See you!
I've been to all...
Dorkoid is the yellow one, regardless.
We love you, Mito.
What I mean by that is, we love you.
Stop it.
Dorkoid.
But, um...
I love the part where Doki accidentally called herself Small
Brain and you were like, yep.
She's a bird after all.
You know.
Favorite moment from WrestleTuber?
Ah.
I think Yu San's entrance was so...
I didn't even know that was going to happen.
So...
I didn't...
That was my first time seeing that too.
So, it was really, really something.
Will you let us know when you get in the robot at Offkay?
I didn't get a meeting greet, but still want to meet you.
I think that's still being planned.
But once I know anything, I know it's like kind of last
minute.
Because Offkay is this weekend.
Oh my gosh, Offkay is this weekend, you guys.
Oh my gosh.
But I will let you guys know as soon as I know.
because yeah I don't don't know what thanks for being at the
truck event thank you yeah the truck event was really fun
too everybody was super duper hype and hold on sorry and
there were so many people I was I was really shocked
actually right before I went on I was like messaging my
friend because she was there Oh gosh, they kind of
sandwiched me between two DJs.
I'm gonna bring the mood down so much because I'm like, not
a DJ, it's not like continuous music.
Like I'm gonna be singing and it's gonna be weird.
And she was like, no, it'll be fine.
You'll just, you'll have a lot of fun.
And so I was really, really actually quite nervous about it.
And possible block game adventure collab with who?
Maybe.
I don't really know how I can feel more proud.
Thank you for existing the way you are, but don't stop.
Thank you.
I'm so happy you chose to reach out to interacting and speak
content and she could use a friend who can call her out on
her shit.
Yeah.
me out we call out each other i feel i actually think i get
dumber around her i actually think i'm like i'm physically
stupid more stupid when she's around
rachel tober was awesome it's so great to hear you took you
time outside of the event to hang thanks for sharing it
means a lot of to us better social weirdos we love you guys
you deserve
Brain cell sharing is real
Oh my gosh Rice Nat and Orca right next to each other Please
stop Stop
What was I going to say though?
Don't call them out like that Oh, they were right next to
each other.
I can't help what I see.
I can't help what pops up on my Twitter, you know?
I can't help it.
Good to see you at the truck.
Thank you!
But yeah, so I was really nervous for the truck.
And then, in the end, everybody was...
The energy was so there.
People were lifting.
There was Kujaku.
There was so much going on.
It was a lot, a lot of fun.
And people, there are people on top of cars, on top of
trucks watching.
We love Anikuda.
Anikuda, psycho!
Oh, his sweater has been so good.
Oh, they built a fire pit out of glow sticks.
Yeah, if anybody went to see me, and I've never been to
Anikuda before, i hope that you got a little bit of a taste
of why i love idols so much and idol and like you know doing
calls and um just stuff like that like it's just a such a
fun energy that um that um truly only can be felt in that
kind of in that kind of place so oh it was so fun though I
felt so happy I just felt so fulfilled on on Saturday I was
honestly just this weekend this past weekend I felt so
fulfilled I felt really I probably felt the happiest I have
in in quite a while.
I'm really happy.
Wish I could have gone to the truck event even though it was
a drive-away, but Russell Tuber was wild.
Glad you had fun and hope you had fun in JP too.
Thank you, Jay!
Thank you for the welcome, Silva.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
There's still things that I'm trying to catch up on.
some things that I feel like I still feel I still feel
really nervous about or uncertain I guess maybe is a better
word because I feel sort of like how do I say this?
How do I say this without being weird?
Everything's weird though.
I feel I think basically I...
I don't know how to say it.
Sorry, I'm not very articulate.
Step by stuff.
I guess that's mainly it.
I'm just trying to take things step by step.
But I'm trying not to...
Lose out.
I'm trying not to be so passive that I...
Lose out on opportunity.
it's kind of it's hard it's hard it's hard going from going
from a place that took care of everything for you to having
to do everything on my own and you know not knowing at all
what to do or how to do anything and being by myself um so
um oh sorry i'm i'm biting my tongue a little bit here but
uh it's a big adjustment i bet yeah so um but hopefully
hopefully i can get things um moving especially once i get
back from japan hopefully i can get things moving forward
and you know know moving forward means not only just more
opportunities for me but then also more things for you guys
as well because um thank you for not becoming a grocer stop
why did you guys always bring up that i was thinking why did
you guys always bring that up oh my gosh we believe in you
thank you yeah it's
okay to be weird weird droid What does that mean?
Oh But um It's because it's so upsetting you even thought
about it It's surreal to think it was a possibility Because
it's such a shocking thing to hear what?
What do you mean?
Oh my gosh, thank you for the aquasupa I'd like that wait
like what me to become a grocer
This is so Akasupa telling me to quit.
If you became a grocer, I would buy food every day.
I would just be back as a normal ghost.
Don't worry, I'd avoid the self-checkout for you.
No.
Yeah, but
I don't know, maybe I'll I was going to say maybe I'll do it
in my free time, but I don't have much free time anymore,
really.
Kater, thanks for the super chat.
You're weird, so don't mind being weird.
You know what I call my cat?
When he's being weird, I say stop being weird.
weirds though like stop being a weirds though you're being a
weirds though i don't know why i say it like that you know
when you talk to animals and like your vocabulary breaks
it's like when you talk to babies why sell the mint when you
can be the mint johnny thank you for the 10 gifted thank you
so much thank you thank you does pies ever act weird oh all
the time she is also a weirds though
imagine if your idol was she retired and you bumped into her
at the register of your local 7-eleven it's crazy you almost
did that i mean that happens though there was one akb-48
member she quit when she graduated i don't know if she i
don't know if she um opened the ramen place but she like
started working at a ramen shop basically
my friend really wishes to meet you at afkai expo but sold
out instantly sold out i thought it was a lottery i hope to
see you there though at your panel i love you so much can't
wait for us to see you afkai thank you fantastic thank you
thank you thank you
it is a lottery it was and then there was a sale of left Oh!
Who applied and then didn't want to come see me?
But it got taken up instantly.
I had no idea that there was going to be an open ticket
sale.
Oh, I had no idea.
I thought it was only a lottery.
Pastel Sonico!
Sending love mint.
Thank you!
Thank you.
favorite weirds though.
Thanks, Nixie.
What a crazy person that could have been us.
Yeah, that could have been me.
That could have been me.
You'll never guess who won it.
Oh gosh, I'm scared.
There was only one left.
There was only one left?
What?
Actually, just one?
That's crazy.
That only...
The one piece.
That's insane that there was...
Just like...
The one person canceled and then the one opened up.
That's so funny.
Oh my gosh.
Are you guys okay?
Trying to get the one?
Wowie.
I'm excited though.
I'm so excited.
my first convention oh my god
and um oh my gosh it's gonna be busy busy busy weekend
though true gotcha oh sorry no no win
oh sorry david i just saw your thing your don't know too i
haven't been here long but as i see it if you have always
been loved as an indie that's active for less than a year.
As an indie that's active for less than a year, you had more
wiki entries than some much bigger VTubers.
Wiki, wiki, wiki, wiki entries!
So happy I became a member.
Here's to the future.
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you!
Wiki, wiki.
Wiki, wiki, wiki.
Wait.
Wiki entries.
Wiki.
Wiki entry, like a Wikipedia?
Like a...
There's the VTuber Wiki though, right?
Thank you.
Thank you for whoever's updating that.
I suppose.
Probably hadn't been updated in a really long time.
Good luck reaching out to new people.
I know it can be hard sometimes, but I know you can do it.
Have a good night.
Thanks, Meryl.
Oh yeah, it's pretty late now, wasn't it?
Um, if you guys had the day off, maybe people in the United
States, then I hope you had a good day off.
The Feet Wiki.
Shut up, Cole.
What are you at?
I saw the figure you made.
It looks so good.
But don't put it on the Feet Wiki, please.
It looks so awesome.
Thank you for making it.
CD?
Is that how you say your name?
Said I.
Welcome to membership.
Thank you.
The crazy thing about the VTuber wiki is that anyone can
edit it.
Even me?
I'm gonna go edit my own wiki.
I'm just gonna copy and paste the Metal Gear wiki.
I'm gonna copy and paste the synopsis of Metal Gear Solid.
I'm gonna replace my it.
Don't do that.
There's probably some people that would be so upset.
like you just erased all their hard work and then and then
and then they're like they come back they're just like oh
something else happened with mint phantom i'm gonna i'm
gonna update her wiki and it's all gone and replaced by
metal gear synopsis
don't get banned but i get banned for that it's my own wiki.
This is the information that people need to read, okay?
This is the information.
May I ask how is the stinkiest boy doing?
Thanks for asking, Sham.
Andrico's thanks for the 10 gift aid!
Uh...
I forgot... Wait, hold on.
I forgot if you mentioned this before, but do you accept
snacks as gifts at Ofkai?
Um... Sealed snacks, uh...
I... Probably...
I think it's technically said no food.
Um...
I kind of, I don't, I don't really mind.
I mean, I don't know.
You can fill the page with all new mint lore.
But, um, um,
um, Butaro, Butaro, Butaro, Butaro.
He's been acting a little weird lately.
Um, lately he's been, like, just, um, very much, like,
hanging out under the bed.
And I can't get him out.
Like, he'll eat.
doesn't hang out with me i think he is in this weird
adjustment with um with paus and that like paus started
sleeping in the bed just a little bit and i think it's made
him a little self-conscious or not self-conscious a little
um worried like he maybe is like his his personal space is
getting taken over so um how old is he he's pretty old but
he's still still very active like he's still running around
like they play together so but then he just kind of goes and
retreats under the bed yeah he's very territorial he's super
duper territorial so um uh but he's sour about having an
interloper yeah which is i thought it was weird because um
it's been over a month now but um i think because it don't
it he only started acting this way once she started sleeping
in the bed with me so i think he was just like whoa whoa
whoa i'm fine with her being around but in the bed um that
is my spot i won't be able to harvest any in time for afkai
but i think if i can get some honey from my beehives would
she want some technically it's food and not sealed no
judgment if not oh morning dude that sounds so awesome but
honestly i also worry about traveling with it um and i'm
afraid that maybe even staff would reject it um so i'm so
sorry i hope that sounds i would love your honey i want to
get fresh honey
i recently got a new cat and my old cat has been worried by
give her cuddles to make sure she remembers she's not being
replaced yeah i've been trying to do that a lot with him so
i'm like i'm just like him lots of hugs and kisses so
hopefully he knows that he's not being replaced
um okay guys i think i'm gonna go i gotta get some more
water so i think i'm gonna go head out um i will i'm
probably okay so i'm gonna make a schedule for this week but
i'm also gonna write like on it like off kai and then also
for next week and the week after I'm basically gonna be gone
three weeks now that I think about it wait not three weeks
one uh two weeks two weeks but um I will still be streaming
so um and then once I get back once I get back from Japan
thank you so the five gift and thank you you guys I was
gonna ask for permission but I'm not asking I'm not get
back.
Metal Gear Saturdays are back on the menu, baby!
Whippy!
I'm starting at Metal Gear Solid 1 and we'll be playing
Metal Gear up until whenever I feel like stopping.
So, um, yippee!
Yippee!
Does Fortnite a snake count?
Oh my gosh, I should play that, right?
I should, I wonder if I could get Doki to play Fortnite with
me.
I should ask her.
So, we're finally getting acid.
Yeah, yeah!
So, I did.
I know I did the Twin Snakes some time ago, but I really,
really just want to have all of the Metal Gears kind of on
my resume in my channel.
So, I hope you guys don't mind that I'll be playing a lot of
Metal Gear.
until probably the end of the year.
Are we getting Survive?
Oh, that's another thing I need to play with, don't kiss.
There's too much stuff.
Ellie's so hard.
Thank you for the Super Jet.
Thank you.
Hoping for Ace Combat 2.
I think once I'm done with the Metal Gear stuff, I will go
into Ace Combat.
And then I think after Ace Combat, I might even start Xeno
Blade.
It is a long journey.
Time to put Doki into playing MGS.
But, um, it'll be like a long, I feel like almost probably a
year's worth of just like long story-based games.
you can, I guess, look forward to that.
Yippee!
Um, and of course, and of course, it's not just the only
stuff that i'll be playing so membu fortnite maybe that'd be
fun wait can we do like a lobby or is it would i have to can
i do a lobby or monado time yes you can is ape escape three
part of metal gear solid completionism asking for a totally
not monkey friend i want to do as much metal gear stuff as i
can so it is not off the table helping for a minecraft
adventure with doki maybe finding diamonds again i don't
think i've ever gone on a diamond thing But I will see.
We will see.
A manga card.
Thanks for the 10 gifted.
Thank you.
But yeah, that's just kind of some of my future plans that
I've been thinking about.
And like I said, I know I've played Metal Gear before, so I
hope that it will still be a fun experience for people.
I was kind of nervous because I was like, what if people
don't want to watch me play if I've already played
everything before?
And I already know all the twists and I know this and that.
but um uh hopefully like I said I kind of just want the
games on my channel so if people come to my channel they're
just like oh wow she really likes metal gear you can always
play MGS 1 integral English and VR missions to check them
off your resume and then you can officially say you played
all versions of MGS 1 true one thing that I wanted to do was
um uh was play the different versions of the game.
So basically, like, if I played the HD collection of
something, maybe I'll play the original, like, PS2 version
of it this time.
So, um, I'm still working on that to, uh, um, to give it a
little bit of difference.
Um, hey, Bozo, do better.
Yo, oh, do better.
I'm sorry, I'll do it.
You better do whatever the hell you want.
I completely rented a stoop.
Stop!
I'm gonna cry again with Peace Walk running.
Me too.
Oh gosh, I just, I'm actually most excited to play MGS2
again.
I think at the end I'm just gonna be a little baby ball and
just like I don't know there's something about the end of
MGS 2 that makes me feel so even though it was riding so
silly dumb stupid ah but yeah um anyway do better mint
okay okay I'm gonna go to bed and And, um, I'll see you guys
tomorrow.
Don't know what I'm playing tomorrow.
Oh, wait.
Maybe I think I do know.
Why don't we wait?
Uh, I had an idea for something I was going to do tomorrow,
and I don't remember.
So, I'm going to sleep on it.
No, not Metal Gear Survive.
It's the Black Sushi.
I have to do it.
Just a little bit.
Any chance of uploading your truck rave performance to
members to premiere on one of your off days?
For those of us who can't make it to off class, Oh, I can
try.
Oh, the one that I recorded.
I pre-recorded.
Yes.
Let me write that down so I can have it set up as a premiere
for the weekend.
Upload.
Oh.
What just happened?
jumped.
I did a jump.
Upload truck to members.
What was that?
I don't even know.
Okie dokie.
Thank you guys for hanging out with me.
Thank you guys for spending your Monday with me.
If you haven't watched the podcast yet, you can watch it
while both of us and Matara will be MIA a little bit this
weekend.
Thank you, STF2!
Thanks for the vibe gifted!
Thank you!
You have eight remaining jumps down.
And, um, it was a nice podcast.
I'm glad.
I'm glad!
Thank you guys for listening.
Thank you.
And I'll see you guys tomorrow!
Same time, same time, same time.
Otsumita!
Oh!
You know what time it is.
Oh.
Do-do.
Let me tell you something.
Are there something weird?
Sleeping in your bed.
Ow!
Let me tell you something.
Busting makes me feel good.
Do you like the sharp glasses?
Busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting,
busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting,
busting.
Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin
Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin
Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Pocky donut, thank
you for the five.
Gifted, gifted, gifted, gifted, gifted, gifted, gifted.
Yeah, yeah.
Busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting,
busting, busting, busting, busting, makes you feel good,
feel good, feel good, feel good.
Please remember to rub in the wind to Matara on the next
podcast.
know it freaky ghost made morning dude thank you freaky man
baby ow ow ow if you're all alone let me sleep in your bed
let me tell you something sleep and makes me feel good
freaky ghost diaper where'd you get the diaper from I I
ain't afraid of no sleep.
I ain't afraid of no bed.
An invisible bed.
Freaky ghost bed!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Boistin, boistin, boistin, boistin, boistin, boistin, boin
Boistin, boin!
Darnins!
Thank you!
Yeah, yeah, yeah Thank you!
Feel good!
Yippee!
Thongs!
Thongs, thank you as well!
For that 10.
Wait, was it 10?
Wait, can I count?
What was it?
Uh...
Oh, five!
Oh, thank you for the five cryptid.
Bye bye.
Thank you.