three two one swap hey nothing
nothing nothing you've been like dealing with this for years
now why now you laugh
nothing nothing hi guys hey everybody so first off i just
want you guys to know we were we were selling technical
difficulties for at least 30 minutes oh my god we were like
so prepared yeah we were so prepared guys yeah it was just
very unfortunate that the last five minutes that we had like
just something came up unexpectedly it was crazy it was so
crazy oh yeah and it was on mince side not on my whoa wait
wait wait um i i plead mac and cheese you plead germany
People wouldn't fall out.
Yeah, okay, look.
The reason why I didn't start and Mint started before me was
because Doka mean, we had to connect to a special server to
be there.
And I forgot, I was connected to that special server.
So I was streaming over at Germany.
So someone out there was watching the starting screen in
Germany and being like, well, where did this person come
from?
It's like Grandpa Joe, just trying to watch like jeopardy
and he's like the worst part was the star screen was like
not even playing it was just a still image so he must be
freaking out right now and being like aliens or some shit
how do you say that in german what do you think i know
german well you okay miss invited to a german convention
look i would say an european convention is a is a convention
all of eu europe is not just german mint wow gotta open your
mind it was in germany yeah you gotta open your mind and be
more inclusive to the other countries in europe okay name
every country in europe all right european union who's not
in the european union Well, then they're not European and...
Oh, oh, oh!
And I'm joking.
Guys, that was a joke, guys.
That was a joke, everybody.
Wow, and now she's lumping everyone in Europe under the
European Union.
Wow.
No one can have individuality here.
Oh, yeah?
You name every country in Europe then.
I already asked you.
Oh, you're ragging me on about my lack of European
knowledge.
You think I know?
I don't know why you're ragging me.
If I could have named random countries and you wouldn't know
because you don't know Europe apparently.
Okay, name three countries and I'll tell you which one is
real.
You know, we're going to play that.
All right, give me a sec.
Oh, no, she has a Google.
Give me a sec.
I also have google You gotta google That's not knowing the
answer If you're googling I don't know Alright Oh what are
you googling huh I'm googling No I said nice thing I googled
nice things to send to my mom Bye Oh so you're not even
prioritizing the stream No that i'm waiting on you doki
you're the one holding us up okay all right all right fine
fine okay peso why are you laughing wait what peso was the
currency though malawi malawi which one's the fake which
what's the third one
irchia i would like to phone a friend You don't know either!
They were all real.
They were all in Africa.
At least that Europe!
You said you know every country in the world.
So I gave you every country in the world.
I gave you specific...
You don't know any African countries.
That's fucked up.
I know.
I know some, I know Zanzibar, then...
I gave you three and you couldn't even tell which one was
the real one, but they were all real.
We said, we said Europe!
Yeah, and they, you wait, wait, countries in the entire
world.
So it's like, entire world, huh?
Okay, entire world!
Oh my god, this is, this is slander.
Oh my god.
Anyway, should we play the game?
okay i'm over playing geogesser all right we're playing
geogesser now you're right i should select a south america
country oh yeah how many countries have you been to in south
america like zero
i've been to one yeah which one was it Oh yeah.
Yeah, but you were there for like one second.
Does that really count?
No, I talked to the locals and they said, Papa Frita is so
small.
That's all you got from it.
What even was the fucking context?
I was eating really small fries McDonald's at the airport so
they were like making fun of you yeah they were she was like
I need to take a picture of this you're eating the small
fries yeah so I turned up mint a little bit guys I turned
her up so you guys can hear her better um it's not like
she's giving us any good input or anything but I'm gonna I'm
gonna go I'm gonna send you to Brazil we're gonna go to
Brazil guys don't you admit you're coming to Brazil all
right are you ready all right so apparently we found out
that um we can actually potentially kill people in in this
game oh yeah and like um and like we if something if any of
that actually happens wait so if like my characters die do i
just stop playing the game i think you just take over i
think you just take over a different character okay maybe
maybe i don't know we'll find out i guess we will see when
you kill off your character also um also there's quick time
events by the way yeah do you know that this is basically
like until dawn have you played yeah and then my chat was
like oh man Min and QuickTime events.
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't know.
I'm good at the QuickTime.
I wonder if I should play this with a controller.
Oh, because I am.
Oh, you are?
Okay, I'm going to grab my controller.
Yeah, I feel like this game is meant to be.
Until Dawn was meant to be played on the controller.
You're right.
Hold on.
Okay, I'm good.
Isn't this the creators of Until Dawn?
I'm pretty sure.
I think so.
Okay.
Yeah, so it was meant to play.
All right, yeah.
ready new slot oh i want to be joe or charlie guys which one
has a higher chance of living
oh joe schmo joe schmo joe schmo charlie warley joe he
believes in the heart of the cards okay oh you're right i'm
gonna be joe i identify with joey just kidding joey's a wimp
Oh, I'm ready.
I'm ready.
I'm ready, Charlie.
I'm going to handle your Charlie.
I'm Mint Phantom.
It says it right there on the screen.
For now.
Okay.
All right, here we go.
To play with the controller, press A.
Okay, cool.
Okay, that's cool.
That'd be funny if we're like, you can only play with one.
The other has to do M and K.
Oh my god.
That would be torture.
Man of Madan.
Madan?
What is it?
You don't know either.
I think it's Madan, right?
Chut.
I think it's Madan.
Okay, to be fair, everybody knows I pronounce things wrong
99% of the time.
That's going to be you.
That's going to be you in that box.
In that box.
Oh, wait.
In that box, it did.
I know.
That's what I'm saying.
That's it.
Oh, Elvis Presley.
I bet, like, oh my god.
Are we coming back from the war?
I guess so.
What war, though?
There's a lot in America.
I don't know.
There's so many choices.
Give us a date.
But this is, you know, this is based on, like, a real ship,
right?
Wait, it is?
Yeah, like, this is based off real life?
Yeah, they found a ship that, like, everybody died on.
And they couldn't figure out why they all died.
Doki Bird is Joe is what I said in the corner.
That's right.
The director called me up to act on this movie game.
That's you, Charlie.
Oh, I'm wasted.
Yeah, you're so drunk.
Oh, no, Charlie.
There's no subtitles.
Oh, yeah, you turn it on yourself.
I turn mine on.
Guys, I have subtitles.
Guys, I'm there.
Wait, how do I turn it on?
I guess we'll find...
You'll have to find out after this scene.
I'm gonna find out my future.
I have subtitles.
Look at it.
She's hot.
Oh my god, he's fighting that thing.
Kick his ass.
Oh wait, this is me!
Oh my god.
Punch!
What are you gonna do?
R to aim?
Rt to punch.
What do I punch?
This thing?
Punch?
are to choose.
Can I like move it for you?
Oh, I can.
You can?
Yeah.
Can you not move it?
Wait, I am moving it.
Are you not moving it?
No, I'm moving it.
This is totally me.
No, you're not?
Okay.
I want to know.
Will I be this?
Oh my god, me!
Wait, how do I pick?
Oh my god.
How do I pick?
I'm killing it.
Wait!
What are you doing?
I'm doing QTEs.
I'm QTEs.
qte's oh we're doing different things why can't i pick
because oh oh why'd you pause the game wait guys don't you
have to oh let me let you go do your some go do your fucking
settings yeah hold on i'm doing my subtitles are you
actually doing it yeah yeah i'm doing my subtitles okay
we're good continue i'm ready okay now you threw off my
groove You threw up one and you're fighting.
Yes, I'm fighting Wait, I can't press anything Wait, you
should have you should have picked Charlie.
You should have picked Charlie.
Yeah, I didn't turn you up anyway This gives me a chance to
turn you up.
Oh my god.
I'm continuing that game Yeah, it's my QTEs What's R?
What's it's not letting me pick I swear, I'm pressing
everything!
Yeah, because I'm the one who's playing!
No, I have my own screen!
I have, what is that?
I don't know what's going on on your side!
I'm playing the game!
It's not a big deal!
It's not letting me play!
She called me and said everything!
You suck at the game, I already beat it!
Oh, I said nothing.
Hey.
Oh, you're already done?
Okay, yes, I didn't say anything.
wait are you playing like a game of cards or something i was
trying to do the dialogue section if i couldn't pick a
dialogue what do i look like i was gaming and you were dying
to some old man who's asleep what do i got coming my way oh
wait now i have to do the thing you just did oh you were
able to pick a second highlight for the Odyssey back yeah
this are you freaking out I picked it I picked a thing what
did you press you just move with R yeah but how did you
select it um oh I'm gonna use the rooster tile you just you
just hover over it you just hover over it that's all you did
that's all you did that's really what do I see you're wrong
too it It wasn't just press R, you just hover.
You guys, you just hover.
Oh, wait.
I didn't, I won't pick it up.
Oh my God, I don't know anything about my son.
What about my son?
I don't think you'll never know.
I think you're dead.
I'll never know.
I'll never know about my son or if I'll ever be rich.
I just did nothing.
balance the audio in this.
He's told me like, blood.
Huh?
Oh, are you done?
Yeah, I'm done.
You don't need to know anything more about your future.
If I don't know my future, you don't know your future.
Did you beat the dummy?
Yeah, I beat the dummy.
I did it faster than you.
Did you get hit?
No.
I don't believe it.
I don't believe you.
Did you get hit?
No, I did not!
Did you get hit on the quick time events?
If anybody's dying, it's on your side.
No, I got an achievement for it.
I got an achievement.
I think all of us get an achievement for finishing it.
Oh shit, the death box.
That's gonna be you.
I mean, judging by the quick time events, stuff, I think
it's you.
Don't write death POV.
I might not make right dialogue.
Look, see, we got our strengths.
I'm the quick time event person, and you're the dialogue
person.
Wait, why are there three boxes of death?
Wait, why are there?
Who's the third person?
Uh-oh, it's chat.
It's chat.
Wait, one of our chats survives.
Uh-oh.
Oh, who's that guy?
Where's my 50 cents?
Yeah, I was like, what 50 cents?
Man, you don't need 50 cents.
You stole my 50 cents That's the third guy No that was you
You just got punched by a dude The
audio is like so Why is it so loud but he's so quiet?
Why is the sound of like so loud?
Why are you dead already?
Come on don't keep it up When I do you're the drunk one You
are too!
You got punched in the face!
He put me for fucking 50 cents And then I got punched
Like...
Guys, it's not the game voice that's low.
It's the...
It's everything else is high.
Yeah, I think that, yeah.
I keep trying to, like, adjust it, but it's, like, all over
the place.
Uh-oh.
Oh, there is a ship!
Whoa!
Oh, no.
What?
Titanic moment.
It struck...
Ew!
What is that?
There's some ghoul.
The death is leaking into the water.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
Frankenstein.
Do you guys know that Frankenstein, the reason his arms are
stuck out is because he was supposed to be blind and they
just wrote that out of the story but kept his arms sticking
out.
It's kind of messed up.
It's Frankenstein's monster.
Whatever.
Um, actually...
Okay.
If you're gonna give a fact about Frankenstein, you crank
your analogy.
Frankenstein's on my side.
Where the fuck?
Whoa!
What's going on?
I'm in the brig.
Vince is Charlie.
He's you.
Oh wait, that's me.
Yeah, you're looking at yourself.
Oh yeah, I'm looking at myself.
Wait, where are you?
I'm at the sickbay.
Okay, I paused it because I knew it.
Because I did just the audio!
The audio is fucked up!
You're right, you're right, you're right.
I'm putting the sound effects and the music down.
We do not need such high sound effects.
No, I'm going to put it like 6, 70?
I'm going to put it at 70 too.
See, you're welcome.
What is audio preset?
I don't know.
I just put it.
All right.
All right, I turned down music and the sound effects.
Are you ready?
Hold on.
All right, fine.
You can put, you press continue then.
press and continue did
you press you never mind oh no continue yeah you wait i
waited too long so now i'm adjusting again okay okay okay
now you can press continue all right there we go three two
one i guess people can use like the settings thing to fuck
each other over whoa there's blood on the wall wait there's
blood oh wait i got the med kit don't worry i got you okay
it's not my blood oh call an ambulance but not for me okay i
know where the blood came from i know where the blood came
from i need to move me in my chat there's text that's on the
um right side what a dick okay i i know where the blood came
from okay hold on i'm paused oh my bad sorry i'm moving us
over i'm moving us over i'm moving us over chat come over
here chat that's not a bad chat come here oh you guys are
like centered to oh gosh okay you guys don't worry about it
okay sorry all right five four three two one there's so
there's a dead body on my side um there's just blood on the
wall here let's see oh i'm looking at a key whoa whoa what a
key i have a key I'm just looking at blood.
Like, come get me out of here then, maybe.
Maybe that's for me to get out.
I need to see.
Wait, it's a doctor.
Is he dead?
There's a dead...
Yes, I'm pretty sure he was stuffed in the locker.
I'm pretty sure he's dead.
Private Charles Anderson.
What happened?
Wait, what happened while I was sleeping?
Oh.
Oh, we were both sleeping.
Ten days approved.
Oh.
Yeah, what the heck happened?
To Pops, come back soon.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure we weren't sleeping for that.
line no yeah I'm opening up I'm opening up a lock I'm coming
out I'm coming out of the ship out of the ship where are you
I'm I'm outside the ship now okay I don't like how you don't
know what's going on oh my gosh this is tank oh it's
Resident Evil.
I'm stuck in the brig.
The brig.
Something's gonna pop out at me.
Oh.
Wait, is that you?
Wait, do you see me?
Are you in this?
Yeah, that's me!
That's you, Charlie!
Just get me out of here already.
Oh, you were in detention for punching me.
I didn't touch you.
I didn't find you.
Oh, yeah?
Why were you locked inside?
I don't know.
Of course.
What's in the subway?
Something's wrong.
Let's get out of here.
Why are these guys looking at me?
What is happening?
Find out what's happening on this.
Where are we going to go?
This way, this way...
This way?
I don't know.
Don't you hear me?
I'm stuck in the walls.
What?
This way?
This way.
Okay.
I don't know.
Run!
That's gonna be you.
Who's that?
Oh, press A in time with the heartbeat.
Okay, if you don't get this right, I swear to God.
You fucked up!
Oh my god!
You scared me!
Like, we were fine!
We were fine!
Where do we go?
Where do we come from?
Cottonite Joe!
Come here, Joe!
Oh wait, this is where we came from.
Turn around.
I like how like we just were like, ooh.
Ooh!
We're just two bumbling guys.
and joe charlie and joe the adventures of charlie and joe
what is this oh my god how did you miss up that you just
press a i wanted to see what would happen if he's gone oh
yeah yeah you wanted to see what did he didn't shoot us it's
fine he was safe he was safe okay oh what the hell i'm
speaking oh wait a minute i'm gonna put settings up right
now okay get ready i need turn you up again wait what do you
mean yeah okay setting time actually this works for me i
need to fix yeah yeah yeah i need okay we both needed to fix
it so that's fine okay i'll turn my sound effects 60.
why is the sound effects so loud i don't know actually i'm
gonna turn mine down a little bit too yeah okay i'm gonna
turn you up a little bit and i'm turning the overall game a
little bit
Is this a way out or whatever that game is?
Well, it feels like it.
It's like the horror version of a way out.
Sorry, chat, you cut off a little bit.
Sorry, guys.
Let me...
All right, here.
I'm ready.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
I already clicked ready.
Okay.
I don't know that.
I can't see.
All right.
Five.
Three.
Two.
One.
Okay.
Here we go.
We're walking down the hall.
We're fine.
Everything's good.
did you go oh there you are yeah didn't we come here who's
that what was that what was that joe did you not see it i'm
charlie you're joe you're not seeing charlie do you not see
a guy running in front of us no there was no guy wait oh no
what's going what are you talking about charlie i think i'm
charlie i'm think i'm so drunk joe take your meds joe take
your meds joe i couldn't the doctor's dead there's a door
flashing yeah yeah over here over here smell to you you oh
wait do you not see it there's like a yeah flashing over
here get it i'm getting it come on joe hey charlie yeah help
me okay okay just came back from the sick bay why is my face
just so all right oh a okay i'm pressing a repeatedly yeah
he's dead yeah you said it foobar and that
sound effects are so loud and then some what does that even
what does that mean oh my god oh that's a lot of blood are
we getting invaded what's happening what happened on the
ship stays on the ship oh i'm first i guess yeah even though
i opened the door yeah our feet are really smelly wait why
is there like gas on the floor that's what i'm saying we're
smelly go damn another step who's the lucky winner i'm
checking him out i'm trying to check him out wait yeah I'm
stuck I'm stuck I can't oh there it is oh my god what's
going on he looks like he looks like Peter Griffin like I
want to see too oh my god it's him well he's not one of us
wait what's wrong with his eyes he's like looking he's like
blank eyes yeah let's go this way oh there's nothing this
way we gotta go through the door like it was like like the
frat boys be like hey guys what's What do we do?
What do we do?
Everything's...
Wow, look at these camera angles, so cinematic.
Oh, did you went through that door?
I can't see anything, where are you?
I'm heading downstairs.
Okay.
Oh my god, it is so cinematic.
I can't see where I'm going.
Wait, do I just go straight?
Oh, Fubar is a military sniper fucked unbelievably beyond
all recognition.
Whoa!
Oh, you get LB!
To walk faster.
Okay, yeah, I like that.
Okay.
right now we can can we run like i don't feel like i'm
walking very much me too i feel like i don't think i'm
walking that fast not gonna lie either are we maybe we're
not pressing the right button it's lb wait i don't know it's
just maybe it's wrong which was me um i'm the one whoa oh
did not see that hey no i didn't say anything you see that
kid over there a kid only me no it was a child right Joe
what's wrong with you what's of course you Doki would be the
one you would be the one so you're walking in circles you're
just like I don't know I don't know Charlie I don't feel so
good Charlie I've been seeing children I'm seeing children
oh oh oh my god go go go go oh uh-oh Is that a good idea?
Oh, why did I grab a knife?
What the hell?
Why can't I ever have a gun?
You know why.
This is accurate.
This is very accurate.
Why can't I ever have a gun?
You were meant to have the katana.
The katana.
I don't think you are having hallucinations.
I don't think you should be holding anything.
Is that you?
That's me.
I saw another child.
Did you...
I saw a child again.
Yeah.
What the fuck do you see on your screen?
Oh!
The dead people are actually talking to me right now.
Oh, okay.
So at least we're both crazy then.
Oh, what?
What is happening?
It's you talking to me.
But you're dead.
Wait, what?
Yeah, you're...
You're looking at me.
You're dead.
I'm going to investigate.
Wait, how do I investigate?
Oh, there we go.
Are you investigating?
I'm still hallucinating.
I'm investigating your body.
Oh, there's a man here.
Wait, there's me.
No, I think you're the man.
Wait, what?
No, child!
I see that.
The child has your knife.
You gave the child a knife.
No, I still have it.
I still have it.
No!
Oh.
Oh, I shot the child!
Oh my god, he's a zombie!
You missed!
How could you miss?
Are you shooting me?
I don't know, but I missed apparently.
Where did I die from that?
I think I'm dead too.
This guy used the force on me and killed me.
I tried, I missed the child and then and I died from a heart
attack.
You died from cringe because you were so bad.
You died of cringe, real.
Hello, can anyone out there hear me?
Who is he?
What's that Charlie Orcho?
Give us your location.
Do it!
Do it, man.
You're our only hope.
Random sailor!
What the hell is that?
Uh-oh.
wait what what the hell yes poor arms dokey I think
something weird going on here yeah I don't think that I
think it should might be haunted he's got his little baby
cross God cannot save you now whoa oh he's dead oh my god
he's dead oh my god he died of cringe too everybody's dying
of cringe oh my god it's so loud i just cannot i liked how
they were like picked between joe and charlie and they're
already dead yeah that was the prologue we get the whole we
get the game now
this isn't the ship we're at a mansion now
did they still make these games i don't know i know they're
doing really bad right now you know what I saw the reviews
for it the newer episodes were not doing so well oh who's
this guy he isn't he the guy that was the the psychiatrist
in until dawn oh is he I think so oh apparently we're going
to get a copyright strike because of the song.
I'm turning it down.
It's okay.
They're just going to get her ad money.
That's all right.
Look at this.
The ring, the girl.
What is going on?
Yeah.
Like, wait, wait.
Why is she there?
Is this like some, like, paranormal activity?
and like
is this like a video game version of like the Annabelle
ship?
Oh probably.
And the nun?
What were they called?
They had names.
They were like a couple that investigated paranormal
activities.
Yeah, yeah.
Um, Anne and Lorraine Warren or whatever.
What was the name of those movies called?
Wasn't it just Annabelle, right?
No, they had a name.
There was a series before Annabelle.
The Conjuring.
The Conjuring, yeah.
yeah yeah insidious oh yeah yeah we're the conjuring we're
the conjuring joe and charlie like walking down his own
hallway so dramatically yeah oh now he's lighting candles
hello is the sound and welcome yeah thank you to my
repository okay okay his suppository is that things you
stick up your ass if you're wondering why I know this guys
it's because I watch a lot of doctor shows yeah that's the
only reason that's the only reason then why do you know it
huh the curator of stories stories of love wait you're not
answering the question man you know why did you know what
suppositories are oh because I watched the shows with you
Oh, it's true.
Oh, yeah, you were there.
Yeah.
You choose to tell.
Oh.
You see, this tale is only part written.
He's breaking the fourth wall.
He's talking to us.
Yeah.
And determine whether the lives of those with whom you are
interfering continue to flourish.
We don't have a funny guy, don't we?
Snuffed out.
You see, we each make decisions according to our own moral
compass.
I think I have a great moral compass.
You literally couldn't press A.
but you shouldn't fear death it is after all a lot of
pressure okay it is the tax one pays for having lived and it
comes eventually eventually still none of us want for it to
come too soon do yeah hey hey hey i'm already dead i fear
nothing sometimes separately what one does may not make
complete sense to the other because we all have yeah
anything you do makes no sense to me and that is you that's
why it's perfect we're playing this yeah it's perfect i
think the goal is to at least have one person survive
probably interfere but i might be who will it be you or me
here's one for free oh there are pictures in this world that
can show you some possible future oh oh so it's like a hint
yeah they may just help you to make better decisions oh no i
think that's subjective if they're better or not result in
the yeah like how do we know if they're better decisions
yeah that's all for the moment we'll talk again soon enough
we'll have the opportunity to account for all the actions
that you've taken thank you sir thank you thank you
hour like i don't know this guy this is a trial period oh
there's that's where we were that's the opening screen oh it
was just the water oh oh dokey bird is alex i'm you're brad
i'm brad you're brad i'm probably really cool only brad
which one is this brads have cool brads are cool Is this the
Brad or the Alex?
Oh, I look like a nerd.
I'm your brother.
We're brothers.
Brothers, Brad's brother.
How do we always end up being brothers?
Wait, which one?
Is that you?
Are you the nerd?
Yes.
Look at this nerd.
Look at you.
Oh, my God.
Wait, you're insecure.
You're insecure.
Alex, brother.
Why does yours says innocent?
Like, what does that imply about me?
So, uh, look, I'm an innocent maiden.
Down.
Diving.
Well, maybe you could show me how the pros do it.
Ooh.
Doki Bird is deciding.
Let's see.
You didn't take lessons?
I guess you must have came out of it without taking any
lessons.
Kind of, yeah.
You think I can, like, just save you like that?
I'm gonna say nothing.
That's right.
Know your place, nerd.
Whoa, careful.
Hey.
Dive cam is, like, super...
Oh, yeah.
Be cool.
I'm an influencer.
Conrad, or, you know...
You're an influencer?
Maybe.
I don't know.
I have a camera.
So don't sweat the little stuff, man.
It's not cool.
Don't make me regret letting you tag along.
Yeah.
Don't make me regret it.
Are you deciding again?
Yeah.
You know, I'm not, like, the best.
around new people.
Oh, you're anxious.
We're anxiety women.
Make me feel better.
Bread.
We're buddies.
Oh, wait.
I can see your traits.
Oh, that's what you're looking at.
What was it?
RB?
Oh, I can't see it.
Yeah, RB.
Wait, we have secrets, too.
I can't see it since I'm in the pause.
Oh, my God.
I'm guarded, genuine.
I'm genuine.
Insecure, generous.
who the fuck is conrad and fliss we're we have like we're
not there yet we're not there yet we have other people alex
reminded brad he's not just a tagalog alex was annoyed that
brad had not taken diving lessons oh my god come on so i
can't even see them now i'm gonna see it now you're gonna
see it it's r b it's collections and characters i'm witty
i'm eager i'm innocent yeah but are you genuine like me
you're not genuine wait mine literally says genuine how do i
see the other one genuine oh you can't see it we can only
see ourselves okay mine says guarded generous genuine
generous yeah i'm generous i mean i let you come over to the
diving to the diving place okay okay i could let you drown
if i wanted to my bro or my brother but see i'm being
supportive i mean like we're buddies you know oh my god
we're buddies oh just out here to hang cool out and kick it
yeah you gotta loosen up bro let's just kick it and be
legends man you're apex legends all right amigo sorry i'm a
little snappy i'm just what's wrong medical school would be
stressful you know i've been here i'm doctor oh my god I'm a
cool nerd You're a fucking influence It's been like two
weeks, come on man Yep, right on cue What?
I'm smart and cool, what are you?
I'm innocent, did I?
I'm innocent I'm not gonna be a doctor, I'm gonna save lives
You need to save your own first So, uh, can I get your input
on something?
Oh my god, I'm gonna propose oh you are a big thing i'm
trying to make a decision about yeah about finishing med
school no but yeah it's just kind of a big life choice you
know okay i don't know what's the right thing to do um do i
marry her or not i'm gonna say nothing
why are you so supported
Your girlfriend, Julia.
That's her brother.
He's relaxed.
She's foolhardy.
What does that mean?
Oh, yo, you want me to hook you up with her brother?
Oh, wow.
Get a room.
You like that.
This is Alex.
Hey, what's up, man?
Conrad.
Yeah.
Watch it, sis.
Lady killer.
Right here.
What?
Oh, that's me.
He's ignoring you.
This Conrad guy looks like...
Bradley.
She looks like that actor.
I know you have heard so much about you.
Dr. Horrible.
Dr. Neofatric Harris.
Yeah, Neofatric Harris.
Hey, man.
I want to crack a cold one.
I'm cracking a cold one.
Every second.
I'm going to be cool.
I'm going to be cool, you guys.
Yeah.
Cool.
We're cracking a cold one.
No!
She called me Needy.
I'm not Needy.
I swear.
I think this is my first time having a beer are you cracking
a beer yeah i'm having i'm cracking one with a cold one jib
oh wait i'm oh what i thought it's throwing up throw up i
can't believe it wait who's that who's this this is my love
interest now where's the old crust bucket skip running out
captain of the duke of milan oh dang she looks like a badass
oh my gosh see your too yeah i'd invite you to make
yourselves at home but uh why are we why is everybody yeah
isn't she the captain like yeah you don't know who's sailing
the ship like what's going on here we go uh you're selling
i'm buying i hope conrad dies first yeah me too Don't look.
Conrad, that's fucked up.
Do not flirt with the person who knows how to drive the
boat.
What are we doing here anyway?
We're diving?
Is that it?
Yeah, we're learning how to dive.
Cool.
The Duke of Milan.
Oh, that's you.
No, that's you.
Wait, you're not in the blue shit.
Oh, you're right.
Wait, a fucking bird.
She's, like, comforting, man.
You know, maybe I should.
She likes it when they're weak.
I'm going.
I see those hot picks.
What?
Oh.
What about over here?
What is this?
Oh, we're going, she's going through the picks.
Can you see me going through the picks?
No, I'm fucking talking to the captain right now.
I'm looking at some.
Oh!
I found a ship.
Well, hot diggity dog.
Dong?
Alex!
Come here!
I think we got something.
I think it's hot diggity dog!
Wait, you did your homework?
What do you mean?
It's here.
Oh.
Yeah, we got a wreck.
We got a wreck.
We have to do some diving.
You suggested.
The captain said it's not a good idea, but I trusted you,
Mint.
Okay, cool.
I trusted your call.
Cool.
Check it out.
If we die, it's on you.
hot diggity these your eyes on this yeah I'm looking at the
pictures now Brad's calculations were right on the money
always bet on Brad see I'm smart Brad is smart we found a
plane yeah I don't know the captain was like not a good idea
technically we should call this in to port authorities as an
unreported wreck technically are you sure you don't want to
do this the right way Doki Bird is deciding.
Don't let Doki Bird disown it.
Look at the look on his face.
I'm going to be disappointed.
Are you saying we shouldn't die?
Oh.
Why am I Conrad?
Oh my god.
Wait, you're Conrad now?
I think we got to listen to our experienced, beautiful,
smart, and beautiful captain here.
If she says we should do things right.
Please, I didn't bring you on this trip to get laid.
Wait, what?
no no no it's not me what i'm just saying she's right not
because she's beautiful i mean she is beautiful but that's
like a coincidence oh my god oh my god hey i'm conrad now i
have to do what i have to do generously we're dying the
client but if anything goes wrong i think i'm i'm thinking
i'm gonna marry a i just can't wait to be like a karen for
real yeah i think i'm gonna marry a why did you not say
anything why did you say nothing when i asked you i'll set
up the tanks the boys will do the final check it's not my
call take a look at the camera see if you can find anything
that one second loading screen yeah what the hell is that
maybe you should check on your bro yeah where where's my
where's the bro oh where's brad oh brad where are you
The way you, like, walk and glide around.
Ooh, I'll find you later.
I'm looking at the binoculars.
I'm looking at the pictures again.
I like the pictures.
I'm an iPad kid.
Ooh, that opening.
Okay, we got it.
Okay.
Can I put it back?
This is, like, such a tiny ship.
Where could Brad go?
I think he's laying down.
Oh, I'm stuck.
Oh, wait, where am I?
Wait, wait.
Hey.
hey hey i'm gonna talk to my girlfriend me too got the gear
good to go you're like you're vibrating and then need a hand
i'm in this conversation too let me breathe it before i
think we're in good shape it's probably not a bad idea i'm
actually in the conversation hey hey jj you alright jj hunky
dory gotta say not too happy with our captain at the moment
she's right there wait what i'm gonna be I'm gonna be
annoyed.
Are you gonna be white right here?
We paid top dollar to come out here in the middle of nowhere
to do whatever the hell we want without any namby-pamby's
breathing down our neck.
That's the good old American way.
I'm serious, Connie.
All right.
I'm gonna get these rebreathers set up and then we'll go
through the final steps together.
Great.
I'm gonna kick back and enjoy the sights for a little while.
I can't believe the captain didn't even hear that.
I know, me too.
I mean, I'm gonna idol our captain like a great ape creep.
He admits to being a creep!
Oh my god.
He's self-aware.
Why are you vibrating in this place?
Hold on, I'm trying to go to Brad.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I want to talk to him.
I want to look at the weather.
Going to Brad.
I'm going to Brad.
What's this?
Oh, I turned it off.
Wait, I think I see a picture.
Wait, hold on.
Oh, is this one of those sneaky pictures?
Well, hello.
What is this?
Oh, I found one.
What's this?
What are you looking at?
That told me nothing.
I unlocked a premonition.
Oh, that's gonna help me us with decisions, remember?
Wait, I wanna see so I know that you won't fuck up.
He's gonna be in here.
What's his premonition?
Wait, that's Brad.
Yeah.
I shouldn't have had that beer.
It doesn't do anything.
What does that mean?
I'm gonna be...
I'm trying to make a decision!
I'm trying to look at a premonition right now.
I'm making a decision.
okay brad's like in the bathroom i'm gonna be a dick you
gotta admit you are down for the bro but that's one less
dude on fliss's radar i mean i hate myself that puts the
wind in the sails of a seafaring gal but you got that whole
brainiac thing going on that's nothing to sneeze at don't
worry stud she's all yours oh oh why did he do that with his
face okay that's my cue to beat it make my moves on captain
captain kiss i'm looking at while you're bullying yourself.
Where are you?
Are you in the bathroom?
I was opening the closet.
There's another room here.
Oh, I'm going in.
Yeah, now I'll talk to my little bro.
What's up?
How you doing?
Hello, locker.
Oh, I'm going through people's things.
That's really normal.
What's this now?
Oh, I'm looking at the clone too.
Fancy.
Good on you, Alex.
Why am I going through your stuff?
What the hell?
Look, I comfort my bro.
Have you bullied him?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
I was just snooping a little.
What are you doing?
I'm just being normal.
I saw you looking at my cologne.
I took your cologne, actually.
Wait, you took my cologne?
That door doesn't open.
Yeah.
And then we talked to our bros.
All right, I'm going to go talk to the captain now.
Captain Kiss.
I'm going to watch you talk to the captain.
Watch me.
Watch me Rizzer up.
Yeah.
All right.
Hey, girl.
Oh, captain, my captain.
Get out of my gut seat.
No, we have rules out here for a reason.
You guys got a respecter.
At least you showed me a little respect, even if you're the
only one in the group.
Really?
Oh, captain, my captain?
I like it when you're stressed.
Hey, I like it when you're strict.
Sometimes I just want to be kept in line, you know what I'm
saying?
I don't mind a little submission element.
Oh, my God!
Is there another way for you to turn that off?
Turn one off.
That thing where you have to hit on me like every two
seconds.
I think she likes it.
Bro.
So, is it working?
Where are you?
Come back to my cutscene.
My upstairs brain.
Oh, there you are.
These rules are all pretty basic stuff.
How much experience do you have with these kind of dives?
Are you still talking to me?
Reck diving is like my thing.
Pretty much an authority back home.
Oh yeah.
If you move around, does he move?
Then why don't you want to follow the rules for unreported
wrecks?
For all you know, this could be a war group.
This Derby hit would be illegal anymore.
I'm gonna be playful.
You know, you're even more toxic here when you're angry.
And I am going to be at police.
She's never spoken to a woman before in your life, haven't
you?
You've only talked to your sister.
Damn!
It's my turn to talk to her now.
You talk to her, you talk to her.
I'm watching, I'm watching.
Are you talking to her?
No, I'm stuck.
Wait, wait.
The conversation?
Wait, I'm stuck?
Wait, I'm stuck.
Wait, that went inside of me too.
I can't progress anything.
No!
You see me just look around?
What's going on?
We broke the game!
You broke the game!
Fix it!
Fix it, talk to our sister!
Oh, wait, wait, there you go, there you go.
Alright, try again, try again.
No, I can't move!
You can't move!
Wait, there's something over here.
Hold on, I'm gonna go look at it.
Yeah, yeah, start the next scene, man.
Start the next scene.
Oh!
What's going on?
Oh my god, I'm looking at her driver's license!
I'm such a freak!
Bogus.
How do we start the next scene?
Um, hold on.
I just doubted her credentials.
Wait, she's your sister.
What do you mean you doubted her credentials?
No, no, no.
Oh my god, you're still standing there.
How do we start the game?
Hold on, I'm gonna push you.
I'm gonna push you.
Put me into the boat.
I can't push you, I can't push you.
Well, I'm gonna go talk to my sister.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, we fixed it.
Don't be on here.
Okay, so this is the re-breathing.
Way cooler than a regular scuba setup.
It takes all that CO2 that you'd normally just exhale into
the water, and instead, it gets totally reused.
Then it repeats.
Okay.
Oh yeah, yeah, we have to do, okay.
We won't die.
We won't die here.
Okay, I don't think I'm diving.
I'm not suited.
Are you gonna be my girlfriend now?
Check your O2 first.
Oh, maybe.
Oh Okay, thanks.
Check your O2.
I'm gonna be playful.
I'd like to take you underwater.
Oh, that's my sis you're talking about.
What the hell?
What the fuck?
You were like creeping on the captain earlier.
Jesus, why are you so loud?
This is the line.
I was looking at the dive camp.
I saw this huge hole in the tail.
Kabooey.
Oh, nice work, man.
Thanks, Conrad.
Okay, you little clown fishes.
I'm going to go see what Fliss is up to.
Oh, my God.
Leave her alone.
Right after defending your sister.
You're like, anyway, I'm going to hit it.
I'm going to the captain again.
I'm going to be chew.
Are those two going in or what?
Wait, what's the baton stick or the camera?
We don't need a camera.
We're going to need that baton.
All right, kids.
Good to go.
I don't know what this is.
Just remember the rules, please.
A bangstick.
Ha ha.
You ever have to use one?
On a shark?
Nope.
OK, are you going in?
Oh, you're deciding.
Take the camera or Julia?
Why is the lighting really dark all the sudden?
I can't tell what's happening.
All right.
Please better not be pissy this whole trip.
And she should remember who's signing the checks.
Very large checks.
How to buy us out of this little wiggle room with the rules.
Oh, it's fixed.
It's fixed.
Oh, my God.
What's happening?
Oh, you guys are going in.
Why is she just looking at us like that?
I think she's nervous.
Whoa, these are high-tech.
I got a stick that bangs.
Uh-huh.
That's why you took it.
Julia liked the last name.
Whoa.
wait so am i doing nothing nice all right it's up to you
don't you wait a minute you were brad now comrade and now
julia like pick a lay there's no way there's no way oh my
god there's dead bodies in here there's dead bodies in here
is this madon no this is a plane why are we playing yeah why
are we going in here oh my god found this wreck Here we go.
Down we go.
Why are we diving when it's the sun setting?
Should we just wait for a day?
Whoa.
You good?
Are you still talking to her?
No, I'm watching the cutscene.
Oh, shit.
The sharks.
Uh-oh.
You're going to need to use your bag stick.
She acts like we're going to ransack the plane.
Hey, a souvenir would be cool.
The boat looks really far away.
All of a sudden.
I'm going to be flit.
Okay.
Alright, you know what?
Sure, I'll give you one.
Wait, are you on the boat?
Yeah, I'm Fliss.
I'm underwater!
No way!
We know why somebody died.
Let's swim around a little and find a way in.
One of the pictures showed an opening.
Doki Bird is Fliss.
Why am I?
Why am I Julia?
all of a sudden you're the carrot oh my god here I go I'm
going inside the ship oh my god comrades like comrades wants
to invest in my business what okay oh I want Conrad's money
oh I almost just killed Julia I think be dangerous oh my god
that scared me oh my god I just noticed something was what i
mean explore the the plane can i just take a second to say
holy shit alex we did it wait for the others to return from
the dive oh you are doing why are you doing the action part
i don't know why am i doing the action part i'm just
chilling i'm just chilling on the ship right now wait what
was that what was that hold on oh i can talk to you you can
yeah hello I Did you guys hear me?
Oh, I heard it.
I heard it.
Oh, we're looking at a hole.
Don't ignore her ignore fliss Julia leave it You said ignore
me Not worth it.
That pipe's pretty tight.
She's angry.
I'm gonna call you guys again I'm not even you think you can
you think you can just ignore me like that Ring ring ring
don't be such a girl now.
I'll be fine to Julia go dad seriously.
Oh, you gonna ghost me now?
Yeah, I'm doing risky business, okay?
Don't be such a gonad, Doki.
You think I'm not going to spam call you now?
Oh my god.
I think she might die.
Uh-oh.
Don't worry.
I'm calling you guys again.
Don't.
Oh, there's an octopus in here!
Don't be such a gonad.
Okay, if you guys die, it's not me.
Yeah, you guys die.
I got it.
Uh-oh.
See, what's this?
Those are the photos.
Uh-oh.
I'm lost.
Oh, he's here.
You're a good boyfriend.
He gave me oxygen.
Oh, nice.
You're gonna, now you're gonna kill fucking Alex.
You're gonna kill Alex.
I spent so much, I spent a lot of difficult decisions to get
Alex.
to where he's at and now you're just gonna kill him off i
know what i'm doing i know what i'm doing okay i don't need
a lifeguard she is so rude i told you she's such a karen i
hope she dies this this is oh the rescue plan you found a
secret yeah yeah because i did risky business i told you oh
i'm lagging oh my god what's happening okay search go easy
on the booze i'm gonna i'm bullying
It's easy to bully him.
Well, let's avoid that tube.
Here we go.
What do you know, Brad?
He doesn't know anything.
He's Brad.
It's a loser.
Okay, all right.
Oh, oh, the ship is around World War II.
Yeah, right?
Because, uh, oh.
Uh, you hear that?
What is that?
Let's check it out.
Oh, God.
Uh-oh.
What is it?
I'm using my bang stick.
What am I banging?
You're welcome.
I got you that bang stick.
I did it.
I used it.
Did you like it?
Oh my god.
It's a dead man.
I'm taking...
Um...
She's banging.
I'm banging.
Uh, I'm investigating the ghost.
I'm going to win.
What happened?
I went.
An eel attacked me!
All I get is the ship with fucking Conrad.
You get to explore.
I have to deal with fucking Conrad.
Got it.
Plane crash, not high on my list of ways to perish.
I'm just saying, maybe you should have picked Brad instead.
Oh, there's another guy.
Wait, hold on.
Let me investigate him, please.
Investigate.
I'm trying to turn around.
So are you beached?
Easy now.
This stuff's been down here a long time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm piloting the plane.
Oh, my God.
I'm piloting.
Should I hit on Conrad?
Yeah!
Do I do it?
I'm going to hit on Conrad.
Do it, do it, do it.
Don't touch anything else, please.
Oh, my God.
Conrad said he'll, like, invest in my business.
You're in.
I'm in.
Good God.
Oh, my God.
My business is going to flourish now.
how the girl was just like it's not like we're gonna ruin
the ship or anything and here i go like ruining the ship i
like how like i'm also being your wingman right now oh he's
holding something his wife and kids oh my god he's in right
how to turn this on
am i just waiting on you guys to return to the ship i think
so i think so He's just literally waiting.
They knew they were gone.
Yes, hurry up.
Didn't what's his name say that like wrecking, like diving
was his thing?
Oh, there's pirates!
What?
Uh oh, what do you mean there's pirates?
Like yo ho.
That's not the Coast Guard.
Uh oh, wait, what do you mean?
Oh, I'm stuck.
I think.
I'm stuck.
Hold on.
I think I need to come back.
You should call me back.
I think there's pirates.
You should call and say like, hey.
give me give get up here oh no oh oh what's going on there's
pirates fucked up whoa whoa whoa whoa they're moving the
ship they're moving the the plane oh my god they're
destroying it wait what they're destroying the plane grab
that oh there's a shark who's they i don't know shark
something cold come at me shark come at me shark it's a gray
reef shark not interested in us let's go wow your guy is a
doctor and also a marine biologist how does he know
everything okay mint we're coming back mint um we're coming
back comrades a okay he's he's antagonizing the pirates mint
what what are you fidgeting oh my god i I think Alex is
trying to propose under here.
I wanted to bring something up with you, but it's...
In the water!
He's trying to propose!
Um...
Oh my god.
I don't know what to say.
Uh, I'm just gonna say nothing.
What's going on?
It doesn't matter.
Let's get back up to the top.
Oh, he gave up.
Okay.
Seriously, what's going on?
What's going on, Alex?
Hey, seriously.
What is going on down?
There's so many things going on.
Oh.
Just forget it.
I shouldn't have said anything.
Come on.
My relationship with Alex is going down.
My relationship with Conrad is also going down.
It's nice to know we're both sabotaging each other's
relationships.
I know.
It's fine.
I can make it up.
I make it up in tenfold.
Whatever you say to her doesn't mean anything.
We gotta decompress here.
Oh my God.
Oh, Goddard's barbecuing.
Oh, fucked up.
I'm more like you.
What do you mean?
I'm controlling the captain.
I don't even get to make a choice.
I'm going.
Fuck it.
He's like, we gotta decompress.
She's heroic.
Oh, and Alice is just like chilling in the water.
Yeah.
Wait, I'm like stuck on...
All right, Conrad, it's going down.
Guys, I'm messing up Conrad.
After all the hard work I did flirting.
Hey, JJ, don't worry about it.
What's going on?
Why did they go at sunset?
Yeah, what's that money for?
There was a little mishap with the barbecue.
I'm altruistic now.
was lit up yeah for real um it was conrad's fault it was why
are you paying the ocean yeah why are you paying the ocean a
fishing boat came by and got damaged on the dive line oh
that's what happened yeah they were being a little surly
about it so conrad made it rain and they pissed off wow
whatever they didn't even take the money right what i want
to know is what'd you guys find well what did you find we
found the plane and it is huge full of cool stuff yeah like
eels and sharks apparently yeah what why the dive line
actually yeah the dive line how bad uh there's no cockpit
anymore for starters well that's just fucking perfect well
that's not our fault like we didn't do that that's you
you're the captain of the ship oh well how is it my fault
yeah i'm no i'm just saying red threw money on the ship do
okay yeah how we do man oh he's laughing at us you're
getting to know these intrepid adventurers then alex and his
little brother brad trying to swim with the big fish both
seem out of their depth yeah and julia julia of alex's life
and he i don't know after what meant i don't know about that
it's not one diving trip that's gonna destroy their
relationship and then there's captain fliss strong
forthright stubborn stubborn do i detect a spark between her
and conrad i don't know what i'm doing forced them to like
each other wait we have a special feature unlocked that's a
special feature and some i think they may regret his jacket
looks like a giraffe like a cantaloupe skin apparently we
made some decisions that they're gonna regret lady no i mean
they regret i think you made some decisions that they're
gonna regret brad it was insane it was like traveling
through time no well it was like traveling through time and
accidentally ending up in a dimension where the past is
underwater and like everything is covered in barnacles
julia's stupid it was like traveling to the past stupid it
was like traveling to the past but everything is underwater
and everything's covered in barnacles And shy.
And since he was drunk, he forgot to bring it to us.
I can't believe there's sharks in the ocean.
Did you know that?
Sounds like you've had some experience with this kind of
phenomenon.
Yeah, I've been studying it for years.
I'll go look for him.
I didn't even meet...
Oh, wait.
I'm...
I'm Brad now.
Wait, who are you?
I'm watching...
Oh, I'm Julia.
I'm Julia.
You're Julia?
You got the shortened end of the stick.
You're like an open book.
I'm gonna let you drop.
I can read you from a mile away.
Something's up.
Oh, wait.
my gutsy i can see you i wonder what's going on are you
happy don't fuck this up privacy oh you tell me you live
okay don't worry i'll watch from here uh yeah maybe yeah
yeah i think so you think so or you know so oh my god is
everything okay why i see you in the corner Yeah, is
everything okay, man?
What are you gonna do?
Man, you're gonna ruin a 10-year relationship?
Let me go from here.
That's fine, it's fine.
He's just staring.
Look, when we get home, we can talk about some stuff.
What do you mean when you talk about some stuff?
I mean, it's not like we're breaking up.
Man, what are you doing?
What are you doing to our relationship?
Yeah.
Stuff.
stuff got it oh my god this guy he acts like an ai for real
brad is right there no i got yeah i got distracted let's go
get him sure i got wait are they like making out downstairs
are they oh i did that you're welcome it um i worked so hard
on this for you What are you doing?
What's going on?
I'm sorry to interrupt your seven seconds in heaven.
Oh, yeah, the beers.
I was just getting them now.
What?
We're not going to address that.
We're just not going to.
We're just going to...
Oh, man, you worked so hard, and I brought it home run.
I brought it home for you.
You tried to sabotage it after I worked so hard for it.
It's a seven-year relationship.
If they were going strong, they would...
My intervention would mean nothing.
Maybe we can figure out why the planes aren't here.
What happened underwater, man?
What happened?
Oh, search for the nav pad.
What the hell is it?
You got the nav pad, dive master, J?
Oh, no.
Not yet.
What's that?
What's the nav pad?
Oh, this thing.
You all right?
You seem kind of preoccupied.
I'm grabbing it.
Wait, is this it?
is this i'm talking to my brother what am i doing oh i'm
looking at the pictures wow oh fishies air rescue service
conwin islands oh that's me we're going again tomorrow
that's me oh i can't wait that's me can't wait to see this
sucker for myself what are you doing man we're conversation
with everybody except for julia oh sorry i was looking at
pictures oh what let's go up yeah oh i thought it was a
tablet come here you fixing what see i did that i did what
did you do easy tiger oh we should get back i'm making out
with alex right now right here all right you kissed alex
yeah you fix it fix the problem you caused well yeah no i
was i did it i i caused that i mean i caused the
relationship to flourish you did it's blooming it's blooming
if you did decompress too fast then you should go easy on
the beer alex i'm fine i think if i got the bends i would
know by now i think i'm fine not always sometimes the bends
can be super delayed it could be hours or a day or two the
bends yeah what's the bends uh when you come up from a dive
too fast oh oh oh yeah uh decompression sickness oh nerd wow
that was in all caps it's really serious divers get sick and
die from decompression sickness every year and that is why
the good dr conrad says drink him if you got him because
either you're fine or you're gonna want a little something i
don't think i want to listen to dr conrad yeah um i think
alex is an actual doctor from this guy just drink a beer oh
no i have to make the decision don't you dare beer o'clock
beer o'clock oh my god if she dies it's on you cheering gold
literally doctors orders that you're like beer o'clock those
are coordinates all right let me listen to my brother who
throws money at problems hey i'm not julia you'll be julia
eventually too wow you find anything else i have to be julia
to take care of the mess you made from a nearby us base
reckless all of you excuse me i told you to leave everything
down there alone oh come on we've been through this already
i'm not talking about the law oh hey talking about
superstition wait what superstition is that it really really
the dead don't sleep well in these waters may sound silly
enough to you all but i was raised on this shit and it
sticks oh are you gonna call her like a liar come on yeah
maybe it's not julia being a carrot maybe it's a carrot i
just don't like i don't want anyone else to like julia
either you think you can scavenge down there and it makes no
difference but every single thing you bring back has an
essence it's like a ghost you invite to the surface here we
go you never think about much of anything well maybe you're
so rude gold story not like for fun people drown in these to
respect the resting place damn straight brett you got a fun
ghost story right oh i do do you come on decide say a good
yeah yeah once upon a time yeah come on let's hear it oh
yeah let's hear it oh yeah let's hear it let's hear it i bet
you can spin a good yarn it's kind of messed up actually oh
okay yeah scare away little bro okay here goes this story is
true it had happened to right near here in an old lighthouse
classic setup wait true story where'd you hear this i
thought i already i thought alex already knew the story why
are you deciding like you don't know what's going on old guy
well down by the dock side i found an ancient old man skin
like a leather book why did your wig go up because he told
me his for just a dollar here we go okay the lighthouse
stood atop an atoll isolated from the rest of the world
alone because it was a spooky lighthouse the lighthouse
keeper would hear the waves pounding the rocky shore okay
one misty morning he comes upon a woman oh female oh women
he hurries to her aid and she falls into his arms sobbing oh
my god he hurries her back to the lighthouse he asks where
she's from he doesn't waste any time It's smooth.
Conrad, shut up.
Yeah, shut up.
Shut up.
I live here in the lighthouse.
My parents are upstairs right now.
Dun, dun, dun, dun.
Dun, dun, dun.
That isn't so.
Of course, he's lived there alone for years.
And the woman becomes hysterical.
His pupils are so dire.
His sister parents are upstairs.
So, they go to the top of the lighthouse.
And there, splayed out on the floor, is a man and a woman
brutally murdered with an axe.
an axe i mean do people even use axes anymore i'm just i'm
just reporting the facts chopped up into little tiny giblets
giblets um it's a good story man it's a very good story you
know sometimes you have to embellish the facts wow you tell
a better story then okay you're literally the one that asked
for the story no julia like relationship went up come on say
say it was you you're the you did oh i'm gonna do relax the
woman says it was my husband and she turns to the closet it
says he's in there yeah the husband and that's why i've
always been a little weary of marriage so the lighthouse
keeper oh no no alex no alex is putting his head in his
hands right sure enough there's a man inside what but he's
cut his own throat oh He looks closer to see the dead man's
face in the dark.
Closer.
Oh my god, the uncanny.
It's his own face.
And then its eyes bulge out and screams.
Whoa!
What the fuck?
What the hell?
Why did that come from?
I think Brad is possessed.
Yeah.
I think he's possessed.
Holy shit.
Oh, come on.
That wasn't scary.
scary i think he told the better last time do better next
time brad you've all had your don't he pick better prompts
next time wow i saw you scream i saw the screams around me
that's the regulation we're all required one more beard
before hitting the hay what regular issues are these it's
standard issue regulatory institutional i don't think i
trust conrad with anything i don't either who invited this
guy he's like that type of guy that's like i'm gonna tell my
dad what said about me do we not notice the storm that's
incoming and we're on a tiny little boat that's gonna
capsize oh oh no now there's the storm i think we're in
trouble i think we're in trouble oh my god i think we fucked
up i think we messed up yeah yeah oh oh you think those guys
are gonna come back and take our ship yeah Oh!
What the fuck?
Where did they come from?
Did you bring stuff up to the ship?
It was the tablet!
You brought a tablet!
That's why we looked at the gold!
Oh, uh-oh.
Uh-oh.
They have opposable thumbs.
They're fine.
We're fine.
They're looking over us.
Wait, is that the treasure?
Is that the...
That land looks human.
Wait, those... Are they the pirates?
He's got a gun!
That's... Oh my god.
Oh, oh, oh.
What do I...
What do I... Oh.
I tried right triggering, but it didn't let me do anything.
Um, I think he's about to die.
What did you do?
I...
Did you not do your quick time effect?
I couldn't figure out where it was supposed to go!
Oh, my god!
I did my quick thing!
Look at where it's gotten you.
You're still trapped, too.
failed the quick damage from his head where's brad oh
there's fliss oh there they are that's the fisherman that's
the pirate this guy this guy means business why why'd you
piss him off that we can't it's your fault they're here
because you pissed him off you threw money at them it's your
fault i can't control conrad nobody can't control conrad
It's your fault.
Oh, you're deciding.
Okay, Conrad, what's your genius idea this time?
What is she doing?
She's crying on his...
What is happening?
What are you doing?
I don't know.
I don't want to do it.
What are you doing?
I don't want to do this.
Oh, oh, but I missed my event and it's my fault.
I'm trying to be a challenge now.
Did you miss it?
You missed it.
There was no...
Okay.
Oh, oh, oh, no.
Oh, no.
I have to choose.
You do it then.
You guys see what I meant.
Yeah?
I did it.
How did you do it?
I had to choose between Conrad and Julia.
Okay, let me try this again.
Let me try this again.
Oh my god.
This is how we're gonna die.
How did you do it?
I right trigger and then I pull with the right.
I'm trying Let me pull Just use your right I swear I do it I
swear to God I swear to God I swear to God This will never
be Alright you fucking do it again I'll do it I'll do it
I'll do it I'll do it Okay watch this It's so easy How did
you do that?
How did you How did you do it?
Okay your turn Oh, never mind.
Oh, no.
Oh.
Why is he bleeding?
Where's Brad?
Oh, no.
I gotta turn the sound down again on this thing.
It's so bad.
I don't know what you said.
How did you guys do it?
Wow, you let Fliss die because you couldn't un-gag her.
I didn't know what you said!
I didn't hear you.
What are you doing?
What's the good news?
I don't see how this could get me worse.
The bad news is these are kind of maybe the fishermen I
pissed off.
Oh my god, Conrad.
Just great.
And the good news?
I recognize them.
What?
How's that good news?
I thought you'd ask the good news first.
We're such an idiot.
Jesus.
Oh, wait.
I'm gonna untie him.
We have to get free.
now yeah come here come here conrad put on some pants man
wait did you have to hold you hold down the right stick yes
yes oh why did you see that i told you look look i didn't
realize you had to hold it who's the gamer now you fell your
quick time event twice oh once it was just the gun Oh my
god, this guy.
Oh.
Yeah, sit back down.
Sit back down, idiot.
Wouldn't they think it's weird that we're un-gagged?
I know, right?
Why don't... Oh, what the?
Alright.
I succeeded my quick time event.
I did mine!
I did mine, yeah.
Okay.
I stopped you from getting beat up.
Alright, Conrad.
Oh, he Conrad kind of deserves it, though, right?
Wait, Conrad's gone.
Bye, Conrad.
Bye.
What did he?
Wait, are you getting taken away?
I'm seeing what's happening.
Oh, shit.
Oh.
What's happening?
Oh, so, like, the guy was like, you're full.
Oh, and then Conrad gets punched.
I saw that.
Good.
Oh, where is he going?
What's happening?
Oh, my God.
They're taking him out.
I mean, if they kill Conrad, that's okay, right?
They're beating Conrad.
We don't care about that, right?
I'm making Julia scared Okay, what do you want?
What are they talking about?
Who gives a fuck?
Okay.
I didn't say fuckers.
I said
Oh, wait, they're actually killing Conrad.
Wait, they're actually killing Conrad.
You did this!
Yeah, you pissed them off.
Uh-oh.
Oh, wait.
They have the gun?
Oh, no, it's Oh my god, they're gonna kill Conrad.
I'm gonna say nothing.
Don't say anything!
Oh my god, they're gonna kill!
If I say something, I feel like they're gonna...
They're gonna get agitated.
I got it.
What?
What is that?
I saved Conrad, you're welcome.
No!
Why would you want to save Conrad?
Because you told me to!
You literally told me to!
Oh, I got a cuticle cutter.
I'm cutting the ropes.
I'm gonna say nothing again.
Oh, they're coming back.
They're coming back.
Go.
Come on, come on.
I feel like if I say something, I would, they would agitate
him more.
Oh, he's coming back.
Hey, welcome back, Conrad.
I'm back.
I saved Conrad just for you, Min.
I've kissed you love Conrad so much.
Yeah, I want to see him get us killed even in different
ways.
I feel like that.
Like, yeah, I feel like you have higher survival.
Oh my god, he's dead.
Alex, why did you get up so slowly?
You have no restraint!
Shut the fuck up.
Just open the door!
Julia breaking heads.
Not the other way around.
Fliss seems to be getting buddy buddy with him.
Uh, wait.
Why is Fliss... What's going on, you're in?
Uh, I'm with Conrad and Alex.
Oh, you're with us?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, you're Conrad!
No, I'm Alex!
No, I'm Conrad!
But I'm sure he's fine.
These guys probably just want money or something.
Yeah.
Man, if I let Conrad die here, I wouldn't have to be forced
to play Conrad.
Everyone has to play Conrad at least once.
Even you, Chad.
Everyone has to feel the shame of being Conrad.
saving Conrad, you will have to deal with Conrad later.
No, they knew that you liked him so much.
They let you stay as him.
I literally saved him for you!
What did they do to Julia?
Are you okay?
Are you okay, little Julia?
Hey, hey, are you okay?
Are you okay, little girl?
They didn't touch me.
Okay.
They asked about our parents.
What?
Which money they have.
Oh.
It's going to be a hard to see.
situation yeah there you go nice what if everybody dies but
Conrad should we do that make it a bit or it's our mission
is keep Conrad alive is he just counting yeah what is he
counting oh I think he's seeing the time between the
lightning and the thunder oh that's smart yeah yeah Wow,
it's spoken like a true Conrad.
Wow, nerd.
Came here on a boat.
Maybe we can take it.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's a speedboat.
The main guy here.
He's got a gun.
Uh-oh.
Uh, I'm gonna, you know.
Well, at least one of us can get on their boat.
Add some help.
We're gonna get on that boat.
Right.
Okay, I'm gonna say nothing.
So you have to get on the boat.
What?
Oh, what do you think?
She's asking you.
I can get out through the window.
We got to break these off first.
Oh, that's you.
That's you.
Don't get here.
You're going to get through the window.
Yes, you're going to get through the window.
Yeah, good call.
Good call.
No, Conrad.
Conrad the goat.
I said nothing.
So you don't see me sneaking.
Okay, sneaking mission.
Let's do it.
All right, be sneaky.
Be sneaky.
Oh, no, please.
I don't want to be Conrad anymore.
No, I have to be Conrad.
Uh-oh.
Go, Conrad.
Go.
Oh my god.
Go, Conrad.
Go.
Oh.
Is this me?
Is this my quick time event?
Oh, shoot.
Ah!
Oh!
I got it!
Don't fuck this up.
Get the scissors!
Don't fuck this up!
Ow!
Hey!
Oh, I might have fucked it up a little bit.
What did you do?
I'm doing my quick time event right now.
I thought it said X.
What?
Just get it!
Oh, Bradley!
I'm escaping.
Get out of here, get out of here, Conrad.
Go live.
Live a long life.
Oh, Obi.
I did it.
I think Liz is going to die.
I have a hostage.
I went escape.
I didn't grab a knife.
What?
What do you mean?
Wait, what did you do?
hostage I'm gonna kill him oh my god there you are like
spider-man oh I don't care about you Julie oh I tried I
really did try I'm Oh my god, is he dead?
Did you dodge it?
Conrad's scared!
We did it!
Conrad's gone!
We saved Conrad!
Conrad lived!
Neither of us have to play as him again.
We did it, guys.
Thank God I was Conrad and doing the quick time.
I saved you.
I could have shielded Julia.
But I saved you instead.
Yeah, because you know we need to save Conrad.
He's gone.
Oh my God.
He's gone his little big adventure.
He's just Conrad.
Oh my God.
Guys, apparently people were like, people usually never save
Conrad.
He usually dies there.
Conrad deserves better.
Gone Red?
We did it, guys.
He's gonna be the hero in the end.
Yeah.
Oh, my God, the sound effects.
Can I turn the sound effects down real quick?
Yeah.
Okay, I'm turning them down again.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe it.
They're like, usually Conrad gets shot.
I don't know how you guys see.
We have our priorities straight.
Absolutely.
Okay, I'm good.
The only two people who saved Conrad.
Willingly.
Not for, like, completionist's sake.
Okay.
We're hostages.
Cool.
What do we do now?
She's, like, looking for him.
Why do you make all the important decisions?
Connie!
All right.
Shut the fuck up!
Why can't you wipe the blood off your face?
Why is she looking like...
We were only talking.
There's no harm in just talking.
You want to talk?
Yeah.
We practically won the game.
Keep the body of the cow.
We have one survivor, so we basically won.
I'm just going to say it.
gotta be in on this geez guys we travel in the same way i
bet you told them about the manchurian gold they're in
cahoots they don't even know about the gold why did you tell
them about the gold oh my god well fliss what do you have to
say i can't believe what i'm hearing i just lost everything
i have and this is what you think what do you mean you lost
everything Put a cork in it.
Oh, oh, oh my god.
Oh, dang it.
That quick time event was to save Julia.
Oh, yeah.
Come with me.
Oh, Phyllis again.
Kahoot, Kahoot, Kahoot.
What happened to Brad?
I talked to this guy.
Brad is right next to me.
And talking to you.
Why not?
Why won't you talk to me?
Move the gun.
Please, take the gun off of us.
We should save Julia next.
We'll save the worst people.
They can have each other.
Julia and her brother, they can have each other.
What's going on, Alex?
Um...
How bad is the store?
She's helping them.
She's gotta be.
You really think she is?
Why are you like this?
you like this alex what do you want i don't know i'm just
talking to you man um uh should i provoke them you guys or
what should i do i literally was compliant i'm not i'll bark
no bite you're just a little kitten ain't you a kitten my
discord kitten you wanna test that theory yeah come here
come on talk to me No Look, I'm being compliant.
Look he's being a little baby.
That's enough.
No talking.
What the fuck are you doing down there?
What are you trying to make sure we don't die?
Where are you?
Oh, you're with bliss.
You're antagonizing the fucking other pirates.
Oh, oh my god.
Oh, oh Oh, oh, quick time event quick time.
Oh, oh, oh, whoa I'm I got my both mine did you I got mine
too?
Okay All right, I doubt it.
The water.
Oh, my Titanic moment.
Police, you're downstairs.
I'm upstairs.
Our ship is flooding.
We're going to drown.
Wait, what's going on?
The ship is flooding.
Oh, my God.
There you guys are.
We're drowning.
I'm going to hold on.
I'm going to rescue Brad instead.
Get out of here, Brad.
Get out of here!
I hope you guys are okay, because I had a choice to save,
but I chose not to.
Hey!
Move it!
We're gonna drown.
Oh my god.
Why was there so much water in there?
Because we're in the ocean.
The water's not so close to go in the boat.
Good job looking after number one.
Real smooth.
Great leadership, Fliss.
What did I do?
I literally saved us by...
Brad can't help himself.
He's a little baby.
Uh-oh.
Oh my god, we found the ship!
We found the ship!
Oh my god, we found Madonna!
Yeah!
There it is.
Oh my god, get in there.
Ah!
There's Madonna!
The man, that was the man.
of him the man oh
my god wait that wasn't conrad you don't think right no
because no i think it was conrad everyone's still alive yeah
we did it we did it we're keeping people alive
i think he's disappointed in us i think he wanted conrad to
die you appear to have saved somebody oh a bold move that
paid off we mean yeah yeah i would have done it too if it
would be yeah it was a quick time event i don't think you
would have i did all my quick time events most of them i'd
like to offer you some forewarning of what's to come do you
want to see it tempted oh oh we can do decide.
Wait, do you want to know or not?
I want to know.
Okay, let's know.
I got to make a decision, yeah.
In agreement.
Clue it is.
Yeah.
The merchant of Venice, Act 2, Scene 7.
The prince of Morocco pulls a scroll from the eye of a skull
and reads, all that glisters is not gold.
Often have you heard that tone.
What the fuck does that mean?
I don't...
What?
Anyway, that wasn't a hint.
That wasn't a hint!
That's not even a bit, it's barely a riddle.
I presume you're eager to get back to your story.
What?
Here's a thing.
Everything may not be entirely as it seems.
All that glisters is gold.
Probably shouldn't have said that.
Oh, don't be greedy.
Mint, don't be greedy.
I'm not.
It's you.
Did you get the tablet?
I had to to progress.
I think.
Oh, yeah, I did.
You're Julia now.
No, no.
You're Fliss.
Oh, I'm Fliss now.
Okay, this is my first time being Fliss.
Oh, no.
Now I'm Julia.
Now to fix the relationship you ruined.
Like I said, if they were truly happy for those seven years,
my little tiny decisions did nothing but how many tiny
decisions did you make there was like no decisions why are
we going to the that ship why can't we stay in our little
ship what is that oh what they find it's a dynamite isn't it
what i don't think so what was that why did they suddenly
decide to search in there i know that's what i'm seeing why
can't we just stay in our tiny ship Oh, it's an engine part.
Come on, Julia.
Apparently it was sinking.
What the hell is wrong with me?
Yeah, that's what I said.
And you were like, we're in the ocean.
How was I supposed to know we were sinking?
I thought just water got in.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, we're all going to die in here.
Yeah, we're going to die in the ship of Madon.
But we know Brad would live in the bathroom here.
No, that was the bathroom of the other boat.
No, it was the bathroom of this boat.
No, I don't think so.
Right?
It was blue.
The ship is blue.
It was...
Oh, we're walking now.
Hey, hey.
Oh, we are.
I was here to stay here.
Hey, remember you can walk faster.
Oh, LB.
I'm walking.
What's here?
I'm walking here.
I got a thing what is this guard duty oh he's watching me
he's watching me I was reading that yeah stop reading I
sucks okay you're supposed to be walking I'm walking
barefoot my job I'm gonna get tetanus oh who are you walking
into this guy oh I walk oh oh he pushed me to my bad my bad
my bad we're walking we're walking apparently we can't even
walk right
there we go oh oh oh no your little bracelet oh my god no no
my bracelet that's like a hundred thousand dollars daddy
bought it for me that's like real gold what's wrong with
your head oh that's a dead body am i able to walk am i
walking oh i am i walking oh wait oh yeah we're I'm gonna
push back.
Sorry, I walked the wrong way.
Are you okay?
You look a little worried.
What's wrong?
Yeah, I don't know.
Oh, Scooby.
What do we do?
Scooby, Scooby.
Oh, gosh!
Who is that?
What is that?
Hey, move.
I wanted to see what the poster says.
The mask of madness.
If you dare to look death in the eye, now showing in the
mess hall.
Do you see what I'm seeing?
I'm in the dormitories.
What are you seeing?
I don't know.
I'm not just walking.
Oh, I can see.
There's an item here.
Grab it.
Are these guys going to do with us now?
Why?
There's Miller.
Miller.
Why are they like not supervising us anymore?
I know.
Where are they?
Oh, I can also look at it.
What is it?
It says Miller.
Miller.
I'm waiting for you here.
I'm at the other side.
Okay, I'm coming.
I'm coming.
Master Miller?
Oh, no.
Oh, there's Alex.
They're slow.
Just as slow as we are.
I don't think LB works.
I'll be honest.
I don't feel any faster.
I don't think so, though.
I don't think it works either.
Why is he moving like he's one of us?
Like, he's moving like an NPC.
Oh, there's rats!
Rats?
I didn't I didn't see any right oh there's something over
here oh what's this it's an internal model memorandum
memorandum this is gonna give us a hint you're covering
Patterson's guard duties tomorrow he is sick again
conveniently it's always when he has guard duties and hold
3a first is 24 o'clock check the chart for rotation oh again
you found a secret maybe that'll help us this is the third
time this week none of us like it down there Maybe Patterson
should buck up.
Get, just get on it.
Maybe it'll, like, help us.
I want to look at the secret.
Yeah, go look at the secret.
I want to look at it.
Oh, it might be in the menu now, right?
No!
I think so.
Yeah, I think you got the secret, so I don't have to look at
the secret.
That's two for two secrets for me.
Oh, son, you're in port to see.
Okay.
Oh.
There's lots of doors here.
Yeah.
are they putting us in the brig wait this is where we were
isn't it when we were conrad and no we were never here I
don't remember this area oh we're locked in oh my god hey
it's pitch black in here give us the light where did that
light come from it doesn't look that dark yeah oh they gave
us a flat they're such nice they're actually so nice yeah
Wow.
He didn't pions aren't that bad.
I bet you weren't actually going to shoot Conrad.
She had a...
Oh, oh, oh my God.
How do we have a lighting?
Gosh, I almost missed that.
My controller was like, in my lap.
How is that still good?
Like, not waterlogged.
I know.
Wait, maybe because the ship never went to the ocean.
Um, Manchurian gold.
It asked to have something to do with the Manchurian gold.
gold we're not far from those coordinates anyone else creep
the fuck out by this ship friendly what's the ship's name so
was manchurian gold the name of the ship that'd be a weird
name i've seen some pretty weird names for ships maybe they
took a vote what's the ship's name oh wow your relationship
with alex went down what how did he go down i literally just
asked about the ship's okay what is this relationship we're
trying to save huh when to get us help we should wait for
him wait for brad um we should just leave i didn't know that
meant we call the coast guard but the duke's radio is shot
we gotta find a radio on this ship oh yeah good luck what's
the status of the duke how would the radio still be working
i saw one of the goons i know right it's been like out of
commission for so long the duke of milan is a floating brick
without it we need to get it back while those guys if i
thought it was sinking if it was sinking then whatever they
think they're gonna find on this floating ship gonna be
still there you gotta take advantage of yeah exactly i don't
think it was sinking fliss i don't think so you told me it
was sinking that's why i agreed with you i don't know why
that told me it was sinking no you said it first i didn't
know i was like why don't we just do this but you're like no
it's donkey or whatever but i i mean obviously that's not
true they're being just as bad to eat no water we were
drowning there's water everywhere just get a fucking bucket
oh my god it was julius who was just like we're gonna drown
accepted oh hey we apologized to each other cool after we
were arguing with each other they apologized what's that oh
we did our job i grabbed something a room oh i got something
here too some glasses i don't know we're too busy arguing i
know okay okay how are you doing what's this oh i found a
secret hey baby doll i miss you like crazy three months
until my next leave and jumping into your arms three months
i've been on the shore leave with these guys had a few beers
but don't worry i'm keeping everything ready for you if you
catch my drift how's work i hope that boss of yours is
leaving you alone I know you can take care of yourself, but
I feel helpless being so far away, and I want to keep you
safe.
This guy, Miller, was really freaked out.
I got a lot of time to think while I'm guarding the cargo
hulls.
It's dark and spooky down there.
Some of the other guys have seen a figure roaming around,
but I always got you with me to keep me safe, too.
I'll be with you soon, and get a job as a mechanic, and we
can get married and have two children.
We'll be happy together forever.
Love you so much, Miller.
Sam again.
Look at the picture on the wall.
Oh, what picture?
Come here.
This one.
This one right here.
Right here.
Oh, okay.
Is that going to give us a secret?
Yeah.
And like look at it and then like look up.
Are you good?
There you go.
I don't know.
What was wrong?
What is wrong?
I wonder what happened.
All right, I'm looking up.
Wait, it won't let me look up.
What do you mean?
With the right, with the right analog.
It didn't let me.
What?
It didn't let me look up.
Oh, you missed the secret.
You missed the secret.
I missed the secret?
No!
Yeah.
But I want to look at that too.
Move.
I'm listening to the...
Do you know French?
Yeah?
We?
He says, I don't have the tools to do as I say, and that's
all.
What the hell?
I'm live translating.
Fuck you.
I'm live translating for you.
Oh, okay, thanks.
Nothing, asshole.
it shut up junior you're sitting there and watching the
prisoners this is a real canadian is that this is a prison
do you not subtitles on you don't have subtitles on do you
no i do i have them on
yeah but what if you weren't looking at them and still
translate
i'm talking to the boyfriend Oh.
I'm still listening to these guys.
Hmm.
Oh, I'm telling him.
I'm telling Alex about the ghosts.
Oh, I'm going to listen.
I thought the rest of the guys were just trying to scare
him.
Hold on.
I'm stuck.
I can't get over there.
Hold on.
I'm stuck.
Oh, that I can't get over there.
How did you get over there?
Hold on, come on.
LB, LB.
I just want to tell you what the fishermen will plan on.
Yeah, I want to know what the fishermen is going to be
doing.
Yeah.
Oh, there you.
Maybe they'll let us go if they find all that gold.
And if they don't find any gold, this whole situation...
What happened?
Alex just disappeared on my screen.
What did you do, Alex?
Oh my god!
This is a fucking old ship, but maybe it still has a radio
that works.
I doubt it.
The bridge.
That's very hopeful.
Where the fuck is Brad in all of this?
He's in the room.
somewhere he's just existing okay well we're not gonna do
anything from in here we need to keep looking around and try
to find a way okay in the end we gotta make sure julia
survived yeah all right there was some stuff over here oh
there is there is over here yeah there's oh here there's one
over here i'm staring where what's this oh you got it you
got this Yeah, I know how to hold now.
You're pushing me out of the way.
I did it.
Nice.
Oh, what's this?
No!
I found it!
The way out.
That's the game we're playing.
The way out, everybody.
The way out.
How am I?
Oh, there.
Hey.
Hey, what's this?
I wonder why it's abandoned.
a newspaper secret found wait we're looking at the same 47
archaeologists missing in iraq 24 british archaeologists
have gone missing in the mountains of iraq the hudson
expedition arrived in the kingdom in september last year
with a starting goal unearthing and then oh oh this must be
the thing we found in the cargo yeah this could be the cargo
thing that's why they're all possessed and scared.
Yeah.
They're cursed.
This is cursed.
Is there anything else we missed in here?
Oh, what's this?
Oh my god, Bradley scared the crap.
Oh my god, he's right there.
Oh my god, he scared me so bad.
He just he just doesn't do anything.
He's useless.
Yeah, I'm here to help you.
We know somebody that's not gonna survive.
I can't get it open.
We can get it over here.
We're not keeping Bradley alive, right?
No, Bradley can die.
Yeah, Brad's just gonna die.
Down with the nerd.
No nerds allowed.
Freaking closer to the open.
Freedom.
Oh, uh, this is the way out.
Yeah.
This is the way out.
I'm excited.
My excitement's going up.
Doki Bird is deciding.
I got this.
No, I got this.
Oh, yeah.
Someone should create a distraction.
This is going to be loud.
Okay.
Alex, relationships.
Oh, Julia goes up.
Oh.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What is she doing?
What's going on?
Wait, wait.
Yeah, you make a distraction.
Me?
Yeah, why don't you do the distraction?
Oh.
Um, I'm going to distract.
Here I go.
I hope Fliss doesn't die.
Ah, blah, blah.
Bradley, get away.
Hey, you dumb switch.
Maybe I shouldn't let you distract.
Yeah, hey, all that stuff she said, but double is gross.
Your mother's mothers, too.
Whoa, don't talk about my mom.
Oh, are you doing it?
No, I'm doing the quick time event.
Oh, thank God I'm doing the quick time event.
That's right.
Your mother's all sucking.
Let us out.
Yeah, your mother's.
Yeah, dear.
Yeah.
Are they coming?
Why are you screaming?
Because they don't want them to hear us Doing the vent.
We're already done, Fliss.
Shut up.
Come on.
What do you mean?
You're Fliss.
I'm not... I...
Uh-oh.
Wait, what's going on?
Come on, Fliss.
Fliss.
Fliss, come on.
There you go.
God, I can't believe she's not wearing shoes.
Replacing.
What are you deciding?
Replace it.
Yeah.
they'll never know then they'll never know oh no
where did it go we're fencing among us among us oh man among
us we're gonna get separated at some point i feel like it
too find a way off the ship we need to keep going come on
there's gotta be some stairs around here okay okay what's
going on wait why am i holding the light wait who am i oh
wait who am i what do you mean who are you i don't know
always wait oh wait are you alex i'm alex are you alex yeah
yeah yeah wait what's that word oh wait there's something
over here too there's stuff in here yeah they're all leaving
but we got yeah we're splitting up already i found a piece
of paper oh it's good to know that we're splitting up
already i found the guard duty regulations they say i found
the uniforms wait how do i oh there we go guys nobody is
allowed into 3a seriously nobody okay guys uh i'm coming
back where are you no alcohol where are you hold on i'm
right by the front door the door we just like here look at
me turn around i'm turning around you see me where are you
i'm right i'm right in front of you oh there's nothing in
there that yeah yeah yeah yeah i think we're gonna get
caught up by the pirates no why are you looking down like
that why are you always looking down oh i'm sorry i'm trying
to look at where i'm standing i'm the one with the lights i
have a flashlight too but how do you have a oh wait i found
a map why is the light flickering there oh it abounds what
was that oh okay so cargo hole two is out of Are you gonna
remember that?
Cargo hold two is out of bounds.
Oh, yeah, when are we gonna get to cargo hold two?
Wait, where do we go?
Why was the light flashing over here?
Yeah, you first.
Here?
In here?
You first.
What's going on in here?
What's going on?
The lights actually work?
Oh my god.
Wait, I'm in the bathroom.
I'm in the bathroom.
Oh, I found a light in the bathroom.
Ladies first.
All right.
Anybody?
It's reading time.
I found a secret.
Dear Eilis, I'm finally coming home.
This is it, darling.
One last trip across the Pacific and I'll be back to you and
the girls.
I can't wait to see your faces.
Tell Ned and Nancy to get excited.
They're going to see Daddy real soon and he's got gifts for
y'all.
I'm sure glad to be back at sea.
It's hotter than an Oklahoma summer out there on the land
and there's no escape from it.
I've been all right because I got your letters to keep me
going.
They censored them, which is probably for the best.
the others steal them to read and I don't like them reading
our letters.
It really creeps me out.
It keeps telling me there's a little boy on board and it
sounds like Ted.
What?
Wait, Doki, our feet are smelly.
Our feet are smelly.
Oh, oh, we gotta go.
We gotta go.
I didn't finish the reading it, but oh, we gotta go.
Our feet are on the side.
I think that's the side.
We gotta get out of here, man.
I think, oh, Roro, Roro, oh, Scooby, Scooby.
Where do they go?
I think, oh, this way.
You hear that?
I think the moment it starts getting smelly, that's when
death is coming and we split up.
We split up.
No, no, they're right here.
They're right here.
They're right in front of me.
All right.
I like how we're the only ones with the flashlight and we're
like back.
In the very back.
Yeah.
Oh, oh, my bad.
time to explore that's a lot of people who are suspiciously
nowhere to be found yeah wait there's stuff yeah there's
something here oh what's that maybe everyone's hiding in the
hole are you picking it are you picking it up i think it's a
skull of a rat oh there's another thing here too it's a rat
skull oh so much how is like i sure love how all the legs
are oh my god i just got grabbed by a thing i've ever heard
in my life skipper has catoed the boost for this goddamn
trip okay none of these glory what the hell are you doing
this lore is not interesting he's just talking about alcohol
can i turn down the is it the sound effects that is what the
music has to be the sound or is it the music that goes i
think i'm gonna hold on i'm turning it i think it's the
music no it's so bad i think it's the music it's going down
to 35.
you got the spooky you got the 35 i'm yeah some spooky it
was so loud oh my god wait how are you scared of ghosts
you're you are a ghost i'm scared of jump scares yeah but
it's just your neighbor grabbing your hand i don't know
every go look at our feet look at our feet look at our oh i
could grab wait okay i want to see what this jump scare is
oh yeah yeah do the rat do the rat do the rat i'll do the
rat oh i'm watching i'm watching oh oh i'm looking at it i'm
watching i'm watching am i going crazy i might be going
crazy there's nothing you lied to me there was nothing there
what you're going crazy you didn't take your meds i have
smelly feet don't you have smelly feet it's not my fault
it's not my fault someone here was lying oh i found a
picture frame i think this is a Is this a premonition?
Oh.
Uh-oh.
What is this?
Uh.
Here you might want to look at that one.
Okay.
We gotta make sure nobody dies.
Uh, yeah, I think, uh.
Oh.
All right.
We gotta make sure Alex doesn't die.
When you're Alex.
It's on your head.
It's in your hat.
No, I got no.
They already warned you how to save Alex.
I don't know what was going on there.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Bradley doesn't have shoes either.
What's wrong with you guys?
Mint has to protect herself.
It's not my fault.
I'm dead.
So that means I couldn't protect myself from the beginning.
Oh my god.
The flashlight.
Turn down the flashlight.
Turn it off!
There's someone down there, alright?
Shh.
Everyone's quiet.
I'm the loudest whisperer ever.
Just turn it off.
Why are you putting your hand over a flashlight?
Oh, there's the pirates.
Save the battery, man.
Could be those charging flashlights, you know?
The...
The weeweewee.
The whirring ones.
it's the distributor cap from the duke oh yeah i shouldn't
get that yeah i'm sure yeah we gotta get that so we can
leave right oh no oh oh he's gonna break it he's gonna
destroy it so nobody can use it oh never mind what's he
doing he grabbed a weapon we need one he has a hammer yeah
um all right grab it then hurry I don't need you barking or
this big guy I swear to God if I have to play Fliss because
of that I swear to God
well she was the one who was like I'm gonna go get it okay
then go oh you're calling back in Bradley's a hero now Brad
Brad do this all right who's gonna be Brad, who's gonna be
Fliss?
Uh-oh.
If I'm getting Brad, I'm making sure he dies.
Just so you know.
If I get Brad, I'll do the same.
I'll do the same.
Oh, my God.
No, I won't warn Brad.
I'm just gonna hide.
Good luck, Brad.
Good luck.
Brad is the victim.
oh my god oh seven brad we were very clear that we don't
want brad anymore brad has been voted off the island oh my
god oh my god oh my god oh no fliss oh no he sounds really
concerned oh no fliss oh no the other pirates are coming
over this is such a long cutscene Oh my god, don't gasp like
that.
Oh wait, it's the gun!
It's the guy with the gun!
Stop crying!
I'm going to be doing it.
Who's going to be doing it?
Not yet!
Oh my god!
Oh come on, Brad!
What the hell?
That's not us.
It's the AI.
Yeah, it's the AI.
Wow, you guys, come on.
Don't let them out of your sight.
Girl, you're holding a whole-ass lantern.
Like, they're going to see you.
I think it's our...
I think... No, it's your fault.
You literally told Fliss to go down there and get the thing.
I mean, she should have...
She was the one who brought it up in the first place.
I got this.
That's a very sick rat.
Oh, you're Fliss?
Am I Fliss?
Yes?
Uh-oh.
We're split up.
Wait, what are you?
I'm Alex.
Are you Alex?
Yeah.
Are you getting...
Are you...
Oh, no, we're split up.
Why do I need to see this now?
Are they interrogating you?
Are they torturing you?
We're just walking.
We're walking somewhere.
Oh, okay.
I'm here.
We went somewhere else.
I might...
We might have these two die.
What?
Are you sacrificing...
fliss so that no fliss is cool both of us you're the one
that go down fliss they're fucking go down there i know she
it was her idea she said i'm gonna go down there and get it
and i said okay do it bet that's what i said to her oh my
god julie looks really scary she just looks like a she looks
so scary just standing there in the middle of the walkway
yeah we like fliss we don't want list to die you're the one
that said bliss down there you had a choice not to send
bliss down there she probably she wasn't gonna listen to me
let's be honest she wasn't gonna listen to me she was gonna
be like i'm going down there whether you want me to or not
we don't know that we don't know that you gave her the
choice oh my god this was telling you to do it no she no she
wasn't she said i'm gonna go get that and then my choice was
tell her don't or go get it and she She made her choice.
She could have been like...
Yeah, but you said go get it.
You chose to go get it, didn't you?
I'm stuck.
Hold on.
Where's the door?
Okay, everybody.
I'm stuck.
You guys, I'm stuck for real.
Oh!
How do I go through this door?
Wait.
There's a dead guy.
Uh-oh.
Dead person.
Oh, it was just a hat.
JK.
Wow.
I'm stuck.
I'm so stuck.
stuck how do i get through here so we have a very paranoid
gunsman oh he's very scared is he experiencing oh there we
go finally is he experience no what's going on what's going
on on your side i'm fine everything's fine i have a hat now
we've been here before we have yeah i got midon i got
midon's
the oh wait hold on there's got to be stuff in here to find
right there's not a dead body in here there's not a dead
body in here there's not a dead body there's screams on my
end there's screams on my end you're take your meds take
your meds uh uh don't don't look it's fine nothing you don't
want to stop over here why aren't you i just saw some organs
okay chill calm down you saw organs yes they were organs
there were like live organs somehow they were live in the
hey wait what you found a secret oh i found i'm having beef
casserole just ground to a halt on this one day no way ship
just stopped functioning tuesday was cereal
home fried potatoes boiled eggs i found a body
You're like, cereal, back on Jokey's side, there's a body.
That's not until, that's not until Fridays, come on.
The body is not on the menu yet.
Wait, there's soup here.
You want some?
Oh.
Soup du jour, mademoiselle.
I found another secret.
Please, relax.
Oh my god, Julia.
I'm just messing around.
There's no time for messing around, Alex.
God.
Oh no, the stinky feet is here.
Oh, I have stinky feet too.
I just noticed.
Oh, we're so...
Oh my god, where are you?
Why did we split up?
It's fine.
Oh, there's a child.
I think there's running.
You're really...
Okay, you're really in trouble.
I'm thinking about what's for you.
I haven't seen anything yet.
I remember the last time there was running children.
Uh-oh.
Wait.
So I heard something.
What did I hear?
I found a notebook.
It says...
Let's see.
Nothing.
I can't even open.
Open the notebook, idiot.
Oh, I just look.
Oh, there we go.
Oh.
Okay, it's a diary.
Oh, read it.
Read that diary.
June 18th, Wednesday.
been at sea long and i'm sick of the damn food already that
muck we ate tonight was a joke the cooks do their best with
what we got i'm sure but man i'd kill for something fresh
first thing i'm doing when i get home is having me a tall
glass of milk
june 19th thursday every one of the u.s papers was talking
about that massacre in philly Are these the guys American
or...
All I'm seeing is while you're reading this diary, our
kidnapper fucking died.
I can't...
I'm just like, listen, you read the diary and a kidnapper
disappeared.
It's crazy to think how we're out here traveling the world,
trying to keep our country safe, and there's people killing
each other in the streets back home.
I could show you Zabia after reading about home, but the
captain has issued a ban on booze.
Guess how I'll be counting sheep tonight.
Oh my god, there's more.
Oh no.
Oh, secret.
Who found a secret?
It was a you?
No, oh wait, I found it.
Yeah, I found a secret.
June 20th, Friday.
Some of the guys had a little wrestling competition in one
of the cargo holds today.
I did okay, but Wagner eventually knocked down.
me out of it.
I joked he should be disqualified on account of his size,
but no dice.
I like how you're reading it.
I'm still trying to find a way out.
You're just standing there reading the dice.
It'd take a whole crowd of people to pin him down.
He certainly ain't eaten the same as the rest of us, that's
for sure.
June 21st, Saturday.
I'm sure the cargo we have in the hold has something to do
with the squad that went missing.
Their leader Jones heard a legend about a room full of
ancient solid gold statues from Manchurian child emperor
they said they were said to be cursed but that sounds like a
load of baloney it's the child it's the child also mid I
hope to God um that you're heading over to where I'm heading
over because I'm progressing right now I'm reading I'm
progressing in knowledge okay I don't know if they found
them but they never did return from their mission maybe
they're returning now okay that's all of it cool all right
cool um I got away and Like, I'm back in the cargo hall.
Oh, I'm, like, far.
I don't know where I am in the kitchen.
Yeah, I could tell.
I could.
I could tell.
Oh, I got the knife.
I heard something, though.
I think I'm starting to hear people.
Uh-oh.
Wait, I see a premonition picture.
I'm getting a premonition.
Oh?
I'm getting a premonition right now.
What was your premonition?
Mine was the one where, like, uh, it was a guy in a hood
with a stick.
Oh, my God.
I just saw Bradley's death.
Wait, how does he die?
How does he die?
He gets stabbed!
Wait, I have the knife!
Wait, but it's someone...
I just picked up the knife!
It's someone wearing a raincoat.
Why'd you pick up the knife?
No, he was the one that was holding the...
I didn't know!
I picked up the knife!
I literally just picked up the knife while you said that.
What?
What just happened?
There's something in here with us.
Didn't you...
Bradley, what's going on?
I zoomed in.
Did you hear anything?
I was.
I picked up the knife!
I'm scared.
I know I saw something.
It was moving in the shadows.
Something's moving in the shadows.
It's probably just a rat.
Oh, Charas!
Rats.
Probably just rats.
That's all it was.
My relationship with...
Don't fucking laugh at me.
My relationship with Julia went up.
But she was really bitchy about it.
All right, we've been here before.
I'm sure...
Oh my god, they split me and Brad!
What do you want to do?
Turn around?
We've seen all this before.
Wait, I got split off!
Wait, you split up?
You're by yourself now?
Yeah, I'm by myself.
The door closed on us.
Uh-oh.
Oh my god!
Wait, I'm in the room with the dead bodies!
Crapy travels.
Uh-oh.
Which dead bodies?
The-the-the-the-the-the-the ones that were carried on the
ship at the beginning.
Gotta get out of your toot suite.
Okay, so can we just get the fuck out of that?
I couldn't pick the other option.
Brad, like, I'm seeing hallucinations.
Uh-oh.
Oh my god.
I'm with the bodies.
I'm with the dead body.
Oh, I can't look at that.
I can observe every single body.
Oh god, I'm scared.
I'm scared.
We're both fucking up.
I found a secret.
Wait, there's two bodies in here.
There's two bodies.
What the?
It's practically falling off anyway.
What does that mean?
Oh, that's a bullet.
Is this even human?
What is this?
Look at this.
What is going on?
I just want to reunite with at least somebody.
want to understand the deal with this place oh leave now
leave leave leave leave leave hold on i'm not done yet i'm
not done yet julia oh there's zombies are you okay what's
going on i'm not you found a secret you found a secret and
there's zombies i'm just looking at the bodies
I don't- I found another secret!
I don't want to know.
Let's get out of here.
Save Brad!
Save him!
I got some serious locks in these cascades.
I got another secret.
That's four for four.
What do you mean?
You're getting secrets!
Woo!
What do you mean?
Oh my god.
Hold on, there's something over here.
Uh-oh.
Something's gonna be behind here.
I mean, there might be...
Brad might be dead.
What?
Wait, it's not letting me do it now.
Oh, no.
I'm in the ballroom.
Hold on.
I remember what happens on Ghost Ship, not the ballroom.
It's okay, that was outside.
That was outside.
Wait, it's not letting me do it.
It was inside the ballroom.
I saw the movie.
No, they were out on the...
the deck.
They were out on the deck and then that's when it happened.
They were dancing on the dancing at the pole room.
The pole room's on a deck.
Uh-oh.
It might be stuck.
Oh you guys hear that?
I'm trying to use... I'm trying to do this.
I'm trying to do this but it's not letting me.
My right stick is stuck.
I think press it.
I think I'm having a donkey bird problem.
You gotta wait until I progress.
Keep holding the trigger.
I am.
It doesn't let me progress unless I hold the trigger.
Is it the left one maybe?
No, right?
Oh, you're going through my problem now.
Actually.
Wait, I don't think it'll let me...
Wait, I don't think it'll actually let me progress unless I
do...
Oh, wait.
No, there's a room over here.
Never mind.
Okay, let's go.
Oof.
Okay.
Sorry, guys.
I tried.
I really did.
All right.
Let's see.
What did you have to do?
Spin it.
It was like...
I'm trying to open up a curtain.
but like it was my god hmm hold the stick i was i'll try one
more time oh this there's a pentagram book there's like a
sorcery satan book in the ballroom that's not never know yes
we'll never know i read the spooky book oh you caught you're
cursing us if we i read the spooky book and there's blood
yeah there's blood in the you are seeing a whole lot of bad
stuff i haven't seen anything put me in this situation.
Oh, what do you mean?
I didn't do anything!
Oh, I'm in, like, a really bad area.
I feel like I'm...
Oh!
What the?
Why so spick and spank?
Oh, there's a blood fountain.
Why do I get all the bad stuff?
I think I see a corpse.
Oh!
Fuck!
Oh my god.
Oh.
This is no time to be fucking around.
I'm serious.
I can't take it.
Wait, what's going on?
Wait, now they're real people!
Ah!
Oh my god.
What's happening?
What's going on?
Um, Oh, what the?
I'm touching.
Oh, what the fuck?
Where are you touching?
Where are you touching me?
I touched it.
You touched it?
You touched the bad thing?
Oh, and you're telling me not to touch the bad thing.
It wasn't a bad thing.
I was taught.
I little, I just booped a guy.
Come on.
Like, he was...
A dead body became alive.
Is that not bad enough?
I just went boop on his face.
Oh, I see another premonition.
Oh!
Oh, my God.
Wait, what just happened?
Wait, what?
Somebody's drowning on this one.
We got a hurry.
picture oh okay i think i was too slow oh i turned on the
lights the lights are on now uh the lights were oh oh no
it's the guy it's the guy with the hammer he's after me oh
wait oh i'm bradley bradley wait is he live bradley's alive
why am i by myself are you that's right
what?
I was following you.
He's like talking to you.
He's like, Fliss?
Fliss?
Wait.
Wait, where'd you go?
I think I was following you.
Fliss?
Oh, I think I've been trouble.
Oh, there's a dead body!
Yeah, you were already trouble.
I left you there.
I'm going to touch this guy.
Don't, don't, don't jump at me.
Don't jump.
Why am I taking the bullet out of it?
You You're definitely in trouble.
I left you there.
Why'd you do that?
I tried to save you at the quick time events.
We what you said you were gonna kill Now I have to save
myself now I have to save myself.
I was scared.
I'm sure I've just left you You know what I I kept him alive
so you had to play him.
I'm playing PT actually hey Who were you?
I'm following you, but you have less clothes on.
I think you're trying to seduce me.
Oh!
I'm watching.
I'm following.
Fliss.
Wait, what happened?
Fliss!
Oh!
She just disappeared.
Oh, she's back.
I think Fliss is a ghost.
Yeah, that's what I saw, too.
You saw yourself?
You know, you were a ghost.
Oh, I'm looking at the bullet again.
Oh, this time it says My name, no, it says Alex on it!
Is Alex going to get shot?
I think so.
Oh, no.
Oh, Fliss?
What does that mean?
Girl, what does that mean?
Do I open this again?
Nukes.
Oh, Manchura Gold!
You found the gold.
I found the gold.
Guys, we're going to be rich.
Don't be greedy.
I'm up with a hand.
I'm playing PT.
I'm playing PT, real?
absolutely now you know how i felt the guy with the gun is
here now what's going on this is this is why i kept brad leo
alive i can't see you're in the way this is why i kept brad
alive now you have the body is now it has textures floating
what is that what is that floating what is going on
a little bit i think oh the bullet turned into a slug and
it's eating me okay okay are you are you killing bradley off
right now oh we got we got slugs on us we got slugs on us oh
my god i'm exploring kippy kaya look at all these i'm
playing pt i'm playing pt look at all these items around me
let me read some more let me guys guys oh I'm stuck.
Okay, never mind.
Oh, look at all this lore.
Okay, read it out loud.
What's the lore?
Come on.
All right, I got a book, too.
Oh, my God.
The Stanford operating procedure for handling hazardous
chemicals.
Oh, are you ready for some science?
What the?
I put the book down.
This is my fourth time going through the same hallway.
There's just blood on the ground.
ground and a bullet let's see it says oh it says oh oh i
just saw alex die wait what no it's not really him i'm
hallucinating oh okay okay that's good because we only want
to cry to die oh my god i fucked it up but like i'm pretty
sure you can take it home you had every opportunity
panicking oh oh that was a quick time event my bad uh-oh oh
oh i might act he might actually die oh wait did you
actually kill him i was i was adjusting the sound and i
missed the quick time oh no he's fine he's fine oh okay you
can't die from a hallucination okay this is we just have
oh you guys no we're in a different hallway now we made it
out I can't believe it.
You were given one quick time.
I had to do like 20 during that entire ride.
You and you get one quick time event and you messed it up.
I was adjusting my sound.
Alex was so loud.
It's fine.
Don't worry about it.
We're just worried about yourself.
Why are you so obsessed with what I'm doing on my end?
Oh, I feel like something's going to come out now.
What's over here?
Oh.
Who's that?
I'm hearing screams.
Get away.
Are you hearing screams?
I don't even know where to go.
Oh, it's over here.
I don't know.
Either.
I'm just...
No, drop down.
Gosh, there's so much to do.
There's so many options.
This is really...
Skeletons.
This is really choose your own adventure.
It really is.
Because I don't know what to do right now.
I'm looking at Skeleton 1.
Some sort of altercation.
Okay.
Oh, there's the...
oh internal memorandum what you will ask to be kept informed
of the radio situation we attempted outgoing messages of the
following times with no response oh my god i'm going crazy
you found a secret but i'm going crazy that's how it tends
to be isn't it i mean bradley's been pretty crazy this whole
time so like oh i found a wrench oh my god take that take
that weapon weapon back to the Take that?
Take that.
Yes!
Oh, that's the wrench!
I found that wrench earlier!
Wait, next to the guy that was hanging?
Yeah, okay, wait, what?
Next to the guy that hung himself?
Um, he was- There was no hung person when I was there.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm- I'm pretty sure.
Yeah?
What's that?
Oh, the tiniest A button I've ever seen in my entire life.
Wait, what's going on?
Oh, there.
Press A.
Okay, I'm going to head outside to the deck again and see if
I can get out again.
Press A.
Oh, I think I'm trying the door.
I'm going to go outside.
You're going outside?
Yeah, I'm going back outside.
I'm going outside again.
I still haven't seen...
No, no, I'm not hearing this.
I'm not hearing this.
It's an old boat, Bradley.
The outside is real.
it's an old boat bradley chill out okay i'm going downstairs
i got my wrench when you go outside you you're you it makes
you go back inside oh so he'll pt pt yeah wait i'm back here
julia here we go oh you cannot see the bottom oh boy oh boy
bradley you're gonna die you're gonna die bradley what's
going on oh i think i'm i'm fine actually oh you dropped the
wrench no don't drop the wrench we worked so hard for that
what was the point of all of that brad is that you oh i'm
seeing shadow people oh i'm in trouble brad is that you no
wait is that do you see me oh no i missed the cutscene i can
kill brad right now wait no don't that's me that's That's
me, man!
Don't you!
That's me!
I'm gonna kill you!
You're as happy!
No, it's not you!
That's me!
Don't do it!
That's literally me!
Do not!
Wait, there's multiple!
There's like five zombies here!
No, there's nothing!
There's your whole thing!
Don't do anything!
I almost bashed your head in.
I'm serious.
Yeah, damn it!
Who are you playing as, Fliss?
I think so.
Holy shit, you almost...
I almost killed you.
It's because you begged for it.
Oh my god, the guy is right behind us!
Oh shit!
You're like, Alfred, over my head.
You're like, hmm, do I choose it?
Oh, wait, are you Alex, right?
I think so.
Wait, I got pulled out.
What do you see in the water?
I don't know.
I got pulled out now.
Oh, I'm in the ship.
I thought baby.
Or I'm in the plane.
Like before.
Oh, he's a...
Oh, my God.
It's out.
There's a zombie.
Oh.
Kill the zombie.
I punched him.
I think Julia's gonna drown.
Wait.
You're Julia.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
I was like, what do you mean?
Wait, I did everything I was supposed to do.
No, I'm fine.
Oh, hello.
You seem really calm.
Oh, what the?
Okay, I have to help you now.
Wait, there's multiple of you.
What just happened?
Wait, what's going on?
It's all just black.
I can't see anything.
I clearly saved your life.
I couldn't see anything.
Oh, this is a premonition.
What's going on?
Who do I save?
Did I do it?
Who do I do it?
I'm heroic.
What do you mean, who do you save?
It's really my choice.
Wait, who's shrouded?
Who's shrouded?
Keep doing.
Do it.
Keep going.
Oh, my God.
Holy shit, man.
You made me kill a man.
Wait, was it you who died?
No!
You were already working on it!
I was making sure he got faint, not actually kill him!
Oh, do it!
Do it!
You were the one- you could have let go at any time, okay?
I'm just saying it.
You did?
Thanks, Min, you...
I could have made me kill a person.
You could have, I don't have any control over you.
You did the right thing.
Yeah, you did the right thing.
It was him or us.
Oh, what the...
What the fuck?
How did he get thrown over?
Oh, what the fuck?
Oh my god, it's him!
What the fuck?
What is going on?
What the?
Oh, oh my god.
What's going on?
Oh my god.
Punch him.
Do something.
Oh my god.
Run!
Let's go!
Are we doing anything?
Quick time event.
Maybe.
Who is he?
That's the guy that had the hammer, right?
That's the hammer guy?
Yeah.
Why does he look pruney?
He was in the water.
It's John Madan.
Oh, my god.
It's Madan.
It's the man of Madan.
Oh my god.
Hey, stop, don't mess up your QTE.
You can't trip on the stairs.
Fuck.
Uh-oh.
Come on, Julia.
Hit it.
He's here.
What's the matter, Dreamboat?
Don't show up to me anymore.
Uh-oh.
Whoa.
Oh.
Uh-oh.
Time to use our fist.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, you did it.
Oh my god, I'm so proud of you.
Those are the most quick time events I've ever...
I'm actually...
Wait, which way do we go?
Which way do we go?
I don't know.
Are you deciding?
I don't know!
Uh... Oh, what?
Jump!
Shit.
Let's jump.
We're correct.
Oh!
My bad.
It's okay.
Okay.
Um...
Just to help me up, you know?
Okay.
Maybe we shouldn't have jumped.
I pressed Y, but I also pressed...
Fight back or keep going.
Which one?
Keep going, keep going!
Oh, okay.
Oh, okay!
That's fine.
You're gonna kill a second man.
You're obsessed with it.
Oh my god!
I did!
I'm a hero!
Bunk!
Oh my god, keep going.
Oh, Brown Sun!
Oh my god!
You're killing him!
I'm blood first here!
Oh, this is the premonition.
Yeah, you saved him.
Oh my god, it's Fliss.
Oh, thank god.
Yeah, it's me.
Come on, let's go.
Where's Bradley?
Oh my god.
You guys are somewhere safe.
Everybody's alive.
Oh my gosh, we're doing it.
We're doing it.
We're supposed to kill people, but somehow it's working.
Wait, how is Bradley alive?
We're too good at the game, I think.
oh my god keep going keep going murder works
i think yeah i think we'll be all right here okay okay what
why do you think that well i don't trust you bradley oh yeah
i don't bradley you almost killed fliss he's just a surprise
that everybody's alive spiritual wouldn't you say yeah it's
kind of crazy i didn't see so many dead people kind of
disappointed in that why don't we meet you hadn't saw them
come alive apparently have you figured out what's going on
how to stop it how to save the lives of your poor
unfortunate we just gotta leave yeah just leave i hope
although it seems ship's previous occupants never managed to
quite a lot of deaths that night the whole ship died right
let me help you out oh oh boy another hint okay yeah I would
do too okay I need some help yeah give me a hint yeah I
don't want spoilers well then how can I put this the maybe
forces at play here that are more scientific and even some
that are more political you know less supernatural what
perhaps you've started to realize something this facial
expression everything and everyone may not be quite what
they three two five two what the fuck does that mean I hope
that helps what does that mean well aren't you excited to
find out what your poor unfortunates are making of all this
and how you might avoid any more unnecessary yeah it's all
gas it's not go on back to it it's not supernatural it's not
cursing we're hallucinating because of the gases yeah the
more we're inside the more we're getting hallucinations gas
gas gas oh I'm Alex you're Julia okay alright what the hell
was wrong with you back there I don't know Mitch you almost
my head that's ridiculous that's ridiculous what the fuck is
going on with this ship we're seeing dead people it feels
like there's some like like evil like literal evil going on
down there let's just stay calm and relatively sane about
this okay the stuff I saw it's like there were these old
soldiers they were bodies they were dead but then they came
alive and that doesn't sound wasn't the only alex oh alex
wasn't the only alex the only alex that's why i was confused
that's like what do you mean alex wasn't the only alex um uh
i wouldn't hurt you i'd never hurt you you know that right
i'm true i know it's just this can't all be happening all
relationships went up we're fixing it we're fixing it we're
fixing it we're fixing your no their prior mess they had a
mess already we're just we're just making it better you know
what do we know that's real um um is this a ghost ship am i
crazy or are we on a ghost ship like ghost ships are real
and this is one and we're totally on it and oh holy we're so
totally i was gonna say the same thing yeah i'm not crazy
people to see weird here apparently the guards were super
freaked out by something they saw in the cargo holds oh we
found a note that said a bunch of guys got to get out of
guard duty because they were really freaked out by something
yeah oh oh there might be like bacteria on the gold that's
eating our brains oh yeah it's a brain-eating bacteria
anyone figure out what happened to all the sailors did they
catch a rescue boat or something oh i mean we've seen their
bodies mausoleum yeah and a ship so where'd all the corpses
come from they actually look like they've been scared to
death
about the gold it can't be like ask about the goat i'm not
gonna ask about the gold why not it's a cursed gold it's not
cursed our kid was like don't be greedy no it's fine oh i'll
ask about the gold don't worry i got you that gold should be
around you right anybody catch a glimpse of it it's a
fucking jungle and it's looking all over our gold yeah i'm
pretty sure this isn't exactly and neither let's just go
well that's supposed to be greedy i'm just wondering just
wondering what's wrong with being curious we're not going
anywhere without the distributor cap the duke needs it to
run didn't you grab that though she grabbed it no one of the
captains grabbed it oh if we can find it and use it oh it's
working that's great but do you think it still works yeah
but where's the radio it was blinking see i know that means
the radio's on but where's the radio station probably over
there right yeah oh yeah oh what the oh okay who am i oh i'm
fliss i'm fliss okay okay i'm alex okay before we start wait
i need a pause i need the bathroom okay i'll be right back
okay let's look at the collections and characters everybody
i'm fliss i'm innocent i'm relaxed oh oh all of our oh my
god my relationship with Alex is insane I just watched it go
all the way down Brad is whatever Julia's pretty down Conrad
but I'm innocent I'm relaxed I'm excited I'm altruistic I'm
guarded I'm motivated oh my god what secrets wow oh actually
we haven't even found that many have we what's this flight
plan uh-huh private Miller master Miller our bearings What
are these?
The kitchen knife.
Oh, these are the hints that we've gotten, I think.
Yeah, these are the hints.
Our premonitions.
Cut of your jib.
In the offing.
High and dry.
Master Miller.
Yeah, Master Miller.
Let's see.
Whoops.
Oh, gosh.
I'm so used to playing Japanese.
games where the circles to press okay oh my gosh ryan carter
oh i'm back oh welcome back all right what were you doing i
was looking at our secrets yeah did we get some good secrets
oh yeah oh i'm surprised we're making it this far all right
i'm ready honestly okay all right anything else in here or
worth something so i think we're supposed to go outside see
inside the more we inhale the gas you're right but we're
outside it's fine we're yeah that's what we got to see
inside outside now totally effed oh my god we're so effed
right now i'm just going for it why are you playing as
flissa not my girlfriend julia yeah i don't know yeah i i
looked at our relationship uh flissa's relationship with
alex is completely down like in the back what what did you
do what did you what did i what did you you literally go bed
like let's go down there i've never been fliss i've been
fliss like what's this over here what's this what's this no
what's this what's this i'm gonna get it i'm gonna look at
it i'm looking at it i'm looking at it i'm looking at it too
i'm looking at two i'm looking at it holes bullet holes oh
there's bullet holes there we can't use them we can't use
them we can't use it we gotta go forward oh yeah he did
accuse her of being in cahoots that's true yeah it did
didn't you accuse me?
No, I didn't do that.
It was Alex.
Oh, we're finding a way up.
Is that what we're doing?
I'll keep my eyes.
We have to find a way to get to the radio tower.
Oh, I thought, okay, I thought we had to just get over
there.
Oh, my gosh.
We're acting really casual for like, you know, some guys
that are like, you know, for almost for seeing several dead
people.
And I killed a man.
I killed several men.
I found a way up.
Over here.
Help me out.
i think this is our way up i mean it's the only way up give
me a lift what give you yeah you're a strong powerful woman
oh my god damn shouldn't it be me that gives us right holy
and he doesn't even help her get all the way up yeah he just
pulls you a little bit i was like all right i did my
dang she's strong oh we're back oh we're back did no one
help brad nope there he is he's standing right there i know
i know but no one helped him get up he just clapped up
himself brad are you okay wait i'm gonna go talk to him come
here brad you're gonna talk to him bro we gotta find the
radio tower i just want to say what are you thinking brad
the more we're inhaling the gas we're on the he doesn't care
he really doesn't care about me okay fine he doesn't care
about you you literally Well, he almost bashed Maya.
If anything, I shouldn't be wanting to talk to him.
Okay, we gotta split up maybe.
We got this way.
No, we're not splitting up.
Who's that down there?
Who's that?
There's someone down there.
What?
No, but that's Brad.
No, no, no.
Over here.
Wait, there is.
Wait, you're right.
Who is that?
I'm going the other way.
Who's that?
I'm going.
You see, I told you this way was the better way.
I told you.
Oh.
Ladies first.
the flashlight i think ladies first i think i'm a gentleman
all right i'll go here all right no i can't see it it's so
dark did you just go madame madame why don't you so dark i
can't see i'll flash i'm holding the flashlight in front of
you now no no it's not it's on the wall it's on the wall for
me oh my god what is going on here what is this oh i don't
like that camera i don't Oh, it's gone.
Wait, it's gone?
It's gone?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's gone.
Ah!
Oh, it's Julia.
Okay.
Hey, Julia.
Why were you so afraid of your own girlfriend, huh?
No, I just wanted you to go first because I'm ladies first,
you know?
Oh, okay, okay.
Gotta wait for her, too.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess I'll do it myself.
Yeah, do it yourself.
What is that?
Why were you screaming at my girlfriend?
I mean, it's Julia.
I thought we wanted to keep Julia alive.
Yeah, but I still don't like her.
Oh, my God.
Okay, we're trapped in there.
Okay, we're trapped in the toxic gas again.
Yeah, great thinking, Alex.
Good job.
Oh, there's a guy in here.
There's a dead body.
Oh, this has to be the radio tower, right?
No, this is.
is the captain's room right oh oh this is the captain's room
there's brad hi brad i'm looking for oh premonition
premonition yeah we need to know the premonition what's
going on with me yeah yeah yeah oh my god oh what is it it
was uh one of the bad guys he just shoots himself easy what
easy peasy we have to convince him to shoot himself then
yeah okay i'm taking in these gases there's a door to our
right yeah there's a door over here bradley are you okay why
are you like i don't think bradley's okay i feel like at any
point i'm gonna walk over and they're gonna be t posing oh
the door doesn't work that door no okay all right we gotta
go through this way then yeah all right here we go oh my god
julia please no but there's gotta be a radio why are you so
chill why are you just like standing there like that i know
chill is that another premonition no it's their route showed
like they went from california oh i went to united states
and then korea if you were headed to san francisco you'd be
crazy to take this route it's almost like they didn't want
anyone to know they were coming this is such a messed up
that is a long route a long why'd they go all the way down
there yeah there's two islands there oh i got a secret we
got a secret bradley blair i found a note Oh, I see you.
I'm watching you pick it up Let's see the United States
Department of the Navy Ship was blown off course cloud cover
was bad They couldn't establish a position Oh, there was a
storm Well, and somebody went overboard Oh, someone failed
their quick time events That could have been you, Mint That
could have been me, but it wasn't Oh, there's a dead guy
here The radio Wait, this is the radio Here I found it It's
there's only one way No freaking I found it This thing
actually still works I found it Alright There goes nothing
Alright Let's see if you know how to do it You found it You
found it Good old shortwave radio What am I listening for?
Oh fuck It's a number station Number station Military
bandwidth Military bandwidth Which one are we trying to
fire?
Yeah, the military.
Military, probably, right?
Yeah.
Beep, beep, beep, beep.
Come in, please.
Do you read us?
Over.
Beep, beep, beep.
Please.
Over.
That guy doesn't, I don't think that guy's real.
Yeah.
At least there's someone listening.
The signal's in and out.
That guy is too panicked.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking, too.
I'm going to say, I'm going to say our coordinates.
If you can hear me, we're on board an abandoned freighter.
it's nine one one say your address first one five one
degrees 20 minutes west over over
is this guy okay panicking yeah right um mayday mayday oh
thank you sir uh we're on a large freighter say the address
why are you yeah over coordinates coordinates coordinates
come in over come in come in please anyone Come in, over.
Oh, you've screwed it up.
Oh, no.
Fliss, you ruined it.
Damn it.
What's this?
No!
Hey, come here, look.
Oh, no.
Brad wants to go down.
Hey, look at this.
Bradley's awfully brave, isn't he?
Just push him in, Fliss.
Push him in.
Push him.
It'll be so funny.
Yeah.
This has got to lead somewhere.
No shit.
Maybe we can't find a way to get the power back.
Anywhere we'll lead somewhere.
working i think someone should wait here in case a message
comes through i'll go obviously i can do this i can let brad
go let brad go come on sounds like you're scared of someone
stepping out of your shadow scared of my idiot brother
getting himself killed we should have left him to die we
should have left him to die oh oh you decide what are you
gonna do i you're okay if you're You're insecure.
Julia, no, she's not my bodyguard.
I can take care of myself.
What?
Why are you going?
Um, listen, Brad again.
Whoa, whoa.
Julia says she can handle it.
Oh, yeah.
She can handle it.
It's you.
Case closed.
Oh, my God.
You gotta let Julia and Brad.
One of us slain Julia and Brad.
Hey, Brad, the other.
Oh, my God.
Don't say, don't say that you're going to do it.
if you're not gonna do it don't don't say it i hope you get
julia and brad i hope you get julia and brad i hope you get
oh i'm julia i'm julia i'm brad oh julia definitely has
tetanus she's all scraped up broken bones oh no everything
still work everyone okay decide our we okay uh uh we're okay
oh god you're the crazier one you're gonna be you're gonna
try and kill me at some point now you'll know how i fell
we're gonna have to find the generator if we can get it
started we can power up the radio okay we'll wait here by
the radio finally somebody's gonna die now someone will die
oh thanks for the tiny lighter to set you on fire oh let's
go i feel like not light put a lighter up hey with toxic gas
i know right like it just doesn't feel like a very good idea
yeah are you okay there you go oh we look like real like
scooby-doo game yeah oh was that the sick bed is that what
that said over there we need a final generator let's go to
the sick don't split up guys it's probably really nasty in
here really gassy in here That's where all the dirtiest of
germs are.
This is where all the gas is.
There's a door here.
Oh.
Inhale the gases, guys.
Sniffer, sniffer.
Yeah.
Yeah, I love going crazy.
Oh.
More hallucinations.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Medical officers report.
Minutes of meaning between scientist X.
CWO.
Walter Bishop and CWO.
Tom Palmer with Sergeant Peter Wood observing and X for
meeting with our team and says we can mutually learn.
Wait, what'd you find?
Oh, my thing talks about Charles and Joe.
It talks about, like, Charles beating up Joe.
Oh, my thing talks about Manchurian.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, this is actually really important.
Okay, the United States has been aware of certain agencies
investigating the chemical and biological agents in warfare.
Our act, limited by the Geneva Protocol, have experiments.
We are unable to describes an investigation during to test
the effects of human subjects on the molecule crystal
structure hallucinogens code names Manchurian gold chemical
munitions battle it was even relatively minor observed to
trigger significant hallucinations men highly convincing
subjects seeing and hearing things that were not really
there even the danger was manifold and and it's in
intensity.
Okay, so it is toxic gas that we're inhaling right now.
What else was over here?
It was nothing.
Lock me in jail, bad boy.
You have a boyfriend.
What the fuck?
I'm unhappy in my relationship.
I can tell.
I can tell you've been actively sabotaging it.
Oh, this is the report.
Oh, this is where I was at.
Yeah, you're right.
It's the Charles and Joe beating up thing.
Yeah, this is the thing I read.
And then there should be blood on the wall here.
I can't believe you tried an NTR with his brother.
That's fucked up.
Yeah, there's the blood that I saw earlier.
Oh my gosh.
Don't worry about it.
Anyway.
Guys, the longer we stay here, the more toxic gas we're
gonna get.
Toxic gas.
I can't wait to see chills, you're in.
I can't wait to see the kids.
How did you...
Oh, that's me.
I'm in the sick bay.
Whoa.
Did you hear that?
Well, that's the body!
That's the dead body I found!
Wait, that's him!
The little kid?
What?
Maybe this was somebody's son from on board?
Two pops.
Come back soon!
No, there's a dead body literally right next to me.
Where?
I'm going to go see it.
Oh.
Uh, I don't see a body.
There's literally no body here.
Wait.
Oh, on the ground!
Yeah, tell me, like, what do you mean?
Oh, Arf.
I'm looking at him.
What is this?
Is this important?
I observed signs of severe distress consistent with evidence
of panic observed in the same soldier during his watch duty.
Oh, it's talking about the hallucination that he's been
getting.
Ooh, Manchurian gold, Manchurian gold, Manchurian gold.
Yeah, this is the body.
Yeah.
Yeah, this dead body.
Yeah, I didn't see him.
I thought he went in the bed.
Because that's where, like, sick bodies normally.
would be yeah he was stuffed in the in this in this closet
locker and i oh yeah yeah that's what i was like yeah like a
hundred years ago oh wait where did you go i'm here oh there
you are i was like oh this way are we splitting up already
yeah we're splitting up like we gotta get that generator oh
come on go oh i'm stuck wait hold on stuck we can go down
let's see what's around oh we can only go down you ladies
first nope you i think bradley's the lady right here okay
here come check this out yeah i found the ladder oh sure
yeah wait what are you looking at is this the generator oh
gotta find the kitchen raggy that sure looks gassy in here
rock roll I think I can just...
Are you okay?
Ooh, dang.
Come down here.
Come down here, Julia.
She won't be able to get back up if you tell her to come
down.
Come down.
Oh, my God.
You have shoes.
I have bare feet.
I'm just a lady.
Please.
Oh, God.
What's up?
It was...
Wait, I didn't see anything.
I just heard it.
Did you see it?
You too.
I just heard it, too.
Wait.
I was not paying attention.
I don't think there was something there.
I'm seeing things, but you're not.
Okay, so follow my thinking here.
Okay.
We know this ship was carrying the Manchurian gold.
Yeah.
But that was really some sort of hallucinogenic bio-weapon
developed in China during World War II.
Right.
And we know that it was super unstable.
Mm-hmm.
And delete all over the ship.
So maybe it's still here?
Maybe it hasn't dispersed after 70 years.
But why am I?
It's having the same effect on us, you know, paranoid
hallucinations.
Yeah.
Oh, my God, Brad, you're so smart.
It's not like we figured that out.
He is the one.
He's the brainy nerd and the officers thought it was just a
bunch of jumpy GIs trying to get out of guard duty This
isn't a ghost ship.
It's a floating bio weapon That's crazy.
We might die because the military wants to keep it a secret.
Yeah.
Oh Maybe there was a connection Maybe they made contact
maybe an only con route survives
Because that's usually how it goes the military wants to
keep it a secret know those coordinates yeah no they'll yeah
they'll be like we'll be like we're saved and then the
military shoots us that's how it always goes yep oh
netherland diesel engine oh rhododendam yeah oh my god this
is not an american ship oh my god american at all it's not
made in america they lied to us how dare they you go the
other way you explore the other way no i'm talking splitting
up yeah why not i can't believe we outsource this ship to
europeans that's why it's cursed that's
i don't think there's anything over here except gas huff it
up huff it up the gas huff up the gas my delusions oh my god
anime girl anime girls are real we're gonna see the children
it's this way there's stuff here okay i'm seeing it anime
girls oh my gosh oh my god remember to hop up the gas oh
what's this wait did we come this way no no we didn't we
came from upstairs and it's working oh you're right yeah
this is it all right just throw the switch and let's get
back upstairs how how yeah how do we go back upstairs okay
let's get back upstairs there's got to be another way up
sure oh yay baby we lost power but we have it back can you
hear me over please say your situation over oh we need help
now there are things on the ship that are trying to hurt us
over oh oh again come on work dammit okay well okay well we
We have people coming to shoot us.
Yeah, we have people coming to shoot you.
Oh my god.
We did it.
Wait, there's a way over here, but there was also a other
area all the way on the other side.
Oh, gas.
Sweet, sweet gas, sweet, sweet gas.
My wife will.
She will be mine.
My god, this is how your wife was become 3D.
No, 3D, PD.
Oh, there's a dead guy here.
Wait, where are you?
I'm looking at a dead guy.
Whoa!
Where did you go?
He is not looking so hot.
Where the fuck did you go?
Did you go this way?
Oh, we definitely split up.
I split up, Doki.
Chloe.
Oh, wait, what?
What the hell?
I brought you back.
The fisherman must have bothered over from the Duke of
Milan.
You think it still works?
Looks like it's got a little juice left.
Maybe a couple of minutes.
Should we bring it with us?
I mean, it's heavy.
Yeah, take it.
Still, you should.
Might as well.
Yeah, why not?
Hell yeah, we should.
Half the boat is submerged.
Yeah.
The crows.
Uh-oh.
Oh, no.
Just when we need to run.
Wait, we can hit him over the head with it.
You're right.
This is where he's gonna shoot himself?
Wait, what the fuck?
Oh.
Oh, he's totally lost it.
He's totally lost it.
He's crazy.
Oh, you see it?
Wow, imagine the smell in there.
What is he doing?
That's the guy...
There's the...
Oh, there's the thing!
The after the boat!
What is he trying to do?
Is he gonna cut him?
He's opening... he's gonna open him up to see his secrets.
there's gold inside him there's gold inside open me up
there's gold inside oh he's hallucinating he's hallucinating
again you could totally like scare him just be like i see
you oh my god okay Don't you dare, don't you dare fuck this
up.
Don't you dare.
Okay.
We die, you messed us up.
There's a lot of pressure here, Doki.
There's a lot of pressure.
At least you focus more.
There you go.
See it, Doki.
There's a lot of pressure.
You failed?
No, I didn't.
I didn't fail.
It sounds like you failed.
Avoid Olsen.
Uh-oh.
What are we supposed to do?
it i don't know i have time to read notes right okay wait
what oh my god there's mucho texto oh wait what uh human
bodies that have undergone mistreatments i don't think we
have time to read okay i'm coming what's going on oh oh oh
what's going on oh oh god oh god hide hide oh
He's holding something.
I'm just gonna check it real quick.
There's something there!
I swear to God.
I was just curious.
Now we're gonna die.
No!
There's no use hiding.
No.
This guy can only, he's, you know, he can only hallucinate
and...
There must be plenty of that to go around, more than enough.
He'll hallucinate us, killing us, it's fine.
Where were we gonna go anyway?
Oh!
Oh, no again.
Oh, God, oh, God.
Please.
And I'm to be left here to die.
But I am...
I told you it's so much pressure.
I knew I should have given you the pressure.
If I can't give you pressure, then okay.
It's fine.
We'll just kill him.
I jumped.
I told him I stopped giving you pressure.
See, it's fine.
I mean, these drawings are better.
We'll stand up, sir.
Oh.
Keep going!
Just keep...
I will see.
Bradley, please.
The doors are rusted.
Come on, we gotta keep going.
This is where he tries to shoot.
We have to convince him to shoot himself.
Yeah, this is the guy that I saw shoot himself.
Turn around.
Then we'll get a gun.
It'll be fine.
Yeah, real slow.
Okay.
all right oh oh why is he here none of that no change no
yeah why is he here why how do you get here how do you get
here what do you mean i said no changing what oh uh mint i
swear to god i'm gonna i'm nice we've got no problem with
you we just want to get out of here please I'm sorry, but if
you're breathing, then you don't get much of a choice in the
matter.
You don't got to say.
What?
What do you mean?
Oh, he's seeing him.
He's seeing him.
Not again.
It's all gone changing on me.
Oh, the gas.
What's changing?
The gas.
Stay away.
Stay back from the mist.
Wait, what's happening?
Oh, there's a man!
Oh, there's a man.
Don't breathe the mist.
The man, I'm a man.
Oh, my God, saw him too.
Don't breathe the mist.
Oh, the mist, the mist.
Oh, I'm gonna say nothing.
Really?
I'm gonna say nothing.
You coward, you coward!
Inside with us, now.
Please just calm down.
Why did you say something?
I didn't make the decision!
It's in one of us, isn't it?
We have to convince this on him.
It's in him.
I'm gonna say it's in him.
Oh, yeah, I'll say I haven't breathed.
I haven't breathed any weird mist.
Please, I promise.
My deceitful went up.
Oh, you burnt in the mist.
I'm gonna say no.
happening you breathe yeah bradley you breathe it you
breathe in the no he's gonna shoot brad shoot brad shoot
brad there is no there was something back oh where did i do
this there's no mist ah there was something back there okay
all right look oh he's gonna shoot brad oh you just killed
you just said see all right we want it did you breathe it in
no say no We held our breath.
No, look.
We held our breath.
We did not breathe any of that stuff I fucked up I think
you've got brand is too much.
I fucked up For hours You've been holding your breath this
whole time.
It's true.
You're holding your breath right now.
Oh Oh, oh Uh-oh, it's in me.
Oh, we did it.
Wait, you did it.
We did it.
It's in me, isn't it?
We did it!
How do...
I can't feel it slowly.
He's gonna shoot...
What if he shoots us first?
It's gently...
Okay.
Come on, man.
Oh, come on.
Shoot yourself.
The mist.
Persona!
What the hell we did?
Grab persona distract!
Wait, what are you doing?
What do we do?
You decide!
Stop!
Stop lying!
You can all see it in me, can't you?
I didn't say anything.
Why are you making him stall?
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, they think we're alive.
Dude, just can't stop monologuing.
Oh, there it is.
Oh, maybe, maybe.
Persona?
Hey, man.
Come on.
Just put the...
Oh!
We did it.
Let's go.
We killed another man.
Murders.
The options.
Yay!
wait why don't you keep the gun is it empty someone's like
you could have saved him wait we're supposed to save him oh
oh um no it wasn't a premonition it was our premonition i
thought we were supposed to kill him we were that was our
mission oh i'm fliss oh it's 4 44 a.m how spooky oh my god
so spooky Yeah, they took us hostage.
Why are we supposed to save?
He's the bad guy.
Doesn't sound like my problem.
There might be some more gear down there we can use.
Murderers of my dad.
We were the murderers all along.
Oh, my God.
Oh, they're going down.
Okay.
Oh, why are we saving the kittens?
happens oh my god i swear i don't think i'm no i'm fliss i'm
fliss okay i think it's all i'm doing this dead yeah are you
doing it right now yes i am mess up hey i had a good track
record with this it's on you how do you mess this up it's
too much pressure
I don't understand how that works with you When I stress you
out You do if you actually Oh my god There's a man down
there The man of a man The murderer is a patat The murderer
is a patat Come on let's go Why can't I walk fast Come on
move Liz Move you I'm trying she's so slow Every time I pass
it and failed it.
Even though you don't have to do it.
Even the king says he failed it.
What if it calls me?
Oh, oh, you disappeared.
Where did you go?
I'm heading over.
I'm slowly heading over here.
Oh my God.
Oh.
Oh, no, what's that?
Oh, he's coming over.
Does it matter?
We need that distributor cap.
Stop talking.
Here.
he's so loud alex i know he's like hey it's over here hey
it's here this is not the way that we win where how how are
they gonna find us oh was that your hand i don't know i sure
hope so i hope so too i hope so too oh oh wait i don't think
we can go How's there still more?
Wait, who's that?
Oh, he is.
It's just...
Oh, he's just...
I think we can make it across.
What?
Jump.
Are we actually going to do it?
Here we go.
This is a lot deeper than I expected.
Yeah, it's pretty...
It's fine.
Get ready for the quick time.
Oh.
What's the first one?
Ben, please.
Oh wait, I don't think I had to do it.
The gases.
Oh no, the gases.
The gases are like really bad here.
He dropped the hammer.
Wait, what is...
Oh, what is it zooming on?
The hammer?
The hammer.
We'll get it.
We'll grab that.
I swear, do not use the hammer against me.
Oh, is he getting a heart attack?
Oh, he's going to get scared to death.
Yeah.
He's getting scared to death now.
do this i think we have to do this fast oh we're gonna get
hard yeah this is the moment alex are you kidding me oh my
god i have to make sure i don't get a heart attack i
chickened out let's go are you fucking all right i gotta
make sure i don't get a heart attack i'm outside breathing
that fresh air i can't believe it is this actual bullshit
i'm fast as i can i'm going to i'm pressing lb lb is this it
here oh i can't see anything oh my god oh my god i'm going
to the door it's fine wait what's who's that what's that
down there hold on i'm coming hold on i think those are
bodies wait that's a guy right there oh of course but they
will shrink your movement military has indicated that and
five is platoons have gone missing what i'm coming i'm
coming hold on are there any notes Oh, there's a lot of
stuff in here.
There's a lot of stuff in here.
Hold on.
I'm trying to figure it out where he is.
He's dead.
It's fine.
Diplomat immunity.
Oh no.
The rats.
Water purification.
Ooh.
There's rats eating the dead body.
Already.
Why do you get to go outside?
I'm reading.
I'm exploring.
It's kind of nice.
Oh my gosh.
I saw a dead body.
He was just chilling, though.
Manifest of personal effects.
Oh, no.
The dog died.
Oh, these are the guys that died.
Oh, no.
Oops.
Hmm.
Get off.
Are you getting them off?
Get off, Rat.
I'm fine.
Hold on.
There's, like, three notes in here.
Give me a second.
Get off!
Oh, what did I just hear?
Oh, my God.
Uh-oh.
I didn't get to read it!
uh-oh what's going on was that a rat oh uh-oh why do i have
to deal with all of this there's rats here wait i just heard
something oh my god there's so many rats i'm freaking out
i'm freaking out over the rats oh i see you freaking out
over the rats chill out i what the hell what is going on
what's going on.
What?
Um, decide well, I guess.
Who are you?
That's me, that's me, Don't do anything, that's me!
Yeah, it's me, idiot!
It's me!
Is that you?
That's me!
Don't do anything!
It's me!
Uh-oh.
I think Bliss might die.
You are the one who's gonna kill Game is bugging out man.
Why are you dying?
What's going on?
What is there are no rats?
The rats don't kill me.
Don't kill me.
Don't you dare Don't you dare Millie.
I'm gonna get come on Alex.
I'm gonna put you out of your misery Alex I'm gonna put you
out of your misery.
I'm gonna put you out of your misery.
Don't do anything to me!
Stop!
There were no rats the whole time!
Oh my god, the game is bugging out real.
It's always you that's about to kill me.
I know you were the one holding the knife.
What are you talking?
You were a monster on my screen.
You were a monster What are you talking about?
You had two heads Well, you looked like you were getting
eaten by rats, but you weren't actually oh what the hell?
Oh my god Where the fuck did he come from?
Why are you there?
Wait Brad?
No way.
Did we survive everybody?
Did we save everybody?
Did we do...
Oh my god, did we...
No way.
Oh my god, we're back on the boat.
We saved everybody.
Oh my god.
Let's try it.
Even Conrad.
That's such a crazy.
Holy shit.
Are we just gonna forget that everything happened?
leave this ship and just forget anything ever happened yeah
what about conrad like i thought conrad was gonna come back
for us i know i thought so too that fucking bastard he just
dipped oh my god no way that actually worked oh there he is
no way there he is there's conrad
no way he came back wait he came back he has a gun no way
he's gonna get on the ship don't I think we killed Conrad!
No, they're gonna kill Conrad at the end!
Oh shit, oh shit, oh shit!
Oh!
What the hell is this place?
Oh, it's inviting him in.
Oh, oh, there he goes, there he goes.
Oh no, there he goes in.
Oh my god, Conrad!
You're gonna die, you're gonna die, Conrad!
Conrad, no!
Is it abandoned?
Do we get a choice?
whoa no just let him die no way we saved him just for him to
go back to the ship he has his airpods on where is the coast
guard he just got up yeah let him get in here oh my god the
sequel is a man of caution i just want to show off my
brother he was trying to help us to get help but He doesn't
know anything about boats or sailing.
Oh, it's like the Aton until Dawn ending.
Or they do the interviews and stuff.
Oh.
It's just her being sad about Conrad.
That's it.
Conrad.
No, he's dead or not.
He's just chilling.
No way.
That's the ending.
no fucking way we're like where's conrad technically we
saved everybody no way that's the ending oh my god oh my god
what's he gonna say he's just gonna stare at us come on say
congratulations all your charges are still breathing and
that's something that's that's really impressive for us i
think yeah well that really is things became a little
intense but alex I can't believe it.
We were not trying to save people.
It's all about decisions, isn't it?
Decisions made in a hurry, in a panic, made with the heart
instead of the head, or vice versa.
Sometimes those decisions take a long time to have
repercussions.
But there are repercussions.
There are always repercussions.
Yeah, Conrad's dead now.
We don't know that.
there's no proof i think i think so i think he's dead the
boat literally ending the boat literally invited him in
again maybe in little hope maybe somewhere else oh but be
certain we will meet again oh inevitable uh apparently
there's a dlc i don't know if that guy was goes baiting us
what the i'm skipping i'm skipping i'm skipping yeah skip to
the end
there's dlc for real is there really a dlc oh that was a
joke okay oh are they vibrating what's going on oh you're
getting a heart attack whoa they're vibrating they're
vibrating whoa what's going on because of the beer isn't the
beer the decompression the decompression i swear to god you
killed her because of the oh my god it's the beer she's
shaking a lot shit shit this is decompression sickness we
came up too fast oh my god come on come on come on d why are
they vibrating so much Oh my god!
Yeah!
We almost saved everybody!
He said congratulations!
We went through the credits!
Oh my god!
I gave it!
Doki, it was beer o'clock, please!
I'm fucking...
I'm fucking beer o'clock!
We almost had a perfect run!
fucking thing i'm like fear i can't have this
oh my god fucking thing you have to understand
yeah it was after the credit so it doesn't count you know it
doesn't count guys it doesn't count guys it doesn't count
count what happens after the credits is not our fault oh my
god i can't believe oh my god she died for pyrro cloth under
everything we've been through like a pyrro cloth goddess oh
my god holy you know i'm surprised like everybody lived i
was surprised too oh my god that's right we're special no
other vtuber plays the game like us we we stumbled our way
into victory you can guarantee an original experience here
on our channels
I can't believe the whole clock.
You fucking kidding me.
Why did the decompression take so long?
He said it was like a couple hours or maybe a couple
minutes.
Who knows?
That was good.
Did he die?
How did she die?
That was good.
Did you like the game?
That was fun.
was really we should do the sequel to this next time is the
sequel the same where we have to play two different
characters i think so yeah like yeah i heard little hopes
not as good though but i think all of these are all kind of
like kusso gay a little bit yeah it's not the it's not the
game you guys it's who plays the game yeah it's who plays
the game guys oh my god as you say nobody died credits is
not like our fault yes yes anything that happens is not our
fault yeah it might not be bero clock it could have been
something she felt no one important died i mean that's true
that's true like we probably saved alex you know is conrad
alive i don't know yeah conrad's alive guys conrad's alive
like how someone was like you were supposed to save that one
kidnapper But like, he kidnapped us.
He kidnapped us.
It's called.
He's a pirate.
Yeah, self-defense.
Yeah, it was either us or him.
I think someone was like, it's a hallucination.
She's allowed.
She's still on the trip or the ship.
She's like, Conrad, I waited for you.
So it was like time of death, Bureau Claw.
I didn't think that that would be.
You didn't think actions had consequences?
No.
After the doctor boyfriend was like, maybe you shouldn't
drink the beer.
People are saying don't do little hope that it's actually
bad.
Oh, is it actually bad?
Wait, how many games are in the anthology?
There's House of Ashes apparently.
It's House of Ashes good?
Conrad survived up to the credits, therefore it doesn't
matter.
So true!
so true i went very hard on those quick time events
house of ashes is good oh okay okay we'll do house of ashes
next yeah i mean that was really fun that was are we say how
bad are we saying though like what in what way is it bad
because like i mean like i don't mind bad if it's funny
story bad or is it like the is it like buggy bad yeah like
if it's buggy bad and then maybe not but if it's story bad
we can make it work i thought this one was great it was like
the perfect this one was good yeah this one was pretty good
the story is terrible oh okay that's perfect for us yeah
pretty much yeah it's like fucking i was trying to be a
mercer and then min here was reading a diary in a british
accent we watch somebody like get killed it's like dear die
dear die right in my end i was like ah
you know whatever yeah we'll fix it we can fix the story um
yeah don't worry and if the story is boring we'll just make
a podcast again guys it's not who it's not the game it's who
plays the game Yeah, it's who plays it exactly That a great
time We gotta continue the The trilogy Yeah, we got The
anthology It was like the dark picture Yeah, we have to
continue the dark pictures anthology Oh god Okay, well thank
you Yeah, thanks man I can't believe everybody lived Other
than like beer clock I can't believe it It just happened in
such a terrible stupid way Like I thought maybe she would
die on the ship and be like oh my god it's kicking in and
whatever compression yeah but no she's that one position you
make she just collapses on the boat she died of cringe
oh man oh my god it just came out of nowhere too we were
just like yay we did it also we weren't intentionally trying
to save them we were just it just we just stumbled upon it
We just like tripped and fell into saving everybody somehow.
Yeah, somehow.
I mean, we did all the QTE.
Well, I failed the one QTE, the heartbeat one.
We still lived.
One.
The one important one.
The one at the end.
Okay.
I see we're rewriting here.
history right now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so what?
I see you're not even paying attention to beer o'clock.
I wouldn't beer o'clock wouldn't have happened if, I don't
know, you exploded the, the grill.
So I really don't do it.
You not drink the beer.
It was, it was beer o'clock.
That's a bad idea.
It was fine.
We didn't care about Julia anyway.
Yeah, that's true.
She was kind of stupid.
Yeah, she was pretty much a Karen, to be fair.
She was.
Yeah.
So it's like, you know, nothing, you know, he told Alex
could have got, Alex could have got so much better, you
know.
Yeah.
He saved him from a marriage.
Now Alex is gonna fall in love with Flix.
Or Flix.
Yeah.
Flix.
Flix, yeah.
They have to fix their relationship.
This is so much better.
Yeah, Fliss almost got together with Conrad.
Oh, my God.
They were making out.
Yeah, yeah.
And then we saved them.
We got Fliss for Alex now.
He's a strong woman.
Conrad just literally, like, front of the boat, like, barges
into the ship.
Yeah, where was the Coast Guard?
Like, he just went there by himself.
I don't know.
He was clearly not driving the boat.
No, yeah.
So it makes those...
Why was he the only one there?
Yeah, I was like, we didn't...
Where did the coast guard go?
Also, how did he get the coordinates?
Yeah!
How did he get the coordinates?
Well, we gave the coordinates over the radio, but how did he
know to go with, like, what?
Yeah, but then, like, the thing is, they were on the
military boat.
Yeah, exactly.
Everybody else was also on the military boat.
Yeah.
So, like, I'm so confused.
Why was there nobody behind him?
oh my god that i'm it's all right everybody lived everything
that happens after your credits was a hallucination someone
said if you don't get the distributor cap you get rescued by
the coast guard oh so you picked up the the cap you told us
that you told me to pick up the cap
okay but like if we if we picked up the cap then like then
like Conrad.
Would Conrad be on the boat?
Yeah.
Conrad be on the boat.
He'd be on the boat and then be like, oh my God, we're
rescuing you guys.
Okay.
I think you're getting gaslit.
I think we're supposed to get.
I think we're supposed to pick it up.
Um, I don't know.
I'm pretty sure.
No, because we called the Coast Guard.
They were coming.
They were on their way.
This cannot be on me.
I am not.
Wait, so, so, like, if we didn't pick up the distributor
cap, we would have seen Conrad on the boat, and I would be
like, Conrad!
I think so.
Yeah, they were on their way.
Someone said not picking up gives you the better ending.
How do I not pick it up?
Do I just, like, not do it?
Like, how do I just say, how do I not pick up the cap?
Oh, they would have ran into each other.
Guys, I gave you guys a different, I gave you guys a cooler
ending, okay?
I think actually the ending we got was so crazy.
Yeah, the ending we got was so much better.
It was actually so much better.
Like, do you guys really want to get rescued by Conrad?
Come on.
Someone was like, you got the better ending.
Now the world is protected from Conrad's frizz.
We took out both of the siblings.
It's fine.
Yeah, we got a two-for-one special.
great anyway thank you doki this was a good time that was a
good time ggs we'll come back for the next was it little
hope or whatever one we decide to play i guess so yeah yeah
we'll come back to that ggs all right we're gonna talk to
our chats now all right see you mid bye bye
huh give me one second you guys give me one second
I'm sending you over.
We're going to the merry cafe.
Yay.
Let me put on some BGM.
Oh my gosh, I'm so tired.
brain once again is just melted from from this uh what's
this
there we go ah i hope you guys liked it i hope you guys had
fun and uh and stuff that was an experience
the five gifts i thank you guys so much thank you for all
the super chats and all the uh and all the um don't knows
and everything i've been i've been looking at them so sad
julia died of natural cause thanks for the pink watching you
two together is my beer o'clock oh my god no don't die yeah
that was fun anthology is so goofy i know i kind of love
them I love them so much.
I think that one's my favorite just because it's like it's
like my it's it's it's I like that it's kind of based I well
I guess it's little hope also based on of true thing I don't
know but I like that man of madame is actually based on the
true thing it makes it a little bit more interesting for me
peak comedy mint doki kusuke is a winning formula oh that
was my that was my controller winning combo glad i caught
this thank you you guys trolled the narrator guys so hard
spoiled by beer o'clock gosh that was so funny i can't
believe of all things she just ends up dying oh we conrad's
never hear our name said in media so this stream was an
absolute treat hearing y'all say hi conrad conrad's gonna
die for your beer o'clock ones oh thank you great collab
thank you that was one of the most hilarious brain rotting
collabs of all time i'm glad that we were able to get
through the whole thing i was wondering if uh because i
wasn't sure how long the game was so um but glad it glad it
ended up working out and that we were able to just complete
it i think it's longer if you do it by yourself because
obviously you're going to be going back and forth between
people more but yeah it's a good length i think so too i
think so too that was so fun longer if you're solo and
thorough ah yeah yeah yeah also was like kind of skimming
the notes so you don't oh i've been craving for someone new
to play this and you guys were so fun thank you yeah it's
like you don't really see it very often played i mean it is
kind of kusuke but it's so fun right silly collab.
Also, my postcard came in today.
It looked like it was in condition.
Yippee!
I already ordered the new postcard, so, uh, you'll have two
of them.
I can't believe we didn't get the death POV.
We did!
Kind of.
I don't know what's up with me and the heartbeat ones,
though.
They really stressed me out.
But, um, you know.
Hmm.
Whatever.
It's fine.
Everybody lived.
Pre-credits.
Both of you are so cute and silly.
Ah, man.
It's getting late, so I'm going to head out now.
I hope you guys had fun.
I hope you guys have a great night or a great day or
whatever.
And thanks again for watching.
Thanks again for hanging out.
It's been so long since you've had a beating heart.
It freaked you out, I guess.
True.
What's the stream tomorrow?
I can tell you it will start at the same time as today I
actually have no idea because I've been so busy getting
ready for anime expo and stuff oh my gosh when I tell you so
yesterday was yeah yesterday was Sunday yesterday Matara and
I recorded um recorded Siege thanks to the vibe gifted the
collabs between mint and doki are some of the best collabs
of all time thank you i'm glad to think so um uh she and i
she and i recorded sunday we recorded two things on sunday
and then we recorded two things today for the podcast so i'm
just like i have not had a chance to even think about
anything so um uh like we recorded yesterday's or today's
podcast we did it all yesterday basically and saturday night
no we did saturday night then yesterday after i did two
streams and then we and then we did two more today my brain
is a little bush so it might be pretty chill tomorrow maybe
like blues if you'll allow me and um then wednesday will be
metal gear and thursday is is anime expo so any of those
games i did actually actually so it's really funny because i
had them all in my car i should have probably just wishlist
them but they were all in my car and then i had to buy manna
madan so i was just like oh i'm not gonna remove all of them
just to buy buy one thank you thank you tribe princess um so
uh i just bought them all i got balloons from the same sale
yeah it's on like super sale and it's so fun when you
brought up mata stream from friday i knew y'all have had
recorded it like yesterday yeah it was like really really
because um she uh she wasn't she hasn't been feeling well so
it's been kind of hard to get our oh i have to change my
change the thing on the menu to today's episode wait i think
i have it hold on but um it's been kind of hard with our
schedules lately i'll be honest so um but you know i think
that's like the hardest thing about kind of doing the
podcast so far has been just kind of being oh i could i
don't think i have it saved never mind is having our
schedules align so she says she's getting better yeah a
little bit or she still has a cough sometimes but rinsky
thanks for the five get the thank you thank you thank you um
also grant i see your don't know have you seen deadly
premonition it's 124 on steam i did get it actually you need
a lot of fan patching i got it because i want to play deadly
premonition but i know that the steam one is not very good
but i got it because i mean it was a doll and i like having
options if you know the switch version doesn't work out so
mini scooter i saw you thank you thank you thank you so much
my birthday is coming up on the third but i won't be able to
be here since i leave for ax tomorrow oh no could i get a
quick happy birthday also i'm excited to see you this friday
you're gonna be there thank you oh my gosh friday oh i have
to practice my songs Happy birthday to you Happy birthday to
you Happy birthday dear weeaboo danger Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday Yeah, what was I gonna say?
Yeah, I have to practice my songs for Friday Oh my gosh, I'm
so nervous Ah, I'm so nervous.
Alien isolation is also $10.
Ooh, thank you for letting me know.
I'll go add it.
How much is it usually?
Alien, I...
That game stresses me out, though.
That game stresses me out.
Wait, there's a seat...
Why is there a season pass?
What's the season pass for?
beer o'clock hey dokey
oh if anyone invites you to explore a giant abandoned ship
just frit frit frit frit jate what's that mean anyway okay
I'm gonna go because I got stuff to do so and I gotta rest
thank you guys so much I hope you guys had fun thank you as
always for Hanging out.
And I will see you guys tomorrow for Probably Blues.
Probably Blues.
I managed to get my hands on the MGS vinyl collection.
I'm so hyped.
Yes, me too.
Except it doesn't come out until October.
I'm so sad.
Only caught the last half, so I'll have to watch the vibe.
You should give Still Wakes the Deep a try for a whore.
Still Wakes the Deep.
Thank you for letting me know.
No.
Oh, wait a second.
Oh, actually, this is on my wish list.
This is what, oh, this is what Matara and I talked about in
the podcast.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Have a good rest.
Thank you for the stream.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
14 endings?
Wait, what has 14 endings?
There's 14 endings for, for Manimodan?
No way.
Um, good luck, everybody.
Holy shit!
Why are there so many endings?
Oh my god.
I mean, I guess there has to be an ending for like each
person dying and each person surviving.
I'm looking at the video and it's one hour long of it.
What the hell?
Yeah, because of who lives and dies and if you call the
radio or the boat.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh my god, I guess it's time to watch them all.
I want to see how people die Okay, okay, I'm heading out.
What joy?
Thank you for the good thing I've done.
Thank you.
Thank you
There it is.
Thanks Grant Okay, thank you guys See you later.
See you tomorrow and Yeah, I'll probably just play balloons.
Okay Bye, have a good night!
Have a good night!
Bye bye!