Oh no!
I forgot tea!
I forgot to get a drink!
Oh well.
Spend a couple days.
Did you miss me?
You have customers.
They're doing their own thing.
They told me I walked over there and I was just like, would
you like me to serve you?
And they said, actually, please don't come over here.
Don't even look at us.
Don't even bother us.
So don't worry about it.
I think they're...
I think they're up to no good.
Amen.
Yes, I miss you.
Yippee!
Sorry, we're booked for a private event.
Yeah, exactly.
Thank you!
Oh wait, hold on.
Oh!
Welcome back, boss.
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
I went away.
Actually, if you listen to the...
If you listen...
Well, maybe for some people, you already know.
I talked about it in the podcast a little bit.
I went to...
Did you miss us?
Yeah.
Is that Jerma in your cafe?
Is that what Jerma looks like?
I don't think Jerma has glasses.
That's German.
Oh.
I talked about it a little bit on the podcast if you
listened.
If you listened today, thank you for listening.
If you haven't listened to it yet, thank you for listening
to it in the future.
And if you are haven't listened to it, why not?
Thank you.
And the waitress is too shy and introverted to call out the
customers bringing outside food into the cafe.
Wait, you're not allowed to do.
Bring it.
outside food thank you for the akasupa inspired me to go to
a con recently it's a lot of fun and even though i didn't
cosplay i felt like a fish out of water i still have fun
recognizing and taking pictures with several cosplayers now
planning what i want to cosplay is next time i go let's go
wait where'd you go where'd you go andre goes thanks for the
10 gifted and blind boy welcome
I was at the dentist during the podcast.
That's why.
You should have listened to it with your dentist.
They would have been like, oh my god, they would have had a
hold on your teeth.
They would have grabbed it.
They would have gripped it.
They would have firmly grasped it.
They would have been like listening to it and just gripping
your teeth in anticipation of what we were talking about.
The dentist would have said, based?
Based?
maybe I don't know but yeah I've talked about it I've said
this like three times now I've talked about it a little bit
on the podcast and I went to a convention I went to Anime
Central and I made a surprise appearance at Ayami Sensei's
panel it was so last minute oh my gosh it was extremely last
minute surprise question mark question mark okay it was a
surprise because there's there there was no plan for me to
be in that panel until maybe like 10 minutes before the
panel and then ayami sensei called to me she was like mito
chan join my panel and i was like is it okay because it's
your panel like you're the guest I felt really bad I was
like you're the guest people are coming to see you not me
and so that's how the last minute it was extremely last
minute what was the panel about she tried snacks American
snacks so some of them I gave to her and some of them were
given by fans so So I saw Someone say that they didn't get
the Meet and Greet tickets for Ofkai I'm sorry I think I've
seen several people saying that I've seen very Few people
saying that they've gotten tickets And more people saying
that they didn't get tickets Welcome back we might have
missed you or something Thank you Sold out already No no
they weren't They weren't sold they were a they were a
lottery and um actually it's funny because when I when I
mentioned to Sensei, the Ayami Sensei that her meet and
greet her sign, her sign autograph session at Anime Central
also sold out which I didn't get I don't I say sold out but
they were free I'm pretty sure but um when uh when i told
when i showed her that i was like oh they're completely full
and she was like yeah you're awesome thank you can't stick
around so i'll i'll catch the bond have a good night um also
core core oil fitness bugs is like a bug don't know what no
Thanks, Yoko.
They were free.
They were free, right?
Most of her merch sold out.
I know, I know, I know.
But when I showed her that, she was just like, actually, so
many of my fans said that they didn't make it into the
autograph session.
So who made it?
And now I'm thinking that.
I'm like, wait, so many people.
are saying that they didn't make it in to my meet and greet
so
who's showing up
who's who's gonna be there poor boyfriends I know really
happy she did so well me too it seems like she had a lot of
fun she kept thanking me a lot which I was like you know I
just did your panel I really didn't do anything but she she
was saying that lurkers probably maybe who knows who knows
but um hopefully uh even if not at the official meet and
greet maybe we can find another way to um to meet somehow
during the convention if you will be at afkai and if you
won't be at afkai maybe you be at another event that you
will be going to so yeah yeah so we've got lots of fans mint
i don't know i don't know i'm in north i'll be in the
parking lot let's go yeah i'll be in the parking lot at adam
at adam in north i'm gonna be in a parking lot.
I will be singing in a parking lot.
Choo!
Glad you had fun with Ayami Sensei this weekend.
Also, congrats on your upcoming concert appearance.
I can't go, but I'll be cheering you on in spirit.
Thank you!
Yes!
And that was announced, too!
I will be appearing at a concert.
Well-liked, popular person.
Heard there was a YouTuber who had their me-and-greet
tickets sold out, but only recognized one from their chat.
So hopefully you have better luck.
Oh Wait, you said oh sorry.
Hold on Heard that there was a VTuber who had a meet and
greet ticket sold out, but I only recognized one person from
the chat What that's crazy?
I don't know I even though, you know, it is still also
exciting to meet new people So I hope there's no one
listening who's just like I'm a lurker and and I got I got a
meet and greet excited to uh to meet me no no i am still
very excited so what is otakon doing there behind you
they're having a barbecue they're having a barbecue don't
worry about it don't worry about it hold on i'm gonna eat
some more of my cereal
i got Reese's puffs i hope it doesn't hurt my stomach It
should be okay.
Minto hates me.
No!
Peanut butter chocolate flavor!
Welcome to membership, thank you.
I'm gonna mute.
I'm embarrassed.
Casual lurker, but sad I couldn't see you at Ascent.
Maybe next con, but yeah.
Mmm.
Yeah.
Sorry if you couldn't make it to the IME panel.
Like I said, it really was like so last minute so even if
it's just like announced it beforehand there was no time
beforehand for you for maybe some people to go so sorry but
hopefully I can go to another con as an official guest How
did the drawing go?
Did you guys...
Hold on.
Let me get the picture.
From...
From Sensei's...
From Sensei's, uh...
Twitter?
Oh good, she's not Shadow Band anymore.
At least for a while, I couldn't search her.
Save image.
This is how the drawing came out.
LeBron James, scream if you love Mipin.
Ta-da!
Isn't it so cute?
She made me look so shy and cute.
Then people were telling me at the end of the panel that,
um, A strange shadow happened.
I don't know.
Like that was...
But when we talked, she said she was going to give me a hug
out.
What happened?
Did she get shy?
Maybe.
Maybe she got shy.
And made me as shy as she felt.
You know, who knows.
The shadow had sussy intentions.
Was it?
Was it...
A pickle shake?
What did it, what kind of shadow was it?
When people were saying that there was a sussy shadow, I was
like...
What do you mean by that?
Wow!
Thank you for that!
I'm glad you had fun at Ace and hope I'll be lucky enough to
see you out of Kai soon.
You're so fun to see.
Even if I can't be here all the time, have a good rest of
your stream.
Thank you, Luna!
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you!
Thank you so much!
Haunted pickle?
Was it hedgehog shaped?
What kind of shadow, if there's anybody who...
went to the anybody who went to the panel
I assume she was like looming over you what do you mean
looming over me
the hedgehog no not the hedgehog I was like why are you guys
bearing of a hedgehog where's your listening comprehension
because I said shadow like the hedgehog no there was I'm
not...
Oh my gosh, thank you for the...
Stop, please, thank you!
I could have been there, but I got a puppy this month.
That's exciting, too, though, right?
Oh my gosh.
Does it pee and poo everywhere?
I love Latina Sonic.
Shadow, like the headdrawn.
Yeah, I get it now.
don't go welcome to membership thank you um
oh it was sensei's shadow while you were saying no etchi
don't lude wait really wait actually
is that her impression of me I feel like
I need to get this framed and put on my wall.
No, Echie don't loot.
That doesn't sound like you.
Well, I mean, for me, I mean, I'm still embarrassed by it.
But I don't dislike Echie and loot things.
knows that by now what was it oh oh i i was i was oh there
was a there was a booth at at anime central that was selling
um that was selling actually there were several booths
selling dojins i was so shocked how many there were and um
one of them was just like i'm haunted i'm hunted by
something and i i at the time i was just like oh i'll come
back for it because because um uh because i didn't have a
bag that could fit it that like i didn't want to carry it
around um i wasn't going back to my hotel room to put it
away anytime soon and so i um i I went back the next day and
it was gone.
I was so surprised.
I was like, are ghosts in demand?
Maybe.
I think I know which one you're talking about.
Yeah, it's sold out.
Are ghosts in demand?
Yes, they are.
They saw you eyeing it?
No!
No, no, no.
They couldn't have.
I'm a ghost.
They couldn't have seen me.
Mm-mm.
But I did, like, kind of haunt the booth a little bit.
I was like, oh, man.
Let's see.
What else is stuff that I bought?
I bought a blanket that also had ghosts on it.
It was so cute.
I saw it.
And I was like staring at it.
I was like, I say it's a blanket, but it's like, it's very,
um, let me see if I can find the artist's name.
Because it's so, it's, it kind of reminds me of like, it's
like, when I looked at it, I just felt this overwhelming
sense of like, halloween and fall.
And it just made me so happy.
And so I didn't even think I just, I just bought it.
I was like looking at it, I was like, I think I need this.
Um, where's the artist's name?
Um, oh, the artist's name is Julia Likes Cats.
What a good name.
And it's like a, it's like a, let me see.
Actually, you know what, maybe I can find it.
Julia Likes Cats.
Blanket.
I think they called it a woven tapestry.
but oh let me type tap tapestry oh this is it this is it I
found it I found it I found it hold on it's loading no
Instagram please uh oh no I don't have Instagram no oh oh oh
oh no I can't look at the picture unless I have Instagram uh
oh Okay, it's gonna be like the worst, most blurry picture
ever, but this is what it looks like.
Oh my god, it's even worse than I thought.
Look how cute this is.
I just saw it and I was like, this is so...
It's just so nice.
It's so like fall and everything.
Isn't it cool?
It's not a bad photo.
It's kind of bad.
It's a little bad.
Yeah, it's so cute So
Post stamp size Yeah, I saw, I got that I got some Dojinchi
I was like Looking through some old Dojinchi Some places had
like newer ones I got one from Kawari Because I really like
that artist and I got of course I got Ayami Dojin-si the
newer ones that I hadn't gotten yet Ayami-sensei and I oh I
was looking through some older ones and I found like an old
catalog of like from melon books that had like a bunch of
like they have like paceri in there but I barely even
recognize it as paceri art it's like I was like Wow, this is
like a real time capsule.
And I also had an older Dojinchi of another artist I like,
Kujo Ichiso.
So I got that.
And there wasn't much blue archive.
I got a little bit of blue archive.
Oh, there is a Metal Gear print.
I got that.
And I
think that's about it.
Someone though, someone gave something to give, someone gave
something to Ayami Sensei to give to me, which I was like,
huh?
I was so shocked because I was like, no one will have
anything.
Well, first of all, I didn't expect presents at all.
I didn't expect presents at all.
But also, I thought that there wouldn't be anything because,
because, you know, I was a surprise guest at the panel.
Nobody even knew I was there.
Um, someone, someone gave her a signed poster of, of a
signed Metal Gear poster, signed by Hideo Kojima.
To give to me, I was so shocked.
And it had like a nice little note that was like, dear mint.
This has been sitting in my, in my, what's the word?
Uh, in my closet for a long time.
I want you to use it and appreciate it.
Or, like, display it.
I felt so bad, though.
I was like...
I was like, oh my god.
Um...
I felt bad that they gave it to Ayami-sensei.
Because I was like, ah, you should be giving gifts to her.
Not to me!
I wasn't even a guest.
so that's so cute it was really nice though yeah it's a lot
of fun and the panel was really funny um overall i had a
good time uh the last time i went to anime syndrome i have
been before last time was many years ago so um but i've
always liked the convention itself and uh
So I...
Um...
Yeah, I guess you were Ayami's guest.
Maybe.
I'm surprised they had it ready.
Me too!
Me, actually, though.
I was so shocked.
And...
Many years ago.
Wow, old!
That was years ago.
Um, oh my gosh, one of my favorite memories from...
From Anime Central is...
If you don't know, the convention is very close to an
airport oh my gosh thank you for the family gifted thank you
thank you so much thank you thank you so much oh my gosh
ojare yes ojare yeah it's very close to the airport and so
when I went it might have been the last time I went but the
artist Main, the singer, Main, was there.
And she's like the voice of Cheryl in Macross Frontier, but
she also was like a really big Annie song singer as well.
And so I remember, I remember in the concert, she was
singing Diamond Crevice, which is the like,
that song from macross and as she was singing it and like in
in the it was like the sun was setting and so it was really
beautiful out and it was like really sunny and the sun was
setting so the sky was kind of pink and then behind her
there was like an airplane flying at that moment as she was
singing it and so like i was like oh my gosh in my brain i
was like this this is this is macross so what and i just
remember my brain that whole time like i felt like i was
ascending into another dimension i was like this is the
coolest moment i don't think i could ever experience a
moment cooler than this ever it's one of those live moments
i still think about it to this very day and because of that
because of that one moment anime central is one of my
favorite one of my gonna go um when she told me that she was
gonna be there she told me quite some time ago so i was just
like i i will go just for you and that was before they
announced some of their other guests this year which was
like soramaru uh the voice of of of niko yazawa from love
live and oh my gosh thank you for the 15th we have moved
your attendance It's true!
Katsu, thank you so much for that 50 gift!
Thank you!
So bad, thank you for that.
Another 50?
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
Larry, welcome the membership.
Thank you, thank you.
Sally and Maki too.
Yeah, I actually didn't get to see her.
I'm so sad.
My schedule always didn't always overlapped.
with her, but I'll play the next convention.
Going to my first anime con this weekend.
Wish me luck.
Good luck!
Oh my gosh!
But yeah, so it was just like it was so fun.
I went to all the Sayu panels and everything and so even
before even before I knew that they were going to be invited
I was going already for Ayami, so I felt really like, oh my
gosh, this is crazy.
What's your policy for gifts at Afkai?
That's a great question.
Thank you for asking.
Anything but food is okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Anything but food.
Well, That's at least what it said on the site.
I honestly don't mind, like, snacks, if they're wrapped.
But, like, no handmade food or anything like that.
It was my first con.
I went to meet Ayasuzaki and got her to sign my Nita Minami
CD.
Oh, my God.
I had a lot of fun even though I went alone.
Yeah, sometimes things like that are so fun even alone.
Oh, my God, Simran.
Thank you for one month.
Can I buy hard?
Thank you for the favorite.
Give the thank you!
Oh my gosh, thank you guys.
But, uh.
Um.
But yeah.
So, gifts are okay.
Which, I think, um.
Uh.
I don't, am I allowed to say this?
Um.
It will be like my first time receiving gifts so I'm really
excited about it because um uh back in heaven there were
times when people would give gifts and I um we were told
that we would receive them and I never received them and I
think about it all the time because I just feel so bad about
it how there were people that were giving certain things or
maybe bought something with their own money and then I just
the gift so um yeah uh i i don't know if like maybe maybe if
maybe i'm still waiting on it i don't know but um uh yeah so
but um even from previous times to like the i just uh people
would give stuff and then it would just never show up in the
mail so i'm really sorry if that happened um But so That's
That's why I'm excited this time That I will actually Be
able to Be actually Actually be able to receive Receive it
So Heaven's customs are kind of crazy Heaven delivery caught
lagging There was stuff too That I was really looking
forward to But Um, yeah, so.
For heck, thank you for the 50 gift.
Thank you.
But I'm excited for this time, so.
Um, I don't know if...
Because I think for the gifts, it's maybe only for people
that got meet and greet stuff.
I will try to see if there's a way.
If you want to...
Not to say that you have to gift me anything or you know,
anything like that.
But if you want to gift something, I we'll see if there's a
way that you can gift it a place to gift it where I will be
able to receive it did you ever receive your letters?
I did receive those yes yes I did receive those so that's
why I thought it was strange that I never got the gifts as
well thought it was strange that they just didn't include it
and I don't know maybe if it was like a lack of
communication or if some one side you know if someplace sent
it and then whoever received it then didn't send it or if
the first place didn't say i don't know i don't know where
the lack of communication is happening i don't know i don't
have any contact anymore so uh yeah yeah i just think it's
kind of crummy if they say gifts are allowed and people give
gifts and then you know but anyway Ready to wave light
sticks for you on Anime North!
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you!
Guess, I guess now we know we can gift.
Yeah!
If you want.
If you want to.
You don't have to though.
Please don't feel like you have to.
Or if, but even if you just like want to write a letter or
something too.
That's okay too.
Yeah.
What's with the guy in the back?
He's having a barbecue with Snake.
It's Otakon.
I guess looking at it here, Otakon just looks like a random
guy.
He needs his lap coat.
He's casual Friday right now.
Time to write a letter.
Why do you have an egg?
Why you look so evil when you say that?
Labo, it's lizard!
Lizard!
Thank you for the gift.
Thank you!
Excited and nervous to meet you at Hopkai.
Deloran!
Why did you get a...
Did you get a meet and greet?
Yubi!
Thank you.
Nali Pop, welcome to Membuship.
But yeah, there's been a lot of things.
I'm sorry that I'm kind of like low energy today because...
The weekend was so much.
And then...
I came back and I was like...
I haven't thought of my schedule at all.
I should have pre-planned.
I should have planned my schedule for this week.
So I'm sorry I don't have a schedule.
yet.
And also,
I, uh, I, what's the word?
Um, uh, I can't remember.
Sorry.
My wallet is still recovering from Japan two months ago,
even, so even though I've been meaning to do Asen, I
couldn't afford it.
Ah!
I think you'd really like it a lot, Ghost Talker.
Maybe you could ever go.
I didn't want to be angry, unfortunately, but if you see a
Zagreus cosplay with Kazoos in his server school's mouth,
that he has a gift for you.
Thank you!
Just finishing your podcast with Matara while cleaning my
restaurant.
Oh my goodness, it's amazing.
You kept me waiting.
I hear receiver chats.
Hope your Monday's going well.
Hello.
um brain loading yeah it was just a really busy weekend and
um oh no i don't remember oh but yeah sorry about low
energies because i'm just so sleepy but um Yeah.
Casey, welcome to membership, big ham, welcome back.
Happy to be here.
Otasine for life.
Yeah!
There they are.
My little guy is hanging out.
Actually I have them labeled as the boys.png.
The boys.png.
We're chilling.
But!
We're not just chilling.
guys we're not just chilling we're not just chilling because
there's something else alex mezzo welcome back thank you
mateo thank you for watching me too thank you media post con
life dubie bleh i think it's just i feel it's really weird
because of this this this a sentence particular because
because i didn't win and any of the autographs and also
usually I like I go for Sayu but I really love going for
concerts and so the fact that they didn't really have like a
concert that I was uh super interested in so I didn't get to
so I didn't go but I was just kind of like I'm just kind of
like like hmm I feel not unfulfilled but I feel like I did
so much and so little at the same time you know what I mean
Thanks for having me.
Sally didn't win any meet and greets, but I'll be here.
There are Ofkay hanging out and buying all the merch of my
Oshis that I could find.
Your wallet.
No!
If we can gift without winning, I have something too.
Thanks for being amazing, Vito!
Thanks, Miss Miss!
Thank you.
Shadow Demon Lord, thank you for the gift!
Mmm.
Um...
Uh...
I have something...
that we can do.
I have something that we can do you guys while we chill and
while we talk.
Is it okay if we just talk today?
My brain is really slow.
I can barely keep my eyes open.
I'm so sleepy.
Is it bloons?
No.
I wasn't sure if you answered this before, but are you okay
with people cosplaying as you?
Of course!
Have you want to?
I'm honored if you want to cosplay me.
Oh my gosh.
Good morning, Meg.
Good morning!
Good... Oh, Goo's Morning.
Sorry, Glenn German.
Goo's Morning.
Minto time.
Are you guys ready?
Oh, yeah!
Hold
on, let me refresh it.
We're watching fish!
Why should we watch?
I'm actually really interested in live spider cam.
Oh, sorry.
Spider crab cam.
Let's see.
Let's check it out.
Oh, there's music.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
This is so...
Oh.
This is so spooky.
Look at the size.
of that crab.
Why is it so spooky looking?
Why is their webcam or their live stream not working?
No.
Okay, I guess we'll go to another one.
Let's try.
Let's try the live Monterey Baycam.
Oh, wait.
You guys can't see it.
Sorry.
It's cut off a little bit.
Let's try this one.
Whoa!
Oh my god, there's so many birds.
Oh my god We have a visitor We have a new friend See otter
Okay we'll check them out That's a big guy right there Is
that a goose?
Talk to me goose Sorry
I just felt like a whiplash Like I got slapped or something
Yo what just happened Oh my god.
Oh, this was supposed to be chill.
Me too.
Look how cute they are.
Oh, they're jumping around.
See ya.
See ya, loser.
You're not allowed on this little rock formation either
anyway.
Oh, wow.
Wait, does it move around?
Oh my gosh, I feel so at peace right now.
If you don't know, oh my gosh, there it is.
Thank you for the birthday gift and thank you so much!
If you didn't know, before I graduated many, many years ago,
I used to watch the Aquarium live cams.
My favorite streams are Meat Zatsu's.
Let's go!
I used to watch these just kind of hanging out.
And three years ago, many, many years ago.
The waves are so nice.
I know I feel really relaxed watching this.
Let's go see.
Some people said they want to see Otter Camp.
Ah!
There's just little guys!
Oh!
They're spinning and twirling and swimming around.
I wish I chilled with y'all sooner.
No, you're here now!
We're chilling!
What are you talking about?
You're here now.
I think it's...
Oh, he's so slick.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, he's looking at me.
That's me.
He's looking at me.
Welcome
back.
Oh, there he is.
Yeah.
Wow, there's so many people watching this one.
200 people are watching this one.
Wow.
Hey, Aminto.
Hey, yo, dopo.
Thank you for your mind.
Thank you.
That was so baby.
There's three!
I hope they're having an enriched life.
We'll be watching them.
Yeah.
So we just can watch and talk and just kind of hang out.
And, you know.
Of course, if you want to ever...
These are live cams.
They're basically 24-7.
If you ever want to watch, it's the Monterey...
The Monterey, Monterey Bay Aquarium.
I keep getting these shorts of people that seem to have pet
river otters.
Pets?
I don't know about that.
Minto love.
Thanks, Nisoc, thank you.
I kind of want to see the penguins though, is that okay?
African penguin cam da-da-da ew oh god oh oh it's disgusting
oh my god exactly what I oh god imagine the smell in there I
can imagine the smell oh gosh it's nasty the rocks are
stained do not imagine the smell.
Look at that.
Oh.
Is that a penguin right there?
I can't tell.
Or is that a rock?
I don't think it's a penguin.
Oh, I imagine the smell.
Yeah!
No!
Let's go!
He did it!
He jumped off!
Did you see his little feet go?
Tap, tap, tap, tap.
Have you seen the live cams?
The what?
Live cams?
Here we see a group of poopy penguins.
Benny cabbage pie.
My cat just pissed on me!
Oh!
Can I have some words of comfort in these trying times?
I'm really sorry, Shin-chan.
Um...
You know, they say sometimes...
Oh my god!
Is this guy...
I thought he was using the restroom.
Um, you know, some say that when you get...
When you get peed on by something, it's good luck, right?
So...
Um...
Where's that pooped on?
I don't know.
Who says that?
I don't think anybody says that.
Oh, it's bird poop.
My cat threw up in his litter box, which actually rules.
I wish he would do that instead of the poor.
Everything about how ZVTubers are basically zoo animals.
We watched them frolic and play and occasionally throw
peanut super chats into their enclosures.
It was funny after the panel with Ayami Sensei.
Her manager, Ayami Sensei was like, Turn around, my manager
wanted to say something to you.
I was like, oh, okay.
Um, yes, sir.
And he just like starts making like, like he's like throwing
a baseball with both hands.
He like keeps throwing.
He's just like, Super chat, super chat, super chat, super
chat, super chat.
She was so silly.
She was so...
Oh, let's look at the shark, Kim.
Oh my god, that's a big fish.
No.
He just came up from nowhere.
Super chat.
No.
Damn it, it's my birthday today.
And I'm dropping by to say hello.
Lay, happy birthday.
I haven't been able to catch up with your streams.
Have a nice day, Minto.
Thank you.
Thank you so much for dropping by on your birthday.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, dear Lay.
Happy birthday!
The Super Chat is Baha Blast colored.
She really liked the Baha Blast.
Super Chat!
Oh gosh!
Thank you guys for the Super Chat!
Super Chat!
Thank you for the pink!
Whoa!
He's so big!
Where these guys come from!
Wow!
Eat!
I like how many different types of sharks are in here.
Spot sharks, rays, and other fishes as they cruise through
our rocky reef.
The shark cam is available from 7 a.m.
to 7 p.m.
Pacific time.
Okay, good, we have time.
Moist.
Welcome to Mapo Shizu.
Hi, Minto, and Whisper.
I just got home and we chilling and talking.
Also, welcome back.
We'll be having fun.
Also, super chat.
Thank you.
Yeah, we're just chilling and talking.
And I don't really...
I'm trying to think of, you know, what else?
Oh my gosh, you can see the people, like, walking by.
It was kind of creepy.
Now I'm watching the people.
Now, now, now they're in the zoo.
Oh,
sushi.
Thank you for the five gifted.
Thank you.
So...
Whoa!
Oh my god.
Did you guys see that?
He just did a...
That guy just did a flip!
Hayao, what's your favorite ice cream flavor?
I like cookies and cream.
Do a barrel roll.
What else do we have?
What else do we have going on?
Oh, let's see, aviary cam.
Oh, they're so cute!
Oh, you can see the ocean from here too.
Look at that tiny little bird.
Oh my gosh.
This morning, my cat, Paz, she was looking out the window.
She loves looking out the window.
It's like her favorite activity to do.
It's her enrichment time.
is looking out the window and, you know, observing the
world.
She saw, she saw today, she saw a lizard and she stood up.
Ah, sorry.
Oh, God, they were really close.
Oh, my gosh, their beaks are kind of bent.
They have such interesting form.
God, they're huge.
They're really big birds.
But, uh, um, today in the tree, I saw the fattest bird I
think I've ever seen in my entire life.
This guy was so fat.
This guy was just a real... Wow, he's amazing!
Oh, no!
Oh, my God, it's so cute.
Look at him go!
No, cameraman, stop the camera!
Stop the camera!
Oh, thank God.
Oh my God.
Oh, he's okay!
He just won't stop!
Oh, oh, he stopped.
Oh, gosh, thank God.
him started to cry so cute do it do it big bird do it oh you
jerk oh man yes yes go back in oh man he scurried away oh he
drank his bath water wouldn't you if i saw something that
cute i'd drink its bath water too I need to consume some of
that cuteness.
I need it.
Your boy Steven Adams.
Thank you for the rose.
Thank you.
It was super cool to see with Ayami tasting snacks in
Chicago.
I hope Ayami passed.
Oh, Hong, a little gift airway.
She did, she did.
Hey, cameraman, there's nothing here.
Cameraman, show us the goods.
Show us the birds.
I'm in chill stream.
Also, man.
Ah, grain of sand.
What are you talking about?
I'm not excited about the sand.
Excited about the birds.
Oh, boy sand.
Where are they?
Where's the birds?
I think they're all dead.
Sometimes I think about if the world ended.
Oh.
Look how diddle, little, he's going around in circles.
Look how cute his little tippy-tops are.
Tippy-top, top, top.
Come over here, bird.
Is it possible to deliver you a letter at virtual vacation
concert?
That, I don't know yet.
I can look into that, though.
I can look into that.
There they are.
The birds are back.
The birds are back in town.
Back in town.
The other guy was like a ghost signing.
Did Streamlabs don't alerts break?
I think they're very delayed because of the gifted.
I'm sorry, they'll show up eventually though.
I'm sure they will eventually.
Oh, I see that some have been donated.
I'm sorry.
More bathwater.
Oh, he's so wibby.
Oh, he's so cute.
This one kind of sucks.
Let's check out the kelp forest.
Whoa.
That's a lot of fish up there.
Wow.
Whoa.
I typically like the ones where I don't see the walls
because also the way the kelp moves is really
at 28 feet the kelp forest is one of the tallest aquarium
exhibits in the world
oh my god does that have to be so aggressive why was it like
that oh my god what just happened Me too!
What is up with this camera?
I feel so like calm with the way the kelp moves.
Oh my god, that's an ugly fish down there in the corner.
They're so ugly.
That guy's ugly too.
That guy's cool.
I like him.
I like how he goes bop bop bop.
fish shaming whoa all the fish are coming out they're all
coming out there's so many fish in here i want to see the
school though hey cameraman can i please whoa he's huge is
that a parrot fish maybe oh okay oh okay whoa wow whoa wowy
goodness gracious big boy fish Boss fish.
Bro was built like candy corn.
Oh, there's sharks in here too.
Thank you, Mr. Cameraman.
Hey, Mint.
Did you know that recently scientists have discovered a
super terrifying plant?
It's named since shivers down my spine.
They call it bamboo.
Bamboo.
Terrifying.
Ever seen the Georgia Aquarium in Atlanta?
Oh, God.
Sorry.
They have actual whale sharks and Manta rays.
Wait, Manta rays are the really, really, really, really...
I know whale sharks, but Manta rays are the really, really
big ones, right?
You know what I like to do?
I like to go to the stingrays.
And I like to...
You know how some aquariums have the...
Georgia Aquarium is amazing.
I wanna go!
Been there a few times in the past.
I wanna see a whale shark.
I wanna see...
I want to jump in here and show a fistful of seaweed into my
mouth.
Might be a little salty, I know.
Good night, Minto.
It's fun catching you stream.
Thanks, Damien.
Have a good night.
Um...
I like to...
The touch stingrays.
I like to put my hands underneath them and have them nibble
on my fingers.
It's a good experience.
Whoa!
This one feels like a screensaver.
This one doesn't even feel real.
What are you eating?
Reese's Puffs?
Thank you, Luke!
Thank you!
Wow.
I feel like I need some more like ethereal kind of music
instead.
I love Mint as my GF and she has Boing Boing.
Are you okay?
Uh oh.
Get some help.
It's okay.
Jellyfish, that's it done.
Yeah, basically.
Minj is with Ayami now.
Let her go.
There's the Jellyfish Music anime this season.
Oh, yes.
I have heard about it.
I don't know anything about it, though.
What is what is it about?
There's a few shows that I've been wanting to watch this
season.
Oh, that reminds me.
I have to watch Blue Archive.
Um, I've seen this jellyfish stream for 50 billion hours.
It's my favorite.
I'm somewhat of an avid diver.
My most favorite moments are when I'm under and I get to see
all kinds of sea life.
I've seen dolphins, some small sharks, and the most
memorable is the lionfish.
Whoa, aren't those poisonous?
Do not pee on jelly stings.
I think you're supposed to.
You're supposed to pee on jelly stings.
If anybody in here got stung by a jellyfish.
I'd pee on you.
So that you wouldn't die.
So don't worry.
I got you, homie.
I got you.
I got stung, mint.
Help!
Did you?
Did you really?
Thanks.
I think.
I would help a homie out.
Minto being a bro.
Homies would pee on each other to save them from the
jellyfish stings.
Ghost can pee.
Don't think about it too hard.
Thanks for the gift of every...
I thought the pee wars were over.
Was there ever a war?
Planet of the Apes.
Help, I've been st- Tuna.
Oh, Tuna.
I don't think I'm going to make it.
Help me out here.
Spears likes the strawberry jelly.
Do you need a tampon?
Are you okay, mister?
Why do you use the strawberry jelly?
Do it?
It's his birthday.
This is actually your birthday, too, no?
Strawberry jelly equals jellyfish.
Um.
I don't think...
I think so.
I'm never...
Mint, please, it's Tudas' birthday duel for the birthday
boy.
Stop peer pressuring me!
I went to do research before you...
Before I what?
Oh, pounce on the next dogen.
I suspect the theme is developing.
No, the one that I got recently was a hypno...
one I think I'm kind of into into the hypnosis recently
don't
worry there's nothing else in it Minto please say my name
with contempt to this looks
good like a wallpaper.
I know, right?
That's why I keep it up.
Like, actually, recently at night, when it's, actually, hold
on.
You're not going to hear anything real quick.
I kind of want to hear what the music they have on for this,
if it's like a, oh yeah, it's kind of like a
just like that.
Just like that.
what was i saying oh i um at night i put on like a it's like
a it's not a live stream but it's like a it's like a crazy
like eight hour long video or something like that and it's
just of like it's it's jazz and then it's like Tokyo at
night and it just switches between some videos of Tokyo at
night and akabane welcome to membership that's my face What
are you trying to summon, Minto?
Oh,
a snack.
And one day, Batara offers to walk on us and Mint to pee on
us.
Good day to be in the room.
Only under extreme circumstances, and you must be stung by a
jellyfish.
It's my good friend, Bob.
Bob's birthday.
He got into an accident and can't use his arms.
Can you wish him a happy birthday for me?
I can.
I'm just gonna say Bob, though.
Because I'm scared.
Okay, cut that part out.
Don't tell him that I'm scared.
Don't tell him that I've been burned before.
Cut that part out.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday dear Bob.
Can I
get a happy birthday too?
It was in January.
No, you can wait until January.
It's already the middle of the year, you guys.
It's almost the end of May.
Next month.
in a couple days in like in like a week and a half it will
be the middle of 2024
back when So Senkyo was a borderline national holiday in
Japan and Iota would buy thousands of singles to vote was
this behavior based or a cringe follow up was So Senkyo
rigged or not thanks
um let's see hmm um you know I have to wait till March sorry
man sorry I
when was April 4th and you missed my soup bar really?
I missed it hold on okay I'm gonna wish you happy birthday
and then we're gonna answer the question Happy birthday to
you.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, dear Salias.
Just
the jellyfish thing need to be recent because I've been
stung before as a kid.
Oh, Takizo's winning the running, everybody!
Oh no, Takizo.
I think you just put a target on yourself.
Okay.
So Senkyo.
For those who don't know, So Senkyo was like this...
I mean, I think they still do it in AQB, right?
They have a...
They have this big event where...
It's just a voting.
It's a ranking event, essentially.
That's all it is.
And then you vote for your favorite member of AQB48.
And then whoever is in like the top 16 or is like the top
girls in the group.
And they get...
whoever's number one is the center for the next single and
things like that so they haven't done so thank you since
2019 really this out shows how much shows how much i've paid
attention in the past couple of years yeah you buy cds to
vote essentially and also i think you're the only person to
pronounce my name right let's go but um so you you buy the
cds and you vote for your favorite, favorite, favorite girl,
and then you hope and pray.
And I've participated before.
I've, I've bought like, it wasn't a lot.
I think it was like two CDs.
So honestly, I made zero difference.
But I, um, the people that would buy so many, I, you know
what, No, I don't think that was based.
I think it was a waste.
I don't think that was based.
I don't think so.
I think...
Because, you know...
I think it was...
Yeah, I don't think it was based.
Cringe then?
Yeah, I guess I could say it was kind of cringe.
And I just don't like...
I don't really like when...
When...
When something is like...
Just so solely based on...
How much money someone can spend.
I don't know.
That just feels like kind of wrong.
Like if I were in something like that, I wouldn't want
anybody, any one of you any of you guys yeah pay to win
basically yes it's just pay to win and i feel like if i were
in that same situation and people in it like i wouldn't want
you guys to spend your money to like vote for me and things
like that i just it just doesn't feel it just doesn't feel
good you know so yeah i don't know like if that makes you
happy then who am i to stop you but if it's like just it's
just you know how much of that were the girls getting and
all especially for that for like so thank you like you had
to buy so there were people buying tens and thousands of CDs
like an insane amount someone at Miku Expo Newark a couple
weeks ago paid me 120 dollars for my two-year-old Daisenko
200 with a broken strap and low batteries and a Miku insert
film because the official $20 for a dice that go 200 stonks
stonks
oh that's funny but you know it's funny it's like funny
because i say that but then at the same time there are times
when i buy a bunch of cds for like a but I'm not buying
thousands of CDs I'm buying like 10 or 20 CDs so I don't
know one time I bought a bunch of CDs for a Kickstarter well
like I think they came with the Kickstarter and then I got
like some extra perks like I got a video and I got stuff
like that and I got I got some of them were signed by each
member so yeah but i think it's if it's like a if it's for
something like to get a checky for yourself then it makes
sense but if it's a like vote for someone to be the most
popular in our group i just don't like i don't know i never
really liked so thank you i'll be honest i just didn't i
just always thought it felt kind of icky you know pay to win
pay to win just makes me feel icky not in this economy you
know you can't do that in this it would be so bad anyway
sage welcome to my buship it's totally an investment to get
them later and spread the word right well for me i mean yeah
i got my first pay for my job thank you because you leaving
heaven was the kick in the bum to me to leave Oh my gosh,
really?
The fun plans I want to tell you, my life is observably
better because of you.
Oh my gosh, but dear, thank you.
Expensive.
Oh my gosh, fun.
Thanks for the 10 gifted.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Yeah.
Let's go to another one.
Hmm.
wait there's moon jellies too oh they're so pretty now
actually I don't know which one I like more I think I like
the other one more because the trails have like a better
effect on the screen there's like more going on right thank
you for the 20 gifted gracias thank you I feel like I like
the other one better.
I feel like this one need, they need more, but look at that.
That, it looks like the moo, the sand dollars, right?
Looks like the design on a sand dollar.
Oh my god, I want to eat this.
Oh god.
Oh my gosh, someone earlier on Twitter, they posted slime
that they made of me, and I've never bought slime before,
but I'm gonna buy it and I think I'm gonna eat it.
It says do not eat on What if I'm just...
Just one like...
You know?
Slime eating stream.
Do not eat it, Mint.
But I really want to.
I'll call poison control.
Will I actually be poisoned?
Oh no.
Pee in my mouth.
Don't do that, Emmerine.
I think I regret saying that.
Let's move on to the next thing.
What haven't we looked at?
Did we look at the live open sea camp?
Whoa!
Why are there so many bubbles?
You are alive, young lady.
Here it goes.
What are I going to do?
Exactly.
What am I going to do?
Die again?
Mint.
No!
Say that, Evan!
Okay, I think this one will trigger some, like, what's that
fear of the deep ocean?
The fast less foam phobia.
I think this one would kind of trigger that in some people
because the dark, like, the background is so dark and you
just see the fish kind of coming out of nowhere.
I passed my certification.
Certification exam after work after stinging of months.
I celebrated by ordering an iMass figure.
Let's go.
Congratulations.
I got here to go.
I knew you got.
I knew you had this.
Mint.
No, don't say that.
It fish jump scare.
Do you guys have that phobia?
Oh, they're zooming.
I was stung by tiny jellyfishes when our family was on a
trip to the beach and turned out The whole beach was
infested by it Later that day, the beach was closed because
of it Holy cow!
I've never had, um...
I've never had a jellyfish sting, but, um...
What was it?
I remember going to the beach once as a kid, and I don't
think I got it, but my sister got sea lice, which I didn't
even know was a thing.
Did you guys know that sea lice is a thing?
I'm gonna go back to the birds.
Oh, or the beach.
What is sea lice?
I don't know.
But it, like, I remember it caused, like...
Hold on, I'm going to look it up.
Sea...
Sea lice.
They're little tiny creatures.
They're copepods.
Oh, no!
Copipot.
But they cause all these really bad bread bumps all over my
sister's leg.
Sand fleas.
I don't know.
Ew.
Don't look at the pictures.
Copipot.
Going to sleep on the floor, I wanted to tell you.
I love you.
You're my favorite nerd.
a fun nerdy stream.
Here you go.
Good night.
I thought Kojima made those up for MGS2.
What, the sea lice?
No, those were different, weren't they?
Those were the...
What were they?
Fleeze?
Sea fleas.
Are they real sea fleas?
Or they were different kind of...
Pod.
Remember one time, a jellyfish spawning season almost
destroyed an aircraft carrier.
I was on by clogging up all the cooling water.
That's crazy.
But sea lice are very tiny.
They're small, small little guys, I'm pretty sure.
They're teeny tiny and then they get on you and they...
And then they give you bad rash and it happened to my
sister.
Top Gun in the movies versus Top Gun in real life.
What do you mean by that?
How did you know I watched Top Gun?
I had a question about Top Gun.
Is there...
Do bird strikes, like, really happen?
Is that really something that can, like, just take out a
plane?
If a bunch of birds run into a plane?
Do you watch Top Gun every time?
Yes!
Yes, I do.
The carrier almost got destroyed just because sea lice
clogged up the cooling water.
Sounds like a chill issue.
It's very dangerous.
Can take down even big planes?
Oh no.
New fear.
Rashes?
Oh, it's alright.
We're talking about sea lice.
If sea lice exist, do sea monkeys groom themselves of them?
Ew.
Spent.
Flam!
Smento.
Hmm.
Hudson Bay Miracle Landing caused by birds.
Look up Bash Bird Animal Airstrike.
Airstrike Hazard.
bird wait what was it bird animal I think that animal is not
necessary but it's irrelevant right bird animal hazard these
bird slash wildlife aircraft strike hazard Wow oh my god
this is so funny the picture they use for this is so funny
it's like this the bird like looking directly at the camera
a bird strike is what caused the plane to go down in the
hudson wait no it didn't long time donator pilot or first
time viewer a bird strike is actually what took down the
plane captain solenberg was piloting that became the miracle
on the hudson in 2011 wait seriously Wait.
Bird strike.
What's...
No way!
Wait, I'm seeing 2009.
I remember hearing about this, though.
That's so scary.
So how do they...
Owl would, like, you know, you're flying.
What, do you have, like, radars that show where birds are?
Like, how do you avoid that?
Oh, I don't know.
I saw that bird.
Look at chicken cannons.
They fire them for tests.
I'm not going to look at them.
They made a movie, I think.
Really?
Hudson River, two years ago.
Not sea lice.
Giant jellyfish clogged up the carrier's intakes.
They were being scraped off for days.
Oh, gross.
If you like Top Gun, have you ever considered playing Ace
Combat.
People like to describe it as MGS with fighter jets without
how over the top the story gets.
I do!
Um, probably, uh, once I get back from Japan, I'll probably
start Ace Combat.
Um, I don't know which one to start from, though.
I'm still trying to decide.
But probably once I get back from Japan, because I'm trying
to avoid, actually, or, maybe in August I can start it.
Because I'm trying to avoid it with, like, some of my bigger
events that I'm, you know, if I'm going out of town or
something like that, so...
Wait, you're going to Japan again?
I am!
I'll be going to Japan again with Matara this time.
We actually have some plans that we'll be doing.
But I'll still be streaming while I'm there.
She and I decided we're going to be streaming every other
day together.
So we're going to be like, one day she'll be streaming and
then, you know, you might hear me in the background.
I might be like, Matara, I'm...
Taking a shower.
Don't go streaming in the bathroom.
Stuff like that.
And we plan to at least...
Let's see.
What time is it now in Japan?
We hope to stream...
It will probably be a little bit later than our usual
streaming times.
But we're going to try and stream at our usual times.
So we'll wake up early in stream and then go about our day.
But there might be also some nighttime ones on our end.
So hot tub stream.
She went to the bathroom.
She would find a wisp with a jellyfish sting on the floor.
How would you get there?
First of all, I would say, how did you...
I would say, where did this jellyfish come from?
I think that's what I'd say first.
And I'd say, why are you in my house?
Shout out to Giri's house soon to be Matara's house Well,
the plan is that we're rooming together But if she wants to
go to Giri's house More room for me I guess Why is nothing
happening on this live stream?
Sorry guys, I picked a really lame one Let's go back to
Otter Camp
So cute
The jellyfish was luggage i've seen a girl oh they're here
they're here so many vids thank you thank you for haunting
everyone at asen this past weekend hope you shower hope
you're showered with gifts in the future and in honor of
your cafe guests here's a little philanthropy thank you
thank you so much
um i don't remember what i was saying Rosa the otter.
You guys know the names of the otter here?
Oh, wait, sorry.
I'm seeing if they...
These female sea otters are all rescued and non-releasable
to the wild for health or behavioral reasons.
They play an important role for their species at the
aquarium.
Not only as ambassadors to otter kind for our guests, but
also as surrogate mothers for stranded sea otter pups.
Oh, that's so sweet.
the volleyball scene oh my gosh it's so funny because when i
was watching top top gun maverick um on this trip i found
myself i was like skipping through all the relationship
draws which usually i eat that up usually i'm just like you
know i like to watch romance movies sometimes and things
like that like whatever but this time i was skipping through
all i was I was like, I don't care about you, lady.
And then I would be like, get to the mission already.
Which I found very different from what I'm usually like.
Oh my god.
Robo!
Thank you for the very big Akadodo.
I mean, I finally passed my defense and signed a job offer
last week.
I've had some tough times.
Tough times never last, buddy.
And I really want to thank you for always being around and
being me too.
By the way, I put you in my acknowledgement.
I hope you don't mind it.
Oh my gosh, thank you.
Like, congratulations.
Oh my gosh, congrats.
I knew you had it.
You had it in you the whole time.
Oh my gosh, congrats, Robo.
Thank you so much for the really big Akadono.
Thank you.
That's so fun.
Oh my gosh, I don't think you're going to do that.
I don't think I've ever been in an acknowledgement before.
Oh my gosh, what did you say that I, what did I do?
Provided a minty fresh experience.
Remind, wait.
Was your thing on me?
There was a streamer named Doug that raised 300K for Rosa
the Sea Otters birthday.
Wow!
That's incredible.
They actually on the Monterey Bay Aquarium YouTube, they
have a donation thing that says, We get by with a little
kelp from our frogs.
But you can donate.
It says total raise is $20,000.
I think I'll raise that.
Have you heard about the surfboard thief sea otter?
I'm not.
By say.
Thanks for a month.
Thank you.
9 out of 10 dentists recommend Mint Phantom.
Almost 4K...
Oh, sorry, I don't look at the numbers.
Sorry, don't tell me how many people are watching.
Four people are watching.
Spooky number.
Thank you for...
Thank you guys for hanging out with me.
I really appreciate it.
We're not even, I'm not even doing anything.
I'm barely even talking about anything.
Mint time.
Oh.
Don!
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you.
I'm one of the four.
It's calm.
Yeah, we're just chilling.
We're just hanging out.
Chilling with Mint.
I'll change the title and stuff afterwards.
Whoa, he just went through the door!
Do it again, Otter!
Do it again!
I, but today was quite busy for me.
I was catching up with a bunch of...
Actually, I haven't caught up with emails yet.
I've caught up with messages, I believe, to people.
I had to pay a bunch of people because I was paying for,
like, art for the Patreon postcards for the podcast.
I bought some extra little things for off Kai if you are
going to off Kai if you're going to the to the I think we
said the panel if you go to the panel there you'll get maybe
a little extra thing if you come early so how the postcards
been sent no I know it's really super duper delayed I'm so
sorry you guys we're gonna be sending the first two april
may together they will be sent um almost all the art is done
for them um but we just have to sign them we haven't met up
she was a matara was supposed to come to my place the my
mint cafe at the beginning of the month and she didn't so oh
we're gonna ship them during off kai i believe
Since you mentioned it, can you show the tough times never
last video for the new wisps?
I never saw it.
Thanks for the stream freaking ghost me.
Again, I have it.
I have it somewhere.
Hold on.
Uh, maybe it was under here.
Oh my god, he's crawling!
Oh my god, he looks just like Butaro.
He looks just like Butaro!
No way.
Oh my god that looks just like my cat That looks just I
gotta add a cat Emote, don't I?
I gotta commission more emotes, don't I?
See you on Upkai I'm even going to the May Cafe After you're
meeting me Thanks, Rude!
Okay, I think I found it.
Oh wait, um No, these are all my idle videos Oh my gosh, oh
my gosh!
Oh my gosh, I didn't even know I had these on here Oh!
There's videos of me...
Okay, so a long time ago...
My Yoshi...
I would do, like, video calls with her.
And, um...
You're not allowed to record them.
So I would record myself talking to her.
So I would set up my camera behind me so that...
But not enough so she could see that I was recording it.
So I have...
Oh my god.
It's me sitting in my closet.
Like, back when I used to stream in my closet.
Oh my gosh, I had no idea that that video was there.
That's so funny.
Wow.
I also have...
Sorry, I'm looking through my pictures folder right now.
Which I don't have a ton of stuff in here.
But I have a folder called Google Earth VR.
And the only...
I don't know why I have this.
The only thing I have in here is...
But I think it's upside down.
And also, it's called schwanggao.jpg.
Did I take this?
Schwang.
It's somewhere in Germany.
I don't know why I have this.
I don't even remember using Google Earth VR.
Okay, I'm still looking for the video.
It's not under videos.
Maybe...
I still need to open the door in my microwave.
It'll turn on automatically while it's open.
Do you think it's a ghost?
Wait, your microwave is turning on while the door is open?
I think you need to throw that away.
I think you need to disassemble that.
I think that's not safe.
I think that's...
Pretty bad.
You put your Schwanggao away, young man.
Have you ever gone flying upside down over the German
countryside?
Apparently I have in Bihar.
You know, I can't keep still.
I'm crazy out of control.
Where could it be?
I thought it was under here.
Wait, what is this?
I don't know.
Hmm.
Somebody stop her.
Now this is gonna drive me crazy, though.
This is gonna drive me crazy.
You know what?
I just had an idea.
Yeah.
I had an idea.
For people who can't make it to the meet and greet.
Hmm.
Maybe, maybe.
If I can't find the video today, I'll find it eventually,
and then I'll show it eventually.
Sorry.
I really have no idea where it's at.
Where it's at.
But I saw it recently.
Wait, that means the other videos that were in there are
gone too.
No, where's all my stuff?
Idea?
meetup?
Stop spoiling it!
What if we meet in VR chat?
But I don't have a, I don't have a model.
I don't have a 3D model I could use.
Hmm.
Please, I lost the meet and greet.
Wait, Mo!
You don't need a meet and greet to meet me.
Frog model?
Would you love me even if I'm a frog?
What is this guy doing over here in the corner?
He's like circling around with his tail.
What is he doing?
I think he's playing.
Wee!
Yes?
Probably.
Okay.
I love you even if I'm a frog.
I would love you more if you were.
a frog do i need to get a frog outfit i was thinking about
that though i was like what kind of outfits do i want i
already have my next outfit plan so you can't choose that
one but maybe in the future if you guys ever want to give me
ideas for a third outfit
who knows
ghost made bikini that was so fast That was so...
That was so like...
Here's my chance.
Swim suit.
I thanked my friend Mint for unconditional emotional
support.
I haven't come out as a weeb yet.
I was too shy to say my Oshi.
You're a weeb.
oh my gosh i had i've reached peak weeb levels everybody i
have reached i have reached extreme weeb levels that cannot
be undone i believe which i mean it's pretty hermint the
frog which are like okay first of all when i was um when i
was waiting to go home i was getting food and i got uh it
was like a greek bowl i got like a greek bowl and when i was
getting my food the person checking me out was just like by
the way we're out of and it was in a food court so they were
like we're out of um we're out of spoons you can go next
door and get chopsticks from the from the from the chinese
place and use those to eat it instead thank you for that i
got super yara go flour Phantom boy.
Phantom boy!
Yorgo floor.
Never Akasupas when I can acknowledge it.
It must be really important to you to get the Phantom boy.
I wasn't going to Ofkai because I was scared.
But someone convinced me to go.
Didn't win the lottery, but I was drawing fan art to give to
you.
It's bad.
No!
I'm excited to go to my first condo.
Thanks for making me go out of my comfort zone.
Oh my gosh, Amelia!
I hope you have a wonderful, wonderful time.
I hope we can meet somehow.
Got home from Jim.
Very tired, reproductive.
Watch the podcast during.
I'm wondering if you're able to show us the pick of your two
cats getting along.
Oh, I posted it on Twitter sideways.
Sorry that the editor missed it.
But yeah, I had to use...
I had to use chopsticks for my Greek food, and I felt really
silly about that.
So I was just like, gosh, I feel like a weeb in this regard.
But then, when I was hanging out with Ayami-sensei and our
managers and everything, they were just like, you know,
Minto, are you sure you're American?
I was like, I mean, I...
Thank you, I guess I'm an American ghost.
Choo!
Thank you, Yanwei!
If my health improves, I'd love to go to a con and give you
my Rex and Ray model kits.
Oh my gosh.
They're painted Itasha style with an unrelated VTuber on
them.
So that would be weird.
So would that be weird or inappropriate?
I might still make Mint Itasha versions later.
Oh!
I don't know if I would be able to bring them back without
breaking them, though.
I'd be so nervous.
But I would love to accept.
them even still if you are willing to part with them i feel
bad you put them together and painted them and everything
nexi phantom boy thank you for the aquasupa thank you oh my
gosh but yeah when i was like oh i think everything's coming
through now spy turtle whoa whoa whoa hey buddy you're not
welcome here spy turtle this is this is an anti bbc area no
british here no broadcasting finished making a devil's food
cape from scratch gosh how are you so handy you have bees
you cook are you are you a weeb how are you like this how do
you watch me and have your life so well together
But, um...
But yeah, when I was hanging out with Ayami Sama...
Sama Sensei's manager...
She is Ayami Sama to me.
When I was hanging out with her manager and stuff, they were
like, Are you sure you're American?
And I was like...
I... I mean, I...
I don't remember quite where I died, but I think I died in
America.
And they were like...
They were like, You...
You act too Japanese.
They're like, I was like, well, I have like, you know, I
have family in Japan too, but they were like, you act, you,
the way you, you, your manner is, everything is way too
Japanese for you to be American.
I was like, in my brain, I was just like, this is it.
This is, this is what every weeaboo probably ever aspires to
have said to them.
You have assimilated.
I know.
I am.
And I've been told before, it's so funny, I've been told
before, like one time I was in a taxi, I was getting driven
home by a taxi driver in Japan, and he was talking with me,
and he was just like, wow, you're like, you know, Japanese
is good, and this and that, whatever, and you like, you seem
very Japanese, I think, I think you are reincarnated
Japanese, well, I don't know, like, my past go.
You know, it was, you know, it's kind of confusing, I guess,
when you bring reincarnation into it.
But, he was just like, I think you were once Japanese in a
past life.
And I was like, I don't, I'm, you guys, I'm a, I'm a
Japanese princess.
Sorry, hold on.
It's, I cannot, I don't know what's wrong with YouTube
raids, but the thing, look at it.
I have to screenshot it.
I cannot, I think it said, Nauru.
Thank you for the...
Raid!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
This is what I see when I get a raid.
Something's wrong with YouTube.
I can't see the name of the person.
Look at this.
This is what shows up.
Oh yeah, I see it.
Yeah, Ruchu!
Thank you for the raid!
It's just white!
Thank you for the gifted ducky.
Thank you.
Did you die by truck gun?
Hmm.
Who knows?
Yeah, sorry if I missed somebody's raid because I can't read
it because YouTube is broken.
YouTube's actually broken.
White on white.
Sasuga.
Yeah.
Everybody coming in.
Hi, I'm a Japanese...
Well, I'm dead.
I'm a mint.
I'm a ghost.
I died, but I'm also maybe was once a Japanese princess and
pre-incarnated.
And then I died again, I guess.
Two Japanese people have told me that I'm a Japanese.
Well, he didn't say I was a Japanese princess.
I've had the white on white YouTube problem for the last
week.
It's so weird.
Yeah, it just started recently.
Thank you Yeah, I've reached I've reached peak I've reached
every weeaboo's dream
This is I can't go I can't go any higher than this can we
get much higher?
No, this is it I'm I'm secret Nihonji.
Look at him play with the donut For everybody also coming
in.
Hi, we're watching Animal Live Cams.
From the Monterey Bay Aquarium area.
Yes, yes, yes.
Wait a second.
Did I miss some?
Hold on.
Bloodlust, thank you for the...
Rogue for Raba, thank you for the 50 gifted.
Wait a second.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Am I missing some?
Bloodlust, thank you for the 10.
Dragonuity, thank you for the 5.
Chris in a box, thank you for the 5.
guys i think i missed them oh gosh
let's go to a new one because all the otters have left
spider cam
oh my gosh this one is so scary also it's broken they go
here every time and then it freezes i think it's broke oh
it's sad okay let's watch the penguins again Oh my god, look
at all this shit.
This guy.
Oh, oh.
Oh my goodness.
But this guy I think has had an ex- I think- either he's
molting or he just shit himself.
This guy needs a diaper.
Look at him.
He's shit himself looking at the Riaju penguins over here.
There's a couple here, there's a couple here and he's just
looking on with envy.
It's even worse now.
I think it is.
I don't remember seeing this calamity on the rock.
And who did this?
Who pooped all over the rock?
It's sliding down.
This is so sad.
It's cuffing season.
And this guy's got lonely.
He actually doesn't look too good.
I'm kind of concerned.
I hope he's alright.
Like, maybe he's, like, over...
Like, maybe it is molting, and he's, like, overly plucked.
Like, he's, like, plucking and everything.
Mint, please, I'm eating.
Enti, welcome to bamboo shift.
Thank you!
Oh.
The camera, like, just barely shifted so that we don't have
to see his sad, sad self, you know.
Molding too hard.
never look up male penguins protecting eggs I won't look
that up now that you told me to I wish there were chin strap
penguins those are my favorite kinds of penguins the chin
strap I saw those in I saw those in in Antarctica but they
it was every time I went to go see them the weather was
always so terrible Javi or Javi Javi sorry so it's at one
month already OMG thank you for one month thank you thank
you thank you um look at this guy's over here alone maybe
you should try courting him there's one up here too um we
saw the chin strap penguins always on the bad weather and
then um oh my gosh The Adele?
Adele?
Penguins?
Was it?
Let me check.
Membo.
We are memboos.
Thank you.
Penguins will always remind me of my homie GrapeCun.
Yeah.
GrapeCun.
It's funny.
Yeah, his wife who became a V-Tuber.
So true.
Starlet Yuki, welcome back.
Excited for the concert.
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
Man, a group of wisps are planning an Antarctica cruise for
winter 2024-25 any tips or recommendations oh um i don't
know uh i would say go earlier in the season because i think
that's when it's less crowded like go when it's still like
spring into summer in antarctica um because i think it's
less crowded than there's less other trips going at that
time as well, so it will be a little bit more secluded, I
think.
Get on a bigger boat.
If you want to avoid seasickness, yes.
Ah!
Sorry.
Oh my god.
That guy just pooped all over the place.
No wonder there's streaks on the ground.
Don't do it again.
Don't do it.
Do it!
No!
Penguin!
Please!
Is he laying down?
Okay, good.
He just laid down.
Primed and ready.
I wonder, there's streaks everywhere.
Just...
Penguins are gross.
They are.
Do it again.
I missed it.
Here I can wind...
I can wind the camera back.
Wait, I think I went back too far.
Whoa!
more up here.
Here, hold on.
Here, oh, there, there it is.
There you go.
Um, but unless you, it depends also on what you want to see
because when I went, it was, the penguins are still looking
for places to lay their, lay their eggs.
and start nesting and stuff but for um later in the season
you can see the eggs hatch and stuff so it really depends on
what you want you know you guys oh poops refuses to
elaborate sleeps that's the circle of life baby i missed you
singing live but i want it i wanted to say thank you for
singing I love your singing.
Thank you, Starfan.
Thank you so much.
Fixy, you walk on the bamboo ship.
I thought this was a wholesome stream.
It is, it is, it is.
Wholesome, wholesome, wholesome.
Good dog.
But, yeah, if you want a bigger boat, I was saying, bigger
boats will help with the seasickness during the Drake
Passage.
But a smaller boat, the more...
The bigger the boat, the less you can go out on to
Antarctica.
So...
Thank you, Murphy!
I was gonna ask, how long till she cries over animals being
cute?
I wasn't fast enough.
Why is it because I cried over the bird?
Stop judging me.
I just like animals, okay?
I think animals are very cute.
Is this still the beach?
Yes, come on.
Shrimp week.
Um, go back to the short camp.
Wow!
Um, but...
Thank you.
Choo!
Thank you!
Are you applying?
It's okay.
It's okay?
You mean implying?
Hey.
It's okay to drink men's bath water.
Um, that's what I was saying, though.
there's a number a limited number of people that can go that
can go out onto land at a time on in in antarctica so the
bigger the boat the less opportunities you'll have to go out
multiple times because they will be accommodating um they
will be accommodating more people to go out and usually like
the staff is like not so big of people going like people
leading people out
So, yeah, that's why it's probably better to take a smaller
boat.
Even if it's the Drake Passage, it's not as good.
I corrected myself.
I am judging and the judgment is that you cute.
Look here.
I don't need I don't need I don't need you guys always going
around and saying weird things and saying things that are
not real I don't know why I just said real
marriage I'm angry that I just said that
I'm angry I'm angry at the world right now.
Marriage.
Existence is hard.
I can't even say life is hard because I don't live.
I'm dead.
I can't even say life is hard.
After life is hard.
Words are hard.
Unlife is hard.
What was I saying?
Yeah, have a fun time in Antarctica.
Whenever you can go.
Whoever super chatted before about going with the wisps.
Actually, can I come?
Can I get an invite?
Because I just want to go back.
If you don't mind, I mean...
That's when I go back.
It's so awesome.
Yeah, just stuff me in your suitcase.
I can fit.
My ectoplasm is moldable.
You can follow in a rowboat.
She's only half joking.
It's true.
It's true Oh my gosh I just want to go back To Antarctica Go
by yourself I'm too scared Well now that I've Um Now that
I've I think the scariest part for me was Um Was Uh flying
By myself in countries I've never been before And I don't
know Spanish i was really nervous about you know argentina i
was like how am i supposed to get around if you go then 2
000 people will follow you we should just get our own boat
okay everybody we're all gonna we're all gonna book the same
trip at the same time okay and we're gonna share a dm for an
invite thanks thanks for the advice yeah of course let's all
book the same boat at the same time and we'll just uh it'll
be the whisper look at that shark wow well i'll just go in
the same one i would genuinely go oh that would be so fine
oh my god it would be the best trip ever i
Woo!
Giant trip to Antarctica.
Wow!
Oh my gosh, this flower!
Come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come
here, please!
come here.
I think that's the edge of the tank.
No, we tried.
Oh, we tried.
Oh, my gosh.
That was the best moment.
Finally, something I'm near to.
He was listening.
Mambo ship chartered cruise to Antarctica.
a win.
It's funny because I was even looking it up recently.
I was like, what if?
But, um, when I got my tickets, they were 50% off?
Or more?
I can't remember.
But they were definitely way cheaper than the price that
they were on the website when I looked, and I was like, ugh,
a little paid.
So, and i didn't even i didn't even write that trip off as a
tax it's like a as like a write off with a tax write off i
didn't even do that even though i guess it technically kind
of went for work but i just you know i misspelled mambuship
to relaxing yourself when getting burnt out during con
because i know relaxing myself by playing games at ace
combat during the convention oh during a convention i'll go
find like a panel and i just sit in the back and i just you
know even if it's not something i'm super interested in i'll
just kind of sometimes sometimes i become interested in it
so like how recently um like maybe a couple
Like maybe like two weeks ago.
How many days did I spend at Antarctica?
The Drake Passage is many days.
The Drake Passage was two and a half days.
And so I was...
So it was like five days on the Drake Passage.
If you count there and going back.
And then in Antarctica it was about...
Six or seven, I think six days.
I think.
Sometimes you just need to chill in the backseat of a panel.
Rest your legs.
I know.
Kawek!
Oh my gosh, thank you for the 50 gifted!
Thank you!
Wait, I hope I said your name right.
I'm really sorry if I didn't.
But thank you so much!
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you for the 50 gifted.
How seasick were you?
Not so bad.
I almost threw up once, but that was it.
And sometimes I would feel a little nauseous, but I would go
outside and the cool weather really helped me a lot.
I'm the organizer of that group of Wisps going to
Antarctica.
You are more than a welcome to join us.
Oh my gosh, you guys have like actually like a...
or that's so awesome oh my gosh i hope you guys have the
best time ever bring minto minto to go bring me into somehow
bring like my standy or plushie watching this gram stream
like this makes me want to go shout sakana just like that
episode of rico rico right
right i once i met The, um, who was it?
Hold on.
Uh.
Um.
What was the part, though?
What are those things called?
Sorry.
I'm trying to look them up.
The little, what are the little, the little bugs in the, not
bugs, the little fish?
Oh!
There he is again!
The fish that are like little tube worms.
Uh-uh.
Is there a jellyfish cam?
There is!
We can go back to it.
We were on it before.
This one's nice.
Yeah, that's the good stuff.
Here, I'm going to change the music even.
No, this one's too sad.
No, no.
I want something chill.
There we go.
Lamprey?
No, not eels.
They hide in the sand.
No, not.
a lamprey oh my god oh the little cute ones that are like
they go hide in the sand and then they come out i don't know
what they're called thanks for the fish
just great thanks for the vibe gifted chimp chimp oh no
they're really small And they like always are like together.
Garden eels?
Oh, I think so.
Yes, yes, yes.
The garden eels.
Thank you.
Yes, yes.
Um.
They, uh, when I, um, I met the voice actress from Liko
Rico, uh, Chica Anzai.
Um, and she voices, um, oh my gosh, my brain.
Chisato.
in Lico Rico and and she I was getting her autograph and she
asked me like she asked me about going to aquariums and
stuff and I was just like I was like I want to I want to go
or what did I say hold on I'm trying to think of this well
she asked me if I've ever seen the garden eels at an
aquarium before and I was like she asked me in Japanese
obviously and I was like not familiar with what they were
called in Japanese and I was like huh?
because we were talking in Japanese before I know!
Chidango!
Shouji asked me about the garden eels and I was like huh?
Wait what?
She's like have you ever seen them at an aquarium before?
And I was like, huh?
And then eventually the interpreter there, she was just
like, have you ever seen the garden eels?
The garden eels.
I was like, oh!
And I went, mmm, not!
And like, it was so funny, I guess, because of, like, how
much I was confused.
And then my reaction to her, to her, like, question, she,
like, bust out laughing.
And it was so cute.
And I was like, oh, oh, he, he, he, ha, ha, ha, woo, hoo.
And afterwards, my friends who were waiting for me were
like, why'd she laugh that much?
What did you say to make her laugh?
What's your secret, Mint?
It was so cute.
She got me, I was so cute.
Yeah.
Didn't they go to an aquarium in the anime?
Yeah, that's why we were talking about it.
So, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm.
actually I'm going to be right back is that okay if I go get
some water you guys go listen listen to the jellies listen
to the jellies I'll be like really fast because I'm just I'm
just getting some more water I'll be right back I
lied I lied I thought it would be quick but I was out of
water I have a I have a um a uh how do we describe it it's
um one of the I put water in and it keeps it warm all day
kind of hot water dispensers.
And I forgot to fill it up last time I used it.
And so it was out of water.
But I got a little bit of water.
Delicious water.
Murphy, does your bank ever call you concerned?
Thank you guys for all the super chats!
Murphy, thank you, thank you.
Hold on.
Raymac, thank you.
Murphy, thank you.
T-cup, nyan, nyan, thank you.
Gapul, thank you.
Raymac, thank you.
Murphy, thank you.
Fickney, thank you.
Kids, raptor, thank you.
Murphy, thank you.
Gliss, thank you.
Flyways, thank you.
Fickney, thank you.
Murphy, thank you.
Beater, thank you.
And Jacob's, thank you.
Wrong, forever.
Thank you.
Murphy, thank you.
No matter of fact, thank you.
Oh, thank you.
Fickney,
thank you.
Murphy, thank you.
Beater, thank you.
Wrong, we have it.
Thank you.
Shady Noctis.
Thank you, Murphy.
Thank you, KJRFJ.
Thank you, Pickney.
Thank you, Runkberry.
Thank you, Hard Underblade.
Thank you, Kenja.
Thank you, Xenofold.
Thank you, Stupid Shark.
Thank you, Karma Strikes.
Thank you, Tadokite.
Thank you, Beater Thickens.
Thank you, Murphy.
Thank you, AKS CF2.
Thank you, Pickney.
Thank you, Murphy.
Thank you.
VJ, thank you.
Again, oh my gosh.
Wait, there's so many!
Thank you, everybody.
Did you ever go to the fishes to ask for some water?
May I drink your bath water?
Hermocrates, thank you!
Yeah, I had to kind of wrap it.
Kind of a wrap god even.
I think.
A little bit.
They didn't get concerned when somebody bought a bunch of
laptops with my eBay.
Oh!
I'm sorry.
Baha blah waterfuds.
Thank you.
Thank you for the gift.
I think someone else gifted.
Dog water!
Thank you for the 20 gift.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Thank you guys.
What kind of hot water thingy?
Kind of want to get one again.
I know Zoji Rushi has one.
Right?
Uh...
Let me look it up.
Zoji...
Oops.
Okay.
New window.
Sochi, Lushi.
Thermos, I think it's called.
No, not the thermos.
Water boiler.
Yeah, yeah.
Are you going to play Ace Combat again after coming back
from Japan, right?
I'm late, by the way.
Either when I come back from Japan or in August.
One or the other because I just don't want to be interrupted
when I'm like...
You know?
If I'm playing...
Actually, no, I think I can do it when I come back from
Japan.
I think so.
A kindoo!
Thank you so much for the gift.
Thank you.
One of my friends is too embarrassed to ask you for a
birthday song, so ask for her!
Would you please wish...
Skel...
Skelivan!
Happy birthday!
Of course I can!
Skelivan!
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday to you Happy birthday to you Happy birthday
dear Skelerman Happy birthday to you Happy birthday Having a
Zojirushi water boiler changed my life It's seriously if you
drink a lot of hot water stuff like tea or...
Oh my god.
Thank you for the...
Sorry, I'm leaning into the...
I'm leaning into the screen.
Thank you for the bread!
Kawaguchi!
Thank you!
Yeah, if you drink a lot of like tea or hot water, stuff
involving hot water, like if you make coffee, I use it when
I'm making coffee.
Like, it is so awesome.
Zoji-dushi water boiler.
It's so good.
So good.
So, so handy.
And then it's also like, it just keeps warm all day.
Ah, it's awesome.
Um.
It's water fun.
Thank you.
I'm impressed by your pronunciation.
Almost no one gets my name right.
I thought it was like a Socrates, so I just, you know.
Looks like Streamlabs is behind.
I know they are.
They're coming through slowly, but surely.
I moved back out on my mom's list looking like it'll be a
while.
Might do it anyway.
When you had a roommate or parent while streaming, what
rules did you have?
That's a good question.
I never streamed when I lived with my parents.
As soon as I could leave, I did.
Shinselaer, thanks for the fun.
Thank you.
But with my roommates even, I think because I streamed in my
closet and it was um on the other side of the uh of the of
the house from my roommates they never really heard me so um
I didn't actually have any rules before even now though
I think uh I think because they also like stream a little
bit um We kind of just, like, understand that this is just
how it is.
So, the live jelly cam.
I know, right?
Isn't it awesome?
Streamer house.
Streamer house real.
Is the MGS episode coming before or after MGS con?
I think I have it on the schedule for...
Let's see.
What do I say?
I have it on the schedule for...
After MGSCon.
My school had an earthquake.
Oh, I hope you're okay.
Stay safe, stay safe.
Here's a list of play first by order.
4-5-0 for story, but you can play Air Combat and Ace Combat
2 as your first game, too, despite them not having a story.
Skip 3 if you want since it's set in the future.
Oh, thank you, none!
4-5-0.
Wait, I've heard to play 0 first, though.
This combat 4 is so good.
So much I want to play.
When will MGS...
When will Metal Gear Delta come out?
When will Konami contact me about the dates for Metal Gear
Delta?
Uh...
Elite Kaito!
Thanks for that, man.
Thank you.
I'd never play a Zero game first.
You know what?
That's fair.
fair the chance of playing Ace Combat 7 I would probably I
would like to play it I would like to actually I really want
to play that again I want to play Ace Combat 7 again and I
really want to play Metal Gear Rising again because I feel
like even though I've seen some stuff about like or rather
since Metal Gear Rising wasn't very long I can remember a
lot about it and kind of like like think back on some scenes
and be like oh now that i know the context for more stuff i
get it but i'm like but i'm like i i probably don't remember
everything so i want to
konami please sponsor i don't think i'm big enough i'm not
big enough i'm not in a company
a company too you're not always guaranteed stuff huh if i
haven't finished ace combat seven story dlc yes i still have
to play that too ah oh tomorrow tomorrow i think i want to
play um ghost trick so we'll have more of that and
yeah i don't know i still am trying to decide my i'm still
trying to decide my schedule for for the week still trying
to set my schedule for the week I don't know what I want to
do yet my brain is so
from this past weekend especially because I don't know I
sleep on a very specific pillow when I sleep at a hotel
pillow unless it's like the hotel pillows are just they're
like I don't know, my hotel, no, not my hotel.
My pillow is the perfect, I'm Goldilocks.
It's the perfect bit of hard and soft.
And the hotel pillows are either too hard or too soft.
So I'm just, gosh, it was so hard to sleep.
I also met Chica Anzaya at AWA last year.
She signed the back of my Chisato plushie.
Cute!
Her staff thought I wanted to sign on its pants too.
Hakina plushie, I had an ask why she got to wear boxers.
It's canon.
It is canon.
You're so right.
It doesn't hit the same when it's different.
The down ones are trash.
Down pillows?
Oh my gosh, they hurt my neck so bad.
Why are we still at the beach?
There's nothing here.
Let's see what else.
Let's go back to aviary cam.
Oh my god, look at them.
Oh my gosh, look at them.
Look at those little birds.
Walk.
Walk with your feet.
My Kamiyoshi minty locks and the three pillows.
Minty locks and the three pillows.
What kind of a pillow is it?
I think it's just like a memory foam or foam, kind of foam.
But it's like, has like one of those pillows that's like
indented in the certain parts.
And it makes you have a good support.
I need a, I need a nice hard pillow.
Are those sandpipers?
It says, oh my gosh, look at him go!
marvel at the long legs of our blackneck stilt or spot the
tiny western snowy plovers that blend into the sand I don't
know I don't think I've seen any of those I think they're
too busy blending in look for leg bands on our birds which
helps us identify them each bird has its own history most
came here injured and can't live in the wild they make firm
down pillows I don't think that's real.
Kelp Forest Cam is always refreshing.
I don't know!
That one like zooms like crazy.
That one is kind of insane.
That one is just like...
Enhance.
Over here.
It's dragging you everywhere.
Oh, look at that!
Oh, this looks like a nice area to live in.
I wish I were a bird.
Where's the kelp?
There we go.
Okay, you guys ready for whiplash?
I've been to this aquarium over a decade ago.
I don't remember much, but I remember Monterey Bay stinks
horribly.
Just the bay itself or the aquarium?
It's probably from all the bird shit everywhere.
Any zoo live cams?
I can check.
Let's see.
Wait!
Look at him!
He's spotted like a tiger!
Leopard seal!
I mean, not seal.
Leopard shark!
Sorry.
I got a little too excited.
Leopard shark!
Oh, they're so cute!
They're so cute!
Look at those spots.
Oh!
Wow, there's two of them.
There's fish.
How do they all co-exist?
Co-habitat.
I really welcome the membership.
Thank you.
The ocean stench.
Well, the algae.
The algae is probably what's making it so stinky.
Stinky algae.
It all, like, gathers up and then is, like, gunky.
A leopard seal would be a real fine.
Leopard seals, I think, are kind of ugly right aren't they
the ugly ones let's see yeah they're really ugly they're
actually whoa it's the parrot maybe parrotfish again i'm not
quite sure
spotted like a tiger you know what i meant i didn't mean to
say tiger i also didn't mean say leopard seal okay you guys
i'm tired let me give me a break
this isn't tantarctica anymore look when you think of a seal
is this ai generated okay i'm not going to use this it's
adobe stock and i can't tell when you think of a seal
you think you think hold on
you think cute you think like this right you think like oh
look at his little beady eyes look how sweet he is look how
cute look at him he's just a little guy if you've never seen
a leopard seal before I'm about to ruin your I'm about to
ruin your day
a leopard seal looks like this this is what a leopard seal
it's this this this they don't even look they look
prehistoric they looks insane do you know do you You know
that like scary stories, hold on, scary stories to tell in
the dark?
The girl, the girl, this one.
Sorry, the pale lady I think is what she called.
I'm about to show a scary image.
This one, that's what they look like to me.
That's what this, that's what, that's what the sea lion
looks like to me.
And then they're always covered in blood.
He's perfect.
He's cute though!
I don't know.
They look like...
They look like a...
They look so...
Prehistoric is all the old...
The only word that comes to my head.
Like, look at this!
Let's get rid of the lady.
Look at this!
That doesn't...
Does not look like a seal!
That looks like a monster!
That looks like a dinosaur!
Oh!
Mr. Knight, welcome to Mambushu!
That looks like a dinosaur right there!
Look so scary!
Their mouths are so scary because they have so many like you
think of a sea you think you think this we're just like oh
little baby seals look how sweet he is look how cute that
guy is and it's just like bam
leopard seals are so ugly okay this one's this one's
actually pretty cute this was that okay hold on this one
this one i'm about to show this one's pretty cute This one's
pretty cute, I think.
Elephant seals are the cutest.
Let's see.
No, they're not.
No, actually they're the worst.
I have seen the elephant seal.
They look like me when I take a selfie.
Leopard seals look like he goes whore.
Have you guys ever seen an elephant seal?
I'm about to ruin your day.
i'm about to ruin your day i'm gonna make you wish you'd
never seen this creature ever before i'm gonna make you
think i love elephants no i'm not gonna make you think that
i i personally mint phantom loves elephants but elephant
seals what the hell is this
what what were you thinking god when you create this thing
on Noah's Ark there were two of these and nobody complained
no one said oh maybe the elephant seal this one
is terrifying
You are so mean!
I love elephant seals.
It's so funny because male elephant seals and female
elephant seals are literally like video game characters you
know when like the girls are so like oh la la um so hot and
the guys they just are like they just have to be grotesque
like that's the male female she's so cute actually kind of
looks like a panda with those markings
But this one, this guy is kind of cute though.
This one's kind of cute.
He's cute.
He's looking.
He looks kind of happy.
He looks like he's got a little bit of a smile.
Okay, I'm going to show you something else really grotesque.
I'm going to make you wish that you've never seen it before.
I'm going to make you say, please, Minto, stop.
But it's out of our misery.
But it's out of our misery, misery.
Uh-oh, the misery.
We wanna be this guy's enemy!
Doesn't even have teeth.
Oh no, he's got two bottom teeth.
Looks like my grandpa actually.
I never saw an elephant seal.
I saw a leopard seal and I saw...
Oh gosh, what are they called?
Hold on.
Types of seals.
I can't remember the name.
Um... I saw...
leopard seal and I can't
remember I can't remember don't bully him I changed my mind
he's perfect you're just jealousy has a banging nose while
you have none how dare you how how dare you how dare you how
dare you How dare you?
How dare you?
I'll let you know.
That my nose could be as great as this, guys.
In fact.
I will.
You
won't catch me without a nose any longer.
You won't catch me without a nose.
any longer.
Oh!
Behold my nose.
It doesn't come off, no matter how much I shake it!
This is how I'm gonna look for the rest of my afterlife.
Thank you.
I hope you can't wait to see this picture every stream.
It's never going away.
This is every.
This is everything.
As I'm live in this kelp forest.
You still don't see it.
Oh, sorry.
Don't.
Does this help?
Who sent that?
What'd you say?
Minto China is my Saiko Ichiban, Japanese Ohime Sama.
Domo.
Bang her nose, mint.
Thank you.
That's the picture she chose.
Does the mouth open?
Does that mean her nostrils are constantly flared up?
No!
Um.
I don't know what that means.
It means I might have a infection.
It looks honestly...
It means I might have an infection in my nose, I think.
Oof.
The picture's worth a thousand words, yet zero nulls.
You can't say that, you guys.
Look.
It's literally right there.
My nose.
This is a rare idea.
see my neck is very long and my nose is right here
deviated septum myoshi is diseased it's okay I'll go to the
doctor and I'll recover you guys actually what if I told you
that this was like my real nose job what if I got a nose job
and i said this is it this is this is the new minto mintos
no mint minnos mint minos mint minos what have i told you
that this was it this was this was my new look forever i see
a pimple no no you don't we would love mint even if she was
an elephant seal where all my elephant CLV tubers rise up
rise up elephant CLV tubers I want to see long long noses I
want to see the longest noses I want to see noses that reach
the ground I want to see noses that touch the ground and
drag all over picking up every scent that could ever smell
on the ground I want you to be always I want you to be able
to throw your nose over your shoulder.
Does your nose hang low?
Does it wobble to and fro?
Can you tie it in a knot?
Can you tie it in a bow?
Oh, this was a ploy to get you to show nose.
Now it's mine.
Yoink.
Have you guys ever seen that guy that like goes into the
Florida Everglades and he's just like, hey guys, I'm back in
the Florida Everglades and I'm walking around I'm looking
for a 20-foot Python.
Oh, there's a frog.
Yoink.
Love watching his videos.
Does that mean Mint is now open to accepting husband
requests?
Whoa, what?
Huh?
Where did you get this idea from?
That guy is awesome.
I love that guy.
A nose like Ayami's chest.
Exactly.
he just grabs everything he does if you don't know what i'm
talking about i'm not quite sure about his username but um
he's some guy he goes to the florida everglades and
sometimes uh he went somewhere else too before but he's
usually in the florida everglades and he just walks around
barefoot his feet are like covered in flies and every bug
imaginable And he's just like, I'm out here in the Florida
Everglades.
Oh, there's a swamp puppy.
And he looks at the swamp puppy and it's a gator or a
crocodile.
I think the swamp gators or swamp puppies are the gators and
crocodiles are.
He calls a crocodile.
Yeah, he yoyings frogs, lizards, snakes, and pet gator.
He yoyings anything.
He's just like, oh, there's a snake.
Yoying.
And like the snake will be like...
his on his arm and he's just like this guy's chowing down on
me it's so funny i think if you probably search florida
everglades yoink i'm i'm almost positive he'll come up
florida everglades yoink yoink i think i think you'll find
him now you're a seal Seals collect husbands.
But I'm the male seal.
I've got the trunk.
Can I collect wives?
Wait, the female seals collect husbands?
Wow.
You would think?
I don't know.
Seals seem to be...
They just look like they would be territorial.
I don't know why.
The real Florida man.
Florida man that is the best way to call him high-level
Florida man yeah oh he boops the dangerous spiders too I
know he's he's just absolutely crazy he's wild but it's fine
I like watching his stuff especially because like he seems
so knowledgeable about each thing because because he'll,
like, see something and be like, oh, that's a blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
That's a Bebop McSpider-Doo.
Yoink.
And I'm like, whoa, how do you know that was a Bebop
McSpider-Doo?
Wow, you're so knowledgeable.
There was a man named Thomas Wedder slash Wad House who had
the longest nose of 7.5 inches long.
I'm looking this guy up.
Thomas Wedder.
Oh!
would mint tomato your nose nose best thank you
did I miss the otters we can go back to the otters one more
time otter cam oh let me get out of the way too wait all the
otters are gone there's no otters here there
are there they are there they are
Oh, they're gone.
Oh, I think I see one swimming under.
There he is.
Yeah, I thought I saw him.
Gonna get that purple ball.
He's just looping around.
He's like, loop, loop, loop.
Solid Marine.
Thanks so much.
Just woke up after getting hit with work today and seeing
the aquarium.
This is some peak as fuck content.
Can't wait to see how it off guys.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Show us?
Sorry guys, my chat is super duper delayed.
My chat is so delayed.
I'm gonna try refreshing YouTube.
Oh,
never mind, YouTube is stuck.
Refresh.
Oh, oh.
I lost chat!
You guys!
I don't know why Utah has been so bad lately for me.
I hope it's not like this for anyone else.
Because it just keeps like always freezing and stuff.
Bring us back.
I'm trying.
I'm looking at you through OBS.
There you go.
I think we're good.
Thank you, thank you!
Choo!
Oh, thanks, sideways!
Your thing finally came up.
You're seeing your streamlabs finally came up.
I think we're finally...
There's a couple more.
It's because it has 200 plus trackers.
It loads for ages.
Or, sorry, 100 plus trackers.
What's that mean?
100 plus trackers.
Me and Rick, get it!
Run while you can...
Tiara!
Do you want to fight me?
Spooker bottom right.
No!
I mean, I'm a little spooky.
I have to be spooky.
I have to be.
Someone asked about another zoo camp.
Let's see.
Zoo live camp.
Oh.
I'm showing you.
Now.
Panda!
Pandas!
Panda, panda, pandas!
Thank you for haunting us.
Yeah, you know, I'm just sucking your life force.
Panda babies.
Look at the little baby panda.
Look at them.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh, wait,
this is live cam highlights.
No, I want the real thing.
I want a real live cam.
I don't want highlights.
I want, I want to be there.
Oh my gosh, this is so cute though.
Even the cameraman was like, this is good, this is the good
stuff.
They're so cute!
I don't want live highlights though, I want the real thing.
Stop, I can't, it's so cute, okay.
Oh my goodness, oh my goodness, oh my goodness, oh my
goodness, oh my goodness, oh my goodness, oh my goodness.
goodness oh my goodness oh wait i think san diego zoo i've
seen these ones before too oh oh my god you guys we can
actually watch people there's a guy in the corner hey who
are you what are you pointing at what are you pointing at oh
get your picture don't drop your phone don't drop it in
there
who is this guy there they are there's the oh he was
pointing at the red pack Pandas.
Kmart, thank you.
The more you talk about Top Gun, the more you make me want
to buy the Top Gun Transformers crossover figure.
What is that?
I don't think you're getting the shot, buddy.
I think that Panda's gone.
I think that Red Panda's gone.
He's like, dang.
I couldn't even get the shot.
He's laughing.
He's like, yeah, yeah, I saw the panda.
Yeah, yeah, you know, it's more, I'm actually, it's more
orange than red, you know, but, um, it's behind the sticks.
No, I don't even see it over here.
I think it's gone, gone.
Show me the red pandas.
Hold on one second.
Sorry, I gotta make it disappear again.
See what live cams they have here.
You guys.
Tiger cam.
Wow.
Baboon cam.
Are those the baboons right there?
I think so.
Oh my god.
There's someone in the chat that is really upset about this.
Let me show you guys.
Look at the live chat.
No monkey.
Oh my gosh.
They should not go to the tiger cam.
They're going to lose their minds.
There's monkeys here.
Monkey in the bottom right.
Hold on.
I can entertain them.
Mute time.
Come to my stream.
Somebody help.
I've fallen in the monkey pit and I can't get out.
Oh my god.
I've lost all...
There's a bird next to me.
Oh my god.
I've lost all use of my legs.
Please, somebody help me out of the monkey cage.
Oh my god, I'm just a baby in the monkey cage, please.
Oh my god, oh my god.
I'm just, oh my god, I hope no monkeys come down here.
Oh no, oh my god.
I'm just, I'm just, I'm just in the, I'm a ghost in the
monkey.
What is that on the ground?
What is that right next to me?
a bird?
Is it a monkey?
I don't know.
The baboons don't want to do anything, though.
Mint, no!
It's happening again.
The baby's love dropped in the monkey cage!
They're going to let these balloons escape.
Handle it.
Okay.
I thought I could tempt them.
I thought I could tempt... Whoa.
Oh my god, I'm break dancing in the monkey cage!
Oh my god, I can't stop break dancing in the monkey cage!
Oh my god, please somebody, I just can't stop break dancing
in the monkey cage!
Oh my god, oh my god!
This is not good, this is not good.
Don't laugh, other way!
I...
Whoa!
My bad.
Okay.
I think we're good.
I
don't think these guys are gonna do anything.
Let's go to the live ape cam.
This is the experience I wanted.
No highlights.
Full disappointment.
I do want to go to the live cam and say there's nothing here
nothing here no monkey no monkey no monkey no monkey no
monkey no monkey no monkey no monkey no monkey no monkey no
monkey monkey these ones streamed a year ago these ones are
from a long time ago we could go into the past and see the
monkeys of the past giraffe cam oh my Wow!
Look at the birds walking!
Oh my god.
The bison.
Those are not bison.
What are these called?
I don't remember.
Haven't seen the new planet of the apes yet, but now I can't
help but imagine mint break dancing in the middle of it.
Where are the giraffes?
Okay, I'm gonna skip forward.
Giraffes?
There's a comet, the live chat.
It just says, why are they standing?
I don't know.
Also, why are they frozen in time?
Maybe that's what he meant.
Why are they frozen in time?
Why are they standing?
Gizels?
Is that what those are.
Rhino?
I didn't see any rhino.
Maybe I wasn't looking for them.
No monkey, no monkey, no monkey.
No tiger.
No nothing.
San Diego Zoo.
What's going on?
Oh, my goodness.
A little guy asleep.
Why are they standing there menacingly?
Pizza mozzarella.
Welcome to membership.
Thank you.
Red Panda.
We're watching Red Panda at 2 frames per second.
I love it.
144p.
Let's go.
Let's see.
What is it?
Actually.
It's 480p.
Thank you very much.
Stop motion panda.
It kind of hurts my eyes.
well guys i have one last thing i want to check before i
head out
one thing i want to check before i head out and that is that
is can we see fuji-san today let's find out
can we see fuji-san today please Please!
Um, I guess we can't see Fujisan today.
I thought I could reload it.
Ah.
No Fujisan today, unfortunately.
Let's see, if we go back to like when this...
Would it...
Oh!
This morning!
Oh my god!
Wow!
Wow, it was so beautiful.
Fujisan a couple hours ago.
Fujisan at the break of dawn.
Come on.
It's a little broken.
It's a little broken, that's okay.
That's okay.
There we go.
This is my favorite Fujisan cam to watch.
There's also another one that I really like, too.
But I feel like this one gets the best...
What's the word?
The best...
Good visual?
Good idea?
If it's...
If it's viewable?
I don't see the other one, actually.
It's not that one.
It's one from a street.
From a highway.
I also like looking at this one, too.
Wow!
Oh my god.
I actually have a recording from this one because it was so
pretty one morning.
I'm gonna cry.
Yeah, best perspective.
There's another one though that's from the road that I
really like a lot too.
Like it's from, you can see a highway and you can see kind
of the lakes and everything too.
So it's really nice.
This one's so nice too though.
Wow, all these normies out taking pictures.
Look at all the couples.
Holy cow.
Couple, couple, maybe couple, couple.
Wow.
Oh yeah, wait.
They're getting a picture?
I don't know.
Gross couples.
This is why this one's not so great.
But if you go back in time when there's nobody,
load.
YouTube is giving me such trouble all the time.
I wasn't recording.
It looks like it came from the 90s.
That's true.
does look like it can the quality on it is so bad it says
wow there's a 4k no way
no way this is for this is it in 4k this is it this is fuji
sign in 4k
oh it doesn't even load oh my goodness doesn't even load
Anyway.
Well, we kind of saw Fujisan today, so that's a win in my
book.
That is a win in my book, baby.
Give me a second.
Is broken.
It is broken.
Would you do an MGA Zatsu with other indie VTubers or some
who are possibly talking about doing it?
Oh yeah, I would totally, I've thought about doing something
like that before actually.
Yeah, I'd totally be down for it.
Oh, where am I?
Oh, here.
My bad.
Thank you for the chill stream.
Thank you, guys, for just hanging out with me.
Thanks for letting me just kind of be a little silly and
watch live cams and talk about anime central and kind of
whatever and whatever.
So, barbecue's still going.
Yeah, it's, you know, it's like a really heavy.
hit attraction at the maid cafe you know it was chill i'm
glad i'm glad that i hope you guys had fun um i hope you i
hope um my brain wasn't too silly for for um listening
because my brain tends to be so silly so um but hopefully it
was okay to listen to i'll try and get more sleep tonight I
lost his sleep last night, actually, but I think it's
just...
It was my first time getting a good amount of sleep in the
past couple of days, so...
It was perfect!
Stream was great.
Needed a chill stream like this today?
Thanks, silly mate.
Thank you!
Thanks, guys, for hanging out with me.
I really appreciate it.
Thank you.
I still can't believe there's so many people that will
just...
when it's sitting here and watch animal videos with me.
Makes me really happy.
So thank you.
Anyways, guys.
I'm going to head out.
And, um, yeah.
Thanks for hanging out with me.
And have a good night or day or whatever, whatever.
And I'll see you guys tomorrow probably.
I will probably, I will hopefully get a schedule out.
probably not tonight i think my brain is too dead tomorrow i
will hopefully get a schedule out for the week but
tomorrow's kind of busy for me um i'm gonna do my i'll do my
best i'm sorry for being so unprepared i'm sorry for being
so unprepared none thank you so there was uh paula thank you
for the dono mint plushie's doko
Ho ho, thank you.
Will large mint plushies be made in the future when I travel
with Minto one day?
But if it's too big, wouldn't it be difficult to travel
with?
Hmm.
David, thank you.
I miss Minto.
I wish chilling with Minto was real.
Nola, thank you.
So glad I got...
I'm so happy I got the chance to be there and see you at
Iyami's panel.
Thank you for being there.
special experience i'll never forget the day for the rest of
my life um and a great time at the con i hope you did too i
did thank you thank you thank you thanks for the 20 gifted
oh thank you thank you thank you for the stream can't wait
to see you off kai shout out to oemo for getting meet and
greet tickets to see you wait what i thought oemo said that
she couldn't get the meet and greet tickets Are you being a
me-in-person grump?
You're amazing company.
Love you lots.
Ah, thank you.
Nothing better than a chill stream with you after a tough
Monday at work.
Yeah, yeah.
Can't wait to meet you out.
I have kindly sleep well.
I also hope you had fun today.
Thank you!
They want to fight.
Fight, fight, fight, fight.
Fight, fight, fight, fight, fight.
Oh my gosh, fight in my meet and greet.
Fight in my meet and greet.
I don't know how this actually works, to be honest.
I don't know if everybody needs a meet and greet ticket.
But it did say that groups were allowed.
So, I'm not sure.
You might want to ask Off-Kai staff.
I don't know if one person needs a meet and greet ticket.
and they need the tickets, yeah?
Because I was like, if you have one person has a meet and
greet ticket and everybody just goes in together, then
you know?
But I just assume it means multiple ticket people can go in
at once.
Okay.
Well, that's all it.
Instead of a meet and greet, let's have a meet and fight.
Oh my god, M and F.
It's just like that game series.
I played as a child.
Meet and fight.
Okay.
Let's have a meet and fight.
Meet and beat?
Oh, wait.
Oh, we're workshopping the name a little bit.
Let's workshop the name a little bit.
Please do not come to Mintos expecting a meat and beef,
please.
Oh, wait.
I can do this right now.
I can do.
What am I looking for?
Oh.
Here.
You guys know what time it is.
It's the end of the stream time.
Oh, oh, oh.
The sound is off.
Yeah, baby.
There it.
Bad up.
Something strange.
Sleeping in your bed.
Oh, my gosh.
I want to go to sleep.
Let me tell you something.
If there's something weird, sleeping in your bed.
Ow!
Let me tell you something.
Bustin makes me feel good.
Bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin,
bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin,
bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin
Seeing things, sleeping in your bed.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
An invisible man, sleeping in your bed.
Let me tell you something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Bus stand, bus stand, bus stand, bus stand, bus stand, bus
stand, bus stand, bus stand, bus stand, bus stand.
Bus stand, bus stand.
Makes me feel good.
Feel good.
Feel good
Baby!
Ow!
If you're all alone, let me sleep in your bed.
Shoo!
Let me tell you something.
Sleeping makes me feel good!
I'm afraid no sleep.
I'm afraid no bed.
Except the ones in the hotels because they might have bed
bugs.
An invisible bed!
Freaky ghost bed!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Bye,
stay on, bye, stay on!
I'm stuck.
Feel good, feel good, feel good, feel good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Guys, we're watching today!
Hanging out with me, welcoming me back.
a couple days, but I really appreciate it.
Thanks for letting me watch animal videos on Tavito!
Bye-bye!