Go.
Thank you, Mario.
Ah!
Sorry.
I didn't think I would get so small.
Hello.
Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello.
Happy anniversary.
Thank you!
Fire Dragon.
Thank you.
Oh.
I'm nervous I'm nervous You would think that like You would
think that like If I have an anniversary That my first
anniversary that I have I'm celebrating Three years later
That I would Be more prepared I'm You would think that I
would be more prepared.
But I'm not.
Oh, gosh.
Cannon, Minty.
Hey, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's stop this now.
This slander.
Just hang out.
I have a few things.
Um...
Some...
Uh...
Plans, I suppose.
Anyway, welcome everybody to my not birthday.
Oh!
Okay.
To my not birthday.
I'll never have a birthday.
I'll have a death day.
Thank you for...
Thank you guys for all the gift and memberships.
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
Kept us waiting, huh?
Truly.
Um, yeah.
Any plans for anime, NYC?
I can neither confirm nor deny anything.
And Drago, thank you!
Oh my gosh, Pyrobug, thank you for the 50 gifts, and thank
you!
Holy cow.
Oh my gosh, thank you for the Hakusuba Flux!
Thank you!
Happy anniversary!
Oh my god, I'm back!
Thank you
so much!
Thank you!
Oh my god, happy anniversary, thank you!
Ah, thank you guys so much, thank you!
I just started!
I just started the stream!
Um...
On this day...
On this day, uh...
On this day, um...
Uh...
Four years ago?
On this day, four years ago, I streamed for the first time
ever in my afterlife.
Oh my god, it's fake.
Ah!
Kept this waiting for a while.
Katsu, thank you for the 50.
Thank you guys for all the gifts and memberships.
and all the super chats!
I'm getting a little overwhelmed.
But, um, yeah.
I never, I had never streamed before.
And...
Why is...
YouTube broken?
Wait, hold on.
I think YouTube has been broken for a bit.
I think it's been broken.
But, it says I have so many viewers, but I don't think
that's the case.
Because I have so many viewers, but I don't think that's the
case.
I don't think so.
I'm seeing 20...
Yeah, that's too many, I think.
That's... I don't think that's normal.
I think that's actually broken.
I don't think it's that many.
I think it's being weird.
I think after the cloud strife, it's broken.
I think so.
It's not...
It is broken!
It's...
Anyway.
Um...
Welcome.
I'm watching on three devices.
Stop.
Oh my gosh.
If anything, it's too little.
No!
I don't want it to be that much.
It's too much.
No, I feel much more comfortable if it's just a normal, you
know.
If it's just a normal mouse.
Oh god, I have 50 tabs open.
Well, for everybody who's real.
If you're here, sorry my voice is a little hoarse.
Sploogoon, thank you for this peek.
Thank you so much.
yeah oh no my account's gonna get banned I'm real I'm real
yeah my voice is a little hoarse because I was I went to a
event this weekend you know well you ever unprivate your
first ever VOD I don't think I'm I don't know you guys even
want to hear that um I, uh, uh, what's the word?
I will be watching it.
Uh, I will be watching it.
Oh gosh, I'm nervous though.
Um, I don't want today's stream to be super duper long.
Jay, Korko, thank you for the 50!
Totally not a bot.
On private your intro video.
You're telling me I'm not real?
Oh gosh, I'm really nervous though.
So today I have a few things to...
I don't want to say announce.
Maybe to announce briefly.
To briefly to exclaim.
I have things I want to...
Speak?
To scream?
Just to bite.
Announce to announce.
Basically, I will say something and be like, tease.
Tease is a good way, right?
I think tease is a tease.
I have things I would like to tickle you a little bit with.
But I don't have so much.
But after we watch some of my old...
stuff after we watch some of my old stuff then I will I will
I will announce that and then I might do like a little bit
of VR and stuff like that but it is it's so crazy that I'm
it's my first ever anniversary celebration so Uh, yes.
Um...
And then I also have a little bit of a giveaway, which I'm
not sure how to do yet, because I literally received the
stuff today.
And I'm like, uh...
I don't know how to distribute it yet.
But, um...
Uh, I was given some stuff to...
give out today maybe i'll figure out a way we can maybe we
can brainstorm together as a as a group you know
fulton it well it's not physical so i can kind of just you
know um but yeah uh we'll figure out something some some
something oh gosh oh gosh i'm so I'm so nervous!
But, um...
Ah!
Shall we just start?
Should we just rip off the band-aid?
Again, I feel so unprepared.
I feel so unprepared.
Yeah, go ahead.
I'm so nervous!
I...
oh let's see i'm going to my videos actually let's start
with my first ever uploaded video right my intro video which
who who asked me to unprivate this oh my gosh
okay i'm so nervous i don't remember i kind of remember my
intro video because you know i took some good amount of time
like editing it and everything like that but for my first
ever stream i don't remember that at all like i remember
well i say at all i remember having like nothing and it
being it being kind of dumb so okay hold on we're gonna do
this and we're gonna make me small i want to see the cringe
oh and also to continue the cringe I have a heart rate
monitor on.
Here, I'll put it down here.
I have a heart rate monitor for when things are too strong.
How does a ghost use a heart rate monitor?
Don't ask.
Wait, is this...
Hold on.
It's a little...
There we go, okay.
Oh, God!
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
It's like an EMF reader.
True, true, true, true.
True, true, true.
Oh my gosh.
Fuck.
Fasundo!
I hope I said that right.
Thank you for the birthday, Captain!
Thank you.
Happy anniversary, boss.
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you.
A cringe detector, probably.
And then we'll kind of, you know, there might be a surprise
something or other later for those who have not seen this
behind me.
Okay, oh my gosh, I'm so nervous.
Oh gosh, oh gosh, oh gosh, okay.
Let's all watch together.
I'm gonna put my glasses on though like you know how when
there's like a roast people wear glasses so they don't seem
like affected.
That's me right now.
Oh innocent.
Thank you.
Is that innocent by standard?
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
I'm ready for cringing.
Sorry about that.
If you heard that that was OBS just stuttering for a second.
If you heard OBS stuttering I'm so sorry.
I don't know, everything's wrong with either me or YouTube
or what.
Okay, are we ready to cringe?
Oh, God.
Are we ready to cringe?
Okay, okay.
Happy month's anniversary.
Thank you.
So this was uploaded four years ago.
July 18th.
July 18th, 2020.
I liked my own video.
I just, you know what?
Self-love, maybe.
I just saw it.
Oh my gosh.
July 18th, 2020.
So long ago.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Oh gosh.
You can see my, it's like telling me my next dream is me.
Okay, okay.
Oh my gosh.
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm, okay.
Three, two, one!
Wait, it's too loud!
Hi, hello, my name is Mint Phantom.
My name is Mint Phantom.
Welcome to my channel!
Yeah, woohoo!
Why is there no thing, no audio?
So my name is Mint, I'm Forever 19.
I'm Forever 19!
I'm the eternal maid.
Yippee!
So just to introduce myself, since I'm new, some things that
I really like are...
Anime, horror, bubble tea.
Oh yeah.
Most of all, most of all, most of all.
Most of all.
Oh god.
Maids and cute girls.
What?
I sound like I need to clear my throat.
Ramen and almond rice.
Uh, but I really dislike Masago and anything spicy.
Nobody cares!
I just can't have it.
I'll, I'll die.
I'll, I'll die again.
Again.
I'll die.
So when I'm not haunting a maid cafe, I really like to watch
idols and anime.
An I.O.
group I love in particular is Niji no Kankakee.
Yeah, Niji Kahan!
Go watch their music videos.
I got a little freaky there.
Oh!
Wow, I still like those.
Basically.
The episode of Detective Conan.
Main Dante Conan.
Ghost, you just have so much free time on your hands.
So I've never really...
What does that mean?
Video games or speaking.
So I thought...
Why are her hands like that?
Becoming a V-Tuber would help motivate me to get better
about it.
That's how I improved everybody.
You know, talk to more people because I'm very, I'm very
shy.
Like, think...
Think Boo from Mario.
Okay, so shy.
That's me.
Don't look at me.
Look at me.
I want to play a lot of horror games, even though they
really, really do scare me.
I'm gonna do my things to me.
Don't say limp-wisted.
I think maybe if everyone's there.
watching with me it won't be so scary i'll try to be brave
yeah i think my japanese is okay it's okay i think i've
regressed a little bit oh no i don't want to hear that
um pre-mgms
with practice please be patient with me i'm a ghost i'm a
full-time haunting oh my full-time haunting it may take me
some time to get used to everything but i look forward to
talking with all of you why i really want to collab with all
the other vtuber cute girls i do hope that i can learn a lot
though and also collaborate with other vtubers and i hope
you're looking forward to my content so thank you so much
for watching and i hope you'll follow me on twitter and
subscribe to my channel for future videos and yeah thanks
for watching thanks for watching i don't really know what
else to say so
have i changed okay bye have i changed it all
i seem so shy i seem so baby i'm just like
My mic changed for sure, definitely.
I just peaked at 116 when the bikini showed up.
She used to be so cute.
What the?
I'm still kind of cute.
It sounds more relaxed now than she was back then.
I remember recording this in my closet.
I used to have to stream in my closet.
And I do remember recording this.
I, I, I, I don't even, I was so nervous, you know, I was
like, I never made a video like this before, so I was, I
didn't even know, I don't even know, Mata loves me, Mata,
before Zanzibar, is Mata here, hello, oh, Roach Bomb Red,
hello, hello hello oh man that wasn't so bad there were some
things I remembered the don't look at me and look at me it
was like kind of an inside joke between me and some friends
so so that's why I remember it because I would just be like
basically I would say like for my waifu and stuff I would be
like don't look at her because she's my waifu but then I'd
be like look at her because you know I want everybody to
look at how cute my waifu is.
So I'd say, don't look at me.
Look at me.
Don't look at her.
Look at her.
So that's where that kind of came from.
And then let's see.
This part is so awkward.
I think I was truly just too lazy to edit in any sound
effects at that moment.
things that why did i make a list of my likes but i didn't
make a list of my dislikes i only said it thank you for the
50 thank you push up push up and um but i still like idols i
still like anime i still like core i still like bubble tea i
still like my things i think everything is the same only oh
i left a space here i left a space here for metal gear
New donut alert?
Pusha!
Maybe.
It's a good one actually.
I'll write that down.
Pusha!
Um...
But yeah.
There's a room here for Metal Gear.
It was foretold.
Hold on.
I can even add it.
I can add it right now.
I'm rewriting a history.
Med...
Gear.
What's this font that I used?
Oh, this was on my laptop.
I don't think I have it anymore.
Oh, no.
It was on my laptop.
I don't think I have it anymore.
Wait.
Maybe?
Oh!
No, it's...
Close enough.
It looks pretty close.
I wonder if it's the, wait, it looks a little, it looks a
little bolded.
Galaxy, thank you so much.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Wait.
Maru?
Normal.
Oh, it looks the same to me.
I've rewritten history.
Let's see what else was here.
Have you guys seen it here?
I'll show you the, I'll show you what the, oh, this, the
quick here.
Let's watch it in slow.
so we can get that that i also uploaded this at 720p if
you're like oh she looks a little fuzzy yeah because i'm an
idiot and it's at 720p so this is nizino conquistador their
idol group and i still like them very much but let's go to
that 0.25 playback
Oh my god, I even missed it so...
Go watch their music...
Yeah, you should go watch their music video.
Shit doesn't sound so good.
You should go watch their music video.
Mm-hmm.
Music videos.
And...
...
Zero Infinite, thank you so much for the-
Oh my goodness, let's see, what else did I talk about in
here?
Zombieland saw gun, Rizero, I still very much like both of
those, and then I talk about Conan too, but I have not
watched.
I'm behind.
I'm behind on my Tante Conan.
behind actually i'm way way way behind what is this oh so i
thought calendar i'm very shy i think that's still the same
i want to play horror games but i'm scared and then i talk
in japanese nihongo um
went mint brain goes thank you for the vibe good did you've
gotten better with your shyness you think so you think so oh
thanks so much for watching and then it goes oh my gosh the
next part is the one i'm really scared about shady thank you
for the akasupa can't wait to see next year's anniversary
where you react react to your react to your intro video no
this is the part that i we're going into into territory that
i do not remember this is my it'll be my first ever ever
stream.
We're not going to watch all of it, but
we will watch something.
Hold on, I have to scroll all the way to the end.
There we go.
The first.
Oh my gosh.
I don't remember anything that happens in this.
Okay, hold on.
The dad The first Waku Waku Moe Moe High Tension Hashtag
Minto Live High-Sin The first ever The first ever, ever,
ever And that's the date 724, 630 p.m.
EST Friday, Kinyobi Waku Waku Moe Moe High Tension Minto
Live Stream Oh, I can't read the comments because they're
like for oh thank goodness i did not like my own live stream
but you can't see it on private videos which is kind of sad
um i don't know how this is so but also i think maybe i
should set the mood a little bit give me one second um give
me one second um i think i hear my computer Wait, where is
this?
Um, um, oh!
Here we go, here we go.
Here we go, here we go, here we go.
One second, oh wait, one second, one second, one second, one
second.
One second, one second, one second, one second, one second,
one second.
Oh my gosh.
What is wrong with me?
Why did I size it like this?
Are you kidding me?
Past Minto!
What's wrong with you?
Okay.
And then, um...
There we go.
I still have all my old graphics.
Isn't that kind of crazy?
I still have all of them here.
We'll get rid of the disc, too.
I keep basically everything.
I keep almost everything because I am a hoarder.
And a freak.
Maybe.
I still have almost, I think, all of my old...
like thumbnails even like this one i tried to do an eight
hour endurance stream this is the thumbnail right but it
kept look at that thank you for 3000 is what it says but
youtube did not like the booba part so i had to like i had
to censor it it's called eight hour thumbnail ffs Because I
was getting so frustrated at the fact that it was not
allowing me to use the thumbnail.
Let's see.
Here, we have 1,000 subs, Minto.
Thank you, everybody, for...
Why do I look like that?
It looks like I wasn't ready for the photo.
It looks like I'm not ready for the photo.
Let's see.
I have so much stuff.
Look, even in that you saw in the...
other thing my likes and my dislikes here it is it's the
graphic you blanked i blanked i still keep everything i'm
not even kidding i have every i think i have so much here of
everything here no way i know add metal gear to that one i
should i should um i have like almost all of my old
schedules let's see what i did here i'm just gonna put on
and bejimp since i'm talking a little bit before we get into
the um into the stream into my first ever hi i almost said
hi shin let's see what did i do on january 4th through
january 10th done i played slitherio and i played among us
and i finished aces attorney and then i did a game collab
look at this schedule i only would stream a couple days a
week because i did i mentioned it i had a full-time haunting
so let's see what did i do november 23rd done i played doom
i played doom for the first time and i played pacify with
maria And Phasmophobia.
And Among Us with Chat.
Nothing is Chase.
Oh my goodness.
Wonder when you finish Doom.
Yeah.
And I went through.
Let's see.
I had like special things too.
Like, like three.
3k subs, I did an Endurance stream.
And I did...
I don't remember playing Owl Oni.
I don't remember ever playing that game.
Did I actually play that?
Then I played Toho, Mountain of Faith.
I did Jackbox with the Fandom.
AKA you guys, the Wisps.
Getting over it.
Karaoke, Free Chat, Marshmallow.
Time to play again?
Toho mentioned.
so to who mentioned love toho so yeah oh my gosh you know
what's even crazier is I have like the files I have the PSDs
of these schedules as well so I could just totally redo them
if I ever wanted to isn't that so wild and then this was
before this was the schedule and I was debuting my, this,
how I look now.
So cute.
I played Sonic.
Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday.
Why don't I have Monday on here?
If I already have break and break, why don't I have Monday
on here?
Maybe I didn't, maybe I took Mondays off every time because
full time haunting plus, You know, I don't want to work on
Monday.
I don't want to go do Monday work and then also stream
Garfield rep.
Garfield rep, truly.
Six boxes look nice, too.
You think so?
I thought it was a little difficult to read.
Because, here, hold on.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you're probably right.
Right?
Yeah.
If it was seven boxes, that wouldn't make much sense.
So just having the six blocks, but it's hard to read, right?
Because you have to go, like you have to zigzag through it.
It's hard to read.
Doing it in the lines.
I don't know.
I always struggled with my schedules.
You played Sonic on Mario Day?
Wait, when did I play it?
When did I play it?
No way.
Oh my gosh, I'm such a hater.
Wait, eight, nine, ten, no, no.
I played it on the 11th.
I played it March 11th.
Eight, nine, ten, eleven.
Barely safe.
You got a horrible case of the Mondays.
It's true.
Saved.
I'm a tired.
Mario Day in Asia No, I streamed it the day after It would
have been Mario Day It would have been the day after Mario
Day In Asia
So close to being a certified Chris Pratt hater You're right
Alrighty guys, are we ready for this?
I'm not Why did I put, why did I lift my Oh guys i think i'm
just gonna oh guys oh guys thank you yours soup thank you
okay sorry if you can hear so much noise i think the fan is
going a little bit crazy but um and also my cat she keeps
jumping on my desk and ruining my cables rip the band-aid
off okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay i still use this
pgm i I didn't realize I used it for my starting screen as
well.
I didn't...
I didn't realize I used it for my starting screen as well.
I made this though, right?
I just was like, me, you're home.
I made my starting student screen.
Shoshou, o'machi kudasai.
Louder!
No!
Okay, I'm gonna skip.
Oh gosh, oh gosh, oh gosh, oh gosh, oh gosh, oh gosh.
Oh gosh, oh gosh, oh gosh, oh gosh, oh gosh.
Jerry, Gary, thanks for the video.
I look like I don't know where I am.
Why am I not saying anything?
Mint, say something!
Hello?
I can hear...
Do you guys hear that?
Do you guys hear the...
It's my laptop fan.
Oh my god.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
Oh, girly.
Yes, we can.
The stream.
That's moving so fast.
Ah, hello.
Hi, ho kaiina samase!
Ho kaiina samase!
Hi, hi!
Oh my god, it sounds so awful!
Hi, hello!
Oh, ho!
Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
It sounds so different.
There's so many people.
Oh my god.
It sounds okay.
It sounds, am I good?
It sounds like I'm on Xbox.
I'm alive, I'm alive, I'm here.
I'm not alive!
What are you talking about?
Minto!
I'm gonna skip um First donation Oh no Is my mic bad Oh no
I'm shaking Oh no Is my mic You guys is my mic bad Thank you
Thank you for coming Oh my gosh There's so many people I
think I think I don't remember how many people Who were
watching At the time Do you still have this mic?
I don't Because you know what this mic was It actually
actually was a headset and I oh there oh I I was gonna I was
going to buy the same headset that I had for this stream
right now to kind of recreate the moment but because of
everything that happened because of all the plane stuff um I
wasn't able to so you sound like you're in a cod lobby I
don't know but this was actually a headset I thought that
maybe I knew nothing about mics or anything like that so i
thought that maybe having a headset would be fine audio
quality but for what i don't remember what mic i use i think
i use like the at 2020 which i also still have for my uh and
like i use an interface for my intro video so uh i
don't like no names in this chat wait I recognize PhD
killers what does that mean there's still some people I
recognize people are already roasting my mic oh I'm sorry
I'm sorry here oh my god but probably nobody here in this
chat watches me or even knows about me anymore no
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I'm looking at the names.
She sounds so different.
I know, right?
It's kind of crazy.
Hello.
I don't, I...
I never thought about doing ASMR, honestly.
I don't know.
This is like this.
Okay.
You guys, this is my first...
This is my introduction to everybody.
This is my introduction stream.
Also, 200 people at my debut.
I had 200 people.
I'm nervous as heck.
I was there.
Los Aruru, gracias.
But 200 people watching me on my debut.
And it was so much.
It was so much.
My little ghost heart couldn't handle it.
And this is my first introduction.
I'm making a fool of myself, truly.
it uh uh seriously the mic sounds different from the trailer
i can't believe there's so many people in here the the mic
i'm using now is is a different mic from my video so i'm
sorry i sound so sad wait so apologetic back then now she
openly hates us wait wait no was that it was that a donation
No, no, no, no.
I kind of, the old donation sound is so nostalgic.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, was that a donation?
Was that a super chat?
Oh my gosh.
Toaster mic with some background- Alina, thank you so much
for the hookers over, thank you.
Wait, maybe that makes it a little spooky, right?
Right?
A dead mic?
I don't even know how to sound like this anymore.
There's so many people.
Oh, donation.
Oh, no, no, no.
So cute.
A little gift.
Got me.
No, no, don't, no, no, no.
Okay, I can't deal with this anymore.
Please continue forward.
Okay, so I know, I know I answered some, some marshmallows
and stuff.
Let's see what questions people asked of me.
This one was if I worked at the Scarlet Devil.
mansion.
Kawaii.
So, yes, I would work there.
Photos 0C7E1905852D417EBFFFA1BF01D686698.png.
The main mincer I ordered in mint color just showed up!
Oh my god!
Let's go.
I was given a four hour work commute this week and I've been
listening to the podcast during the drive so I wanted to say
thank you to you and Manta for saving my life.
Oh my gosh, Serval, stop.
But good luck with your drive and everything.
Four hour work commute.
That's insane.
Working at the STM.
That's for fairy maids though, not you.
Hey, I could.
This is soul.
Let's see what other questions.
Oh my gosh.
Okay.
Oh.
PC.
Okay.
Hello, Maidman.
Hi.
Congratulations on your day, girl.
Thank you.
I sound so quiet.
Where do you usually play games on?
Console or PC?
People are gonna listen to this.
You guys are gonna listen to this and be like, where'd she
go?
Only- What happened to her?
I recently got my gaming laptop.
What happened to her?
So, um, I didn't really play a lot of games on PC.
So I played more on console.
Is it quiet though?
Can you hear it?
Actually, probably better you can't.
So...
Oh my god, I can hear my laptop.
Oh, I see other people like Toho.
Yay!
Sakuya's gonna be jealous.
The breathing.
You've changed.
No!
I haven't changed!
Yeah.
Toho.
You can hear the fuzz, can you?
Wouldn't you want to work with Yu-Gi-Oh instead?
Maybe, but I think Yomu is just, I think if I were too close
to Yomu, I'd be, I'd die again, because she's so cute.
This mic makes me sound so strange.
My favorite Toho is Remelia Ojo-sama.
I don't know.
Kokasa, yeah.
How do I sound like that?
What's the game?
How do I sound?
UFO?
Yeah, yeah.
Right, yeah.
I sound like kind of like a valley girl.
My favorite game is Mountain of Faith.
How do I sound like this?
So, I would play on my Switch.
I play on my Switch.
And next.
You sound so cute back then.
I still sound cute, though, right?
How old are you?
I'm forever 19.
How tall are you?
Oh, I'm about 100.
Cinderella, thank you!
Thank you so much.
like almost five feet and do you like playing horror games
no but yes happy mid-anniversary thank you I'm kind of a
gamer is there someone you know in V-Tuber like my favorite
V-Tuber my favorite V-Tuber because I wonder who I answer
here favorite of all time is really difficult maybe I'm a
gamer are you a gamer?
Shiro-chan do you guys know Denno-Shoujo-Shiro
Denno-Shoujo-Shiro do you guys know Do you guys know Denno
Shoujo Shiro?
I watched, I actually, I think probably around this time I
watched a lot of her.
I think her also, uh, well, actually I don't remember when I
first started Himehina.
Yeah, the dolphin, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kaguya Luna, Shiro mentioned.
Wow.
Wait, I wonder if I mentioned anyone else.
Yeah, she's so cute.
She's so cute.
my emo or my notice just covering my face oh nope that's it
i don't talk about that anymore i don't talk about that
anymore how do i sound like this though so um my name is
mint phantom um hello wait
if people reincarnate after their passing if people
reincarinate after their passing try to be quiet if people
reincarnate after their passing and oh wait i forgot to say
there was something else oh thank you you go shizin sama
thank you and it's okay you didn't ask too much can you do
the breathy after their passing and those who still have a
will to live stay to be make your voice off what is your
grudge what is your grudge what is your what is your so i
actually I don't really remember much of before I was alive.
I remember.
But I'm saving that for another day.
Saving that for another day, baby.
So actually nothing.
I just remember that I, I, what's the word?
Oh my gosh, thank you!
I liked idols and I liked maids.
And so I just brought that with me.
Johnny, thank you so much for the gift.
But my grudge, my grudge, my grudge, from what I remember,
that I never took that one checky with my Oshi.
And so now I'll never be able to take the checky with my
Oshi.
This is too real.
Why you gotta be like that?
Why are people saying small?
Me?
Small.
no no no no no no no no I am not small I am ghost she's so
real hello if it's not a rude question to ask a lady to when
and how did you become a ghost she's so me the the question
everyone wants to know how did I become a ghost so I really
like I said I really don't much but I I do remember this
little I remember no stop saying small I am not small I am
NOT small no I am NOT small no I am NOT small stop saying
small
do oh do you guys know what a checky is a checky is is not
small just ghosts but but a checky A Cheki is a Polaroid
picture.
Stop saying small.
Very popular at maid cafes and idol concerts.
Yes.
Stop saying small.
How did I die?
How did I become a ghost?
So, you know, I have a regret with not being able to take
the Cheki with my idol.
And my idol, my very best idol, my Kamiyoshi.
My Kamiyoshi.
She announced her graduation.
And so I died of a broken heart.
But now I can go and haunt maid cafes and idol concerts.
And they don't really notice me.
But it's sad because I can't take checkies because of it.
So I get sad.
Old Minter.
What kind of a ghost am I?
What do you mean?
Old Minter.
Small.
Stop.
Just ghosts.
They're embarrassing me.
You're embarrassing me.
You are the one of the cutest ghosts that I am not scared
of.
As long as you don't haunt me.
I haunt you.
I don't know who you are, but I am going to haunt you now.
It's true.
I haunt, I haunt.
You can't stop it.
My question is, what made you decide to use ghost as an
inspiration for your avatar?
You can't stop it.
You can't stop the haunt.
One second.
That is... Wait.
I died because of a mint overdose.
Are you guys enjoying this watch along?
You know?
What's my favorite ice cream?
I am, there's so many things.
I really like ice cream, so maybe cookies and cream.
Yes!
It's true!
That's still the same.
Okay, next.
Next.
If you were to serve someone forever, who would- Thank you
for the Aqua Supra!
Oh, those are really hard.
First time I watched it was during an emergency, us with
Artemis.
Oh, wait.
I'm trying to think of, like, among us with Artemis.
It's been a hell of a ride getting your box.
Like, maids with them.
Thank you.
You know?
Thank you so much.
Because if they have maids with them, like, I get it better.
How do I sound like this?
Hello, everybody.
You may not know me, but I know you.
I always just have this, like, lead paint stair going on.
I just
She's got that lead paint stare going
Why her arms like that Could we get over this please Staring
into our soul I can wink I can kind of wink how does it feel
how does it feel to be basically back in 2021 to wait how
does it feel to be back in 2021 2020
now my hands are like this because i'm a ghost here i'll
show you guys my whole model um i'm not very you know these
are my shoes you know look at that i can't really move so
much because back look at my skirt barely like flows at all
my legs barely flow at all back then back then um you know
vtubers were stiff people we were stiff stiff as a board and
um I can barely move.
I'm so, so stiff.
Do before, after comparison.
Actually, how do I do that?
Hold on.
There is a way.
One second.
Hold on.
There's a thing I can do.
Actually, I think I can do this.
Maybe.
Uh...
Chat hold!
Crazy what four years can do to a VTuber.
I know, right?
But, um, let's see.
If I do this...
Um...
This?
Actually, give me one second.
I'm gonna disappear again.
Oh, wait.
Uh...
Never mind.
I don't need to disappear.
I can do this.
Okay.
I do this?
Wait, how do I do this?
Guys, I'm a little confused.
I don't know how things work, okay?
Let's just play the video while I figure it out.
Understanding of how they would treat their maids?
Thank you so much, Sumara style.
But...
I don't know who I would Who I would Sorry, I'm laughing I'm
reading your comments I do like I do like mint ice cream I
do, I do But cookies and cream No, my name is My name is
mint Don't change my name Don't change my name All I have
What did I change it to?
Cookies and cream Oh, no, I meant Subaru?
Would I serve Subaru?
I don't know.
I don't really like Subaru.
I like, maybe I'll serve Rem.
I'll serve Rem forever, because then she could understand
what it's like to have someone serve her.
Who loves her and appreciates her.
Dump her.
Yeah, Subaru does.
So true.
Stupid.
How dare he.
Yeah, I'm an idiot.
I cannot believe.
Have you seen her face?
Have you seen how cute she is.
Have you seen how cute she is?
So, we'll say Rem.
I'll serve Rem Ojo-sama forever.
Rem Ojo-sama?
My favorite drink?
Well, I said bubble tea.
But, um, specifically, specifically, specifically mango.
Mango green tea.
I really like it.
Oh, yeah!
I love mango green tea.
Gosh, who is this girl?
She's so based.
I died falling from a cliff because she died.
She was so small to grab the railings.
I'm not that small.
I'm really...
It's true, though.
Oh, not that small.
Thank you.
Hayato.
Gochishin-sama.
Thank you for coming.
Okay.
So favorite drink, mango, green tea.
I think I do it like this.
What are some of the things that scares you, Minto-san?
Ghosts.
True.
Well, ghost.
And also, actually, I don't want to...
that I'll just say bugs there's a specific kind of bug and
it's so silly so I won't say it wait I don't even know what
I'm talking about here oh did I see someone I wonder if it's
um I wonder if it's come so far some so so so I wonder if
it's a lady bugs because I am afraid of lady bugs have you
ever seen Yuna on The Haunted Hot Springs?
Yes, I have.
And I really love her.
Okay, I think I got it.
She's got a nice body.
So true.
So, let's, okay.
Double Minta!
Hi, hello, Minta-chan.
I want to ask, which country do you like slash want to
travel to?
Triple Minta!
A country that I want to travel to.
Oh my god.
I've never been to Europe.
So I want to travel all over here.
I still haven't been.
So, yeah, not I think.
I thought.
It sounds so different.
No bully.
No wonder you guys liked me before.
You guys liked me before.
Now you're just like...
Now you're like your voices too.
No...
Hold on.
How do I...
No bully.
No bully in the chat.
I don't feel like I can do it.
I don't feel like I could...
I think it's also the...
The mic too, right?
Probably...
You like my current voice?
You do?
It's okay.
Part of it is definitely the mic.
I wonder, let's see.
Okay, so I just answer questions this whole thing.
Oh my gosh!
Hold on.
What's going on here?
Afraid of ladybugs?
Poor Barry.
I know.
It's kind of funny that she's a ladybug because I am afraid
of them.
Okay, hold on.
Let's...
Let's do that.
Okay.
Play.
Oh.
She's side.
The mid chips.
The audio is...
The BGM is so much less.
louder than my voice, you know.
I'm so indecisive, I'm so indecisive.
Am I streaming from laptop?
Yes, yes, yes.
I think everybody does.
I think everybody knows.
Okay, we'll have an official name.
And then we'll have a fandom.
I was gonna say we'll have a dumb name.
It's iconic, never doubt yourself, my girlfriend.
It's a doggy dog world.
So true.
Let's see.
How did they know that I was streaming from my laptop?
Make a tweet, make a tweet.
Oh!
My arms!
I tweet.
Big busts.
Make a tweet, make a tweet.
I tweet.
Big busts.
Put your favorite.
Favorite.
And redacted dust.
They phased out of existence.
Oh, they come back, eventually.
Oh, but I haven't watched it.
Oh, and then I also have...
These guys, look.
I've only read the manga.
I've never watched the show.
So...
Hold on.
Don't hate me.
I don't know what I'm talking about.
Oh, look.
I think people used to call these fart clouds.
I have little...
Little ghost friends.
Go Shichin'Sama!
Kawaii no Yure.
Oh my gosh!
Go Shichin'Sama!
I know, right?
Thank you for that.
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you!
I had three whips at all times.
Four would have been maybe a little spookier, right?
But let's see.
Anything else that happens?
No.
Literally, that's it.
How does it end?
How do I end the stream?
Thank you so much for being with me.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Bye, bye, bye, bye.
Four, four, four, so spooky.
One last donation.
Ah, Fanero, Fanero, Go-Sijin-Sama.
Thank you so much.
Thank you!
Do you guys miss when I called you, Go-Sijin-Sama or
Ojo-Sama?
Bye, bye, bye, bye, bye.
Kind of like, say it just at the beginning.
Bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye.
Say no.
Oh, ah, ah, okay.
Okay, bye.
Oh.
Bye.
Three
seconds, just...
Oh, Adida.
No way.
Oh, gosh.
Okay, bye.
Oh, no.
Oh, my gosh.
Here, let's see if there's anything else, any other streams
and stuff.
I'm not going to go through, like, you know, a ton of them
or anything like that.
Oh, here, I'll get rid of them, I need to.
Wow, it's really like I'm just back in the day, baby.
One of the first, one of the thirst.
The first thing I played ever was Witch's House.
Witches, uh, um, Witches, uh, you know that, what's it
called, game?
The Pixel Game?
Pixel Game.
First.
Stop.
But what did I do for other streams?
to my very next stream the we'll do the witch's house how
did i end the stream though right first moi moi game stream
if you guys have noticed my um or maybe you haven't noticed
but my my uh my playlists are all kind of similar to how
they were back then so my playlists are like hold on i'm
pulling it up so i can remember too oh i have like moi
random hauntings of which this stream is in.
I have Mint's Moi Moi Gaming, Moi Membership Streams, I have
Moi Collab Streams, Moi Karaoke Streams, Moi Spirit Box
Sessions, you know, like, everything is so Moi Moi.
Yeah, everything is Moi Moi Moi.
Oh my gosh!
Wait, you can't see.
Wait, wait, wait.
The amount of likes on this one!
Oh, wait, that's why you can't see.
Not because I'm blocking it.
you can't see it one second small look at this look four
four four how spooky is that how spooky is that yeah okay
let's see so i started oh i
don't even have a starting screen i just jump right into it
baby And you can hear me breathing.
Can you guys see me?
Hello.
Why do I sound so sad?
And the breathing is...
This is the best overlay ever.
game is just clipping into my into my um my uh what's the
word logo just i don't know how this uh this what this chat
is i don't even know am i here am i here am i here
so oh at some point look is in here some ghosties come out
Just look.
Let's see.
I just want to know how I end the stream.
Do I have a close?
Do I have an...
I don't think so, you guys.
I think...
You guys, I think I just end the stream.
You guys, I think I just end the stream as I did before.
Yay!
What the...
What was that?
Oh!
Why was this?
What was...
Oh!
It's the other...
It's...
Otto played another Nielsen Sierra song.
Oh my god, it's so loud.
Why am I so...
low energy i feel so like oh okay we're gonna listen to
boston now okay boston boston boston boston oh no maybe i
have changed more than i thought that i have i was probably
nervous i think so too oh well work i was i i was tired from
being an oh well i was tired from being an office lady so I
was just sad.
I was just so sad.
I'm sorry, hold on, I'll move this too.
I don't know how high my heart rate has gotten.
But it's true though.
It's so true.
But I really liked streaming, so I just, you know, I did as
much as I could back then.
Atsumito!
I-N-F-P.
We did this on the podcast.
Wait, let me ask Mattel error.
What am I?
What?
L-L-M-N-O-P.
51 cards!
Thank you for the- What happened to my face?
What happened to my face?
How do I change it back?
How do I change it?
your back.
Wait.
What
the?
Oh, I fixed it.
I fixed it.
Past Minto is haunting us.
I don't know if you guys have ever seen it.
I think, hold on.
I think it's this.
Oh, wait.
I'll have to try later.
I'm not manifesting enough ghost power.
She's got such a thousand yards there.
It's true.
I'm just kind of...
I watched a video recently about...
Do you guys know the movie?
I've never watched it as a kid, but it's called The Indian
in the Cubbard.
And it's about this kid that gets like a little toy.
And he puts it in his cupboard and it comes to life.
But the kid always has this thousand yard stare.
He's just like...
Just like this.
I wish...
Wait, I wonder if I can make my min-toes look at each other.
Okay, Minto.
We're gonna, um, hold on.
Uh, one second.
We're gonna, we're gonna have you look at each other.
Minto's.
Oh!
You're over there.
Um, one second.
You come over here?
Hi, Minto!
Hello there, Minto!
How are you doing today?
I'm great.
Thank you, Minto.
Now kiss?
Self-love.
Thank you, Miss First!
Charlie is such an amazing person.
So glad to see you shining today.
Thank you, though.
Thank you.
Imagine putting an anime figure in the cupboard.
I know.
What, what?
okay if you could put one thing in the cupboard if you could
put one thing in the cupboard but only one only one thing
what would you put in your cupboard to turn into real what
would you put in your cupboard a Gundam minto no you don't
have that you don't have that a jar containing a ghost
whiskey what that doesn't make any sense
Minto standy Okay, I'm kind of a little freaked out The mint
is staring at me So we're just gonna We're gonna Fix it
There we go
Um, well I don't know what Um, I guess I thought it really
truly that I was like I haven't changed so much Since I
Since I was a When since like I first started streaming But
I've actually have changed so much way more than I ever
realized especially my voice like that's kind of crazy on
that I'm seeing if there's anything else that I've played or
done or whatever she's so different yeah I wonder let's see
like a oh I have a 4.44 sub karaoke stream let's see how my
singing is let's see oh gosh wait this might actually be
this might actually be unbearable hold on 4 4.44k subs.
You've gotten way more confident.
Okay, okay, okay.
Surely, this is three years ago.
Surely at this point I have a, an opening.
Oh, it's the one that I use now!
And a closing.
Okay, okay.
Alright, here we go.
My opening sound is just the joy sound.
Okay.
Where's the music?
You can't hear it?
Is it two songs?
Like that?
Yeah, it's like...
It's the joy sound music.
My birthday, coincidentally.
Happy birthday, Ethan!
Oh my goodness.
It's always something.
These are so funny.
Here, let's skip a little head.
What did I sing?
What did I sing back in the day?
I'm gonna skip here.
Why did I sing the
And then this is a Conan song, Nazo, and then Fanta.
Oh my god.
Wait, what's this one?
What is happening?
Why is it Legend of Zelda background?
Connect, part of your world Mario Pokemon Edition.
Oh wait.
What is this?
What is the background?
Oh my god!
Sweet Kune!
Bright young women Sick of swimming Ready to stand Oh
no.
Oh my gosh.
Mint of the past was so bright.
Brave, no reverb, nothing.
Just regular, regular...
Fake Nate, you're there!
There you are!
And Cosmo, you're there too!
Raw dog.
Stop!
Don't say that!
Ask for my questions and get some answers.
There you are!
What's the word?
But...
Oh
my gosh!
I feel like I've seen flossed around but maybe I'm
gaslighting myself.
Salute to the old heads.
Mewtwo.
Oh, let's see what else is here.
What's this one?
Oh my gosh, wait, did I actually sing Fancy Baby Doll?
This is uh, trancing pulse.
Maybe nothing has changed?
Maybe I need to learn new songs.
Maybe I need to learn new stuff in four years.
Yay!
Ike Nair Borderline was that old.
What are you talking about?
Ike Nair Borderline, I think, was a couple years even before
I debuted.
Sorry, OBS is being weird.
Sorry, sorry!
Okay.
I think, uh...
I think...
I don't know, is there anything else you guys want to see in
my old streams?
I think we got the idea, haven't we?
Oh, is this no relation?
I just recently put out a short of this song.
Show Yomawari?
What?
Like the end of Yomawari?
Okay, guys, this is when I first ever lost it.
Hold on.
This is when I first ever lost it on stream.
Wait, Yo-Mowari?
Three?
Yo-Mowari?
How many parts did it take me to beat this game?
I don't see anymore.
It must be three.
This one.
Moe-moe game stream.
But it wasn't very moe-moe, I think.
I think, actually, let's see.
I was fighting the final boss.
Hold on.
Did I beat it?
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Joshua, thank you!
Here we go.
First time I ever lost it.
Maybe here.
Oh.
Friendly video.
Is that okay?
Is that okay if this becomes my...
Whoa!
What happened to the quality?
There we go.
So from a walkthrough, it says to circle around the edge.
How long was I on this fight for?
A long time.
Oh gosh, this is giving...
This is just too relatable.
Oh my gosh.
I was on this fight.
Okay, started around 138 and I'm at 237!
So I've been on it for an hour.
This fight is actually super hard.
I wonder how well I would do now.
Ugh!
Okay.
Maybe I'll try to still be nice.
But if I let something slip, go man, go man, yeah.
Let's see.
When did I really start losing it?
I wish I could see the comments.
Same winter noises.
After this, I'm going to...
Oh yeah, after this, I'm going to announce some...
Oh my god.
Gurley, I'm going to announce some stuff.
What the mid-ception?
is like really is really dumb to that because they make
everyone conform what am i talking about children even if
you conform to children say your channel isn't for children
oh like obviously this game is not for children but if i
don't swear it's monetized what what sense does that make
you know oh i'm i'm yeah go off go off past mint oh no you
had it You had it!
And then I'm still fighting on my thumbnail.
Remember the thumbnail I told you about earlier?
That's what I was still fighting about.
They kept demonetizing my stream because of it.
If...
Don't whitelist my thumbnail.
Because there's no reason
for my thumbnail.
Happy late.
What do you mean late first anniversary?
Oh, I guess it is kind of late, right?
To be taken down.
Thank you!
Fight for the booba.
Now you get...
thumbnails that are even crazier, right?
I don't know how to juke them into to go out, you know?
I really... When do I start popping off though?
His pinky touched me.
It went, boink!
What am I talking about?
Boink!
But yeah!
I started with the bottom one, but the top one is the
hardest to get.
So, if I get it first...
Because I can like, they're not, because they camped up
there the most.
It's terrible.
It's true.
Pop off, girly.
Pop off.
Peculiar things are the gifted.
Anyway, yeah.
I think that's about everything, isn't it?
I think that's about everything.
Wow.
Look at it back in the day.
I don't think I need this heart rate monitor anymore.
Hopefully, I don't think it got so high.
Maybe I'm normal.
What you going to show the sleepy ASMR stream?
Is...
Is it AP ASMR stream?
Hmm?
50 Econite Borderlines?
Let's see.
Where is that even?
Oh, singing Econite Borderline 50 plus 1 times.
Um...
Oh...
Oh my gosh, wait.
I actually want to see this one too.
Wind boar.
No.
Uh, here.
There.
I become mikumo.
I become mintumo.
Oh my god, different opening.
Cosmo, isn't this the one you made?
Isn't this the one you made?
Let's see.
This could be bad.
I'm gonna be so bad.
Why is it bad?
Wait, why is it bad?
There, my hands are like this because I'm a ghost!
Ah, Paige, thank you!
Ah, Kofi, thank you!
Okay.
Thank you!
How
did I go to this one immediately?
Oh my God, Jeremy, there you are!
Spokane, there you are!
can tell too.
Blood loss!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Thank you.
Guys, this is how it used to sound like.
Have I improved in my singing a little bit?
Have I improved in my singing?
Or did I regret?
Actually, I feel like I've regressed quite.
Can you hit that note now?
Probably not right now.
Must be the new mic.
You peaked here.
I uh yeah I must have I've probably regressed since I'm so
sorry you peaked
wait voice acting stream practice stream at one hour 44
minutes snake what what wait what hold on what what do you
thought wait really how do you wait first of all how How do
you have that information?
Second of all, where is a voice acting stream?
Voice acting stream, voice acting stream, voice acting,
voice acting, voice acting practice stream?
For one hour 44 minutes?
I do snake?
You guys, there's something I need to share with you guys
that we need to bring back.
so there's a video that i really really love i still love it
to this day i think i oh gosh where did i have it saved i
just have to find where i saved it but basically it's like
it's about the eagle and i must show you guys for those who
don't know maybe those who were here back in the day
remember it a little bit but if you don't know where did i
save it though i don't remember oh no No, I found it like
the other day.
Is that under here?
No.
I'll show you guys.
I'll find it.
The eagle fly higher above the clouds exactly!
Oh, wait.
No, these are just random videos.
What are these?
What are they?
Oh, these are just random videos that I have.
Oh, I still have my intro video.
No way.
I still have my intro video.
in here i have a video of i think this is a video of peeka
me saying my name
i still have i have video look at this i have a screenshot
of peeka me when she modded me on her channel i can't get
rid of it it's my precious it's my precious my precious uh
um you know and then i have this screenshot as well of me
next to Pikami when we were playing Among Us together.
Oh my gosh, I know I had it though.
I know I had it.
I just can't find it.
Okay, I should have been more prepared.
I'm so sorry, you guys.
But I'll find it and I'll show you guys next time I find it.
I'll be like, look.
This is one of my favorite videos of all time.
But where did I have it?
Maybe.
Oh wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
wait wait wait wait we're waiting we're waiting and then
we're gonna watch
no i lot i don't think so no uh no dang it oh where did i
save this at hold hold i don't know where i saved it i i do
have it somewhere though as you can tell I save everything.
I keep everything.
I'm a little freaky like that.
So here I'm doing a snake impression.
Let's see.
Oh, Bashamien!
Is she okay?
I don't know what's going on.
I think I'm dying of laughter.
Or just dying.
Again.
Why am I laughing so much?
Wait.
I'm dying.
I think I'm actually crying.
It's higher.
Above the cloud.
Wait, okay, we're almost to 144.
What's that sound?
It's like a It's like a...
Good morning.
While this plays, I'll also look for it.
Oh, Jesus.
The timing.
We'll never know what's so funny.
Next.
I don't see it playing.
What is that?
Sorry in advance.
Can you please say in solid snakey?
Okay.
No way.
No.
Come on.
Come on, you can do this!
I hate, I hate that I'm gonna do it.
No, I don't hate this, I love this.
Hmm, Colonel.
I'm trying...
It's okay, you can do it me.
You can do it.
You can do it me from the past!
The prophecy is true.
Okay, okay.
Metal Gear has always been a part of me.
How did you know this?
This is your fault for saying anything was allowed, yes I
know.
How did you know that this was here in this, in this VOD?
How did you know this?
Hmm, Colonel, I'm trying to sneak around, but I'm dummy
thick.
Oh, God.
I can't even get through it.
That's so funny.
The sacred text.
I'm dummy thick, and the clap of my ass cheeks keeps
alerting the guards.
Hmm, Colonel, I'm trying to sneak around, but I'm dummy.
thick it was foretold in the scripts cojumbo does it again
cojumbo does it again free will is a myth
let's see uh there was this one i wanted to look at maybe
this is the last one that i do because i'm just kind of
curious it's an activator which i did an updated version
when i first came Oh, my goodness.
Please wait to be seated!
Let's see where we're here.
They have like...
Jonathan's!
This Jonathan's is not there anymore.
This Jonathan's isn't there anymore, I believe.
I really need to match that character.
A Goku haircut.
Goku haircut!
You could get a one...
Let's see what else is around.
Milish!
do that but it's oh wait is this it oh we can go back no
okay let's go back i feel like i'm sensing deja vu right now
march 2020 did it burn down no and they just changed the
look the place this is where we talk about akiba cia that
hotamoto grill also isn't there anymore i believe oh i know
this is oh honey on oh my god
Survival game?
What is this?
I think that's still there though.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, Akibo CIA is right there.
Akibo CIA is like right there, isn't it?
Oh wait, no, never mind.
Me meant to meet up at Akibo CIA.
Oh my god, I have made me up at Akibo CIA.
Oh my god!
The CIA.
The way to the Google person.
Oh my god!
It's not there anymore, unfortunately, but...
Oh, wow!
It's like some of the smaller things that I remember, you
know?
Perfect timing.
Anyways, this is fine.
This is a fun trip down memory lane.
I still am confused how you...
Oh my gosh, this stream is just called The Spy Animals Got
Me.
me.
Alaminto for anniversary.
Yeah, thank you, Sai.
Thank you.
The spy animals got me.
It's getting more and more unhinged.
And then um and then my review and then my announcement
reveal this of how i look now and then my karaoke plus
announcement i'm so sorry that's why i announced my
graduation and then i came back it's okay it's okay it's all
good i came back so um yeah we're here we're here now as a
family
So, I have some things I would like to announce.
Some of my...
Well, okay, so I'm still trying to figure out how to open up
the store.
And you'll see from the pictures as well that some of the
stuff is not completed as well.
but there is stuff perhaps that I will be selling in the
future merch merch merch merch and I will share with you
what the merch will be some of these will be on my own store
some of these will be in other locations and of course I
will spam everywhere where you will be able to get the stuff
as soon as it's available but I have three three things for
now yes and uh first if you were in my the membership stream
you will have seen jada oh jada mint plushie mint official
mint plushie that you can take and grab and go on the to go
everywhere.
Very throwable.
Yes, yes.
You can take it anywhere.
You can take all your fun pictures with it.
And all the cool things.
It's about 9 centimeters.
Very portable.
Very squeezable.
Yes, yes.
Yes.
And so here's the back.
One second.
Here's the back.
Look at that, look at that.
I was supposed to have a sample for that was being sent to
me today.
And I was going to like show you with my real hands.
But unfortunately, it didn't arrive in time.
So I believe the plushie will be on somebody else's site.
Of course, I will give you all the details.
But the person I've been working with has been so awesome.
I thought maybe it would be done in time for today to be
like like I would it would be in my like the inventory would
be in my possession but um actually the the vendor the
designer and everything they spent a really long time trying
to find someone that would do the gradient in my hair which
is really nice because um I like that part and so they
worked really hard to to um Here, I'll zoom.
I'll make it big again so you guys can see it.
It's so cute, isn't it?
It's so grabbable.
So, I hope you will grab your little mint and grab her and
shaker.
Yeah, grab her and shaker.
Oh, wait, hold on.
Actually, I'll put it like right here.
Ta-da!
So, I don't quite have a date for when all of these, first
as well they won't be like they won't be um like so you will
probably have to wait sometime before you get them i'm
really sorry but um but uh i i will get it to you eventually
and i don't i'm not quite sure of when the shop will open
when everything will be up as well but of course like i said
i'll post it on the community tab i'll post it on twitter
i'll have it on the menu it will be um everywhere that you
that i can post it so yeah eventually eventually um i'm
looking to ship wherever i can whatever um for the stuff
that i will be shipping out myself i planned to be doing
international um but again i'm working stuff out so so um
yes uh doing everything myself so you know antarctica let's
go um but yeah so plushy the next thing um this uh actually
i believe was announced right before stream but i have oh oh
my gosh the picture's human Oh, oh, oh, one second.
Ta-da!
An official mint happy!
Happy, happy, happy, happy!
Official mint happy.
Akiba is a custom made.
And the art is by Maru.
And it's got my signature down there.
And this, this will not be on my store, but it will be uh um
i uh also may be available at certain conventions like um if
the vendor will be at the convention as well so yeah the art
is really really cute i love the design i like how it's like
kind of spooky and and soft and the chocolate and the wisps
and everything they're so cute so and the little gravestones
everything i love i love it so much so yeah the tombstones
are unexpectedly metal so yeah that will be that will be uh
on sale eventually
um i don't think otaku tan will be i don't think it'll be
done in time for otaku tan unfortunately but um i would say
for mostly everything um within uh by i would say end of the
year which i know kind of early to be announcing oh wait let
me make this small as well too and then I know it's kind of
early to be announcing it and then being like oh yeah you'll
get it by the end of the year but you know merch stuff takes
a while to create and things like and things like that so I
appreciate your patience it's also my first time ever like
making merch so it's been it's been a very learning it's
been an it's been a learning curve for sure yeah the next
thing here I'm gonna move the monotives again put you over
here the next thing I have is a okay so this one you'll see
of course that it's not done it's still in the sketch phase
but um it is will be completed eventually but um oh gosh i'm
kind of nervous about this one i actually i censored i
didn't censor it i um since it's a sketch i didn't want and
the design's not final i kind of blurred it just a little
bit da-da
Mint Daki Makara!
As you can see.
O Nichan, Daki Makara!
The Daki Makara, you can see the side A and the side B.
And it's so funny because the artist is De-Yui.
And it's so blurred, we can't see the moles.
I can kind of see it.
Maybe you can't.
I can kind of see it, but they are there.
I had a different image of mine for the backside.
And the Yui was just like, I think we need to go beyond.
I was like, here, hold on.
I'm going to...
There we go.
So you can see me.
I'm embarrassed.
old mint she can stay behind me like a goat like she's
haunting me there we go there we go there we go um so um you
can thank Deiui for for the backside which I don't hate I
still think it's pretty cute but um she has a stand Jojo
Backside best side Any estimated pricing Is that I wish I
could tell you Unfortunately I don't have anything Set in
stone But once it gets closer To everything I will of course
Tell you guys Probably You know The ducky you know probably
be like normal daki rates and all so table no thank you for
the tangata thank you um but yeah so my own daki makura it's
a little it's a little spicy it's it's a little spicy but uh
Oh, I hope you guys will still like it.
The other stuff is wholesome, so you know.
The spice of life.
Mint is basically a spice.
It's so embarrassing showing off something like this.
And there were even versions that were like even spicier.
Than version C.
There were versions that I was like...
I don't think we can go this I don't think we can go this
far um there were
they're the pig I still remember finding your ace attorney
finale stream in the middle of the night three years ago oh
my gosh pog man thank you thank you so much thank you thank
you how about B and A A was the spy no B was the spiciest
I'm not gonna show you guys i'm not gonna show you guys
because then you'll be like this is what we could have had
i'm not gonna show you guys release the day you cut
she hates us show the director's cut
happy anniversary even though thank you thank you so much
notorious thank you it's like thank you thank you Booyah,
that's J.
Oh my gosh, I'm giving it the peer pressure right now.
Okay, hold on.
Hold on!
Hold!
Hold, hold!
I'll get it.
But I'm gonna hide because I'm embarrassed.
So...
I think my channel...
Oh gosh, okay.
Oh god.
the okay just to i'm just gonna
the comments are so funny that the ue wrote because this
just says emphasize ass oh gosh okay okay okay okay this is
not what it will be obviously but um This is one of the...
This is what they sent me.
And I was like, um...
I don't...
I don't know about this one, Chief.
Oh, gosh.
Okay, okay.
I'm disappearing.
Okay.
Okay, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Um...
Anyway.
anyway that was one of the sketches
too spicy for tv true way too spicy way too spicy and the
last thing that I have is um something that I think is kind
of fun because um I've been I've been so excited about this
maybe it's not the most exciting thing but I've been very
excited about it because um I don't see very many people
having merch like this.
So, and I think you guys will find it fun as well.
So a couple months ago, a company reached out to me, and the
Japanese company, and at first I was nervous about
responding.
I was just like, oh, I don't know, can I work with them
because, you know, the language barrier and working with
Japanese company, this and that.
But I kind of got over my fear and I was like, you know
what?
No, I will.
I will contact them.
And so I even hired a translator to work with me.
And we've been going back and forth.
And they've been so kind and so fun to talk to and work
with.
So it's not the most impressive thing making.
and it's maybe not what you guys think.
Wow, who's saying Tenga?
Where did this come from?
Huh?
No, it's wholesome!
Stop!
It's wholesome!
It's wholesome.
But, um, so, again, I think I'm, you know, maybe it's not so
impressive, like I said, but to me, it's been a lot of work
that I've been doing.
putting into into it so to me it feels a little bit more uh
special um but basically the um uh one second uh
um the the um the company is called mythical block and we've
been working together to create
You know how like there's like the Pokemon like little Legos
and things like that and so I thought I really like those
and I even have like a Neptunia one so when I got this offer
I was like this is so cute I can have my own and then you
will get the pieces and you get to assemble it you can have
your own little mint DIY project yeah yeah yeah like the
nano block so I thought I thought this was kind of like a
fun little fun little thing that you can also put together
it's it's quite small I think it's like three inches it's
like you know it's quite small so you can put it on your
desk you can put it on your bookshelf you know you can put
it wherever you wherever you want mm-hmm small small small
small so yeah how does it taste though like plastic probably
three inches in small yes it's versatile and it's portable
it's portable it's portable so yeah i was i've been really
excited about it um uh they they they were just like just
you know make sure you tell them that it'll be shipped out
in this amount of time and and so um uh i imagine i'll
probably get them around uh around um uh some end of oh
we're working on getting it shipped out to me all the pieces
um oh i also want to mention that um uh so for for the
little lego pieces the the mythical block one sorry i
probably shouldn't say lego because that's like that's like
copyrighted isn't it um it is going to be um limited
you know we can do multiple runs I'm not sure how much of
stuff will sell so so I'm just kind of seeing I'm testing
the waters to get an idea of what what what to expect but
yeah legally distinct block toy so yeah I hope you guys like
the stuff um the merch my first ever my first ever well i
guess if you don't count the um my first ever solo merch
launch because the patreon was with matara or not sorry the
patreon the podcast was with matara but it's my first ever
personal it's my first ever time like doing my own merch and
um and uh there's there's more coming in the future as well
so if you're just like I'm already I am in talks with
perhaps some other places as well so um uh but you know um
yes it's it's kind of there's some things that um I also
didn't want to I didn't want to um start off too much and
overwhelm myself me from three years ago would have been so
jealous we got Oh my gosh, paperbacks!
Thank you for the Aqua Supra!
Thanks for being here and being silly with us.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Um.
Oh.
Um, but yeah.
Take my money.
No!
Men from three years ago would die looking at that donkey.
I'm already dying, not gonna lie.
I'm kind of just like, maybe it's a little out of the way.
outside my comfort zone, but, um, but, uh,
but, uh, it's, you know, I'm not a freak phantom for
nothing, right?
Oh, there we go.
Not freak phantom for nothing.
But um, yeah, uh, this, like I said, the pre-orders for all
this stuff, um, probably will have pre-orders open, uh,
sometime next month.
And then the orders will be shipped out a few months from
then.
So I hope you guys don't mind me being slow.
And I appreciate your patience with everything.
And all that.
Official Freak Phantom Glasses win.
I appreciate you guys always being so patient with me and
everything.
How many plushies can I...
Hi.
People say that they're going to buy an amount, but they
don't actually...
They're just kidding.
You know?
So...
Um...
As for the plushies, I definitely think multiple runs will
be okay.
Um...
Hold on.
Uh...
Yeah.
So, um...
But, you know, if you...
If you...
I'm not kidding.
uh if you don't buy anything that's totally okay too you
know just being here watching is always more than enough um
just having your your support thank you oh spooky thank you
so much thank you guys thank you okay just tip two um and
yeah so of course i always i always uh appreciate just any
sort of support of you watching watching the God's donating
merch, whatever, whatever, whatever.
I'm buying a bigger jar.
Jason, thank you for the 10.
Thank you so much.
Don't give your money to me.
Give your money to Yu-chan.
What are you doing?
But, Yeah!
Uh...
I don't really know what else.
Sorry that I didn't have so much prepared.
Thank you too!
Thank you!
And, um...
I'm going to buy even more plushies than before.
No, please!
I don't know how much they're going to be.
Stop saying sorry.
Okay, I'm...
Sorry!
I'm sorry for saying sorry!
I'm gonna eat some food real quick because I'm starting to
get...
get a little hungry spite is powerful you know what that is
true that is true um i think i'm just mostly um uh i just
feel so uh okay hold on it's time to get sappy well i'm
gonna turn this sappy music on i already feel the tears
rising up in my i already feel my tears rising up rise of
the tears where's my music Wait.
Oh, here we go.
Ah-ah-ah-ah.
Uh, this one, maybe?
Oh.
Hold, mint.
Hold.
Hold!
I already, you know, I feel already so grateful
that Metal Tear Rising that you guys are here um and that
you guys are watching at all um
and that um that uh um it's been it's been uh I don't want
to say a tumultuous time basically I left and I came back
maybe somewhat different
but but to still have you know so many people here that are
even And still, um, sorry.
Um, still willing to give me a chance.
Um, uh, sorry.
It was just, it's been kind of a crazy year.
And so, I'm really happy that...
I could finally celebrate my anniversary, even though I'm
three years late.
And I'm sorry I couldn't celebrate it before.
And maybe there are people here that didn't watch me before.
So, um, now I'm glad that we could, um, uh, instead
celebrate it altogether.
Are those keys?
Are those keys to Metal Gear Solid?
No way, are you just...
Oh, thank you for reminding me.
I can't believe you just gave away keys for the game.
Uh...
YouTube recommended me one of your streams way back, but I
was a hater.
You were a hater!
That's okay.
That would be a hit or two.
You see cringe, cringe, cringe anime, girl.
Do wish I could have stayed a member all three years.
Why, how could I do that though?
How could I just have my memberships open for all that time?
But um.
Oh my gosh.
Tom!
Happy anniversary boss!
Thank you!
Oh my gosh, I used your thing for the stream!
I was like, you're your thing for VTube Studio!
I was like, oh my gosh, Tom developed this!
That's crazy!
Thank you!
I recently found the channel, but glad to found you, Min.
Love for Metal Gear is strong.
Frank Hunter.
Yeah.
Um...
Huh?
Tom.
Oh, I'm here to go see you again.
I'm really happy.
Really, thank you.
Thank you.
Even if you're like, I just came upon this stream and this
ghost seems kind of cool and kind of funky you know
appreciate that too and um i just uh i just uh i just i just
am so grateful that um you guys haven't given up on me and
um that uh i can keep haunting you guys for some time and uh
Maybe I should just say it.
I've kind of, I've been, I have been, I have been kind of
like, I mean, things have been slow because I, um, I have
been trying to decide what to do.
I've been trying to decide what to do with everything.
But I think, I think I've found my footing a little bit.
A little bit.
and even I will say this I will give a hint I will give a
hint even if my appearance changes just a little bit just a
little bit not too dramatic I hope that you guys will still
um still hint, hint phantom I hope you guys uh, will still
stick around but that's not for a while um surgery?
No I just uh I don't know I can't
I just can't really thank you guys enough 3.0 What's going
on?
I think you guys might like the change too a little bit.
Like I said, it's not a huge change.
Not a huge change.
You'll see when it happens.
BBL?
BBL convert?
I'm a newer fan.
Oh no, thank you, Jose.
Thank you.
2.5.
2.5, I think, is a good way to put it.
We're going to BBL.
That's my next thing.
I'm going to Brazil!
I still...
And I...
I guess I apologize.
so much because you know i feel that you guys have um you
guys have changed my afterlife you guys have changed my
whole world and um all i want for you guys is um is to you
know uh for you guys to um also receive you know in whatever
ways that i can give I feel like I'm just like, how is merch
any special because you're just spending money?
But I...
I just wish I could, um...
Give you guys, uh...
Give you guys back, like...
Fifty-fold.
Everything that, um...
You have done for me, so...
Yeah.
Get that, PBL!
And so even if, even, um...
My very sincere feelings?
Yeah, you do.
Yeah, I want to watch you cry.
Before I start streaming.
But yeah, so I never got to appreciate our time in the past
I'm glad to have another chance Thank you We have to pay you
back Tenfold, 500fold What are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
I always Sorry I always feel bad Because I just feel like
guys do so much for me and i can't ever i can't i can't ever
repay it like well enough i just
so that's why i'm always just like i'm sorry because i just
really i'm really so thankful i'm really so grateful for uh
you know being in this
Like, I feel like I'm just, I'm just the luckiest, I'm the
luckiest ghost ever, ever exist, ever to exist.
So, sorry, I'm such a crybaby today.
Like I said, it's been kind of a year.
And so, um.
It's been, it's been a year and even when I'm a little
lonely you guys never make me feel lonely so just kind of
like sometimes you're allowed to be a big shop What what I'm
a leaf mint is a leaf mint is not a tree Ugh.
Sap hours.
I'm not really good at them.
I, uh...
Expressing myself sometimes.
Especially because when I do, I turn into the puddle like
this.
You can repay us by getting an oil rig and starting a BMC!
Yeah!
We'll start a PMC.
I'm not a words guy, but you're a pretty cool ghost.
Oh, I'm a cool ghost.
We're diamond wisps.
You guys are always...
I think you guys make me laugh more than...
make you guys laugh.
Private Minto Company.
Yeah!
Mint Boss.
Private Maid Company!
Perfect!
Wait, what does this...
What does the... Oh, wait.
It's usually private military company, right?
Hunter to serve you, Boss?
No!
I'm the maid!
I'm serving you!
Oh, Contractor.
Contractor, that's what.
Yeah, yeah.
Thank you, Kuya.
Thank you guys for all the super chats.
Thank you so much.
Pervert made company.
Get out.
You know what?
Never mind.
I take it back.
But life's a little boring if you're not a pervert.
Isn't it true?
You gotta be a little perverted.
I think life is more fun now, eh?
So true, ghostly.
Do not scatter our ectoplasm to the heartless sea.
No, I'll eat it.
The fact that you're here with us celebrating now is better
than any merch money, goodbye.
But if you want to grab something, a reminder that virtual
vacation merch is now available online.
It's true, actually.
The fail you didn't go to.
Um, if you didn't go to, uh, virtual vacation, if you want
the, oh my god, stop, Luwu!
Stop!
Oh my gosh, thanks for the rainbow!
Oh my god!
I have the, um, Luwu made some, like, little keychains,
right?
Some mint keychains, and I still have the form.
I still have the model thing that you gave me.
And I'm like, how can I create my own mint army?
Mintification.
My little tiny mint army.
You always make my day, boss?
Thanks.
Thank you.
You guys always make my day, too.
I mean that.
Yeah.
Which is why I always, you know, I want you to be So happy
So healthy And I want you guys to have fun And if Um
If your days are bad You know You can always come to Minto
stream And have a good time I hope I hope Hopefully If I can
at least make you laugh just a little bit I
She doesn't hate us real.
Always remember.
Wait, always, always remember.
Happy Minto Day.
But, um...
I suck at words, but I think you're pretty good.
Those are the best words I could hear.
You're pretty good.
Oh my god, what is this one now?
What is this one?
Here's a sign of my affection.
Outer wilds meant a lot to me.
It means a lot to you too.
So for chat.
Outer wilds means so much to me.
Nah.
Sometimes chat is my ocean.
I like to give every super chat a like after reading.
That's so awesome.
I give that a like.
Wait.
It won't let me like it.
It won't let me like it normally, but it'll let me hard it.
um i do have some giveaways as well but i'm not sure how to
give them away um so you guys might know that i have a code
with uh gamer subs but today um they asked if i wanted some
codes oh my gosh airport ninja thank you for that so far um
they they said if i wanted some codes And basically they
gave me, they gave me, hold on, um, uh, uh, I thought it was
gonna be like, oh, here's a code for 40% off.
No, no, they gave me some crazy codes.
Um, I just don't know how to get rid of them.
They gave me five codes for $40, three codes for $60, and
one code for $100.
off and none of the codes expire yeah so um how do you do
giveaways on youtube i don't know so they actually they gave
some pretty awesome stuff that's crazy i know right so big
shout outs uh to via thank you and uh gamer subs oh thank
you so much for providing these codes i was so No, I thought
it was just going to be like by code, but different.
But no, they gave like real code codes.
So maybe what I will do is probably create like a Google
form and you can sign up because obviously I'm going to need
like some contact email or something for me to send you the
codes and I will do like I will pick somebody at random and
for each one
The Hunger Games Yeah So I don't know Do you guys want me to
do it now Or do you want me to Maybe I'll do it Maybe next
stream or something I can have the The form be up for a
certain amount of time Because I would want VOD watchers To
have an opportunity as well So I'll have the form up And Hmm
take your time to get it set up thank you thank you thank
you after stream yeah because maybe some people are
listening to the stream and they're they won't have time a
chance to enter or anything like that so i shouldn't be
laughing so hard magic do do chance
but um bodies deserve a chance of course make an
announcement also on twitter x and youtube member i will i
will i will i'll post it everywhere so so everybody gotta go
now thanks nine one year because i graduated on april 4th
and then i returned on april 4th so it's been one
non-consecutive year but overall four years four years it's
not about changing the world it's about doing our best to
make our world a bit better yeah it's about respecting the
will of others and believing in your own there's only one
mint but there's room for a lot of wisps thanks boss what if
instead of the hunger games it was the freaky games oh my
gosh what if we all got into and it was just pvp and last
one standing wine oh my gosh what if we crab game did what
if we what if we fall guys tournamented
pvp pervert versus pervert yeah yes marble game oh
There will be blood, blood, shed, shed, just for a code.
Hell yeah.
Freaky fall, guys.
Me, the biggest pervert, would.
Oh, but yeah, thank you guys for, you know, Minch may never
fulfill all of my wishes.
Yeah, maybe that's for the best, right?
um uh thank you guys you know so much for um sorry i start
getting emotional okay uh for for supporting a little ghost
like me and um uh should go with b after all thanks for
accepting me when i'm a little freaky when I'm a little shy
when I'm a little when I'm a little ghastly ghostly a little
little quirky um yeah um I hope you guys uh enjoy the rest
of your night I thought about maybe going into VR chat um I
think I've got to go eat instead.
Words hard.
Mint good.
Big heart.
Love forever.
Real freak too.
And all the donations as well.
I know they've been kind of backed up from the, uh, from all
the gifted memberships.
Um, I just saw a sneer that you said there's a kudo board.
Wait, am I an anniversary tag?
Oh my gosh.
Oh gosh, I think the viewer count just stabilized.
I think it's just stable.
Where is, oh, I was like, where is it?
It's here.
Hashtag mintiversary.
Wait, where do I?
Kudo board.
Oh.
Hmm?
Oh, I see it.
Thank you!
Maybe I'll look after stream in case people are still...
I don't know.
Can people still add it to that?
All the bots are gone.
I know.
YouTube's been really weird lately.
Thanks, Vitt.
You gave me so many laughs.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
I want to do this to Revengeance.
Get your games, everybody.
But if you have the games, don't tell.
take them from other people trying to see if i can find my
first chat the ace attorney vids were my favorite back in
the day i don't have any plans on unprivating the old vods
because you know i'm still kind of embarrassed by everything
with that but um i and also um you know i'm i want to make
memories with with old fans new fans um maybe if you somehow
if i haunted somehow in between when i left and when i came
back i would like to make all sorts of memories and uh with
everybody and have lots of things um you know lots of new
memories so kind of just like uh i'm not like not like
abandoning it not saying you know not saying it never
happened just kind of moving forward and uh
I'll be there no matter what.
Thank you!
Not even unprivating the debut stream.
I don't think we need the debut stream.
I think you saw pretty much everything that was the debut
stream.
Taco!
Thanks for the 50 Gifted.
Thank you guys so much for all the gifted.
If I miss you, I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
I am reading them as fast as they scroll by.
Free the debut stream.
Maybe I will free the intro video.
Plus pre-ordered.
Thank you.
I feel like I want to say more.
Maybe I should have written it down.
But I have too many feelings in my Kokoro in my heart.
Maybe it's better.
I would just cry if I read everything.
So here's to, hopefully, many more years.
And, um, I'll keep, I'll keep doing my best.
Yeah, I can't believe also it's been, I can't believe even
that it's been, It's been four years.
It's insane to me.
Oh, it's so crazy to me.
Sorry,
recently started watching and following you.
I look forward to all your streams or podcasts or whatever I
can make it.
Thank you.
Thanks for finding me.
I gotta find that video.
I gotta show you guys.
That's one thing from the past we can show that I'll find
and I will show it to you guys the eagle the eagle But with
that I think I will head out
You're gonna hate to thank you Yeah, we got a fight Till
days late wait, you're gonna see me at the oh did you you
guys see that um that the anime the anime fest that i'll be
at tomorrow in texas um that ayami sensei will have merch as
well if you're going to be there it's exclusive to the event
um let me see hold on ayami she sent it to me earlier she
sent it to me earlier she was just like she was like oh i
forgot to ask you sooner is it okay if i make merch I was
like, of course!
Let me see.
Hold on.
Anime Fresh.
This will be at the Sekai Project booth, I believe.
Which will have all of her merch as well if you're going.
But look how cute this is.
Look how cute this is.
Look at this.
Oh, sorry.
My face went whack again.
Oh,
oh, sorry.
My bad.
There we go.
Look at this!
Look how cute!
There's a print and an acrylic keychain featuring Ayami
Sensei and me!
Oh my gosh, it looks like a real ghost is haunting me right
now.
Uh, uh, how do I get rid of it?
Oh, oh, oh.
How, how, how do I change my face back to normal?
I'll change it back to normal!
I don't know.
I think I give up.
But anyway, isn't it so cute?
Isn't it so so cute?
We're cowgirls!
Yee!
Yee-how!
They're so cute.
And look, you guys are a cactus!
You guys are a cactus!
So cute.
So, so, so cute.
First time Ayami-sensei has drawn me as like a merch.
So, if I see you tomorrow at Anime Fest, I'll see you
tomorrow.
If not, then I'll see you at whatever event.
Or I'll see you when I stream.
I'm gonna get rid of this background.
Goodbye, background.
Goodbye.
Yeah.
It's kind of surreal seeing Mint 1.0 in this cafe.
Ooh.
It's so creepy.
Oh, okay.
Boston?
Boston, Boston, Boston, Boston, Boston, Boston.
Bustin!
Bustin, Bustin!
Busting.
Oh my god, loud.
And baby!
If there's something strange, sleeping in your bed.
How do I get rid of this face?
Let me tell you something.
If there's something weird, sleeping in your bed.
Ow!
Let me tell you something.
Bustin makes me feel...
Oh!
Yeah!
Bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin,
bustin, bustin, bustin.
Hold on.
Yeah!
If you're seeing things...
Sleeping in your bed.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
An invisible man.
Sleeping in your bed.
Ow!
Let me tell you something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Buster, buster, buster, buster, buster, buster, buster,
buster, buster.
Makes me feel good, feel good, feel good.
Yeah, I'll make a prettier graphic for once the stuff is,
you know.
Make a prettier graphic.
Eventually, you know.
Boosting, boosting, boosting, boosting, boosting, boosting
makes me feel good, feel good, feel good, feel good, feel
good, feel good, feel good, feel good, feel good, feel good,
feel good, feel good, feel good, feel good,
feel good, baby.
Ow!
Let me sleep in your bed.
Let me tell you something.
Sleeping makes me feel good!
I'm afraid of no sleep.
I'm afraid of no bed.
An invisible bed!
Freaking ghost bed!
A meeting.
Feel good, feel good.
What am I eating?
Fried rice.
Me, me, me, me.
Moku, moku, moku, moku.
Feel good, feel good, feel good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
KFP Ghostbusters.
Busting, busting, busting makes me feel good Feel good, feel
good, feel good, feel good Busting makes me yeah, yeah, yeah
Thank you guys Thank you guys for one year, four years Thank
you I'll keep doing my best I'll keep doing my best I'll
keep doing my best Thank you, thank you, thank you Thank
you, thank you, thank you
I'm gonna read the kudo board now I'm gonna read so thank
you guys thanks for whoever wrote in it thank you bye bye