Sorry I was late for the stream.
Sorry I was late.
I'm sorry that my... I don't know why the music was muted in
the beginning.
I have no idea.
That is so weird.
I don't know.
It took five extra minutes to grow a mustache.
No, it takes me like two seconds to grow a mustache.
It's like so easy.
I didn't touch anything either.
I don't know.
My audio has been kind of weird today.
A little bit weird.
I don't know.
Do you guys notice anything different about me?
Or like...
Anything...
anything interesting about me today?
Do you notice anything like peculiar?
Something that you're like, I don't remember that being
there before.
Do you notice anything?
My neck is longer?
No.
More ribbons?
New hair?
No.
New contacts?
tablet exactly and also oh my gosh sorry there's
construction outside if you hear i was like hoping that they
would stop before by now i was just like clearly surely it's
later in the day they're not going to do any more
construction but no they are doing all the construction and
they're being so loud about it and so i um sorry i was
waiting i was like waiting a little did but look at this you
guys look at this I have a phantom hand it's it's um it's
not my hand you know how in like the Adams family there's
that little hand that like does all the work so technically
I'm not drawing today it's our little hand friend yeah the
thing and Dracos thank you thank whoa you thanks and my hand
says thank you also that's so creepy I love it oh god
What are you saying?
Oh my god!
No!
Hand, no!
Stop, stop, stop.
Hold on.
Okay, write something nice, hand.
Write something nice.
Like, M for Minto?
You.
Mud?
Mermaid!
Oh no!
Oh my god!
No!
Stop it!
Stop it, Hans!
Oh my...
Red rub!
Is the Google Form submission already over?
It is!
As you can see in the pinned comment, it says that it would
two hours the deadline was two hours before stream so I'm so
sorry if we didn't make it this time but turn that frown
upside down because I'll do this again
someday yeah da minty da minty okay rocket R Domingue, turn
that frown upside down.
Upside down.
Domingue?
So, today I'll be drawing...
You!
I'll be drawing you!
Just like that!
Well, this hand will be...
drawing you but i'll be drawing your profile pictures um uh
just however i want to um i had a little google form rather
than um having like okay so okay i'm gonna be i'm gonna be
okay hold on hold on honesty is the best policy okay
everybody okay so hold on honest honest ghost I'm an honest
ghost okay hey I'm dragon thank you for the 10 gifts and
thank you um so usually like I feel like whenever people are
like I'm gonna draw your profile pictures this and that
whatever it's like you know you donate like you know you
donate a or something and and then um an x yeah you donate
no yeah x on this x on this um the rotund one they hear the
vibe gift and thank you um but um you know sometimes i think
um you know i think that's a little sad for other people
wanting to get profile pictures as well But also, we're
going to change the honest ghost to...
I become an overwhelmed ghost.
Because sometimes too many people send in...
You know what I'm saying?
And so, then I'm like, wait, wait, there's too many, I
can't...
I can't do all that.
And then I have this compounding guilt.
guilt guilt this is how my my guilt my my guilt because then
i'm just like oh my gosh there's way too many and i get
scared so today i can choose as many as i want to do my
guilt so i can be guilt free because i can say oh i feel
like doing one more today so um i get to choose and you win
hold on um how do you okay hold on that's a hand pointing at
you you you win you win because it's free yeah oh how many
souls were sacrificed for that hand also thank you so much
for singing love deterrence yesterday you have no idea how
long I waited for you to saying this, I've been jamming to
it, driving to and from work for a year.
Now I can switch it with yours.
Please don't do that.
Don't do that.
I feel like...
We win because it's time with you.
Aw.
Mint found a ghost rider?
Boudunch.
So how this is going to work is I had a Google form that
people would fill out and submit their usernames and um and
uh a request um i might i'll be honest i'm probably not
gonna remember what your pro or know what your profile
picture already is because as i see it they're like see this
is me and my big head like this oh my god there's
construction like that i look like that and then your
profile picture on youtube is like this and i'm like there
you you you right there you you look like a little fly
that's you so uh you can't see this i can't tell what you
are like what you're bro sometimes i can sometimes it's like
i'm like oh that's a car um oh that's that's uh you know
that's that vtuber or that's that character um but other
times i'm like i can't tell that's a cat i can see the cat
but um yeah other times i can't tell at all oh you guys you
guys i must tell you i must tell you um but oh before i tell
you um but yeah i have a whole list of people uh here we'll
spin the great wheel and it will land you have a one in
i'm still scrolling one in one thousand three hundred and
fifty four chance
It's better than gotcha odds, everybody.
So, um, yep, I'm on the screen.
That's your name.
Right there.
Maybe.
Probably.
But yeah, so I'll pick the wheel.
I'll pick someone from the wheel.
And that way it's very, it's fair, um, you know, and anybody
has a chance to get a profile picture.
I put in a little thing saying like, Hey, do you have a
request?
But, uh...
Nah, I'd win.
Uh, do you have a request?
And if it's just like, draw me like one of your French
ladies, then I can potentially do that.
Wait.
Who gifted five members?
Wait, unless that's old.
Oh, yeah, that's the rotund one.
Oh, but...
Ho, ho!
Thank you for the 10 gifted.
Thank you.
Sorry, I missed that one earlier.
This game makes you feel like being a fly.
What do you mean by that?
Come on, get the camera.
You're so small.
You are.
You're very cute.
Hold on.
You're so small and you're so cute.
Ooh, there's your blushing.
You're like, oh my gosh, I'm so small.
wheel it's all me um but i have a thing to tell you guys um
let me let me get it real quick first though uh hold on hold
on hold on hold on hold on one moment oh sorry that was very
loud even for me very apologies um oh i forgot to say i
forgot to greet you guys to the stream because i was so um i
was so flustered thank you you're using the color red to
write is really tempting for what um okay i have something
this is one thing to show um so i hold on actually hold on
can i save them both at the same time Oh no!
These are all individual!
Actually, I can just screenshot it.
Screenshot.
Hold on.
I should have prepared this before stream.
Real-time!
Thanks for the 10 gifted.
Temji!
Thanks for the 10 gifted!
Thank you guys so much.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Let's see.
Okay, hold on.
Okay, here we go.
I have more emotes!
This first batch is from Wealthy!
Yippee!
Hold on.
Sorry, I gotta erase you.
There we go.
Yeah!
More emotes!
And that's not all.
I have...
Even more emotes!
These ones are from Juno!
Yeah, I'll upload them after stream.
Yeah, we have lots more emotes.
Even more emotes.
hmm I asked I asked in members what kind of emotes you'd be
interested in and um some people were like oh I want a box
oh I want a clown and so oh I want a nerd oh I want I want
this I want a pen I okay I your wish is my command raymac
thinks of the five gifted so um I cry when I fire oh my gosh
are you okay welcome to membership we are so back again yeah
I thought they're I think they're very cute you have it you
have a bonk you have a prey you have a wink you have a think
you You have excite more.
You have a, oh my god, did she really just say there?
This isn't all the emotes.
This is just what I got for now.
But yeah.
You, you, welcome to membership.
Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
So, yeah.
I will upload these.
Soon.
as goes to thanks for the five memberships thank you thank
you thank you it's raining gifts oh my god i know right holy
moly um let's get started ducky thanks for the five thank
you hold on um
thank you Oh, I was like, why is my throat feel a little
weird?
I forgot to take my medicine before him.
Jomu, thanks for the...
Thanks for the five gifted!
As goes, thanks for the ten gifted!
Oh my God.
Customer Johnson, thanks for the Aqua Supa!
I want to say thank you for the relay karaoke yesterday.
I listened, watched the whole stream once live, and once on
VOD.
No!
Okay, did Heaven survive?
Send to the Father.
love deterrence and snake eater so well it made me realize
you have you can express your love for your passions
uninhibited and unabashed thank you what wait what do you
mean one out of blank tika thanks for the gift one out of
question mark i'm scared
thank you let's do our first person uncanny scary mint emo
win What do you mean?
I'm not scary.
I'm Moe.
Moe.
Hold on.
I don't think he can read it.
Moe.
I mean, I know I'm a ghost, but like, I'm a cute ghost.
Because I'm a maid.
I'm not.
Duh.
Alright, let's pick our first victim person.
I will spin the wheel.
The winner is...
Turtle!
We can't see it.
I know, you won't see it until the name is pulled.
Because I'll be honest.
I have not vetted these.
and pasted them because there were so many so what if a what
if someone's trolling me and says a says something weird and
then i'm and then it just shows up on my screen
turtle oh my gosh i get to draw a turtle hold on let's see
what turtle uh requested in theirs oh thanks for staying
true to yourself and being an inspiration to many which
includes me as well two out of i don't know why i decided to
go on about it when i have nothing else to say plus i'm
broke please don't
is this me or someone else i don't know turtle did you put
turtle or turtles but thank you customer johnson thank you
let's see um turtle oh wait several people asked for turtles
oh wait Turtle asked for a turtle wearing sunglasses.
Wait, several people asked for a turtle's wearing
sunglasses.
Oh wait, no, sorry, that's just turtle.
Turtles, I'm sorry, I think this is different because
there's turtle and then there's turtles.
And you're turtles.
You asked for a turtle.
Turtle doesn't sound like a real word anymore.
That's not me.
I'm sorry, so close.
You could steal it if you wanted to.
But it's gonna have sunglasses, you know.
Hope you had a good day because I had an interesting one.
Three black bears decided to camp my house and not let me
leave for five hours.
Did they stand like this?
Did they stand like kind of all...
Bears standing?
Can I pet
that dog?
No, it's not a dog.
It really is a bear standing dog.
What are we drawing right now?
A turtle!
We're drawing a turtle with sunglasses.
I'm gonna make him really cool though, I'm gonna make him
cool.
Ouch!
Oh gosh, I think I have a pinched nerve in my neck and I
haven't been able to like...
Turn my head to the side all week.
So it hurts to laugh.
Oh gosh!
Oh, okay.
You would think that, like...
Horror, horror, horror.
You would think that being a ghost, like, you don't have to
deal with so many things.
But you know what?
It was so sad when I died, and I was like, yeah, I'm a
ghost.
I've escaped everything from the human shackles.
And they were like, about that.
You have everything the same just as a ghost.
I got ghost taxes.
I've got ghost health problems.
Okay, so a turtle.
Gotta have a big old hump.
Like that.
Can we have the bear standing emoji in the next batch,
please?
I already deleted it.
The bears get a little cold.
organic.
That's not a bowler hat.
Because turtles have
like...
Like that!
That looks like a turtle so far.
Sunglasses.
And he's like, yeah.
And then he's got his little legs.
But this one, this one is giving a big old thumbs up.
And he has another little leg.
They have four legs.
Oh, wait.
Turtles have tails.
Why is he backwards in his shell?
What do you mean?
No, he's not.
Oh.
Turtle.
Oh, he only has three legs, you're right.
There we go.
Let's give him an extra one just for good measure.
And I'll even, you know what?
I'll even color it.
Let's give him a good old green.
There's a turtle.
Oh my god, Squidward!
Tortolini!
Thank you for the food!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Do you think I should have made him bigger or...
Do you think it's okay?
I can make him bigger.
Give me a second.
So you can see him more easily.
Um...
You've been turded.
Isn't this... Okay.
Um...
What's that saying?
They have like a long...
third leg or whatever this guy just has a long fifth leg
just because he's a bit of an abomination doesn't make him
any any different huh what do you mean huh wait what did I
say wrong wait why are you guys are reacting like that
you're scaring me the
fifth leg yeah the fifth leg but it's actually him giving a
cool thumbs up it's a it's really an arm I gave 50 50s five
minutes ago but it didn't happen although the purchase
confirmed wait what do you mean 50 50s I saw it wait you
gave even more
As in a big arm.
Yeah!
Are you guys seeing the vision now?
For the turtle?
And we'll give him a sandy back.
I'm still in a dream.
Cool turtle.
Sorry, I don't know how to do like...
professional artist things like that could probably make
this go faster but I'm doing my best
good afternoon good afternoon good afternoon yeah some
people brought it up but yeah yesterday I was in the relay
and it was so much fun I was so nervous because I was just
like I have like the transitions and stuff between songs and
it was like me turning stuff on and making sure things were
running properly and I was like what if I mess up a thing
but overall it all worked out even though my voice was kind
of like there you go turtle
oh wait I must give you one more thing you're a little wisp
turtle
You're a wisp turtle.
Thank you.
Oh, wait.
I said I was going to make it bigger.
Hold on.
So this is for your screen cap.
There you go.
He's like, yeah.
That's one cool turtle.
Turtle, that's one cool turtle.
Nice.
Alright, let's see who we get next.
Spin the wheel.
Cowabunga dudes.
Next is Dam Dan.
1.30.
One?
No?
Damn, Diane.
Damn, Dan!
If you're here, raise your hand.
If not, that's okay, too.
Let's see.
Also, you guys...
They have no request!
Oh, my gosh.
Damn, Daniel?
Daniel?
Um...
What was I gonna say?
Oh, if you, I forgot to say, if you entered twice, I'll be
able to tell because I'll be able to see that you entered
twice.
So, because I just, I go into the Excel sheet that I have of
your names and I search it.
So, if you entered twice, I'm not going to, even if I pick
you, I'm not going to, I'm not going to.
not gonna i'm not gonna choose you so yeah cheaters beware
cheaters beware in case anybody was worried about that unsta
welcome the membership thank you also i saw this super chat
tomorrow's my birthday i'm going to celebrate my staying
home and eating cake do you think ojo ojo samint could wish
me a happy birthday of course dandelion yellow oh my gosh
you sent a yellow super chat just like your name
Happy...
How do I say happy...
Do I sing happy birthday?
How do I sing happy birthday as Ojo Sam meant?
Happy birthday to you!
Oh, oh, oh.
Happy birthday to you.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, gosh.
Can I hit this note right now?
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, happy birthday.
Near dandelion yellow.
Oh, oh, oh.
Happy birthday.
I had to work up to it.
Thanks so much.
Draw vans or scuff bochi or whatever.
Anything is fine.
Okay, we can do a scuff bochi.
I like it.
I entered twice.
I hope the second went over at the first.
Oh!
I appreciate your honesty, KC Raptor.
I will take that into consideration.
All right, we got scuffed Bochi.
Let me pull up Bochi real quick.
Bochi the Rock.
Let's see.
Let's see, let's see, let's see.
Okay, this is a good picture.
Right here.
No, this picture.
Okay.
Scuffed Bochi wearing vans.
I like it, I like it, I like it.
Alright, we're in my...
We're in my...
Okay, Bochi time.
Let's see.
To draw Bochi.
I think I'm...
Okay, Bochi has those little hair bongles.
I'm gonna give her a square head like her hair bongle,
right?
One thing I really like about Bochi too is when her eyes
kind of like do this.
Like that, you know?
And then...
What kind of pose should she have?
Oh, one that's like really cool, maybe.
Because she's wearing vans.
Those aren't Yoda's.
Those are her hands.
Right?
And...
She's got the vans.
How do I draw vans?
Hold on.
I'm not feeling it.
We'll start.
Hold on.
Was that the Phantom of the Opera?
Yeah.
I was the Phantom of the Opera.
Hold on.
Now I need a picture of vans.
Van shoes.
Oh, well give her the checkered ones.
Aren't those really popular?
Oh wait, no, there's a low...
Wait, huh?
Everyone always wears those checkered vans, right?
Checkered.
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
Yeah.
Hey, Mint, my friend Liz is having her birthday this week.
May I have a happy birthday to give to her?
heard from you?
Sure.
Hey, Liz.
I heard from your friends.
I win.
That is your birthday this week.
Happy birthday.
I hope you have the bestest birthday ever and not all your
dreams come true.
Ignore the person on the screen.
Birthday.
Happy.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday to you, Liz!
I'm not trying to erase the birthday or anything, you know?
I'm just, uh, okay.
All right.
Bochi the Rock.
She's got, she's got her, um, her big sweater on.
And, uh, actually, let's have her, like, kind of, actually,
I think I know an idea for a pose.
Okay.
She's shrugging, she's like, why do I exist?
And then we'll give her a wide power stance so that she can
show off the vans.
I'll be like, why are you standing like that?
So you can notice my cool shoes.
And they're the checkered ones.
like that.
I gotta really fill these in to sell the effect, okay?
She's wearing her vans, everybody.
She's wearing her vans.
Okay.
Asserting dominance.
She's shrugging.
She says, why am I alive?
Oh, she's got her little skirt on.
Oh, wait, hold on.
to erase her middle.
She's got to have her skirt on, you guys.
She's not indecent.
That'd be disgusting.
She's not walking around with no pants on, okay?
Vance called.
They want you to stop leaking their new collab that they
commissioned from you.
That I didn't sign any NDA.
This is me reacting to that.
I didn't sign any NDA.
I don't know what you're talking about.
This might be actually a leak of the new season.
Not gonna lie.
This might be a leak of the new season, though.
Of Bochi the Rock.
Watch, like, an actual Vans Bochi collab comes out.
Wait, I got her hair color wrong.
No!
It's more light.
There we go.
Hi Mint!
I was wondering why a cute ghost Mint kept appearing and I
recommended.
Realized that my Yoshi was back from the dead, kinda.
Glad to have you back, boss.
Thank you!
I'm back, baby.
I'm back.
Yeah.
Sometimes I wonder, I'm like, do people know I'm around?
I wonder if people know that I'm here.
And then we need a blue balls.
Oh wait, it's more aqua ball.
And a yellow ball.
We know.
Bochi the block.
Bochi the clock.
Bochi the rock.
Oh wait.
Bochi the clock.
Bochi the.
The frock?
That's like a type of clothing, isn't it?
Say it?
Say what?
The smock?
The sock?
The padlock?
To continue with the birthday streak, I would be happy if
you could say happy birthday to my friend.
Did I say that right?
It's not my birthday anytime soon, but can I get a kissy
kissy choo choo moa 9,000?
There you go.
Mitye's prize.
Yeah.
There you go.
Okay.
Aqus.
Aqus?
Wait.
Am I saying it's right?
I can't tell.
I can't tell if I'm saying it right.
Okay, now we draw in her...
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, here we go.
Hold on.
Oh, one second.
There we go.
Oh, it's more like a peachy.
Hold on.
Yeah, more like this.
Bread like Accused.
Oh, okay, okay.
Happy birthday Accused!
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday to you Happy birthday dear accused
Happy birthday to you Happy birthday I hope that worked
And what color is your skirt?
Gray.
I think it looks like Bochi.
You guys can tell, right?
I think you guys can tell this is Bochi, right?
You can be like, that's Bochi the Rock.
Or Glock.
Or Sock.
Yeah, it's definitely Bochi.
Okay, good.
I'm actually gonna...
I wonder...
Oh, wait.
I'm gonna...
Let's see if it looks how it looks with it over the eye.
Oh, yeah, I like that better.
Oh, I forgot the color in this part.
Monkey bacon.
Welcome to membership, dad, girl.
Thank you so much.
Okay, in her vans.
Now, who requested this again?
Damdan.
13 like that perfect I think I am satisfied you better be
you better be here hold on let me move it down a little bit
so you don't have to crop it so weird oh wait there we go
let's move it over here.
There you go.
That's a bocce.
That's a bocce time.
Another satisfied customer.
I mean, are you a customer?
It was free.
The icon was free.
Jimmy Corrin, thanks for the gift.
Thank you.
Oh, I missed some Wait, I'm sorry you mentioned earlier
about entering twice, but I got confused about just username
or actually YouTube username.
Sorry about that.
I appreciate your honesty, Rogu.
I appreciate your honesty.
But I think, uh, uh, I don't see like the ads, you know?
I only see how you appear in chat.
Unless you comment, then I see the ads.
But it's usually different names.
Thanks for the gift, dude.
I was talking earlier about the karaoke yesterday.
I was so happy Maria invited me.
I was like, oh my gosh, where?
Babies, Babies, relay.
I was like, this is me.
When she invited me.
Even though I got the dates wrong at first because I'm an
idiot.
I can't read.
I was like, that was me.
I was like,
but um, uh, it was really nice.
Everyone sounded so good.
Oh my gosh.
I was like, wow, everyone is crazy, talented.
She was ball maxing.
Those eyes really well drawn thank you and i was like
struggling what i wanted to do up until the day of because i
was like if i if i um who
is this who is this sorry i was checking something um i was
like if i do a metal gear karaoke i feel like people will be
like you always you you always do too much metal gear i'll
be like sorry i can't help it but also i was like what if
you know people don't know who i am they have to know what
i'm all about right right you don't do enough metal gear
karaoke i figured also i mean like the songs are still good
you know like even though it's like you don't have to know
metal gear to enjoy the music right so I thought it would be
okay all right I'm spinning again so that's why I decided
but it was fine it was so fine and I was I had fun like
finding the photos and everything that I wanted to use the
next person is ginger works ginger Gingerworks!
Gingerworks!
Let's see where you are.
Where are you at?
Gingerworks.
In my thing.
Yes, sir.
I sing snake eater on every karaoke.
No, sir.
I don't get sick of it.
Gingerworks.
Oh.
They asked for an alt mint outfit or creature mint.
Ooh,
interesting, interesting.
Creature mint.
Hmm.
La creature.
Well, someone asked earlier about, like, a spooky one.
But I can't do a spooky one for them and also as the emote.
Let's see.
How about I just do one, like, really...
Okay, hold on.
Hmm.
How do I want to do this?
I must confess that I requested, but the request is very
vague.
That's fine.
Now, some people didn't even request, so...
How do I want to do this?
Okay, there we go.
So crop Crop this They're not very straight though It was a
great karaoke but can we have something other than tree frog
for dinner?
I'm told chicken is good No!
Tree frog tastes just like chicken, don't you know?
Everything that's a different kind of meat tastes just like
chicken According to the world Okay
Okay What's wrong with me?
This one needs my utmost attention.
Concentration, okay?
Give me one moment.
Does this even look like me anymore?
Hmm.
It's okay, once I do the hair, well...
Thank you!
Superliminal.
Ghost made is Moe, made of ectoplasm.
Oh, sorry, M-O-E.
I don't see the difference.
Oh, do I need a little tongue out?
Maybe.
Now I'm reaching...
Oh, whoops.
Redo.
I have to have that final stroke.
I didn't know what to have.
You meant by request, so I just asked you to have a nice
day.
If I get pulled, can I request it in Super Chat?
Of course!
You don't even have to super chat.
Remember when I said crop there?
I lied because I'm coming out of your screen.
Coming out of your screen.
Open up.
Yes, Johnny.
Oh my gosh, I think I've been calling my new cat Johnny
instead of Paz lately because she is so...
smelly she is so stinky like oh my gosh um oh yeah i think i
said like uh on stream how um i thought i was gonna have to
take her to the vet because she was just she was just
spewing poop everywhere at one point and every time she goes
to the bathroom she just blows up the maid cafe it is like a
it is goes off and like actually well i was uh um i was i
was uh cleaning and um i was like oh my gosh someone else or
some i was like oh no johnny went to the bathroom again it
smells so bad and then you know who i see walk out from the
litter box butaro he was like he was like i am the stink
champ and I will not and out I will not let an outsider take
my title he is the reigning champion so yeah see this looks
more like me now
then we'll do the X we'll do that later though pause blow
something up see is in character
oof oof oof
but yeah so uh that's what happened um wait a second oh yeah
okay
kind of crazy um I think she has IBS because okay first
brought her home i noticed i was like yeah she's a little
smelly and then like she would be around my cat would be
around and like she was just farting like crazy and even and
i was like maybe she's nervous because you know she just got
brought to a new home but even now she just she just parts
all the time She'll I'll pick her up and she farts And I'll
pet her and if she gets too comfortable she farts She's so
She's so smelly Oh my god she's actually She's actually so
smelly And like they never brought that up when I was like
Like, when I was like, hey, is there anything I should know
about her?
No.
They didn't say anything like, oh, she's a smelly machine.
They were just like, no, she's totally fine.
Everything's good.
And it's not like I was feeding her, like, new food at that
point.
It was still her old food.
She just was, maybe it's the food itself, maybe.
would you say they gaslighted you okay also a little bit
because when i got her like they were like oh my gosh you
just adopted the best cat ever she's so sweet she's so nice
she's so oh my gosh everything about her she's like this
wonderful purring from the other end better out than in i
always say
But, um...
Murphy, what the hell?
Oh, God.
Oh, God, okay.
Anyway, what was I saying?
Oh, they were like, she's so sweet.
She's a lap cat.
She does this.
She's just the sweetest girl ever.
And I was like, yippee!
I've always wanted a lap cat.
I was so excited She doesn't She is not laid in my lap Once
I think actually it was maybe False advertising I was like
what okay I was like Well you know she's She's still nervous
Like she'll get in my lap Eventually Not even once She
hasn't even laid in the bed with me When I'm going to sleep
I think I was like Like, why do you advertise her as the
ultimate lab cat?
And I mean, she's very sweet.
Don't get me wrong.
Like, she's so, so nice.
And, like, she, maybe it was lab cat.
It's probably better, probably.
She just lays in my lap and farts the whole time.
You want her farting?
I want her.
Well, recently, she, if I'm on the couch, she has started,
like, um, she has started laying next to me so maybe it just
takes her a little bit of extra time or something I don't
know but um but yeah now it looks like me okay what was the
name by ginger works that's right
wait what the hell what happened to the hardness there we go
oh I did that
There you go.
So, hopefully.
And, like, for the first time last night, she, she, uh, did
not, oh, I forgot the, um, she did not sleep with me in my
bed, but she stayed in the room.
In my, in my room.
So, uh, you know.
She's eventually getting there, I think, a little bit.
I forgot my eyelashes.
I forgot how to have eyelashes.
Oops.
Oh, and blushing.
There you go.
I had problems with my big nasty boy when I got him.
Crazy running, jumping, etc.
Turns out the rescue just copy and paste it.
Maybe they were afraid no one would want to poop or...
They were like crying, though, at the pet store.
They were like...
Oh my gosh, we're going to miss you, Paz.
Oh my god, what?
And I was like, wow, she's so beloved.
She's so sweet.
But, um...
I hope that they didn't just copy and paste it.
I hope not.
Welcome to membership.
Thank you!
Anyway.
Yeah, I hope not.
Okay, let's do another one.
Tears of joy to be rid of the sticky wood.
Crying because they can finally breathe.
The winner is...
Ta-da!
Venti does things!
Venti, come on down!
Boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop!
Make the watermelon extra round and perhaps give the cat a
cowboy hat if possible.
Thank you!
Well, I don't know what your profile picture is.
They weren't crying, their ears were, their eyes weren't
watering because they just cleaned her litter.
Okay, wait, we have no context for your picture, except that
there is a watermelon and a cat.
So hold on.
Make the watermelon extra round and give the cat a cowboy
hat if possible.
okay
watermelon cat watermelon cat with a hat what if I google or
not google if I search them on YouTube let's see if anything
comes up
oh oh oh oh oh don't search their oh my god don't search
their username I didn't know that Ventia was a character
from Genshin Impact and um Things is like really vague.
And like...
I didn't know...
Watermelon, can I let's go?
Okay.
So we're gonna make a really round, thick watermelon.
no yeah that works no that works that works look can you
guys see me draw a heart isn't it oh hold on let me try to
do it let me actually let me actually watch what I'm drawing
hold on Could you see it with my hand?
Could you see it with my hand?
With the thing?
Could you see it with the thing?
Okay, so the cat, we're gonna have him like sticking his
head out here.
Why is drawing a circle so hard?
Yeah, you couldn't.
He's happy to be there.
Do you think he needs the ears or...
I feel like I'm drawing something from Battle Cats.
Nah, I like it better like this.
Actually, hold on.
There we go.
I made him a little insane.
Yeah, whatever.
Nice.
Okay, so the watermelon is really chunky.
And then a cowboy hat is like...
Tarnation.
Just like that.
Wait, how do I...
Actually, I don't know what a cowboy hat looks like at all.
Cowboy.
Cowboy hat.
Okay, hold on.
Oh, yep.
I'm getting some fine cowboys.
Whing.
I'm a cowboy.
I'm a cow.
Wait, there's cowboys, but where are the cow men?
I'm a cow man I'm a cow man I'm a cow man I'm a cow man I'm
a cow man meowdy I don't know what the perspective is on
this thing I guess that works actually hold on I'm a cow man
that's what i'd be asking every day hi maya i'm a cow man on
this cowland only boys in these parts but i'm a cow man i'm
a lone can't alone star oh we'll give him a star we'll give
him a star i don't know if this word It kind of looks more
like a fedora, but I think it will have to do.
Hi, wisps, wisps, wisps.
It looks like a fedora.
It's okay, it's okay.
I wonder if I do this, if I like have the ears kind of
sticking out.
here but I kind of look like him looking more like a potato
you know kind of like that better all right for the
watermelon colors we needed like a dark we need like a not a
neon green like a battle deal
also you guys what color should the cat be what kind of
colored cat should it be howdy malady he this guy is a is a
cow man truly what color cat should it be orange
orange cat i always hear that orange cats are crazy but i
had an orange cat when i was a kid and he wasn't that crazy
actually Okay, those should be good colors.
How am I supposed to do this, actually?
I did not think this through.
Did not think this through at all.
I did not think this through at all.
Mine is.
No, my orange cat was actually the most chill cat I have
ever had.
He was so chill.
He was so sweet.
But he did have a problem.
Like, I don't let my cats outside anymore.
when I you know my family before they didn't really care and
oh I didn't mean to zoom in there we go and and but he would
go to the neighbors houses and he would like walk he knew
how to open doors he was a very smart cat like if the door
had a handle he would open it up and so because of that he
would go to the neighbor's houses and let himself in.
And would just, like, the neighbors would sometimes call and
be like, wait, I'm such an idiot.
Hold on.
I'm just going to color in the whole thing and then we'll do
the other stripes.
Why am I...
Work smarter, not harder, everybody.
But, um...
See, I'm stupid.
I don't know how to do this.
But yeah.
And then, like, during dinner, he would just kind of sit at
the table.
And he wouldn't beg for food.
Like, he didn't try to climb on the table or anything.
Like, we would save him a seat at the dinner table.
Because he...
Ouch, it just bit my tongue.
Oh, I love it.
I love it.
Yeah,
he was very polite.
I mean, there was one time he pooped in my bed when I was
sleeping.
But other than that, he was really respectful.
And he was a good guy.
Yeah, I think that's when he was going senile.
He thought my bed was a litter box.
and I remember like I remember him like trying to you know
how when cats like like they like scoop with their paws I
thought he was trying to get comfy I was like what are you
doing little guy and then he turned around just take took a
big old dupe over I was in my bed while I was I was like you
know uh honest mistake truly why is he wearing a snake hat
Snake that ate an elephant.
Wait, what?
What are you talking about?
That's not very polite.
Yeah, that part was not very polite.
That part kind of sucked.
I was like, why would you...
Why would you do that?
I think he was kind of losing it.
Oh no, you guys.
I don't know if I've ever told you guys about my grandma.
But I'm gonna go see her soon.
I'm going to go see my grandma soon.
I haven't seen her in a long while.
She might not even remember me.
But...
Um...
We'll see.
Can't believe Mint just docks yourself to be Johnny Depp.
What do you mean?
Wait, did he poop in a bed like that?
Whoa, who is this wow mustache man who replaced Mint?
What are you talking about?
about?
I'm the mysterious traveler.
I'm a mysterious artician.
Why is it so hard making this a watermelon?
Holy cow.
I think I'm... I think I don't know how to do anything is
that a seal no it's a cat so okay I got this though I can
color it in I can color it in I can make it a nice I'm a
simp the images extension can show you profile pictures if
you have it hover over an image shows you a big version for
example for users in chat oh thank
you isn't isn't it more exciting to kind of get um i mean
you're not paying for it so take take what you can get i
suppose you know you're you're um isn't it more exciting if
you're like what what is she gonna draw me That's why I
asked if you wanted any requests.
Use bucket?
Will it work?
Oh.
It will work here.
It doesn't work.
Wait, hold on.
Maybe here.
Let's try again.
It doesn't work.
I can't use bucket.
I have to color it all in by hand.
I can't.
I can't use bucket.
Brush size maybe.
No, it's okay.
You guys, calm down.
Why are you in such a rush, huh?
I like coloring in the lines.
I like it.
It's making me feel a little bit actually too relaxed.
a nap before the stream because i was like oh no i'm not i
am drinking coffee right now but i'm still so sleepy sleepy
ghost okay
okay orange cat time
Tellamaya, y'all backseating, artisting, Picasso?
Yeah!
Stop backseating me!
Stop it!
You're mad.
This is the process.
It must be done by hand.
Or not at all.
Actually, I wonder if I can book it here.
Yippee!
I mean...
It can only, it can be done by buckets sometimes.
Yay!
Oh yes, the process.
Screw the process.
A little pink nose like that.
And then...
Give this, give this little cow cat a nice Brown fedora.
No, this is not a fedora.
This is a cowboy hat.
What kind of fedora would be brown?
Thanks, Raymac.
There will literally be a day.
Oh, there will literally never be a day I complain about too
much Mint Metal Gear karaoke.
Ah.
I'm glad.
Sorry, all the doughnuts are backed up.
They're coming in eventually.
That was from a while ago.
Yeah.
That's okay.
I still saw it.
Trying to get the color.
Trying to get the perfect.
This guy is a deputy.
He is running this town.
I hope you like it.
I hope you like your...
Oh wait, sorry.
I have to write your name too.
Venti does things.
But don't look that up.
Apparently, Venti is doing things.
But for the karaoke, it's funny because I said, like, I'm
not going to do a karaoke.
Sorry, I'm like tilting my head when she does.
Oh, gosh.
Okay, this is so far so good.
Oh, nice.
I was like, oh, I'm not gonna do another karaoke for a while
because I, because I, my voice, my throat has not been so
good.
And then I realized that the date for, I mixed the date up
for this karaoke, and I was like, oopsie.
So, but it was only 20 minutes.
I just picked really hard songs.
You were truly an artistic genius and the cutest stuff.
My cat escaped from me while I was watching your stream and
I had to take a two mile walk to get back Get him back home,
but I'm glad I was able to catch him and still have time to
watch the rest Is your cat okay?
Are you okay?
Sounds kind of traumatic Anyways, thank you, Venti I hope
you enjoy your um, your big old cat Enjoy that fat melon cat
Enjoy him
I don't know, I really like I have so much fun fun doing
karaoke though and it's like so easy if I'm just like I
don't know what I want to do today karaoke it's so easy our
next person is reverie bunny thank you thank you melon you
have to leave now happy Cinco de meow whoa oh my gosh it is
Happy Cinco de Mayo, everybody.
A cattermelon?
Perry the cattermelon?
No.
Saki, Saki!
Thank you for the mustache.
Thank you.
Reverie Bunyan.
My profile pick with made, mint's made headband.
Uh oh.
Scrabble, scrabble.
Oh, I see you!
If you can't draw my profile picture, just draw a mochi
bunny with your handband.
A mochi bunny!
I can do that.
Mochi bunny.
Mochi bunny, mochi bunny.
That's, I just...
That's so similar.
Okay, hold on.
Choo!
Wait.
Mochi bunny are like...
The little ones with the red eyes, right?
And then they have...
They have the green, right?
Am I thinking of the correct thing?
Yeah?
Okay, okay.
This one's actually not cursed at all.
This one's very cute, everybody.
Stream to comfy, making me want to go to Eip!
Me too.
I'll give him a little smile, though.
Is that okay?
Mmm, mochi.
I think it was...
I think it was, uh...
Family Mart?
Or 7-Eleven?
That I got some so good mochi.
It was so soft.
Make him evil.
It was so soft and so delicious and...
Oh, here I'll give him a little...
Little triangle.
And how do I want to make the headband?
Do I want to make it like here?
Or do I want to make it here?
Me?
Can I gotcha the alert sound and when the alert will show up
in one don't know?
Thank you!
Too bad, too bad, too bad.
Did you see, did you, oh, I did, yes.
I thought it was very cute.
But, um, I don't know why you would bring up that person.
I've never talked about them before.
Oh, wait, uh, let's see.
Um, what is that little growth coming from your head?
My hair?
This?
This is hair?
You've never seen hair before?
Well, that's a ribbon.
This is hair.
It's terminal.
The triangle?
That?
It's just what ghosts wear.
and it's terminal
i've seen people say like it's half a cat ear and i kind of
like that theory too because i'm like dang i'm like so cool
i lost half my ear like i lost one of my ears i only have
one cat ear what if i get a cat ear what if i get cat ears
will it look weird i wonder
Fire 5...
Oh, 6...
Oh...
6...
Oh, I'm J Venom Punished Men.
I think I'm gonna do the headband...
This way.
I don't know how to do...
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, Bunny.
I don't know how to do...
I don't know how to do ruffles.
That looks close enough, though.
right looks close enough maybe you
can kind of tell right here i'll even do i'll even do the
the blue perfecto
i think so perfecto for real and then i write your name just
needs vertical lines okay i trust your judgment
Made mochi Made mochi
Alright, reverie
Thank you Thank you, thank you Krayalbert, thanks for the
five gifted Thank you so much Mochi the rock Mochi the rock
Can you draw me next?
Sure I'll draw you
You.
Yeah, I drew that really good, right?
I know.
You.
Do you guys know that one face?
Hold on.
Okay, ignore the top.
Ignore the top text, but this is the only picture that I
could find that wasn't a gift, okay?
So just ignore the top text.
Um.
I think it's this face?
I...
Okay, every time...
Okay, you want to see me make this face?
Hold on.
Oh, my mustache.
My mustache, you look quite good.
Okay.
Don't I look the same?
I feel like my eyes are going...
Do I look the same as Shinji?
my
eyes are too large
but don't my eyes kind of look like they go in different
directions
no it's not me that far unleashed it's you see there's the
hand pointing
Minto, get in the robot.
Lizard eyes.
It's me.
Frog eyes.
Hold on, let me see if I can blink one at a time.
Did I do it?
Am I smaller?
Why is my mustache so big now?
Hold on.
There we go.
Why is my mustache so much bigger?
Huh?
I'm Chettino.
Yes.
I am the leader.
And where's my...
Why do I feel so different?
What happened?
What happened to me?
Okay.
My hand is still here.
Alrighty.
Let's see.
This one is for...
I'm gonna pick a...
I'm gonna pick someone's name out of the chat and this one
can be your profile picture.
And I'll even write your name on it.
I'm gonna open my eyes and the first name that I see be for
you ready three two one oh my gosh it's going too fast oh
god okay hold on one more time one more time one more time
three two one i see misha gucgee oh there
you are go all yours
there you go thank you
misoguchi omedito wherever you are omedito with your toes
nice i want to see if they come back with this as their as
their profile picture i'm looking i'm waiting i'm waiting
best piece yet what do you mean by that i mean this was made
with the most love maybe oh wait
oh wait i don't want it to be me
wait a second i should have had
No, I don't want it to say fart unleashed or it's me.
No!
Unless that's my face when my cat unleashes its fart.
10 out of 10.
No notes.
What an honor for them.
Mid-Court already made it?
No, they didn't.
They're not that fast.
Right?
Yeah.
stinky add
a mustache to it
that's the ugliest mustache I've ever seen okay that's a bit
better
there we go so mint was gaseous snake all along no it's not
me it's It's not me!
I'm deleting this before anybody else can take it.
The best profile picture.
Thanks for the super chat!
Next person.
Is...
B closing parentheses!
The reason in particular would you be preferred...
Wait, would you prefer to be rounded up 5 foot?
down to four foot.
It doesn't, if something is over five, doesn't it mean you
put it at, you put it to the higher number.
So five foot.
Five foot.
Me.
Be closing parentheses.
Be close.
Oh.
Please draw yourself in the coolest, most fresh, fly,
radical, epic sunglasses in the world and a smug smile,
please and thank you.
Pray emoji.
I've got you.
I got you.
Oh, my bad.
Goodbye wheel.
Okay.
Let's see.
Me and the most cool, fly, fresh, awesome.
I can do that.
Hold on.
Look at these though.
What?
Wrong thing.
Oh.
Oh yeah.
So close.
Hold on.
Maybe if I put them on my face.
When I'm looking center.
Wait, how do I get the mustache in front?
Uh-oh.
I think I just...
Oh, my gosh.
I can't move the mustache anymore.
It's stuck forever.
Wait.
Uh-oh.
Hold on.
Um.
Uh.
I don't know how to get rid of the mustache.
Uh-oh.
I don't know how to move it.
Wait, I wanted to bring it in.
I wanted it to be in front of the sunglasses, but now...
Uh-oh.
My mustache is forever.
It's so close.
It's so far.
If I look too far over, my head also becomes really big.
So close.
Well, um, you guys like my glasses?
it's glued on i used a super glue to keep it on you know
okay let's draw me when i think of really awesome glasses
i don't know why i'm focusing so much on this when i'm just
gonna erase most of it When I think of really awesome
glasses, actually, I'm going to Google the coolest glasses.
The coolest glasses in the world.
Oh, these are.
No, these are terrible.
None of these are cool.
Okay, wait, I actually really like this one.
Okay.
This is my inspiration.
Why won't you show the picture?
Wait, hold on.
What is going on?
Hello?
Computer?
Uh, uh oh.
Hello?
You guys, I think something's wrong with my computer.
Ah!
What's going on?
Oh, there it is.
Okay, thank goodness.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, hurry.
Let's, uh, all right.
This is my...
This is my inspiration.
Wait!
I can just become this man.
Okay, hold on.
He's bald.
I can just take over.
Okay.
We can draw hair on him.
It's like It's actually perfect It's actually perfect
Yeah, I'm so awesome I'm so cool I'm so cool I'm so cool
Let's see.
Let's do this.
And then we'll draw my hair out here, too.
Sorry, you're going to have to crop it, but I believe in
you.
Actually, I want my hair fluffier.
No, my hair is not that fluffy.
Okay.
Oh wait, it goes in.
Never mind.
It's fine.
Just leave it.
I'm being a perfectionist.
Okay.
Then let's put it, let's shade it in.
This time I'll actually use the big guns.
Oh no!
Okay, I'm gonna have to do a slightly, slightly less white.
There we go.
Mint cosplaying snake and solid is a thing.
the same time slightly less white color don't
worry I'll go back I'll clean it up after I'll clean it up
after but you're gonna have to crop it sorry I'm not you
know sometimes it somehow it feels even bolder what do you
mean oh wait but what about the this part okay we'll fix it
we'll fix it.
I'm gonna fix it.
I'm gonna fix everything.
Don't you worry.
We're gonna go in and we're gonna fix everything.
This is gonna be great.
She forgot to draw the growth.
I'm not there yet!
And it's not a growth!
I'm still just doing my hair!
So impatient.
Okay, what was I doing?
Oh, okay.
Now from here, we're going to do this, okay?
You see?
Oops.
We're going to do that.
We're going to get all the edges.
I color outside the lines and then I fix it up.
Maybe it's more time consuming.
I don't care.
I'm just an artist here, okay?
Stop criticizing my art.
Don't criticize.
That means you hate art.
Do you hate art?
Okay, this time I'm gonna have to...
I'm getting really into this one, so I gotta...
Oh no, I don't want you to see his skin.
No, no, no, no.
Inside the lines, inside the lines.
Inside the lines, inside the lines, inside the lines.
Could I have redrawn this?
Probably.
but this is for authenticity's sake, okay?
Uh-oh, it's gonna disappear.
Is my head bigger than this man's?
Um, obviously, because I'm smarter.
This is what they wanted, you guys.
This is what they wanted.
I feel really uncomfortable being this close to this guy's
head.
I feel pretty uncomfortable right now.
I'm not going to lie.
I'm seeing every pore.
Every single line in his forehead.
I'm seeing it all.
I mean...
Um...
He's got nice skin, I'm assuming for his age, you know?
Oops.
You know what?
Screw it.
Uh-huh.
What the?
No, no, no.
Stop it.
There we go.
This is the future the boss envisioned.
I can see his white hairs.
I know!
I can see everything!
Clean scalp.
Hold on.
Let's... Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Let's clean up this part right here.
Ah!
Have you heard that?
No, you didn't.
I didn't...
You know what, screw it, I don't care.
Alright, let's do...
What if I leave it this way where you can see just his...
You can see his head peeking through.
There we go.
Oh, I forgot my!
Oh my gosh.
How could I forget my twin tails?
Which was the layer?
This one.
How could I forget my twin tails?
Right?
Oh my gosh, what's wrong?
I was like, something feels off.
No.
My friend Mike has his birthday tomorrow.
Are you serious?
Are you for real?
What's Mike's last name?
Tell me right now.
It's perfect, it's perfect, it's perfect.
Don't worry about it.
Hooter.
Like the store?
Like the restaurant?
I've never been to a hooter's.
I've never been to Hooters.
And people say, like, go for the wings.
But then people are also like, the wings aren't that good.
So which is it?
Which is it?
Last name is Sugma.
I don't believe you.
That's a Pokemon.
If his last name was Sugma, What?
You know how like, you know, there's like last names that
were what they did back then in the day, like that
originated from that.
They were like, oh, I'm, I'm, I'm Casey Blacksmith, you
know, stuff like that.
What did they do if their last name was Sugmo?
Hooters is men, really?
But it's like, it feels like so exciting to think about.
Like, it's just like, wow, I'm going to Hooters.
I'm going to Hooters.
It looks just like me.
He's already got the mustache even.
Sucking poison.
I get it.
Oh, wait.
I'll make it smaller.
There we go.
I made it smaller.
smaller so that you can see it.
There we go, perfect.
Oh, I gotta write your name.
B closing parentheses.
Wait, can I fit it on his forehead?
Wait, my handwriting is too big.
B?
Closing...
Uh...
No!
P...
Parentheses...
Paren...
N...
Theth...
Parenthesis.
Sorry, it got a little small by the end.
I hope you like this one.
I actually put so much effort into it.
I hope you like it.
I think I look really cool.
I think I look really awesome.
Hmm.
Hold on.
Don't take it just yet.
Hold
on.
There we go.
Ah, important part.
Now it really looks like me.
It looks so good, right?
Mm-hmm.
Hold on.
Let me move my cursor.
There you go.
Screen cap that.
That's yours.
B closing parenthesis.
Yeah.
Yeah, she's okay, I guess.
Like maybe she's amazing, but I don't know.
Free NFT.
No!
You can't right click and save this!
You can't right click and save art!
It's my picture!
I own the pixels!
I create the pixels!
I birth the pixels!
They are my pixels!
I own these pixels!
You cannot steal my art!
Do not right click save!
It is mine!
I own the ownership!
I own it!
I have the digital certificate!
It is mine!
I just bought the NFT
Right clicked Don't do that, it's illegal You're literally
stealing from me right now You are taking my artistic right
To own this art Burst?
I won't right click save I'll just screenshot it instead you
can't do that how dare you you do not own the actual pixels
you do not own it you do not own it I own every individual
pixel I own the hex code you can't have these colors they're
mine they're on the hex code.
Oh, if my model, if I'm in the way, if I'm in the way, if
I'm in the way, if I'm in the way.
When did my arm go up?
It's kind of freaky, actually.
You can't have this.
You cannot own this.
I'm not own this.
I'm even taking it back.
B closing parentheses.
I'm sorry.
Now I can right click and save mint phantom.
Stop owning me.
Get owned.
I will own you.
Stop owning me!
You do not own me!
Be closing parenthesis is my new identity.
I hope they...
I don't know if they're here in the chat.
If they are.
Look at the chaos you've caused here.
Get owned.
Anyways, thank you.
I hope you like your profile picture.
Let's go to the next person.
Mino abla, ablo, ablo.
Isn't it abla, English?
You could say she's been minted.
Whoa, why does it sound like so weird like that?
Next up is...
Whimp.
No!
You're not a wimp.
Whip.
Whisp.
Whisp, Willow.
No, you're very strong.
You're very strong.
Whisp Willow.
What's your request?
I hope it's like, don't draw me all wimpy, please.
Please draw me looking really cool.
Oh, they said none.
On your request, they said none.
My profile pic being drawn by you is already a lot.
Ah, oh no, they wrote something really nice and I called
them a wimp.
No!
I'm sorry, Whisp Willow!
I'm sorry, I'll draw you looking really cool!
I'll draw you looking so awesome!
Okay, hold on.
Okay.
Since you're a Whisp, we're gonna draw you as a Whisp.
Oh, hold on.
I need more space.
But then...
They have Biffy arms.
Like that.
Whimp no more.
Biffy wisp, beefy wisp.
Biffy wisp.
Biffy, beefy wisp.
Beef, beef, beef, beef.
that oh yeah oh yeah giga wisp because he's a post-plast
fighting type he's ready to throw it down he's ready to go
to town he's ready to not be on the ground he's ready to
throw you on the ground He's ready to give big a give give a
give a give a big frown He's ready to He's ready to
He's ready to make you round
Wait, frown and round don't rhyme.
Wait, neither do ground.
Wait, am I rhyming?
Wait, am I rhyming frown or am I rhyming pound?
Wait, I said he's ready to go down.
He's ready?
Okay, he's ready to go to town.
He's ready to give a big frown.
He's ready to...
throw you around no I did it again there's no D at the end
take the crown oh you are so good he's so good knock you
down not knock you up he'll knock you down he's a beef
master he's a beef master Let's see.
I wonder if I can just fill them in.
It's a little bit more blue.
Kind of like this color.
Sorry.
Where's the opening at?
Hmm.
I don't see it.
Oh, my eyes.
Wear a tasteful gown.
Oh.
And he managed to avoid being true.
Oh my god.
Can I do this?
Let's see.
Can I...
No.
That's okay.
I'll do it.
I'll make it quick.
I think the color is supposed to be a little lighter blue
but um that's fine that's fine everybody's monitors are
different it's the correct color on my monitor you know left
bicep yeah this is this is the the tri tri tops this is the
bi tops this is the the Ichitops Um It's honestly only gym
bros would get this You know only gym bros would be like Yo
that guy is ripped This guy This guy knows what's going on
He's so beefed up
I Yeah Yeah
Hell yeah, wispy Yes, this guy will go to your gym And he'll
be like He'll be like Don't film TikToks In my gym Today I'm
going to lift I'm going to lift every pound I'm gonna take
every pound I'm gonna take every pound downtown why you
can't write pound and town what's wrong with me sorry okay I
keep trying to do it keep trying to make it work it does not
work oh
oh my god why is my thing so delayed oh my gosh thank you
for the akasoop I cried with laughter you're listening to
those rhymes thank you vinto world's strongest ghost what is
that what's that last word i'm scared nexi thank you so much
for the hackadono thank you orakasuma thank you so much
thank you this is a fart no guys don't be mean to him he's
gonna beat you out he has the gains
why would you use that word What does it mean?
Don't call him a wimp.
Oh yeah, he says that.
He says that actually.
You can rhyme however you want, Queen.
Thank you.
Don't.
Oh, wrong layer.
Actually, it's fine.
Don't.
We use punctuation here.
Call me wimp.
Because I'm Wisp, it's Wisp Willow, right?
Let me double check.
Yes, I'm Wisp Willow.
Wisp Willow.
Oh, yeah.
I ain't no Wisp.
Whimper Willow, I'm a Whisp Willow.
That's his theme song.
He comes into the ring.
Whisp Willow.
Never Whimp Willow.
I'm Whisp Willow.
I'm punching my pillow.
Never say hello.
Don't call wisp me wimp well.
No, that's not what I said.
Shut up, Tudor.
That's not what I said to put words into my mouth.
I hope you like that, wisp well.
Thank you.
Thank you for entering.
Thank you very much.
Oh, my gosh.
It's already been two hours.
Holy cow.
Please rest.
wrap it up.
Why are you so mean to me?
Next up is
Linery.
Whoa.
Oh my gosh.
My chat is actually like... I think there's something wrong
with my computer today.
um...
All the text disappeared for a second.
Linery.
Wait, is that what you go by?
It says at.
Hi, Mitt.
Hi, Vijay.
Hello.
Hello, hello, hello.
Hmm.
Probably just YouTube?
I'm not sure.
I think it's on YouTube then?
Maybe.
Oh, do as you please with a little heart.
Okay.
Hmm.
So much artistic freedom.
Uh.
When are you in chat?
Wait, where are you at?
Wait, where are I?
Oh, hello!
Hello!
What do you want?
I can't give you anything.
I can draw you.
world sparkling shimmering wimpy or if you don't want to be
wimpy please let me know I can open your eyes or make them
close if you want to I can make you buff or sad or even have
a beard a whole new profile picture add black glasses like
yours okay wait to what to your profile but i can't even
tell what it is looks like an anime girl okay i'll draw an
anime girl with with uh with black glasses i'll make her
cute
okay good start hold on it's just short hair right where'd
you go where'd you go where'd you go oh yeah she's got short
hair okay
like this short right it looks it looks pretty short that's
ugly sorry oh god I don't know how to draw.
Why did I ever say...
Oh my god, Katsu!
Thank you for the 50!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
There we go.
And we're going to put some cool black glasses on.
Wait.
I think it's running into their little smile.
Oh.
Whoa.
Looks like Valma.
Drinkies!
Jankies!
Um...
They're gonna be waving.
Like...
Hello!
Hi!
Okay, they're either waving?
Or they're saying...
Give me $5.
Oh, sorry.
I forgot to do the glasses.
Okay, hold on.
Okay.
That's four?
Oh, you're right.
Give me four.
$4.
You know what that's better because that's a spooky number.
That's what I meant to put.
As a ghost, I can only count up to 4 because anything beyond
5 doesn't really matter.
Anything beyond 4 doesn't matter at all because only $5 I
mean, no, only $4 matters.
And, uh, give me $4.
Let's see, she's got a little, she's got a little bit of a,
of a blush here.
The hair color that your profile picture has is like kind of
a ashy, um, it's like a yellowy grayish color.
Maybe, yeah, I like that.
Perfect.
Oh my gosh, thanks for the four dollars.
Thank you.
Stop.
Okay, it's okay.
You guys can stop now.
The bit's over.
The bit's done.
We've left the bit.
We have abandoned the bit.
The bit is done.
The bit is over.
We are moving on to the next thing.
Thank you.
Beige.
I guess it's kind of beige.
I guess beige is a better way to put it.
But it's like, but like when you go to the hair salon, this
hair color is like very popular.
Like Mume's hair color is extremely popular in Japan right
now.
And it's like a dusty brown is how they describe it.
And dusty colors right now are like extremely popular.
Like dusty pink.
Anything dusty.
And they mean it in like a good way.
Kind of looks like you know from Hidden Marry Sketch.
Really?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's like ash.
They say ashy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
They don't say dusty.
They say ashy.
Thank you.
Yeah, yeah.
They say like ashy brown.
Mmm.
Um.
What was I going to say?
Kutori hair, yes, yes, yes, yes.
My, what was I gonna say?
Oh my gosh.
Oh, my friend, when she went to, when I met with her last,
she had gotten, she had gotten her hair done and I was like,
love the color because she she the color was that was that
hashy brown i was like oh my gosh it looks so good i've kind
of considered it before it's just so cute
stop dissing boom what do you mean i'm not dissing her at
all i'm saying the color is nice what do you mean i'm
dissing her i like the color what are you talking about What
are you talking about?
Okay.
This was...
Oh.
Let me write your name.
Wait.
Hold on.
Let me make that E nicer.
Thank you, Linery.
Thank you.
It's funny how Mume's ponytail is longer than some people
are tall.
Wait, how long is her ponytail?
Her last name is Nanashi, right?
Yeah, Mume Nanashi.
Oh my god!
Whoa!
It's so fluffy!
It's so long!
It's not past her feet.
It's like to her, it's like to her the middle of her
calves.
It's still pretty long though.
No name.
Nice.
Alrighty.
Oh wait.
Let me make this bigger for you.
For when you screenshot it.
I'm so sorry.
I should have.
I should have done that.
Hold on.
Let me make this bigger for you.
For when you screenshot it.
There you go.
Linerary.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I hope it's what you wanted.
I hope it was good enough.
Hopefully.
Okay.
Next person.
Oh, one second.
Okay.
it could be you it could be you it could be you it could be
you it could be you it's you it's you cashews it's you
cashews it's you
cashews if you're here please stand up please stand up It's
me.
It's not you.
You're Raymac.
You're not cashews.
I love gamble.
Yeah, but it's free.
It's free gamble.
Okay, I'm going to get rid of these sunglasses now.
As really awesome as I look.
Cashews.
My favorite nut.
Okay.
that is... Why did I almost just say raspberries?
Um...
It's, uh...
Maybe mine is actually Cashew's.
They asked for Doma and Cashew from G Gundam.
But it's just his hair and clothes on a cashew nut.
Domon cashew.
Okay.
I have to look this guy up.
Oh, wait.
There's a cashew in the chat.
Wait, this is just like with turtles.
And turtle.
How is this happening more than once?
What?
Wait.
Just cashew.
Oh my gosh!
Oh wait.
Oh no, I don't see you.
There's just cashews.
Cashew, did you not submit?
Oh my gosh, turtle!
I like your profile picture.
Cashews and cashew are both in check.
Oh, there's...
Wait, I didn't enter.
I need to keep my picture for branding.
Branding.
I understand.
That's okay.
I get it.
It could have been you.
I'm not good enough for your brand, huh?
Thank you, thank you.
Oh, four dollars.
No more?
No less.
Thank you.
Very true.
And I get to keep all of them.
that because if it was youtube they'd take 30 but i get to
keep that
caches are actually related to poison ivy and can't be
touched with your bare hands really really i'm always so
scared what if one day i get a almond that like devolved and
i eat it and it's you know what I mean
what if I what if it like returns to being an evil almond
and I eat it and I die what if it genetically regresses and
then I mean I'm already dead but like I worry for you guys
wait really what do you mean really did you not know that
about almond
Streamlabs still blocked for you or are they paying you now
I haven't I haven't received any money since I well like
it's it's all trapped in PayPal and then YouTube hasn't paid
me so I haven't received anything I haven't received
anything but it's okay I'm alright I still paid rent I'm
okay this sounds fake no almonds.
Almonds used to be poisonous.
It's true.
Yeah, it's just in PayPal jail because, well, I'm really
lucky I can use PayPal because what happened before I
graduated was they marked me as suspicious and I and they
were like, you can never use PayPal again.
You can never open another PayPal again in your life.
You can never even smell You can never look You don't even
glance in our direction PayPal hates you now You are on the
hit list You are You are forever banned
For the silly drawings Ah thanks And so I had to come up
with another way To get the Streamlabs Donations And um and
uh that was three years ago yeah it was three years ago that
happened um but i figured i have i have worked around it to
the best of my ability
so um yeah it was complicated so it's still a problem kind
of uh but it's okay I hear that happens all the time or not
all the time but more often than it should where it's like I
see like artists who will be like my PayPal got banned
forever and I can't do anything about it so PayPal is kind
of icky can't you contact their customer support oh yeah I
definitely tried and uh they were like sorry we literally
can't do anything I was like oh Okay.
Thanks for nothing.
Yeah.
It's fine though.
It's fine.
Things are fine.
It's just the issue.
I think, I think when I went to heaven, I was very excited
because I was like, oh my gosh, I don't have to deal with
PayPal anymore.
I don't want to.
I was like, oh my gosh, I never have to deal with them
anymore.
This is so awesome.
And then when I came back, I was like, ah.
The troubles of being indie.
But I was like, oh man.
That was funny.
I was talking to.
I was talking to Mitara last night.
And like, like with the...
with the relay i was just like man it was so awesome seeing
like um because i tried to watch mostly everybody but i had
some stuff to do later on in the night um but uh i um like
it was so fun seeing like you know everybody like cheering
on their like their uh like how do i say like their gen
mates i guess like they were just like woohoo the i'm from
i'm from i'm from idol and this person's also from idol
let's go you know stuff like that so i was just like man i
kind of i'm i'm like i don't know i'm i was telling her i
was just like i feel kind of like lonely like i have no like
camaraderie with people anymore and i was just like i wish
like i could have become I wish I could have come back or
like become India with like a group of people or something
so that we could like stick together and she was just like
she was like wow you know like she was actually kind of
surprised but I was like I don't know I just kind of miss
having like the camaraderie but it was that's why I told her
I was like I'm really grateful that she is inviting me to so
many like collabs because I'm just I'm just kind of like
lonely
a little bit she was just like if there is anybody that i
know that like you want to collab with just let me know and
i'll i'll get you in contact with them so she's been helping
out a lot and you know i'm really grateful that she like has
been organizing the collabs with with with me and stuff so
but yeah it's been like not bothering me but it's just you
know kind of been on my mind a little bit and stuff and then
I'm kind of shy so I don't reach out to people so it's kind
of also my fault but I should reach out to people since I'm
sad and lonely
but yeah it's okay did I pull another person oh my god
Cassius is over here being like hello um can i get my my my
Gundam drawing please let me google them oh this guy this
guy this guy is so awesome um okay hold on what outfit
though What outfit, though?
Um...
Hell yeah, he is.
Yeah!
Speaking of cashews, my neighbor has a cashew tree, and my
fridge is full of them!
Cashew juice is super...
I'm so jealous because cashews are so expensive!
Nice.
I believe Mint can make friends despite her What do you mean
despite my smell?
I'm so minty fresh.
It's not me that smelly.
He has multiple?
Oh.
Oh my god, I see your profile pictures.
Okay, hold on.
Like, I see this one.
But I think your profile picture...
This one is from Dynasty Warriors, though.
I think your profile picture seems to be his normal outfit.
Okay, so there's this one.
Then there's...
I don't want to cosplay.
Uh...
This one?
It's so tiny.
Why is it so small?
I can't see it.
This one?
This one, but with the red cape.
Which did you want?
Excuse me, spiky bread coming through.
No!
Stop!
It hurts!
That's his Gundam fighter suit.
That one is good enough.
Which one?
I posted both.
I'll just do the one on the left, maybe.
Because I think that's what he's wearing in your profile
picture.
In my mind, you smell like Baja Blast and not Mint.
I don't even know what that smells like.
But I'm assuming it's fruity, right?
that one yeah that one I pick that one pick number three my
lord um okay I'm gonna I'm gonna have this on the screen
though wait there we go okay put that right over there and
um it's chemically oh they said left oh okay thank you oh oh
This hand of mine glows with an awesome power!
Its burning grip tells me to defeat you!
It makes sense if you watch G-Gundum.
Thanks, Virulent.
Oh god.
I now need to find a picture of Akashio.
What?
I think I'm gonna be sick.
what cashews look like from the tree?
I realize I have never seen a cashew on a tree before, and
it's hideous.
It's disgusting.
What is this?
Oh my god, it looks like a little worm coming out.
Oh my god!
Oh my god, it's awful.
Look at this.
Oh my god.
What?
What is this?
It looks so gross!
It's like an apple with a worm coming out!
I've never seen a cashew tree before!
Oh no!
Oh my god, these are so gross!
No!
Wait, the cashew nut is not the top part?
Wait, where's the cashew nut?
It's the top part, right?
Don't seed shame it.
Where do you...
Where's the cashew nut?
Is it inside here?
Inside this part?
Or this, because this looks like it's cut open and there's
no cashew nut here.
Mint ruined cashews first.
So, wait, what does an almond look like?
Almond.
Oh, see this one looks like a nut.
This one looks so normal.
This one looks...
It's kind of fuzzy.
Looks normal.
Normal nut.
Nothing, no big deal.
NBD.
Zucchini is actually prettier when you see it.
Zucchini.
Can zucchinis have flowers on them or am I lying?
Oh, I want some zucchini now.
I'm kind of hungry.
Oh my gosh, I just realized I haven't had dinner.
I can do a few more.
Zucchinis look normal.
Normal nut, normal nut.
Okay, let me find a cashew.
Cashew nut.
Oh my god It's so gross It's so nasty Sorry Cashew, I'm not
calling you nasty I'm calling your baby pictures nasty
Why can't I find just a singular nut Cashew nut
Hmm Perfect.
Okay.
Perfect.
All right.
Now we're going to draw him onto this nut.
Why is it glistening?
It's oily.
Cashews have oil on them.
A little bit at least.
Don't they?
It's like a cashew oil.
Let's start with his hair.
Wait.
This is so anime.
This is what I feel like I drew as a kid.
Like this kind of hairstyle.
This is like the hairstyle I drew as a kid when I was like,
Oh, I'm gonna be an anime artist.
Anime nut, anime nut, anime nut.
More likely than you think.
We're going to cover up his little pooper right there.
Right there.
Indecent, indecent, indecent, indecent.
Whoops.
Oh, oh, it's back.
Um.
Okay.
It's a nut.
It's not, it's not, it's not, it's a not.
Oh, hi Hannah!
It's a not, it's a not.
It's a not.
It's a, what's a not with you?
Man, I'm the best at jokes.
I'm so good at jokes, you guys.
Not much.
How about you?
Nacho cheese.
Busting a nut.
No!
Save the nut.
Don't beat him up.
Don't bust him up.
Bust a move instead of busting a nut.
Oh my gosh, I knew you guys would love it.
I knew you guys would love it.
Oh no, it looks too awesome.
It looks just like him, doesn't it?
It honestly looks so good.
It kind of feels like, you know how like making visual
novels of like, you know, pigeons and weird characters, like
the KFC and one.
Bust in a nut.
Mint Fantomo.
Stop my name!
Like, uh, like, um...
Yeah, like the What's the word the KFC one?
I feel like there would be one about nuts and cat like cash
This is this is cashew couldn't you know And they their
catchphrase is like nothing wrong about it Dating a nut
nothing wrong about it
pics that go hard this might be my magnum opus of profile
pictures i don't know if i can do another one after this one
it's too good oh okay i'm normal i'm normal i'm normal i'm
normal i'm normal okay i'm not normal i'm thinking about my
my nut
people would be actually discussing like who's the hottest
nut be like oh my gosh
there's something so sexy about how brooding how brooding uh
pistachio is i'd be like he's so kakui wow wait this doesn't
look right hold on Okay, let's... I'm just gonna draw this
for now.
And the other opening.
I'm only gonna give the jacket.
No pants.
This guy is too sexy for pants.
Ah, buh-buh-buh.
Wait.
Kind of like that.
It's his normal.
She's normal.
I'm normal.
I can't draw perspectives.
I'm so sorry.
Like, I'm trying to follow the picture itself, but I think
my perspective is wrong.
I need to go back to art school.
Like, I totally ever went before.
Your magna opens.
Yo, this PFP is packing.
That's what I'm saying.
It's really good.
Then he's got to get his shirt on.
He's got his little shirt.
on this little green shirt and
then I'll do the belt down here oh
yeah there we go and then 200k we did it let's go let's not
Go!
Bust a nut!
Let's go!
Thank you guys!
Thank you for 200k!
Thank you!
Thank you guys so much!
Oh gosh, my chat is... Oh, fake knee!
Oh my gosh, thank you for the...
Thank you!
Oh my gosh, thank you so much.
it's okay thank you so much ignore this part right here okay
ignore that this is how you get 200k subs 200k oh my gosh
brick they gave me the 50 where my chat is really really
delayed i'll have to do something for i i still have to do
something for it well i have to think of
you guys so much thank you thank you so much 200k wow wow
we'll do something oh gosh wait do i have to readjust my
schedule for next week then
i might have to i didn't have anything planned oh okay i
might have to move some stuff around what should i do
Oh, busting nuts at 200k.
Woo!
Let's go.
I have to think of something to do.
I don't want to just do a karaoke.
Omedito.
Arigato.
Oh, pyro bug things are lack of super.
Oh, my gosh.
My chat is so...
I have to like read chat through OBS.
It is so broken on the computer.
It is so broken.
But thank you.
I'm hoping I'm seeing the messages.
I'm hoping.
If I'm a little slow, it's because of...
It's because of...
It's because YouTube chat on...
on browser is breaking.
Rock for Rabbit, thank you!
Wait.
Hold on.
I couldn't read it.
It was too slow.
small it'll it'll appear eventually in browser nut tier list
no this isn't a very pretty color i'm gonna make it more
yellow oh there it is oh thank you for the big gaga doodle
congrats on busted over to it okay oh thank you guys Thank
you so much.
Thank you guys.
Thank you.
There we go.
That should be good for your profile picture, right?
Cashews, here you are.
Oh, wait.
Let me write your name.
Wait, was it cashews or cashew?
Cashews.
Yeah, next to the vibe gifted!
Katsu!
Thank you for the...
Thank you!
Oh my gosh.
Thank you for all the super chats.
It is so delayed.
I'm so sorry.
Oh yeah.
Wait.
I'm trying to draw it along as luscious curves.
There we go.
There you go, Cashews!
I think this one's my best one yet, maybe.
Sorry that the collar is a little weird.
Just ignore it.
Nobody will sell.
Nobody will see it.
It'll be too small.
Congrats on 200k.
Thank you!
Thank you, guys!
Crude Matter, thanks for the five.
Oh, Captain!
Orthwarm, Jeb.
Thank you.
Do you think you'd consider doing midday mink?
I miss listening to it at work.
I definitely want to.
I just want to be in a server, maybe.
I can still probably be on a private thing.
Mike, thanks for the 100.
Thank you for the Akasupa.
Congrats on 200KU Spooky Ghost.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Oh my gosh.
Thank you, guys.
Woohoo!
It really is the best one.
I think this one is my best one.
Oh my gosh, PhD killers!
Thanks for six months.
Membership 200,000.
Oh, man, it's all.
Six months ago.
I was not.
I was at like 10k.
Now I'm back.
And I just hit 200k.
Crazy.
Crazy, crazy, crazy.
Oh, one block.
I do like one block.
You're a super...
No!
Thank you.
200k.
Let's go bust a nut.
Woohoo!
Marilyn, thank you for the five gifted.
Misakuchi!
Thank you for the 10.
I love your profile picture.
Oh my gosh.
Here's the 300k next.
I'll do my...
best i'll do my best to to be entertaining enough for 300k
all right cashews i hope you screen capped it i'll do uh
i'll do two more
one million before the end of the year actually impossible
but thank you for your high hopes
Thank you.
Oh my god.
The claps are for me.
Next person is Alaric.
Alaric, if you're here.
Congratulations.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Undo?
Uh.
Wait.
Oh, wait.
Uh-oh.
You entered twice!
Haleric.
Wait, what?
No.
Haleric, you entered twice.
What is this?
I'm kind of scared.
You sent a picture.
Or a link to a picture.
Haleric, you entered twice.
Why did you enter twice?
You asked for the same thing both times!
I saw you were in chat.
What do you have to say for yourself?
Shame him.
I am.
What do you have to...
What do you have to say for yourself?
This is like...
I kind of want to draw this though, which is why I'm...
Where did you go?
I can't tell if you've...
I didn't mean to?
What do you mean you didn't mean to?
What do you mean?
Okay.
Because you entered twice.
I will...
I'll still do it.
But I will set a timer.
Where I only have one minute to draw it.
And the thing you asked me to draw?
But peculiar things are the gifted!
Do we forgive?
We're shaming a little bit.
Oh my god, I don't want this person's butt on my screen so
large.
What is the context of this photo?
Actually, I don't want to know.
Okay.
I don't even know what this is, but I'm going to give myself
one minute
to draw this.
And, um, starting now.
Time.
Just boys being boys.
Congrats on 200K.
Thank you!
This is the horse.
By the one.
By the one right here.
That's that guy.
That's the horse.
What's up?
Thanks for the vibe, gifted.
Thank you so much!
I think I actually got it pretty well.
I think I got it pretty well, actually.
Let me write your name.
It's uh, it's more, it's less of a profile pic because it's
kind of more portrait style, but, um, I did my best.
Um, sorry, I'm not gonna color it in because, uh, I sped run
it.
I call this one Metal Gear.
Yeah, everybody's watching, they're enjoying.
I think this one's pretty good.
Oh, hold on.
I did forget this one.
It's it.
There's his other arm.
He's giving him a head pat.
He's giving him a head pat, obviously.
There we go.
I
stretch.
Okay.
This belongs in a museum.
It belongs in a museum.
Thank you, Indy.
Okay.
Next one.
Which might be the last one.
We'll see how in-depth it is.
We'll see.
Congratulations to Manthi Rose!
Manthi Rose, Manthi Rose if you're here.
Let's see what you've got.
Whoa.
Oh my gosh, my preview?
of like my stream there's like a little preview in uh in for
youtube it showed me just getting rid of of the Gundam guy
that's crazy a wisp version of my OC in the profile pick
manthi I sure hope you're here I sure hope you're here
manthi uh because Hello!
Thanks for the raid!
Hello, hello!
Whoever raided me, thank you!
Sorry, my chat's a little broken right now.
I can't...
I can't see.
Oh, he's here?
I'm here!
Oh my gosh, wait.
Wait, hold on.
Where are you?
Hold on, I'm looking.
And don't worry guys, I will be doing this again.
I hope you guys like this style.
I just feel like it's, like I said, it's less overwhelming
for me.
And also gives other people a shot.
Even though I appreciate every single one of you and
everybody who...
I never win.
Yippee!
See.
I just, uh...
I want everybody to have a chance.
So, Manti, I can't tell what you're...
Wait, Manti, can you post your profile picture under the
Minto Live hashtag and I'll just get it from there?
Oh, it looks like a VTuber.
Here I am!
I see you!
Kind of.
My chat is so slow.
I don't know what's going on.
I think it's YouTube.
Maybe I should refresh.
Refresh
Uh oh Oh
there you are I'm gonna go check my Hashtag W2 Tax form
thanks for the five gifted Sorry if I Sorry if I Missed it
earlier Chat was being so I can't read anything
I'm looking at everything that's in the file.
The live tag and it's so cursed.
Oh my gosh.
We aren't icky.
Oh, I think it's fixed now.
I think it's fixed.
I think it's fixed now.
Also, Maple, why did you...
Oh, I see it.
Oh, there it is.
Thank you!
Oh, they're so pretty!
Is it okay if I... I'm just gonna...
I'm gonna put it on the screen.
I hope that's okay.
So that I can have a reference.
Easy to see reference.
Maple, why'd you draw?
Why'd you draw yourself as...
as... with a... with a...
You maybe!
Thanks for the raid!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Hello!
Hello everybody!
Oh,
he lost one ear.
Oh, he lost one ear.
All right.
Why are there so many people raiding me?
What's going on?
Thank you for the raid!
Hello!
What is going on?
Why are there so many people raiding me?
What's happening?
I'm in my popular fangs?
What?
Okay, there we go.
Big and bulbous.
For anybody coming in, I'm drawing profile pictures.
nothing too fancy.
We're just kind of chit-chatting.
We're just hanging out.
Hey, I'm dragon.
Thanks for the tank of tits.
Hey, don't try.
Thank you guys!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Oh, perfect.
First, we'll start off with our cat.
Our waspspspspspspsps.
And then you got a little hat, so I definitely want to draw
that.
You got...
Oh, and the hair ribbon too.
I'll draw the hair ribbon.
It does kind of look like a toho.
Art by mint.
That's me.
That's my name.
My name's mint.
I'm minto.
That's my name.
Don't wear it out.
And the hat.
I'm so concentrated.
Okay.
Alright.
Very good.
Amazing artwork there.
Stop it.
You're just trying to flatter me.
You're just trying to...
You're just trying to make me feel good.
Bustin, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting,
busting!
Busting, busting, busting, busting!
Busting!
Busting makes me feel good.
Oh wait.
I was like, why is it acting weird?
There we go.
Look at this cute little guy.
He's so precious.
He's so innocent.
Never a bad thought.
Only good thoughts.
Oh wait, this is the ears.
Never bad thoughts.
Never weird thoughts.
Wisps are good and don't have weird thoughts.
And welcome to membership.
Thank you so much!
Yeah, you're normal.
You're normal.
You're so normal.
You're totally normal.
Right, Chet.
You're normal.
What was that voice that came out of me?
I think I am a demon sometimes.
And the...
I'm going to make the hot blue.
Blue, blue, blue.
And the ribbon too.
I'm blue.
Double-dee, double-dee.
Double-dee.
I'm starting to get really hungry, so it's hard for me to
think.
So I apologize for any brain cells lacking in this moment.
Your art is very amazing and unique and I love it.
Thank you, Ben.
Really?
Well, you don't have to be so nice.
Come on.
I think when someone is just like, your art is unique.
Usually it's like not a compliment.
But I appreciate it.
Thank you.
Yeah, your art is...
It's unique.
It's unconventional.
I call it bold and brash.
Picasso moment.
For real.
Picasso real.
Mint Picasso.
I'm not Domingue.
I'm mint Picasso.
That's me.
Mint castle.
Castle.
Thank you, Mint, let us be nice to you.
I don't accept compliments.
I'm gonna, it doesn't have, usually I'm gonna give it, I'm
gonna give it the front hair a little bit.
Kind of like a little bit of fringe.
Cute.
And a ponytail.
Yeah.
Maybe not the ponytail.
Kind of looks like a...
Kind of looks like, you know, your uncle's...
Your uncle's rat tail.
Looks like your uncle's rat tail a little bit.
There we go.
There we go, I think.
perhaps that is good speaking from experience I don't know
if my oh actually I think one of I had several uncles I
think one of them had a rat tail yeah because uh a couple of
my uncles were in a biker gang so I think one of them had a
rat tail when he was in the gang
um Um, okay, let me write your name.
Manti Rose.
And your QOC.
And I'm sorry, I'm going to delete your OC.
There you go.
Grandma's side of the family, maybe.
No.
The other side of the family.
The other side.
your render of the sack of Rome will be my new profile
picture thank you
thank you thank you for this thank you for turning this
weird detective and a cute little whisp love this so much
thank you it's your uncle ghost rider
Yeah, actually.
Oh, yes, the sack of Rome.
I recall the head pat.
Thank you, Mampi.
I hope you saved it.
If not, get it in the VOD.
Yep.
Alrighty.
And let's do one last one.
Okay.
Mint is my sack of the Roman Empire.
What does that mean?
What does the sack of the Roman Empire?
Oh!
Our winner is...
Sideways!
Congrats!
Congrats, congrats!
What did you ask for?
Let's go!
Uh, nothing specifically, but have fun with it.
Love you, Minto!
Well, you're here, I saw you, so is there anything you want
for real?
Do you often think about the Roman Empire, Mint?
I honestly think about the Romans a lot.
I think about the Roman Empire more now because people
started thinking about the Roman, or started talking about
the Roman Empire.
I think you can't say your Roman Empire anymore because
people are always thinking about the Roman Empire now
because Because they're always talking saying this is my
Roman Empire
It's too suggested now can I have a red 2002 Mazda Miata
with your ribbon on it
I got you I got you not the Miata
Not the miata.
Okay.
This is the one, right?
So whoever is car this is?
Uh, thank you for allowing me to use it for my commercial
use.
Um, actually I'm going to make it a little bit smaller so
that you can screenshot it more easily.
Okay, so first...
There we go.
Alright, we're gonna We're gonna do this
We're gonna put me on the car
We're gonna wrap me on Actually, maybe I should be the other
way Gonna put Yeah, Itasha time, baby We're gonna put me on
the car Yeah, it's gonna be Actually, no, it doesn't have to
be sideways Just be multiple of me.
It can be many of me.
Multiple, multiple minto.
Okay, hold on.
I do have to do this, though.
Gotta pimp that ride.
Yeah.
Actually, for this one, we'll have one here.
Hold on.
gonna make it transparent first and then we'll have this one
here but flipped
that scared me but flipped oh there we go nice okay so four
minto on a car four minto on a car just like this okay now
we erase Which is the first Minto?
Wait, which is the original?
Okay, you're not the original, but we'll take it.
So the reason we're see-through is so that I can just kind
of...
Minto sisters?
Are they single?
Asking for a Frened?
I think Frened should have enough courage to ask for
themselves.
Just saying.
I'm actually considering doing them, by the way.
Kind of sort of abandoned my old project.
And a miata is smaller and cheaper.
Don't worry, I haven't forgotten the headband.
But why red on it?
Why I'm not red at all.
I'm not red at all.
I wouldn't match.
Red for the rage inside you.
Actually, hold on.
I'm gonna take a picture just for this.
Okay.
Just for this, just for this Itasha.
Save image.
Okay.
Now the red will match.
Now the, now the red will match.
Sorry if it's not flushed, by the way.
I'm doing my best.
My minto besto.
Ganba minto.
Oh, not that one.
Is it this one?
Yep.
Wait, I messed up.
Okay, hold on.
These need to be more...
Hmm, how do I do this?
Right now, they're kind of conjoined twins, but that's okay.
One can be higher and one can be...
Oh, like that, like that, like that.
One can be higher and one can be lower.
Just like that.
Oh, wait, wrong one.
This one.
There we go.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la.
I don't expect anybody to ever make an Itasha out of me, but
it would be very cool to see.
I love seeing Itasha.
So, you know, not that I'm expecting it or anything.
I'm just saying.
If you decide to, if you're like, I want to make an Itasha
of someone, a certain ghost maid would be super enthused
about the idea.
I'm just saying someone of my of me my my my personality
would be very excited it's just the hood for this one by the
way it's just the hood I see I see I see I see
why can't i get this why is it going so much why is it like
so janky why is it so lumpy oh what's going on what's
happening stop stop
okay oh my gosh eraser too big I don't think it's the
eraser's fault.
It's like, it's like, when I do it, it's, first of all, it's
like, look at that.
Look at the size of the eraser, but that's all it does.
It's that tiny amount.
And then I think it's like not, it's like making it not very
smooth.
Oh, smoothing is off, that's why.
Maybe I just needed smoothing on a little bit more.
But it's hard to tell where, hmm.
Yamato, please!
Don't do it my best.
No one will notice.
Your profile picture will be too small.
Okay, that's one.
Sorry, I'm like so focused on this.
I'm barely reading chat.
Oh wait, now the smoothing's at 100.
No, no, I turned it off so I can do this quickly.
Okay.
There we go.
Next is this one.
Is it this one?
No.
This one.
Okay.
Let's get rid of the body.
Yaddy, yaddy, yaddy.
Get rid of the bodies.
Hide the bodies.
Dispose of the bodies.
Oh, what happened to my body?
I don't know, actually.
Kind of freaky.
I wonder who's meada this is.
Congrats on 200K.
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Dispose of the bodies.
Hide the bodies.
Get rid of the bodies.
We won't be caught today.
I'm not doing time Not for this crime We'll hide the bodies
away And see the sun the next day Okay, that one wasn't so
bad Oh my god, wait And whatever Are you guys seeing the
vision?
First of all, though, I have to erase my forehead here.
Goodbye, forehead.
All right, last but not least.
This one.
I can totally see the vision.
You can?
I'm a split head now.
hole in the head head empty if if you look and if you peer
inside my mind you will see gas gas gas gas gas that's all
that's going on in there
all right it might be a little bit messy but uh I just don't
have steady hands okay good enough good enough oh no i
forgot the body on the other one we didn't finish hiding the
body we're terrible criminals we're so bad at this frank
welcome to membership thank you very much thank you i
appreciate it
very good sideways what do you think so far My Itasha skills
out of 10?
Oh, but did you think I was done?
Because what would this car be without?
One more Minto!
But this time, Fito!
More.
One more.
I'll have to also...
opacity one more minto one more minto
enhance enhance okay there we go nice very good she knows
what the people want I don't know if sideways is a is a feet
guy feet person I have no idea but I think because you can't
see my legs at all in the car it's kind of important to have
it there you know I think it's I think it would be better
this actually looks pretty good I'd say alright what did I
put that one at 84
okay oh no I took that one picture I gotta add it somewhere.
I gotta add it somewhere, hold on.
84, where should I put it?
Uhhhh...
Hmm...
Oh, I could put it here, I could put it here.
I think.
Oh, no, wait!
I have an even better idea.
I have a better idea, I have a better idea.
Okay, okay, okay.
it's a it's a window it's a windshield uh windshield cover
it's a windshield cover gotta make it a little bit bigger
though not good enough
let's get rid of this
all these pesky bodies parts that we don't need.
Get out of here.
Oh, and then of course the headband.
Don't worry, I haven't forgotten.
I'll probably forget later.
Please remind me if I forget.
Actually, no.
I'll do it right now.
I just don't remember where I have it saved.
I don't remember where I saved it.
I...
I don't know where it is.
Oh, I have it.
But let's hide it for now so I can take care of this part.
Okay.
Whoa!
Sorry.
Scared me.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I can't tell where the windshield begins and
I think this is correct.
It's going to be a little cut off.
You won't see my dashing smile, but that's okay.
That's okay.
Does the car gain an immense ghost powers?
It actually sounds like that when you drive it.
Everybody in the...
You know how like there's some cars that are like...
they have like they make so much noise they're like this one
everybody will know they'll be like wow they're driving the
mint miata
you can hear it everywhere the mint miata no one is safe
I can't tell if this is part of the windshield or not.
So I'm just going to do it like that.
And then the headband.
The radio plays exclusively Busted.
When you honk the horn, it goes, B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-Bustin,
B-B-B-B-Bustin.
How are we feeling, ladies?
How are we feeling?
All right, hold on.
One more thing.
I'm going to draw you two sideways.
There you are.
And, um, where should I write your name?
2013.
Yeah!
Not even sideways.
You're right.
It's okay.
I don't want him to look like he's dead on the ground, you
know?
Rotate it by 90 degrees.
But then the name.
I'll have to redo the name, too.
There we go.
And let me zoom in so you can screenshot.
Oh, uh, uh, once again, there we go.
I'll move out of the way.
Get your screenshot.
Oh, there we go.
The mint miata.
Mintata.
No.
That sounds icky.
Okay, thank you, Minto.
You're welcome!
You are so welcome.
It almost looks legit.
It almost looks convincing, I'd say.
Oh, wait.
I just realized this part is bad.
Wait.
That part was sticking up too much.
There we go, I fixed it, I fixed it Take another screen, oh
wait Oh I gotta move over, oh wait I'm gonna zoom out all
the time
There, there you go, there you go There you go, there you go
It's gotta be authentic It's gotta be authentic It's gotta
be like Really incovencing What am I looking at?
I just got here, you're looking at The new, the fancy this
forget the cyber truck it's time for the ghost truck the
bull brigade the the the ghost wait the mint mobile oh my
gosh thank you for the akasupa can't believe my oh she is
taking my first akasupa i mean what were you thinking thank
you for the akasupa thank you the mint miada oh my
$200k.
Thank you!
The Mintmobile!
There's a bit on the wheel?
This down here?
I see it, I see it, I see it, I see it.
Oh!
This on the wheel!
Oh my gosh, you're so... I'm so sorry!
Oh my gosh, that's so embarrassing.
Oh my gosh, I missed so much!
Oh my gosh, there's even more!
That's so embarrassing.
Oh my gosh, sideways, please.
I don't deserve that, Akasupa.
I messed up.
I messed up bad.
I was looking at this part right here, this tiny bitty bit.
I was like, oh, you're right.
It does kind of stick out.
So I'll fix it.
Okay, now it should be third times the charm.
Wait, third times the charm.
There you go.
Okay, thank you.
Oh my gosh, I can't believe I missed that.
That's so embarrassing.
I'm going to think about that for the rest of my afterlife.
Oh, tiny bit near the front headlight.
Wait, do you mean this part?
Is that not just a shine on the car?
Fourth time's the charm.
Lucky number.
Spooky number four.
Ah, oh.
There we go.
Good job.
There's a bit of mint of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of
mint in the bottom left corner.
You know what?
It's dead.
The bit is dead.
The bit of mint is dead.
Where do you get your mints at?
Where do you get your mints printed?
Bogle's minted?
Well, guys, I think that was a good one to end on.
Like I said, this won't be the last time I do this.
Let me show you what my schedule is for next week.
Though, oh, whoops.
Though, I think it will probably change because...
Whoops, not that.
Because maybe I have to do something for 200K.
So take this with a grain of salt at the moment.
It's not totally complete.
It's maybe not accurate.
But, um...
I'll probably change...
Wait, Atlantis No Nazo can be my thing for 200k.
200k, Atlantis No Nazo!
Or is it Nazo No Atlantis?
Wait.
No, is Atlantis Noazo, right?
What?
Am I losing it right now?
I think I'm very tired.
tired because i'm hungry yeah so oh yeah i have a collab
with leah actually she asked me to send her some stuff for
it and i had to stream so um um yeah collabing with leah on
her channel so technically i won't be streaming on my
channel that day um and monday tomorrow the podcast and and
and Sunday I'm seeing my grandma so yes
yeah but like I said this might change a little bit because
oh and all the times are wrong so please don't look at the
times at the moment oh wait actually only ghost trick is
wrong what time did i have ghost trick for
uh oh ghost trick is actually a 6 p.m esg and atlantis no
naso is actually 2 p.m esg so it's just a little bit wrong
just a little bit wrong but yeah i hadn't fixed that yet i
need to i need to uh get a schedule with figma because i'm
so bad about changing the times.
It's my least favorite thing.
So I'll probably be commissioning a new schedule so that I
can use Figma again.
Okie dokie.
I'm gonna go to eat dinner even though it's kind of late.
I hope you guys, everybody who got profile pictures, I hope
you guys like them.
I'll do some more in the future and uh before we head out
before we head out before we head out
oh yeah oh yeah oh
but there's something strange sleeping in your bed Let me
tell you something.
If there's something weird sleeping in your bed.
Ow!
Let me tell you something.
Bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin,
bustin.
Thank you guys for 200K!
Thank you!
You keep seeing things, sleeping in your bed.
Baa, baa, baa, baa.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Invisible man, sleeping in your bed.
Ow!
Let me tell you something.
Yeah!
Pushing, pushing, pushing, pushing, making me feel good,
feel good.
Wow, thank you for the outcast of our Sadie Nosting!
Thank you!
I'm drawing art.
Feel good, feel good, feel good.
Ghost made.
Freaky ghost man.
Freaky ghost made.
If you're all alone.
Let me sleep in your bed.
Shoo!
Let me tell you something.
Sleeping makes me feel good.
Ah, yeah.
Sleeping.
I ain't afraid of no sleep.
I ain't afraid of no bed.
Invisible bed.
Among Us bed!
Oh my god!
It's a No more goes bad!
Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin
Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin B Yeah, yeah, yeah
Baby, bing Buster, buster, buster, buster, buster Oh yeah,
feel good, feel good, feel good Feel good, feel good, feel
good, feel Yeah, yeah, yeah Buster, buster, buster, buster,
buster, buster, buster, buster, buster, buster, buster,
buster, Buster, buster, makes me feel Oh my gosh, Minnie
Scooter Thank you.
That makes me feel good.
Otomito everyone.
Bye bye.
Thank you.
See you guys later.
Listen to the podcast tomorrow.
And I'll see you guys tomorrow at the podcast.
Oh wait.
Actually I think I have a haunting appointment.
I don't know I don't know if I'll be there actually.
I think I have a haunting appointment.
So if I see you I'll see you though.
Bye bye!
Otsuminta!
Bustin, Bustin, Otsuminta, Bustin, Bustin, Bustin, Bustin,
Bustin' real good!
Yeah, no, no, no, no, thanks for 200k!
See you another day!
Okay, bye.