Monkey time.
Monkey, monkey, monkey.
Monkey, monkey, monkey, monkey, monkey monkey, monkey,
monkey.
Yeah!
This is the weirdest Bunny Girl Cafe I have ever seen.
You guys, I'm sorry.
Today on my schedule was...
Bunny Garden.
Whoa!
Why is a...
Why is Discord sending me stuff even though I have OBS open?
Huh?
Oh, I disabled streamer mode.
Matara!
She said this song appeared on my Spotify and it's from
Metal Gear Rising.
Yeah!
The game is quiet.
It is quiet.
Because, look at this.
I can't stand listening to the music in this game.
Yeah, the game itself will be louder though.
I was thinking actually maybe just putting on my own music.
Put it at max!
Yeah, I might do my own BGM.
We'll see how, you know, we get as we listen to it.
monkey if you guys don't know this game um i actually just
like started replaying it a couple days ago so i'll oh wait
this might be loud okay hold on i'm gonna turn it down oh
that was loud i turned it down insta monkey yippee um i only
started replaying a couple days ago and um i was like i
don't know i was just feeling it i don't know and nothing
caused it I was just like wow love I was like looking
through my games and I was like oh blooms I'm just gonna I'm
just gonna play it again monkey picked it up on the steam
sale no no I already owned this I already owned it yeah so
it was uh easy or not easy it was in my library I guess easy
to play because it was just there yeah happy made day to my
favorite mint made made mint and look even my super chat is
mint colored thank you steel yes it's a i thought i was like
oh my gosh it's made day should i have changed to something
more made like but but maybe it's okay because maybe it's
okay because i should be able to play anything that i want
today How do I turn...
Hold on, I don't want Discord to message me again.
How do I turn the streamer mode back on?
Oh.
Streamer mode.
I don't know how to do it.
I'm just gonna exit out.
I'm just gonna leave.
Quit Discord.
Okay.
We're disconnecting for real.
Settings, app settings, streamer.
Thank you.
Yeah, W Hammer.
Honk.
Did you guys notice we're on a different side of the screen?
Actually, I actually, I flipped my monitors.
So now, you guys are on the right side.
She'd be moving around.
I know, isn't it so exciting to...
to go to a different spot?
Why are you guys a clown emoji?
Why are you guys a clown emoji, huh?
And Draco, thanks for the 10 gifted, thank you.
Keep us on our toes, absolutely.
Absolutely, what was it?
W Hammer, can you post it again?
I lost it.
Wait, um.
Oh!
It's enabled already.
Never mind.
It's because I reopened or I got it.
We're good.
I think it's because I quit.
Settings, app settings too.
Thank you!
Even bazongas cannot overcome the urge to return to monkey.
Happy May Day to my favorite maid.
Thank you!
Yeah, I was like, maybe I should, uh, maybe I should like,
Play whatever I want because it is made day.
It's my day Actually, did you guys know that there's a minto
day?
Unfortunately, we missed it.
It's a March 10th, but it's me like three in Japanese is
three and then in Japanese 10 is can be read as toll.
So minto
Mario day
still in my gig.
No, it's a Minto day.
It's not Mario day.
Forget about Mario.
Don't listen to him.
Um.
You can see I've played a little bit.
Not so much though.
Oh, should we do the balloon?
But I've already done this one.
Happy late mint day.
Thanks.
Toes Day?
What do you mean by that, Hugo?
I can see the Aurora Borealis from my bedroom.
Wait, actually?
At this time of day.
I mean, at this time...
Wait.
All localized within the outsevere bedroom.
Sorry.
My brain is not working very well today.
I think my brain is, uh...
No, I saw some people talking about the Aurora Borealis
today, though.
Yeah, you got it.
It's the spirit.
Right?
I can never forget about Mario.
Can't believe Mint is broke after her time in the balloons
were.
Which one should we do, you guys?
We can do any of them.
Oh, this one's kind of spooky.
I love Spooky.
And it has a bonus reward.
Let's do this one.
I just really want to get off this menu.
I'm going to put everything to the same.
Yes?
Why isn't it working?
Why is it a...
Yep.
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh!
You have to hold on to.
Yes.
Babe.
Butt cheeks.
Welcome to membership bag you.
Yes.
Sir.
What?
That is so weird that you like hold on to it.
Yes.
Uh, disclaimer.
I'm probably gonna play this a little poorly.
Um, I think there's also this monkey.
I have yet to unlock that monkey.
I don't even know what this monkey is.
I think when I was playing before, this monkey did not
exist.
And March 9th is Miku.
March 9th, thank you.
Fairy baby, welcome to membership.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
I thought you were a god gamer.
I am a YouTuber by No Perfect Gameplay.
Actually, Matara and I were recording the Patreon side of
the podcast today.
like almost not just before this but um and uh i was like
man i really just want to play balloons we got actually like
really into talking about balloons even before we were
recording um but i was just like you know one thing that
when i play people will be like oh my gosh sorry matara i'm
leaking um i'm leaking patreon content um uh When I was
like, when I play and like, you know, I don't put my monkeys
in the exact way that like Bloons lover 777 put them in on
YouTube for the optimal Bloons gameplay, people are just
like, No, no, why would you put that monkey there?
Why would you put that monkey there?
It's so funny.
The meta monkey.
But Matara said that she really likes Ninja Monkey and
Boomerang Monkey.
So those are going to be my focuses today because I have not
played with them at all.
I usually play with Dart Monkey, Bomb Monkey, Tach Monkey,
Sniper Monkey, Sticky Monkey,
bucket monkey Ellie monkey magic monkey oh no alchemist
monkey sniper monkey is cool sniper monkey is so good
actually can you stand on top of this oh come on come on
that's a perfect spot it's a perfect spot $500 anyway mint
monkey can't wait for here him to go seriously so basically
everything except for those it's not everything there's
still a good bit in here oh I started using the Gatlin
monkey recently oh and the house monkey monkey village well
I'm gonna put a boomerang monkey can I afford him actually
boomerang monkey is gonna go Okay, where should I put
boomerang monkey?
If you want to unlock that locked monkey, click on the
monkey next to the fountain in the main area and click
monkey.
There should be a quest for.
Where is the maid monkey?
Right here!
Do you guys want some coffee ASMR?
I got a can of coffee here.
I'm gonna open it.
Hold on.
Here, I'll even turn off my noise, okay?
Alright, this is some...
ASMR.
Can't coffee.
My sleeves are in the way.
Ah!
Sorry.
Coffee ASMR.
Mm-hmm.
Yummy.
Okay.
um can monkeys hang out on the bridge no i just don't know
how to use a boomerang monkey i'm gonna put him i'm gonna
put him right here he's not gonna know what to do either
actually he's kind of pricey what does he do though what why
is a boomerang monkey so good maybe i put it here i love
this bit so much what are you talking about it's not a
Hi Pierce.
Boomering is honestly cracked.
Is he?
Rangs aren't cheap.
Okay.
I'm going to give him... I'm going to give him...
I'm going to... I'm nervous.
People are going to be like your monkey placement so bad.
Oh my gosh.
Whenever I play...
Whenever I play by myself, I'm like, Put a monkey anywhere.
hold on just ignore them okay i'm gonna ignore them just
like miss cat said what do they do a pops a blues moab press
is that related to the mating press moab press is goated
don't say it
the primate press
the primate press heavy kylie boomerang hits moab class
balloons multiple times per throw and sometimes knocks them
back a short way along the path okay i'm gonna put him right
here and we're gonna put a little dart monkey right here
because i want him to be there
moab means mother of all bombs I'm just happy to see you
play monkey game again Thanks I don't think I've ever
streamed it here
Minter monkey placement is so bad Yeah, cry about it Cry
about my monkey placement Okay Yeah You might be wondering
why'd you place him all the way over there He's too good
This monkey was nervous This monkey said I won't work if
he's too close to me He's like, that guy, this guy is like
too, too cool.
He's nervous about it.
Oh my gosh, don't let them through!
Don't let them through!
I'm gonna upgrade him.
I have the crossbow master.
Oh, I can do the superfan.
Is this one any good, the superfan?
This monkey business is getting out of business.
Can the monkey business go out of business?
business I wonder it's
not meta but it sure is funny got it go juggernaut I was
like trying to it's it's slow though isn't it because this
one says it's a slower attacking spike a bolt so I was like
I love the spikes depends on the amount of dart monkeys ah
it says converts up to 10 nearby oh they gotta be dart
monkeys oh what if I have a whole field of only dart monkeys
but i do have crossbow masters so we'll go off we'll go for
that one oh
you guys i think we're in trouble
you fool oh we should give enough money for this guy oh okay
come on boomerang monkey everybody believes in you come on
boomerang monkey nice wait have an upgrade So Moab Press,
let's go for that one.
I also want the Red Hot Rangs.
Nice, nice, nice, nice.
The Spicy Rangs.
You Rang.
We're saving up for Forest Monkey.
Nice.
Where should I put him, though?
This path is kind of difficult.
Because it's like...
It feels like it just...
Does every...
Anywhere I put it, anywhere I put a monkey doesn't cover
enough ground, you know what I mean?
Hey, mean toe.
I forgot that I had the room on my phone.
Got a big surprise while driving a client to his work.
Oopsie!
Your monkey placement is just as random and awesome as you
are.
Thanks, Zach.
Thank you.
Too.
The near the first you turn right here.
Here.
The spirits of the forest awakened.
Oh my god, it's so loud, it spook me.
Yes?
Yes, yes?
Yeah, attack them, attack them, attack them.
Yes?
Ha ha!
What's the monkey that says yes?
I think I'll switch to him next time.
Quincy!
Satan!
He's not that bad, right?
It's my first time seeing this game.
Why do they all have Ike him in voice?
This only...
This guy is a wise monkey.
See?
I always read his name wrong, though.
O-B-Y-N, green foot.
Oh, that's a lot of blue.
Handle it.
You guys stop...
Wait, I thought...
Wait.
Target?
No, it's Oben.
You guys are...
Saying...
You guys...
are typing his name wrong my
fav is pat fusty
how do you misread it usually oh yeah i said i was also
gonna use them okay i'm gonna try some um some other monkeys
this guy also needs to level up as you see i have no nothing
for him
My goal is to get to level 100.
I think Balloons would win IRL.
That's where you're wrong.
That's where you're so wrong.
I read the game title as Balloon Tiddy 6.
So imagine my surprise when I open the stream.
Jonzi Poo, you just have...
You...
Um...
You are...
You...
You have a Freudian slip.
Ah!
Thanks!
for the red!
Whoa!
Hello!
Hello, everybody.
I was on Leah's stream yesterday, if you haven't watched it.
Oh, oh, hold on.
Let me also unpin this.
Thank you.
Thank you, YouTube.
Raymac, thanks for gifting.
All the sick things we're gifting, Murphy, thanks for
gifting!
We got shamed.
Yippee!
What do you mean?
What are you talking about yeah definitely go watch the
collab on liya's channel so fun i'm playing with monkeys
right now oh my gosh thank you for all that gifted you guys
wait wait wait oh aks tf2 thank you kenja thank you rock for
robin thank you fun comics thank you and drago thank you yep
collab was great she just I judged my fashion.
Put in a good way.
Alright.
Monkey, monkey.
I don't know what I'm saving up for.
Let's um, let's upgrade this monkey.
Okay, what's the best way of the ninja?
What is the best path of the ninja?
E-moment?
Tonight will be the night that I will fall for you over
again.
what anime characters are you gonna base your fashion on now
i don't think i've ever based my fashion on an anime
character because i don't even know like i feel like so many
anime characters oh no well okay in the past i always wanted
to like look like paradise kiss but my son got me into you
recently this is his I just wanted to thank my son, Pat
Fusty.
Why do you hate your son, Rachel?
Ashen, thanks for the gift.
I know a lot of YouTubers have big heads, but I think you
have had...
But I think if you had no hair, you could fit three faces on
yours.
Why are you so mean to me?
What the hell is this?
asking for help and uh
pat fussy is a name of honor i think mince monkey placement
sucks yeah i'm gonna make it i'm gonna make you cringe
tonight do you play cookie clicker i do you guys what's the
best way of the ninja stop getting off topic
Who cares if my head is big?
And my neck is extendable.
And my hair is jelly, apparently.
I saw a comet, someone made...
It was like a clip of me or something, I think.
And they were like, wow, Vince's hair is just made of jello
or whatever.
I was like, yo!
Backseaters, where are you at?
IDK, I'm not a ninja.
555 gold wait wait I don't remember what that means wait two
two two five so seeking should he can should be first top
path oh that oh that green ninja said top path and green
ninja is a top is up is a ninja so 502 okay top path is Good
early.
Unlock!
Wait, so, uh, what?
Someone said 5-0-2.
So I'll do this one too.
Nice.
What are you doing?
Do your job!
Oh, whoa.
Wow!
Look at him go!
No, go ahead, wait, wait, wait.
4-2-0.
What did you say?
I said you're a ninja.
You're a ninja.
That's in your name!
I think I've told this somewhat before, but you can change
the size of the cursor, etc.
by clicking hotkeys.
Extra large cursor!
Thank you.
Do you guys want to see my big finger?
Tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle!
Has the Dr. Stone hair?
No, Dr. Stone has my hair.
Where you're tickling?
Sorry, I didn't know that we were, you know...
Okay, let's do...
Hmm.
Let's do quick shots instead.
Very quick shot.
I feel like in this game, quick is most important, right?
We'll just keep collecting money.
This guy down here, this is Dart Monkey 7.
He's our backup support.
Gotta go fast.
I finally made a monkey.
You've made a monkey out of me.
You must be swift as the coursing river.
With all the strength of a great typhoon.
With all the speed of a ninja monkey Mysterious eyes The
dark side of the moon Be monkey
I was thinking maybe I would do a English karaoke next week
I keep saying I'm not gonna do karaoke My voice thrashed fun
i haven't done english karaoke is your voice okay i think so
um i think the hardest part is like when i have to record
the podcast and also like talk for a long time like on
stream and everything that was also part of today i was like
i don't think i really want to talk so much in like So,
please sing B-Monkey version of the song.
Any chance of karaoke of the man who sold the world?
I'd have to learn it, but I could do it.
I graduated college today.
Thanks for helping me get through vitals.
Congrats, Red Christ!
Congrats!
Oh my god!
You did it!
The maid who sold the world.
The good G word.
Yeah.
Yes.
Well, with this I can just sit and back and kind of let the
monkeys do the work.
Yeah.
Send out your stuff.
Oh wow, they're getting really fast.
Oh, we have so much money.
Okay.
This might be a little, you know, like premature, but I
think we got to start getting a farm.
Wait, where can I even put a farm in this map?
Oh my gosh.
A green day karaoke.
A Metal Gear Rising karaoke.
I am so nervous.
nervous about that though because like I feel I feel oh yes
this one's good nice um I don't I just don't feel like I'll
sing them good but I guess it's you know I don't have to
sing it well I can just sing it for fun right I thought this
is a bunny garden stream I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm so I
only had monkey on the brain.
I'm really, really sorry.
I'm really sorry that I'm only thinking about monkey.
Oh, no!
Uh-oh.
Oh.
Um, you go.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh.
I thought we were doomed.
Get a boat.
you buffoon you're so right you're so right actually boat
monkey ahoy what's the oh um it is uh this monkey that can
turn them into gold this monkey will turn our lead balloons
into gold i kind of want him to do that let's put him here
um Oh, no, I have to upgrade it.
Okay, we'll get him.
I'll get enough money.
I only have monkey in the brain, so nothing changed.
The more things change, sometimes the more they stay the
same.
Right?
Happy May Day.
Happy May Day!
I really want...
Look at this.
We have lead and spikes.
Double shot.
Whoa!
Balloon!
Jutsu!
Did you guys ever wonder why we're on the right side of the
screen now?
Oh wait, I told you.
Never mind.
Sorry.
Actually, there's another reason.
Okay, and I'm just really excited.
Okay.
More people join.
again there's another reason that you guys are on the right
side of the screen now instead of the left side of the
screen I asked earlier because usually I have my my chat
settings on the right side and and not chat settings not I
don't know why I said set settings my chat on the right side
or left side and me on the monitors so I moved all of us
over to the right side.
Can I just show you guys?
Can I show you?
Actually, it's May Day.
So I'm going to show you guys, okay?
It's May Day.
Oh, I'm drowning.
May Day, May Day.
The maid cafe may have gotten an upgrade yeah isn't it so
cute isn't it so cute well I say upgrade even though there's
like some cobwebs and some dead plants in here it's okay I'm
working on it isn't it so cute yeah and then we have some
patrons in the cafe yes um excuse me a skew up there please
get back to your seat you're causing a disturbance hold on
i'll show you guys with my with my monkey music in the
background okay hold on hold on sorry i'm gonna i'm gonna
get rid of the chat real quick
Okay, uh, hold on, I'll zoom in.
I'll zoom in, I'll zoom in, I'll zoom in.
Oh!
You didn't see anything?
There we go.
Okay, hold on.
Hold on.
I'm a little scuffed right now.
Okay.
There we go.
See, you got some ghosts here.
Look at them.
They're just... I think this guy is... He's having, like, a
first date or something.
He looks really nervous.
You got this guy singing back there.
He's so cute.
Yeah, he's like, la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
la la la la la la la la la la la la.
And the bustin sign, of course, is still there.
Of course, it must always be there.
My play button!
Because I'm a real YouTuber.
I'm a real YouTuber.
So I have my play button in the background.
These guys, like, enjoying a hot cup of joe.
Yeah.
This guy's my favorite over here.
Just like chilling back there.
It's like...
And a little counter here.
Oh, and the stage.
Yeah.
That's it.
That's it!
Where did I go?
Oh, I'm down here.
Isn't it so cute?
So welcome to the new maid cafe!
Why are we on the menu?
Because you're a snack.
Get off the stage.
I could be over there.
Oh, kairi nasaimasu, go chichinama.
Why is the chat going so fast?
What's happening?
Today is main day.
So I'm gonna play Monkey.
Oh wait, my favorite song.
Monkey.
It's time for monkey!
Monkey time!
Break it down!
Why are you so tiny?
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you!
I want this as my ringtone.
Okay, let's get back to monkey business now.
Sorry, monkeys.
Oh, there goes the chat.
It's zooming.
No, I need funky monkey babies next.
I do!
I do know funky monkey babies.
Oh, this one.
I usually do this one.
Incredible performance, it mesmerized me.
New Rainforest Cafe looking good.
Yeah, I hope you guys like it.
I hope you guys like...
Oh, wait.
So this one, and then maybe faster throw.
Moab, Blue Blim, stand for...
Oh.
Thanks, it's time.
Donkey!
CRMG stands for Zeppelin of mighty gargantuaness.
DDT!
I've never seen the BAD though.
Big airship of Doom.
I don't think so at least.
Definitely seen the DDTs.
It's always like what?
Stage 93 that gets me?
When do the BADs come in?
BADs at round 100.
Ah!
What do you mean a permit for those curtains?
Bionic boomerang
I'll do the faster one
Let's just start getting some Some cannons Don't let the
health inspection see that cafe It's like literally It's
like Don't worry about it You don't even need to worry about
it at all Because Because It's like abandoned There's
cobwebs you guys
The curtains are so close to the candles.
No, they're not.
What?
There's only one candle.
And it's...
It's...
It's this one.
But the curtains aren't even any close to it.
This one right here that I'm pointing to.
It's only candles.
I back off my cafe.
Okay.
Back, back, back.
You know what?
You don't deserve to be served here.
You come into my cafe for a stay in.
And you complain?
Oh, my curtains.
My curtains are too close to the candle.
Oh, my food.
Oh, no.
My food is made if it has ectoplasm.
Oh, the curtain is on fire.
Oh no, the cafe's on fire.
Oh no, I'm dead.
Complaints.
You know what?
Go take it up with the manager.
The manager.
It's me.
DJ, DJ, welcome to membership.
Thank you.
I'm the manager here.
Can I have a...
Okay, back to Monkey.
Oh!
Uh-oh.
I became too small.
There we go.
Okay.
Mint Reaction Corner.
Is that what you want?
Okay, guys.
Hey, guys.
Today we're playing Monkey.
Welcome back to Monkey.
Let's play Monkey Game.
Okay.
Let's play monkey game.
Live mint reaction.
It's like one of those Japanese TV shows.
You can't like see so much of it right down here though.
Are you really okay with that?
Oh!
Oh, we handled it.
Oh yeah, I keep forgetting to upgrade this guy too.
I was trying to make him rich.
I'll give him this one too.
Greetings, Minto.
Long time donator and first time viewer, patron of the Maid
Cafe.
I was burned by the molten chocolate dripping from the
curtains.
Can I get a discount on my meal as compensation?
I'm really sorry, but you signed the waiver when you came in
that says, I don't mind being burnt by the curtains.
The molten chocolate is part of the cafe experience.
Drunk C.S.
Lest.
To my osu.
Go!
Don't drink and super chat.
Yeah, there's a waiver.
There's a waiver.
Monkey!
Monkey, monkey, monkey, monkey.
This is the health inspector.
Oh my gosh, your binary ghost.
So you're actually the health inspector.
There have been reports of ectoplasm in the kitchen.
That's a violation.
Okay, everybody scatter.
Scatter.
You guys, I'm lost.
I don't know where I am.
I'm lost.
Wait.
I don't know where I am.
It's really dark here.
I'm lost.
Where am I?
You guys enjoyed.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm lost.
Hold on.
Let me see if there's like a like a reset.
I'm lost.
This isn't supposed to be funny.
This isn't a bit.
I'm lost, for real.
I can't come back.
I can't come.
I'm clicking and dragging, but I don't know where I am.
I'm lost.
Oh my god.
I don't know.
Oh, wait.
Oh, I thought I could have been.
No!
I'm lost.
in youtube studio i don't know where i am okay guys there's
only one thing that i can do here oh my god uh hold on oh i
think okay hold on i have to recreate myself i think using
using props okay hold on oh no wait i actually don't know
where i am okay i'm gonna be a host know today wait how do i
get it above um wait oh no wait oh no i can't move hoshino
now oh my god hold on no wait okay hold on start over redo
redo where am i you guys i this is okay i'm gonna
use bit 1.0 i don't have bit 1.0 i don't have bit 1.0
Actually, okay, I do have this, but I'm not sure how it will
be.
So I'm kind of nervous.
Okay, hold on.
Oh, no!
No!
Um.
You guys, it's...
It's goofy smile, man.
That's what I have.
It's...
It's the one with the big-ass mind.
So glad we played balloons today.
Look
at myself!
I can't...
I can't even...
Okay, anyway.
Let's bloom.
Wow, they just keep coming.
She's really into it.
I'm having a good time.
Oh, hold.
Actually, let me try something.
Fuck!
It worked!
Yippee!
Your other flew out the window.
Oh my goodness gracious That was a silly bit of a A little
bit
I'm gonna start bringing in Sniper Monkey It's my favorite
guy right here Sniper Monkey is my favorite guy Right here
What's the best place to put him though Hmm Hmm
Maybe here covers, no, up here.
Over, no, up here.
Snipe is a good job, mate.
Welcome back.
It's been like 10,000 years.
I can't believe I got lost.
Bottom right might be better.
Oh, oh, he's gone.
Wait, hold on.
Also, let me move me over a little bit.
There we go.
I'm right.
No.
It covers like, it's because of the house.
I wish I could put him on top of the house, though.
Hmm.
Shouldn't have gone towards the light.
Where the dart monkey?
This one?
Yeah, I think you're right.
I think you're right.
We missed behind the car, but I think it'll be okay.
We'll put some other guys over here eventually.
I'm also going to add, um, okay, hold on.
How do I want to do this?
Because I do want to put a village.
Oh my goodness.
The village takes up so much space.
A 3D balloons game would be crazy.
Didn't you...
Didn't know you enjoyed these monkeys that much.
Just look at that smile.
I'm a monkey fiend.
I love balloons.
Gosh, this one's really hard to fit in though.
Yes, we can click on the car and remove it.
Actually, you know what?
We have enough money to get rid of it.
You just ran my monkey over!
Oh my god.
Oh my gosh.
Stonks.
Stonks, stonks, stonks!
And, uh, wait.
That's not who I wanted to click on.
You.
No, we're waiting for the balloon jutsu.
Stonks, stonks, stonks!
more money um okay I'm gonna put him here I think maybe I
will put a little town there let's go for the Moab assassin
okay oh you hear that money baby awesome awesome awesome
your super silly smile or model reminds me of honey and
clover man you're so rich i also like i i'm bad about like
like i'm like what if i want to save up you know i want him
to get to 21 i gotta i gotta save up
well right now we don't need to do any more spending i think
we're doing okay oh i still extra
money isn't really making that much more i can't though.
Truly, I can't tell.
Oh, and let's upgrade you.
Um, we'll go.
We'll go with the Moab meme.
Nice gift.
Binary goals!
Thanks for the 10 gifted!
For Fox's sake!
Thanks for the five gifted thank you!
Oh my god.
Get him.
Oh.
So
fast.
So easily.
Oh.
Sniper monkey.
You know what?
I'm going to put another sniper monkey.
And I'm going to make him shoot faster.
Fast sniper monkey.
Yeah.
Oh.
There we go.
Upgrade the bow.
I don't have any more.
I don't have any.
more that I can upgrade.
I'm gonna put another boat, though.
We'll put another boat.
Here.
Wait, can I put another boat right here?
No.
I think I might.
I can put one there.
Three boats!
Machine gun sniper monkey.
He's cracked.
That's why I like the sniper monkey so much.
What was I...
Oh, I realized I don't hear stream labs for some reason.
I'm so sorry, you guys.
I might have to turn them up.
I'm the lone wisp at the corner by of it.
Don't worry, ghost fire from ghost candles doesn't burn.
Just like how ghosts can't hurt you.
Bunny Garden got a weird update.
This is the update.
This is optimal bunnies.
See, you see Bubba so much, you return to monkey.
Yippee!
Knowledge point.
Return to monkey.
Monkey, monkey, monkey.
Monkey, monkey.
Monkey.
Nice.
Probably should do some more boomerang monkeys.
Oh wait!
Oh!
Um,
I've been, okay, what's the best monkey, what's the best
route for the, for the boats?
Because monkey is just a superior bunny.
Exactly, road, you get it.
You get it.
Top route.
Top path.
Oh no, wait, I wanted to get that one too.
It's okay.
We can at least start.
upgrading some of these guys.
I'm feeling insulted by that.
Actually, there's quite a few rabbits in there, I think.
Where's the monkey girl cafe?
Whoa, why was it stuck?
Ha, ha.
I'm waiting.
Ooh!
He's waiting.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Am I gonna be okay?
Get it!
Oh, why was it taking you so long?
Buccaneer is one of the best towers I am on.
But each path has its uses.
This is the Buccaneer?
Oh, wait.
Oh.
Like, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Ah, I forgot.
I called just a boat.
Oh.
I think we might be okay.
That's the camel can only shoot sniper with goggles.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
But he had the goggles.
He just wasn't doing anything.
But it's okay.
We are good to go.
Ah, attacks super duper fast.
But I really want the extra money.
But it's only one guy.
Okay, I'll get the destroyer.
It's only one guy that will be generating the money for now.
I don't know what I have that is stopping the moabs.
That's kind of awesome.
Is it you?
Um, is anyone gonna attack it?
Oh, the sniper!
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
So funny.
Alright.
What do I do?
Um, long range.
Oh, camel bloons.
Mmm.
Middle path on the destroyer.
Well, I was going to do one middle and one bottom, so.
Whoa.
Nice.
Oh,
yeah.
I forgot that I need to do this one, too.
The frag bombs.
Should I do a frag or should I do bigger bombs?
two layers pop more blooms maybe the bottom that monkey
placement just works can't let any balloon go through if all
the monkeys at the front start them or stop though yeah frag
yeah that's yeah yeah nice there it is it's coming you guys
don't worry it's gonna get you Oh, it'll show up eventually,
maybe.
Yippee!
All right, let's try and get to level 100.
I've seen somewhere, like, the whole thing is just DDTs.
And I'm like, how much crazier can they get?
I think we'll be okay on the next one, even.
But if not, well...
Look at that.
Oh my god.
Hi, sweetie!
Thank you for the rifting you did!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Thank you, thank you!
Let's see.
I
always feel bad when like people gifts.
Like, you know, I, um, I kind of mentioned it when I first
started memberships that like, you know, I kind of priced it
lower because my focus is on the podcast.
And I know the podcast is not forever.
And once the podcast ends, I'll be able to do more
membership stuff.
But, and I won't change the price.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, we're okay.
Oh, round 63.
is kind of crazy.
Spike turrets can be good on those curves.
I was just...
But I have...
I was just thinking about putting this one.
I do not have...
Like, you're talking about this thing, right?
Melted ice cubes!
Welcome to my show!
Trees.
I know.
I do need to plant some.
But I'm, like, trying to find a good place to plant it.
Right there.
It's perfect, actually.
Um, that's two, let's just...
Nice, and, uh...
Alright, 21.
Uh...
Yeah.
32.
14.
Okay, we can probably get the Elite Defender.
Oh, my dart monkey's down here!
It's completely...
Completely nothing!
We'll just get him too.
Moa, I'm the leader.
Nice.
He's helping.
He was.
He was helping.
Stupid shark!
Thank you for the 20!
Yeah, at least there's the emote.
If I'm working on anything, I'll try and post like little
preview stuff.
But...
Right now, I have...
have like nothing that is that i can show bfb handle it
okay now that we're here
oh my god it can only cover these four if only why can't he
go right there
why why are you so big
Oh range upgrade You are so right You are so right So bigger
That's actually what I do is I do this path But Yeah You
know what I will do this Do I want to do the Bureau
Intelligence Bureau or do I want to Chat is always right.
I don't know about that.
But I already have these one.
Nope, never mind.
I have this one as the bottom.
Oh, I should have.
I forgot that I was going to put the thing here.
I should have done this one as the middle also.
Oh, well.
It's okay.
Chat is kind of mostly sort of right.
Middle path for DDT.
Oh.
this one let's add another boat baby
we'll put you right here we'll just stack them all up
actually can I even I can't but that's okay oh wait maybe
the faster shooting up top you and your boats meant Getting
a little crowded in there.
Not that.
The monkey village.
Oh my god, Samson!
Stop yelling at me!
Oh,
this one for DD team.
Oops, no, you're okay.
I'm kidding.
Don't worry.
Everyone yell at her.
No, stop yelling at me!
I'm sensitive today, you guys.
I'm sensitive.
This is like a classic example.
of miscommunication.
Here I was like, okay, another boat.
I was just like, okay.
Oh, sorry.
I clicked out of the video.
Or the video, the game.
DDT is 90 plus.
Are you sure?
I'm pretty sure there's at least one before, right?
Did I miss Bunny Garden?
I'm confused.
I'm sorry, Blake.
I switched Bunny Garden today to Bloons because I'm...
I didn't, I wasn't, I didn't, I was only thinking of
balloons.
Oh.
But this one allows a more range and pierce and projectile
speed.
It just seems like the whammy, you know?
But what I can do is I can put another one here.
I can put another one here.
one we'll go with the bureau big
brain I know and then it can affect any monkeys down here
bigger radios okay oh my god handle it are blooms the weapon
to surpass metal gear nah I am afraid of no blooms I ain't
afraid of no balloons
Oh wait I spent to do this one
Bustin If you want a really good DDT defense Unlock
preemptive strike on the sub Have it see camo with a village
And you're good to go Ah thanks Ben I'm gonna try I actually
I don't think I've unlocked anything on the sub So We should
No, that's untrue.
That's untrue.
I've unlocked some stuff.
Wait, so pre...
What was it?
Oh, preemptive strike.
Oof.
We're pretty far from that, but...
Planted near the village.
Here.
I'm going to do two of them.
Okay.
I can't upgrade it just yet, but...
Middle path is crazy strong.
Is it?
Okay.
This is why I have you guys here!
Thanks guys!
I don't really need that there, but whatever.
Okay.
600.
Ooh.
It might be tough.
I'm not gonna lie.
It might be tough to get this before.
Is it loud?
Let me be honest with you.
Top path for boat is really good.
We're working on it.
That's fine.
Thank you guys.
You guys are so cute.
Sweet.
Okay.
Make it louder.
Hopefully we get...
let's see we're only at 3,000 but that's okay we're working
on it we're working on it even if we don't have it for this
for this one we can have it for future stuff right
louder nice
i'm gonna try and get um this monkey to the crossbow master
and get him to crossbow him oh wait i forgot him i added
this guy
wait where'd he go wait yeah yeah where's the monkey i just
oh
my my bananas we're gonna go rotten
or oh wait i think actually i should go for the elite
defender i think probably
Eke!
Feel nature's wrath.
Okay, 75.
Bananas have gone bad.
No, they're still good.
They're just a little brown.
Nothing wrong with that.
Whoa!
That was so close, right?
Woof!
Easy peasy.
She's gonna die.
What'd you say, gamer random?
What'd you say?
Would you say I was going to die, huh?
I think, uh...
No, I know that I always usually die at 93.
No, unbeliever.
I wish, though, I could upgrade these guys.
Twin gun.
Actually, because we...
The long-range targeting...
wait which one oh no yeah i'm going for the middle
what's the bottom path oh double attack speed enhances
attack speed of other weapons
advanced intel for subs is huge okay well i have that
unlocked so i figure it's probably better to do it oh wait i
didn't get this one oh my gosh my bad Oops, too many boats
and stuff here.
I have too many boats.
Can't see everything.
Can't see anything.
Well, guys, this might be it.
This might be it.
If it is.
I guess we'll see.
Add another dart monkey.
Dart monkey.
Yeah!
Maybe I can.
I can spike-polt him.
Spike-polt my monkey.
We'll make him faster, because he's slow.
Go monkey, go!
We'll just do a couple of those.
We're still alive, baby!
Oh no!
Oh, we're still alive, baby!
It helps that we have a bunch of guys that are able to see
camo balloons.
So, shoo!
Giant foot.
If you set the target of the spike path to the last, you
will throw all the way down the path.
That is a great idea.
That is actually a really good idea.
Yes, yes, yes.
But you're already dead.
Oh, you're so right.
I'm such a hypocrite saying that we're alive, aren't I?
I mean, you guys are alive.
I'm the dead one.
You know, it just goes things.
I think I can make the next one.
I might regret saying that, but...
Holy cow!
Holy moly!
Rise!
Oh my god!
Yo, look at the memoship there!
Rise!
Wow.
Couldn't even get to the trees!
Oh!
easy peasy just like that I am I am gonna add a helicopter
monkey in here though and I'm going to I want to buy a
village whoops where'd he go but I don't think I can hmm
village
for the snipers that is true too down here I'm
gonna put it here okay so here's the here's the plan put one
here so when i fill out this area it reaches with the range
and then we can have one down here that will help any
monkeys over here so we'll just kind of put this one right
on the edge right on the edge right there and um
should we do it well we have this one oh wait oh oh my gosh
i have this one that's the oh this one yeah I was gonna do
that earlier I completely forgot oh my gosh Keith thanks to
the five gifted money money middle path village for camo and
yeah you're right you're right and we could do the bigger
radius oops no jungle there we go oh the ZOMG ZOMG ZOMG
sorry I'm American
ZOMG Oh my gosh So easy
The snipers already see camo I think This one does not This
one This guy doesn't Now he does because of here This guy
did So it was kind of like whatever But This guy who's super
fast did not So it's okay Um I think this guy also already
did.
Oh yeah, yeah, he did.
But that's okay.
It's okay.
We're gonna have monkeys down here that aren't able to see
camo, so it's okay.
Do you think we'll ever do a few games with the Wisps?
You can even make a team clan and have weekly challenges?
Like, like this game?
Like, bloons game?
Can you, can you make teams and bloons?
Is there multi?
This game has a clan system.
Really?
Oh, then hell yeah!
Let's do it!
Co-op bloons!
I'm gonna...
Can you imagine if, like, two people are trying to play
bloons at the same time and I, like, put something down and,
like, whoever I'm playing with immediately sells it and it's
just, like, stop it!
Like, they sell it, like, put another thing in its place
trying to optimize the map and I'm just like, la, la, la...
Oh, I shouldn't have...
I didn't realize it was still there.
Go, monkeys!
Go!
Gosh.
Crazy.
Have you done a boss battle yet?
In balloons, I have not.
I am not.
I am going to put this one here.
I actually have not used the spike.
factory at all and so i do want to trade it a little bit if
i can um magic monkey i also want to i've barely used him um
i want to get the necromancer the necromancer route so we're
gonna put him like right here he's just kind of like a
random monkey but he can start summoning or should i put him
down here for like extra defense down here fire wizard is
cracked i usually pick fire wizard but it was mitara who was
just like i love necromancer monkey so i kind of wanted to
use it
spike 100 killer with middle path okay we'll focus on the
middle path then what is this one anyway oh the spike storm
oh it's crazy it is it is necrows more cracked i only
remember playing balloons during school what's the current
lore on why these monkeys hate balloons i don't is there no
idea back end defense yeah that's what i was thinking and we
get the help of the of the this i do want him to be able to
like fight more so that he can get more experience but it's
okay oh he's fighting he's fighting look at him go go monkey
go
little monkey thanks to the super chat tracks thank you Ow!
It's okay.
Nature prevails.
I'm wondering if I should have a glue monkey.
Sticky monkey.
Hmm.
Just slow down anybody.
Bottom path for sticky monkey.
Bloon Solver is crazy.
Bloon's a problem.
Here's the solution.
I can't unlock it yet, though.
I'm close to the super glue.
Bottom path is good late game.
Let's get a glue monkey.
We'll put him kind of close to the front so we can start
slowing people down.
I'm just going to put him right on top of there.
And we're going to give him...
We're gonna do the bottom path for you.
I usually do bottom path and then two up top.
Zero two five glue is good, especially since you have camo.
Oh, like this one.
Okay.
Zero two five.
Start slowing those glues down.
I mean, those bloons down.
Yeah!
I feel like that already made a ton of difference.
Holy cow.
Oh, wait.
Maybe I should have.
You know what?
Whatever.
Are you doing anything?
Are you working?
It's 22.
Yeah!
Rise!
Can you, like, do something, though?
Can you hear that?
Upgrade some towers.
I think for the most part, I've upgraded anything that I can
unless I'm...
No, we're doing middle path here.
Why is the sub taking so long to unlock anything?
Like, the sub is taking so long to get any experience, but
they're killing a...
Look at... Oh, wait, that's the boat.
What's the name of the monkey on the bottom right?
Is that a new monkey?
I've been playing balloons in a while.
Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo.
Less XP past post stage 60.
Oh, I didn't realize.
Oh, I think actually I was told that before.
And I just completely forgot.
I'm going to place a helicopter down here.
This might be not the best placement right here.
But it's also kind of hard to place on this map.
And I want him.
Because, oh wait.
But he'll also get to attack any type of bloom.
Okay.
So, can you destroy the house?
You can't.
Oh!
Tickle, tickle.
Kelly's good can move it wherever.
Yeah, so usually what I do with the helicopter is I do, um,
I do two, five.
But, no, I'm sorry.
The two up here.
I do two zero five well four in my case but two zero five is
fine even if I so but if I put it here I'll be able to to um
actually I might be able to put it right here oh come on
there is space there maybe down here then over here on the
rock Maybe right here then.
Put it next to the snipers.
Okay, yeah.
I think it'd be best to have the power up from the...
Two...
Five, okay.
Yeah!
Set OMG!
Handle it!
But it's Haram!
Handle it.
What the heck?
So easy.
Handle it.
Go, monkeys!
Go!
We don't have the DDTs yet, so...
Oh my gosh!
I'm watching from bed.
You better be doing the stuff that you were supposed to be
doing, Missy.
You better be doing that stuff.
She's developing a new meta.
You'd be homeless if you had...
Wait, if this had an MGS collab, jet section.
Why are you gonna say it like that?
I wouldn't...
I didn't...
I didn't become homeless when Fortnite had Metal Gear, huh?
So...
I think I'm pretty good.
I think I'm okay.
I think I can handle myself.
As OBGYN would say.
Handle it.
Holy cow!
Oh my god.
Our monkeys.
Oh no, I was like, oh good, we have enough.
No, I need the top.
Oh my gosh, I need so much more for the top.
It's, like, really tempting to, like, purchase the other
upgrades when you see that they're green in a lot of me.
Like, this one.
Ah!
Oh!
Heat tips.
Okay, we're gonna upload.
Upload.
We're gonna upgrade the Moab Eliminator next.
What with the adjective?
for a monkey be like Psycho Mantis or Sniper Wolf?
Monkey, monkey.
Wizard?
Where's my wizard?
It's so hard to see where anybody is.
Uh, he's also pretty...
Oh wait, no, wizard.
Oh, him!
No, he's like got nothing.
My wizard's at nothing.
He's so small.
Manic monkey actually that sounds That actually sounds like
it could be real Manic monkey Who's that monkey?
Monkey monkey Who's that monkey?
Monkey monkey Oh wait Or maybe Maybe I should do the sniper
monkey Hmm Maybe I should make my sniper monkey instead of
you.
This is the...
Moabs are immobilized for longer and take extra damage from
all the other attacks.
You can name your monkeys with them.
A.K.A.
sniper wolf.
I can?
No, I can't.
Change sniper to strong.
Which?
Oh.
I usually do.
Thank you.
Handle it.
Handle it!
Oh, they're fast.
Oh, they're fast and they're furious.
Nature prevails, everybody.
Need to buy the ability to name them from the shop.
Really?
That's crazy.
Coming up on the faded round soon.
We're getting close to DDTs.
I know, I know, I'm scared.
First DDT check.
Oh gosh.
That's why I'm thinking I should...
Massive damage to Moab's and assassinate ability deals six
time damage with a short cooldown.
Take extra damage from all the other attacks.
I think I'm gonna save up for the sniper monkey.
No way!
Oh,
thank you.
I always forget.
I do usually change these, but I think I'm just, like, silly
because I...
Because, you know.
Just silly things.
I must resist.
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh!
Ooh, that was not so great.
That was not so great.
That was a little rough, I think.
That was a little rough.
No, don't leave!
No, but...
Big sniper monkey.
He's slow, though.
I wonder if it's okay.
that he's so slow
ZOMD RISE
it's the next round that I'm really worried about you guys
uh oh wait oh no oh no we're about to lose okay it's the
next round that I'm worried about hmm I don't think I have
so much money that I can like also I should just start
unlocking these because i have nothing else to unlock here
the dreaded 93
both both snipers target strong so we're okay pursuit spike
factory is just down here doing his thing oh gosh you got
this unironically you think so okay i just always die at 93
so we'll see oh okay good
let's go
let's go easy easy peasy i love balloons Oh my gosh.
Is there anything else we should add in?
I was thinking...
No!
We're close.
No.
We'll save up.
Um.
I'm trying to...
I thought it was a good place for Gatlin Monkey.
Hmm.
Add a glue monkey?
Oh.
Okay, if you guys think I need another one.
Where is he?
Oh, glue monkey.
Like right here.
Right next to other glue monkey.
Um, should I just do the same?
Well, this one, maybe I do the corrosive on this one, right?
Or should I just do the same route?
You can make that one aggressive with a balloon liquefier.
Alchemist busts, butt, butt, butt, butt.
Alchemists buff snipers?
Glue does not stack with other glues.
It doesn't.
Uh-oh.
But maybe then we do the corrosive.
So if he gets, if he slows them down, he starts, he starts,
uh, so we'll do, we'll do the corrosive.
Um, then we'll do, we'll do more.
He gets, he gets more of them.
He gets anything that...
Alchemists are really good.
Oh, shoot.
Okay.
I'm gonna...
Alchemist Monkey D.
down here this is the alchemist right my own oh yeah yeah
okay right there baby how does he buff them powerful
monster top path louse oh there's a helpful potion that
nearby monkeys pop lead balloons and do extra damage to
ceramic oh there was a special brew the nearby monkeys
giving them extra damage range Well, range, whatever,
because it's, you know, snipers, but...
Hmm.
Okay.
Let's try it.
And then maybe the pool for, like, extra damage down here.
Top Alk is mega OP.
Really?
Oh.
You can try another round.
Yeah!
Pool is useless, really?
Okay.
I'm trusting you guys.
I'm, like, trying to...
I'm trying not to rely on you guys too much, but also take
your advice.
I don't want to seem like I'm just...
Ah!
Oh my god.
Holy cow.
It's okay.
Maybe.
Oh, maybe it's not okay.
Oh, no!
No, it's okay!
Oh, yeah, I don't think the Moab glue is working!
Uh-oh.
I think
That was close That was close The glue liquefied is
overriding the Moab glue Yeah, uh-oh Uh-oh I think I just
wasted a bunch of money Wait, what's going on here?
Why is it bubbly?
Why is it bubbling like that Oh, because he gave me a
potion!
That's so cute.
Sell useless stuff.
No one's useless to me.
I wish I could move them instead of just selling them, you
know.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, balloon liquefier.
Sorry, I shouldn't have put you there.
I shouldn't have put you there.
Ooh, that scratch is a good itch.
Oh, this one I can unlock!
Should I unlock?
Wait, I might just be able to put that on him.
Wait, what does this do actually?
Glue so strong and temporarily immobilizes all affected
blooms.
Oh, let's go!
You know what?
Let's just get it.
How much is it?
we can do it live live live live oh
my god oh
my god oh my god oh my
god you said not even close but to me that was pretty close
that felt pretty close to me.
I love I love Heli.
Heli monkey is so good.
Heli monkey is awesome.
What is this one?
Upgraded weapons also automatically causing three more
monkeys.
Permanently.
98 is scary.
Okay.
97.
Everything above 90 is a pain apparently.
Here's the second VTuber I've seen excitedly shout I love
bloons Thanks Rico Don't know to test Don't know test to say
Minto is Stinko on Fridays I don't know why I can't hear I
mean the game is kind of loud but But was not clenched My
butt was kind of clenched I don't know why I can't Why I'm
not hearing the stream labs But I am reading them so Lampi
Welcome to Mambusha Thank you Thank you so much
One tier 5 to survive round 100.
I have two!
Well, tier 5 what?
There's no notice.
At all?
None at all.
That's weird.
That's very strange.
How long is the wait for a party at one of your cafes?
Um, don't worry about it.
Orange sniper.
This guy on fur?
I think he might actually need to be first because he's so
fast and if people are down here you need to like go for him
you know oh uh this one we can now pay for right we went for
the we're going for the this one right yeah this is a test
of the emergency super chat system it's not super chats with
the issue what kind of a game is this is a tower defense
game Oh my gosh, thank you.
Holy cow.
I think this one is all, yeah, it's good for now.
Oh my gosh, thank you.
Can't believe I forgot to do that.
Super glue.
Trying to think of I should add something else.
Maybe another ship.
Maybe another boat because they have so much range.
Or a sub down here.
Like right here.
More helicopters?
Nah.
Okay.
Boat on lower.
Okay, so we'll do the boat instead.
Down here.
If I can place them, hello?
There we go.
Nice and cozy.
What did I do for these guys?
guys uh no not you so it's five two right five two and then
more glue is what people are requesting i can do more glue
especially because we got our other guy before maybe we put
him like wait oh he gets the we can get the buffs here maybe
like here
or over here actually over here might be better oh my gosh
please stop spamming i'm definitely not going to add an ice
monkey if you continue to spam thank you oh my gosh holy cow
sorry i'm trying to figure out where to place this guy maybe
actually here would be better because it's because it'll hit
them for down here okay and we're gonna glue so and we're
gonna glob actually yeah we're gonna glob it up okay attempt
handle it oh my gosh please handle it
please rise okay I guess I could have been worse
Why does Midday Balloon so much?
It's not balloons, it's balloons.
Not bad.
It could be worse.
They still got what down here about.
So.
What's in?
Welcome to membership.
Thank you.
And GK Cyrene.
Welcome to membership.
Monkey.
Duck your smoke on the membership.
Thank you guys.
Thank you so much.
Slow them down more for what?
Oh, the ice.
Oh my gosh.
Please.
Pack cake.
I don't even have my guys upgraded.
I don't think they'll do much.
Okay.
I think before I mentioned adding another helicopter.
I wish I could put them right in there.
But, um...
Unfortunately, he might have to be...
He may have to be...
Villageless.
You can sell the Spike Factory.
You know what?
I think you're right, actually, because...
We're not getting anything from him.
So yeah, we'll sell him.
What?
Fireball!
Oh, I really want the Necromancer.
answer.
07 Spike Factory.
Oh, I was gonna say, can I even fit?
I think I can make him fit to where I can add some other
monkeys into.
Like, let me see.
Can I put like...
Oh.
No.
Oh, a little bit.
A little bit.
Um...
Okay.
Hmm.
Spike Factory has served its purpose.
A 000 ice monkey is insecure.
Let's see.
Okay, we're gonna do...
I like to do the pursuit.
We have Moab shove.
Do I want another one, though?
Shove is Emblem.
buy and buy it bigger jets um and our little guys when
they're needed i'm wondering if i should just do four two on
this one i can only go up to three though i don't have the
apache dart ship i don't have apache monkey how do you say
this com com com com chomach Comanche?
204 spam!
You'll get to 4 soon enough?
I don't think in this though because I'm higher so the XP is
way lower.
If you like tower defense, check out Domekeeper.
Oh I do.
Trip trap!
Welcome to membership.
Comanche.
Oh my god.
204.
I think I feel safer like that.
Because then I can do the high level one, you know?
Okay.
Here we go.
Handle it.
C-O-M-G.
really moving because both of them are shoving.
Yo!
Let's go!
Yeah, the sniper and the two planes are just making him
like, stuck there.
Nice.
You know what?
I'm even gonna go for round the next round.
This might be a mistake, but...
Nature prevails, baby.
Nature prevails!
Don't bust it, no!
Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh!
Oh my god, no!
I'm gonna die!
I just wanted to get to level one, had...
The last round was such a tease.
It made me feel so confident.
Oh, we were two levels away.
No.
98 is one of the hardest rounds.
Yeah, wrong.
Okay, Icarus.
Hey, what would have happened if you had the zero, zero,
zero ice monkey?
Not sure how monkeys got their hands on Comanche's when the
Comanche program was canceled 20 years ago before it even
entered production.
Look, monkey technology is not for you to judge, okay?
You vegetated it.
Only you listen to Ice Monkey.
It's mint over.
Dang you.
Dang you!
Wait!
It's free.
If I want to continue.
Need more Hinde.
Free continue!
For free?
Do not.
Why not?
We could get to level 100!
Right?
Only the first continues free.
Just level the monkeys.
You're probably right.
It would be better to get more experience.
Look, that monkey is just like me.
Monkey is just like me.
Game over.
No,
stop here taking my spotlight, monkey.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
My bad.
Game over!
Oh god.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Why are you like this?
What are you talking about?
Collection event.
I'm collecting a monkey!
Insta!
Insta monkey!
Wait, what are these?
Featured Insta monkeys.
Wait, someone said by the fountain, right?
This guy...
There's a... Is it a challenge to get the monkey?
No.
Tutorial to get the monkey?
You can get whatever the hell these are.
Experiments on the monkey?
50 Moab class balloons on each round!
How much money did they give you up first?
The raids.
Oh, is that what it is?
Wait, how do you see the raids?
Hold on.
Monkey boost.
Events.
Ah!
You need to be level 40.
Well, shucks.
social I want to change my oh good good good let's change to
general monk oh no sniper monkey my favorite my favorite
sniper monkey any new heroes I think I have to pay for all
of them there he is the the Pat Fusty by Benjamin.
Um, Eliza.
Adora.
I don't have so much money, though.
I can't even afford a single monkey.
Geraldo.
The goat.
I like Corvus.
Is this guy new?
A guide to the book of spirits.
Help Corvus harvest the bloons on dark paths.
What does he do though?
Oh here.
Haunted balloons!
Are weakened and explode when popped, adding mana to the
mana pool.
The spirit attacks balloons wherever on the map of Corvus'
command.
Interesting.
It's amazing but hard to use optimally.
The Corvus is too complicated.
Whoa, my...
Whoa!
Awesome!
I like how... I like... I like this guy.
That's me.
Oh, yes.
I like when they have different outfits.
I know they're just cosmetic, but they look so cool.
Wait, does he have one?
No.
Whoa.
Ocean Guardian.
Corvus can solo!
That's insane.
Sada is good for being there.
I love this one.
This Yangshi is so cute!
I've never played a Sada.
Slashes.
Oh, can Pop Camo?
She's awesome.
She's so cute.
It's really good on most maps.
Someone said Gerardo.
Oh, here's Gerardo.
Oh, it's cute.
Gadgetier.
Paragon belt.
I'll be honest.
like I don't really read what they do it's probably bad
there's just so many effects there's so many I like striker
Jones too oh my god Octo Jones is so cute biker bones
Geraldo sells stuff he can use oh really I like Ben because
he just gives you more money nothing complicated or crazy
love that i love that hi mentos one time random question but
i need to satisfy my curiosity are you interested in playing
toho fan games thanks for stream yuppie yeah i would be
interested i can play whatever i want now there was actually
um some toho i guess you would call them fan games or not
official some game some other toho games on steam that i'd
wanted to play before but never could so now i will have the
opportunity to i think not i think i know i saw i saw um i
saw fuawa playing mountain of faith the other day i was
watching her and i was like it's making me want to play toho
oh i also want to play mountain of faith maybe not mountain
of faith I don't know which one I would want to play
but I love the music and mountain of faith so much essay
I've never I was never good at subterranean animism never
good at it I was thinking UFO but I don't know I mean I'll
try practicing more off stream so that when I play I can
actually like it somewhere because it's first of all i need
to be good enough to overcome my performance anxiety do not
play mistia's isakaya or you'll lose 60 plus hours of your
life to it that's one of the ones i wanted to play though oh
my gosh mistia's isakaya what kind of game is it i think i
wait did i buy it i do i own it I own it, I bought it.
Highly recommend.
Missius Izekiah on Hero of Iceberry.
Super tough as at first, though.
Clown piece kicked my ass three times.
Was this restaurant sim?
Oh god, that sounds so fun.
And there's lots of...
Holy moly, there's so much DLC.
Does this count as a fan game?
I mean, it has so much content, but I guess it's a fan game,
though, right?
Not a fan game?
I do own it though After I was thinking because I'm like
trying to Figure out like a schedule ish type Of what I'm
doing for like longer Form games like right now I would say
Ghost Trick is like the Longer game I'm playing Right now I
think after Ghost Trick I'll play
Oh my god stop I just looked this up the other night.
And I couldn't remember the name of it the other night.
I was like, I was like, no, wait.
Hold on.
Oh my god.
My brain.
She plays Xenoblade.
I actually do.
Kameniki told me to play it, and I said I would.
So I think I have to play it.
But I'm hesitant to start such a huge, such a huge thing.
Right now.
But Xenoblade will be eventually, most likely.
They just finished translating the last DLC for the...
Two, the Izakaya team are super cracked for being so small.
That's so awesome.
Mike!
Thanks for the...
Pink!
This is the Purgatory Made Cafe.
We would like to inform you that in recognition of your
10,000th visit, you are now a Platinum Tier member.
However, we humbly request that on your next visit, you
cease to Wotage with the breadsticks.
You can't tell me what to do!
As your platinum member, I should have permission to vote
again with whatever I please.
Even if it's like, even if I grab someone's feet and swing
the person around, like pen lights.
Baking a cheesecake for my mom for Mother's Day.
Never made one before, but it smells good in the oven.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
I've made cheesecake before.
It's not so difficult.
It's pretty good.
It's pretty, it's not so bad.
Okay.
Oh yeah, um, yeah, I'm not gonna buy anything right now.
I'm gonna switch the...
Ride in Quincy.
What if I bought...
Oh, I wouldn't want to level up to 20, though.
Wolf pack Quincy.
I'm gonna switch the Quincy, though, so we can...
Are you kidding me?
Nothing gets past my boat.
So we can hear...
Are you kidding me?
up but the highest round someone got was 3,275.
Now my round 250 seems small.
Thanks for streaming.
I'm not done yet!
Sunday is my birthday.
Can I get a song?
Yeah, the Otage to recommend for beginners.
What would it be?
Like, Otage move or Otage, like...
Hold on, I'm gonna pick a thing real quick so I can stop
listening to the song.
Oh, the loop has a golden balloon, so let's do that one.
Um...
Do you mean like Otage as in like Tiger Fire, Cyber,
Fireball?
A move?
Or do you mean like...
Thunder Snake?
I don't know, I feel like Thunder Snake might be kind of
hard for people.
You can start with the simple stuff, like O-A-D and...
And, uh...
P-P-P-H.
And then...
But once you learn Thunder Snake, I'll admit you feel...
pretty cool doing it.
All in with Namaste, Snake.
That too.
Time to do it.
Otage Teaching Stream.
The day I get 3D.
I have to do that and I have to do a dance cover of
Umamushime.
I finally can do that.
If I get 3D, I'll actually have 3D.
so I can use it
okay Quincy my man my man Quincy and then this map we can
put sniper wolf anywhere so it's fine um what is Quincy oh
Quincy's range is pretty good actually I'm gonna put you
right here in the middle alright good job just give me a
target just give me a target yes Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes Shah, shah,
shah, shah!
Easy peasy.
On the chocolate river map, you can find monkeys hidden in
the map and you click them in the right order.
I think I have done that before.
Okay, guys, before we get any further, what are some
monkeys, not ice monkey, that we are trying to level up?
Like, TAC Monkey and Wizard Monkey!
Okay, buy Wizard Monkey.
Buy the Wizard Monkey.
Oh yeah!
I'm not listening to anything...
Anything that says Ice Monkey.
Especially if Nanoplasm says Ice Monkey.
I don't even know if that person is still here.
I might have really made them mad.
I don't even know if
it's...
Ninja monkey.
Oh, um...
Because I want the blue jutsu.
Blue jutsu.
Have I been saying blue jutsu?
This whole time.
Blue jutsu.
Wow, he looks so awesome in this outfit though.
He looks cool there too though.
But this one's so cool!
Wow!
Oh, wait, that's the...
This guy's scratching his head like, why am I here?
Okay, do something, Wizard Monkey.
Uh-oh.
Wow, Wizard Monkey.
Wow.
Oh, we'll do the spikes here.
Oh my gosh, Wizard Monkey.
You really let the ball down there.
Okay, we'll put... I usually put We'll put this one in here,
but we'll wait for Spike's monkey.
We'll wait for Spike's monkey.
He can already evolve!
Intense magic.
Oh, he turned into a nerd!
Blizzard monkey is a 000 tower.
He's doing his best.
He became blind.
What is this astronaut monkey anyway?
I can't tell.
It looks like he's wearing a space suit.
Okay.
Attack monkey will be in the middle.
Here.
Oh, we also gotta do our submarines too, right?
Because we're trying to get...
Bluntoni... Wait, no.
We're trying to get a preemptive strike, right?
So I'm gonna put one guy in there too.
Ha!
Wow, Quincy.
Okay.
I've got a fever and the only cure is ice monkey.
Are you actually sick?
Oh, I forgot to spend money on my intense magic.
Alchemist monkey?
What were we trying to level up for him?
The top one though, right?
I don't know where I want to put him yet though.
Yeah, we were trying to do the top one.
I do want to get this guy down too though.
My guide says 000 ice monkey is best in the corner where I
can't hit anything.
It's the best slide.
Everyone has a 000 ice monkey on their map, obviously.
4 to Alka's OP.
That's what we're trying to get here.
But I don't know where to put him.
I guess I can put him here with everybody, right?
I can have him kind of like that.
Or maybe...
Where will he cover most monkey ground?
He broke monkey ground!
Ice monkey in bio.
Near Quincy?
So it's like right there, good.
I think.
Okay.
Sneak up on him.
Like, right.
Actually, I want enough space here.
So we'll put him right here.
I love when they're all really good friends.
Oh.
I can't even tell if he's doing anything.
Some monkey is listening.
Look how cute he is in the little boat.
la la la la he's like rockin side to side he's so cute
little he's just a little guy oh he's so funny monkey sense
monkey sense monkey sense monkey dollars a monkey sense sub
will shoot if you get the top two yeah we're gonna we're
that one will be oh wait yes wait no we're going for the
middle one sorry we're going for middle barbed darts why is
the chat crazy about ice monkey because there was someone in
here earlier who is spamming that they really wanted ice
monkey so you
can do the top two then go for middle oh I guess that's true
you're right you're so right
Shoot!
I'm sure Ice Monkey is a really nice guy, okay?
Oh, the hearts.
The hearts, I'm confused.
Do they grow more hearts?
Do they just regrow their layers?
Which monkey is your monkey sauna?
Oh, they regrow.
So they regrow layers.
Oh,
yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you for the Akasuba!
It could have used a little more ice monkey.
I gotta have more ice monkey, baby.
Why did you send an Akasuba for the ice monkey?
Why would you do that?
Why?
Balls in your court, Missy.
Oh no.
Can I even afford?
I can't even afford the ice monkey.
I can't even afford him.
How's your Friday going, you guys?
Do you have any plans for the weekend?
Talk.
Welcome to Mumbuship.
Thank you so much.
you gotta i just bought something else oh i can afford him
now okay fine this is for you joshua these freezes one
balloon at a time ice monkey funds
not really i plan to dye my hair oh wait by yourself are you
going somewhere it's already weekend in my country yippee
what are your plans come on What does he do?
I started that, but I don't even know.
Come on.
Ice monkey!
Okay, so what's the best row for ice monkey now?
Let's see.
Frozen bloons grow sharp icicles that can pop bloons that
touch them.
Freezes all regular bloons on screen.
0-0-0, of course.
I hate you.
I hate you guys so much.
Fine, I'm gonna keep him there.
I'm gonna keep him there and he is going to be 0, 0, 0 the
whole time.
Westtrip happy birthday!
And you look at your profile picture.
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday meat mom.
Happy birthday Westtrip.
Meet my...
Meet my mom...
Happy birthday!
Ice monkey sucks.
Please sell it.
Sorry.
If you want me to sell it, Aka Supa... No, I'm just kidding.
Please don't do that.
The ice monkey is not worth it.
It's not worth a bit.
Please.
Also, I love that ice monkey 000 get donated in streamlabs.
One of the ice monkey freeze blast sound effects is similar
to the one the front fruit quench sounds.
Did I say French?
When slicing fruit in fruit ninja.
I have never played fruit ninja.
Lily breeze.
You're gonna have to keep that name until YouTube allows you
to change it back.
I'm just letting you know.
Okay, where are we at?
I want to have this guy out, so...
Ooh.
Ew.
Long reach, maybe.
But I want the bigger stacks, maybe.
Hmm.
Not there.
Oh my god.
Mike!
Ice monkey.
Worth...
Carla, please sell the ice monkey and buy another one at...
He's at 0-0-0!
I did an upgrade!
He's 0-0!
He has no upgrades!
He's zero already!
Stop!
That's a bad one.
Yo, it's not worth a bit, you guys.
Go see the next for the five membership.
Sell the ice monkey.
Look, he's juggling with the ice, you guys.
How am I supposed to sell this?
Okay.
My god!
Keep him in.
Look at his greatness.
Buy another zero, zero, zero, one.
after you sell it.
I said I was gonna keep from 0, 0, 0.
No!
I'd like to cancel Ice Monkey.
You guys, please.
I'm serious.
It's not worth...
This is the dumbest bit ever.
It's not worth sending this!
Okay.
I'm going to continue on moving forward.
Okay, everybody, we're moving forward with our afterlives.
Oh, I'm moving forward with my afterlives.
I can't tell who's winning the bid war at this point.
Me neither.
Okay.
If I sell this ice monkey and put him in the middle of the
field where he will be absolutely useless, will you guys
feel better?
So then I technically sold him and I bought another one.
Bye, bye, bye.
Ice, ice, ice.
Do it.
No, don't sell.
Zero, zero, zero in the middle.
He'll be the mascot.
But I'm worried he can't hurt anybody.
Ice, ice, baby.
Sweet.
I feel like I lost in the end.
I feel like...
I feel like I just got bullied.
Into...
Into this.
No.
I feel like...
Yeah.
Oh my gosh.
Ballistic missile.
Holy cow!
Membership lapsed midstream, so I was darnly not green.
Here's extra after reading.
I don't need extra, but thank you.
I
got two monkey bugs.
Yippee!
Gonna join the 30s gang on Tuesday.
Could you sing me a happy birthday song and a granny voice
with love, Bozo?
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday.
Young man.
Dear Bozo.
Happy birthday.
you let's get the berserker brew after this i am quincy son
of quincy i didn't know he said son of quincy like that i am
quincy so no he has an upgrade ice monkey wins by doing
nothing this is crazy
Ice Monkey has an upgrade!
I
don't even remember what this does.
Oh yeah, that's right.
He's just juggling in the middle.
I am Quincy.
Son of Quincy.
Okay.
I can post this here.
If I put it right in the middle, can I still put monkeys on
the side?
Like a ninja monkey around.
Oh my gosh, can I put this in the middle and then decorate
him with ninja monkeys?
Not the last loop?
This loop instead?
Okay, Samson.
Samson's really, like, adamant of it.
Won't fit.
Are you sure?
Oh, wait.
Hold on.
Oh, I can't afford anything anymore.
But we need these guys to level up, too.
We need these guys to get more experience also.
Ha!
What was...
So it was...
Magic shots last longer to seek out the balloons, even
behind cover.
Pop through two layers.
Oh no, I want the wall of fire.
I think.
We'll do the wall of fire.
Fireball.
I'm sorry, I'm just enthusiastic.
It's okay, just try not to spam too much.
But I'm asking for help from you guys, so I don't mind the
backseating a little bit.
I'm going to do actually the stronger acid because I
remember someone saying the acid pool is not as good.
So we'll do that.
You want some?
You want some!
Ice Monkey Standing Center!
He's like, yeah!
And then when we win, he juggles.
It's so awesome!
My favorite intern.
Yay!
Juggle, monkey, juggle!
David, thanks for the five gifted.
I'm barely taking this one seriously.
I can barely concentrate.
He's so cute.
He is really cute.
He's pretty cute.
Why is it so hard to place these?
Like, what the hell?
Ice Monkey got me distracted too.
Monkey Farms, you're right.
Oh, this has an upgrade.
We're gonna go for the faster production.
Ooh, it's purple.
Okay, I have no money, so...
Why do I juggle so fast?
Juggle, juggle, monkey!
Juggle, ice monkey!
Dark Sider, welcome to bamboo shop.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Holy cow.
Um, I think I was going for banana.
You want banana?
We have banana.
Banana crates?
We're 300 each.
Nice.
Wall of fire.
So this one is 10 battle.
Wow, he looks so cool.
Okay, I need more money.
Oh, pop it, pop it, pop it!
Pop the golden cup!
Pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop it!
Yippee!
Okay, nice.
It's also the banana bank.
Which one's that?
The Wall Street one?
Hub of Monkey Trades earns colossal income, generates lives
each round.
What?
Two more dollars.
Hey, two dollars is two dollars that I did not spend with my
real money.
Even faster.
Bank is the middle.
Monkeyomics?
Oh, all money generated in this farm is now stored in the
bank and earns 15%.
Oh!
I see, I see, I see.
Okay, I'll do another one.
Okay.
And we'll go for the middle path.
Gold balloon for you.
Oh, thank you.
Missed, wow, Falcon of Membership.
Thank you so much.
Oh, this map is making me wish it was fall.
Okay, uh-oh.
I just realized, aren't we have a lot of balloons getting
through.
Watch out for the Moab.
We have a lot of balloons getting through.
Why do I think we're in trouble?
I think we're a bit in trouble.
We'll do the wall of fire at least.
And even the faster production.
What's this one?
Collect a radius of bananas is larger.
Uncollected bananas auto-collect.
Nah, I'd rather have more.
Nah, you'd win.
Did you play this on stream with Mata?
Actually, I would love to if she wants to.
But I think we might be like, Put this monkey here.
Now, put this monkey here.
Is Engineer monkey good?
Maybe we should get him too.
I haven't used him once.
And I haven't really used the Druid monkey.
Oh, I have a little bit.
I lied.
good engineer gaming okay if i put him like here kind of as
like a defense at the end of the you know the end of the the
end of the end of the line top path engineer goaded with the
sentry that's the one i was looking at because it kind of
seems fun removes camo and regrow and pops Wow.
Engineer puts more gun.
I love gun!
But how far do they reach, you know?
Bottom's good for money.
I think we're good for money right now.
A decent range?
So I don't have to put him right here then.
I could put him like here.
And he's kind of like building his little sentries and
they're like...
Average range.
Put them where Quincy is.
Oh, okay.
Like here.
So here actually then.
Yeah, basically.
Not that much of a range.
Okay.
The engineer.
Yeah, but he'll build in his range, but But the sentries can
shoot wherever, right?
So or the sentries can only shoot in the little circle that
he's in is what I'm asking
Oh, he gets the buff here, so Centries have their own range.
Ah, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Oh, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
You can become huge with the middle one.
Longer range.
I wish sometimes you could, like, I wish sometimes it wasn't
just a circle.
Like, I wish I could make a rectangle, you know.
Circles in this game are so hard.
How you doing, Ice Monkey?
Okay.
Are you working hard or are you hardly working?
You know what?
I don't have any snipers, so let's add a sniper right here.
Right here.
Actually, okay, hold on.
How do I want to do this?
Because I also want to add a village.
We could put the village right here and sniper monkeys and
then some guys down here, probably.
Hmm.
Incoming!
Oh, we're fine.
I think.
Yeah.
All right.
Yeah, we're fine.
We're fine.
I need more money.
All right.
It's like the dune...
It's like the dune popcorn bucket.
Right?
Just me?
Okay.
Yeah.
Um, I'm gonna do bigger because I don't think I need to
reach longer.
I think we're okay.
Let's do bigger stocks.
Actually, no, I'm gonna hold out.
Why are you guys saying ha?
What are you saying ha for?
Looks just like it, I think.
Holy moly, we have so much money!
I wish I could upgrade you.
Close though, we're close.
Let's see.
What else?
Um, stronger stimulant.
Shimmer.
I am Quincy.
Yeah, I know.
Son of Quincy.
I am Quincy.
Let's go for the Moab here.
And I'm going to actually do faster firing because we have
the intent of building a village right now.
there so don't necessarily need currently
spend it all on ice monkey we're rich baby I just need them
to generate a little oh wait I can still do the same thing
even though we're taking different paths with each one of
them.
I just realized.
Oh yeah!
That's what I'm talking about.
I think your spikes are stale.
What?
Why do you think that?
They're actually really great!
Monkey bank!
The middle path druid is very broken.
This guy?
Really?
I always go for the top one.
Dang, he generates a life and cash?
But see, this one, like the druid, this one, it only...
He only gets one balloon at a time.
Rosado!
Welcome to membership, thank you!
Middle is OP.
Okay, we'll add him.
Let's try him out.
Rise.
We'll put you right...
Look at him waving.
He's strong trust.
Next to the bank?
Like here?
Wait.
What is the upgrade?
I'm confused now.
Generates cash.
Cash each use plus extra cash per banana farm.
Oh my god.
Wait.
Does this count as near?
Oh.
Let's go.
Oh, the old bin buffs the druids.
I do remember that, actually.
Give us money.
Whoa!
He got rid of all of those.
That was really crazy.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah!
Good job, Quincy.
Son of Quincy.
I'm doing deadly.
I'm doing the precision with this one.
Oh, I should have should have bought the monkey bank.
But that's okay.
What are you doing anyway?
Ah, look on the membership, thank you so much.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Okay, we need jungles bounty.
Oh, we're so close though.
Awesome.
Go!
Get it!
Get the cow!
Yeah!
Two real bucks.
We want the real bucks.
Monkey!
Thanks for the 20!
Thank you so much.
We're super done.
Monkey, monkey, monkey, monkey.
This location, I feel like, kind of sucks.
He's just really random.
He's just randomly there, but that's okay, too.
Is that all you got?
Wow, he was really strangling that guy right there.
Hayden, thank you so much for the five gifted.
Thank you.
Oh, my gosh.
Just noticed how much money we have.
Bank, bank, bank, bank, bank.
Wait, should I do bank on both?
Now I'm conflicted.
No, I wanted a plantation.
I wanted the whole field.
Oh, we are making bank now, baby.
The monkey economy.
Monkey economy.
Potato!
Thank you for the tag gift.
Potato, potato, potato.
He's still hitting balloons.
Oh my gosh, you're right.
How is he hitting them?
Oh, from over here.
That's crazy.
Is there anything else I can buy?
Yeah?
Everything I'm waiting on upgrades.
Oh, except you.
Okay, maybe the spikes aren't so bad.
Headshot.
Hey chat, Quincy is so obnoxious.
Oh, Quincy.
Quincy, Quincy.
I don't like this one, though.
I don't like the $9,000 loan.
I don't want to be owing anybody.
I think that's why I didn't go for the middle one.
But I really like this one.
Oh, wizard monkey.
No, we're still waiting on the necromancer monkey.
Why is there a monkey in the middle?
not able to do anything.
He's our mascot monkey.
He's mascot monkey.
He doesn't do anything.
Is that all you got?
Oh, 200 monkey money!
Holy cow.
It's a lot of monkey money.
Yeah, he's just there to be cute.
He doesn't have to do anything.
What are they?
What is something else that I need to level up?
I haven't really used Super Monkey all that much.
Oh, we were going to do Engineer Monkey.
In fact, what we were gonna do, Sentry Engineer.
We're just gonna put him right up there.
Alright, go, monkey!
Moab!
Handle it!
Reach.
10% attack speed for it.
Maybe I'll just do this one.
Close, though, close.
Oh my gosh, we have money in here!
Alright, indeed!
Quincy's dead father is available as a redeemable item in
this shop.
That's so messed up!
Wait, what?
Alright.
Don't forget to collect your bank money.
But, if it's stuff in the bank, doesn't it, like...
Yeah.
Yeah, earns 15% interest.
I think we should wait until we get it to 9,000, right?
It's Quincy Senior.
What is this game?
Nice, we got the shredder.
Yeah, shredder.
What next?
Actually, I'm going to add another sniper monkey.
Oh, actually, no, no, no, no, no, sorry.
Put you here.
And then another sniper monkey right next to you.
So you, okay.
Will become the monkey business.
And bigger radius.
And then we can also put monkeys down here that will be able
to.
And so this guy, these guys can become like...
This guy can be our fast monkey.
The fastest monkey in the West.
Get it!
Two monkey bucks.
How's our little engineer guy doing?
I don't even know what he's doing.
He's killed 141.
You want some?
This guy is... the druid is cracked.
Incoming!
What's this do?
You can all have some.
Headshot.
You want some?
You can all have some.
I can't.
The engineer's a pain in the butt to level.
Well, that's why he's here.
Oh my god.
She's killing nothing.
You can lower Quincy's voice.
No, I turned it up on purpose.
Because I think it's kind of funny.
Something sounds wet.
And I don't know what it is.
What's that wet sound?
Also, oh, let's get the boat in here, too.
Oh my gosh, wait, I only have two rounds left.
I think I meant to put the boat in sooner.
I completely forgot.
My bad.
Oh, well.
Oh, is the alchemist doing it?
Probably.
There he comes.
I can hear him.
Oh my gosh, it broke?
They destroyed it off stream.
Or off the screen.
Free play!
Oh man, Buccaneer.
I forgot to put you in.
And now it's going to take forever to get you leveled up.
Let's see.
Let's just keep going.
Is that all you got?
Oh, yeah.
I like the way he's, like, squeezing him.
With the vines.
Ugh.
That makes me almost want to restart.
Because I want the nature's bounty.
I want the bounty, man.
Check the bank, too.
We still have a good amount in here.
You know what?
I'll collect it at this point.
14,000.
Heck yeah.
I wish I could buy experience.
I mean, you can with real money.
But I wish I could with my monkey bucks.
For 5,000 monkey XP, it's $1 USD.
$1 USD.
7k might be max in an unboosted bank.
Oh, well, good thing we collected at that.
Just play the game.
There's no rush, right?
So I guess if you're really impatient.
Mr. Alpaisy, thanks for the 10 gifted.
Thank you so much.
If it was zero dollars, I'd buy.
Mint, do you want a dollar?
No.
Our Monkey Village.
Radius gets tier one upgrades for free, for free.
Increased range and reduced ability cooldowns.
What if you sold Ice Monkey for a dollar?
Ice Monkey is priceless.
Ice Monkey is priceless, what do you mean?
Blur-dud-dum-dum.
but a little thing I think oh we can use them I don't know
what else to add I think I'm invincible I do like Gatlin
Monkey actually Gatlin Monkey would be kind of great here in
the middle Gatlin Monkey and actually I like putting Gatlin
Monkey like facing right there you know oh my gosh thank you
guys for the super chats thank you I had a plane Yeah, I
think I will.
No, I don't have them upgraded at all.
I have used them, but not very much.
Hmm.
I'll hit camos and do more damage.
Dark storm is OP.
Not everything can be OP, you guys.
This is goaded.
I'm pineapple.
Oh, wait.
here
my gatlin i have oh it's not a gatlin monkey i have uh i was
working on the top one because i don't like having to swivel
my own guy i don't like that
So I just fixed him there and I was setting on these two.
You know what?
I'm gonna set him up.
I'm gonna put him right next to Ice Monkey.
He's protecting Ice Monkey.
I think.
Locked and loaded.
Well, you know.
Sweet.
Ice, no, Ice Monkey protect him.
So true.
Wow!
Ooh, that was scary.
Oh, it's level 63.
I just realized.
You can all have some.
I hate him so much.
Oh, wait.
Or is this round 63?
Oh.
I think we're in trouble.
I need to actually come up with a plan.
I'll take my $800.
And, um, let's see.
What do I want to add?
Oh!
Oh, you need to be better.
There we go.
Let's see.
Actually, no.
You're first.
You're strongest.
You're locked and loaded.
What next?
Engineer Monkey is doing his best.
Wizard Monkey.
Yeah.
Five walls of fire in the first loop.
Like these guys?
Five Wizard Monkeys going ham.
This is a Wizard Monkey.
Wizard Monkey.
One.
Two.
Three.
Let's go.
Four.
Five.
Yeah!
Look at them.
Oh, no!
I can't afford it!
Uh-oh.
Incoming!
Well, I think we'll make it.
I think we'll be fine.
Ooh, they're getting faster.
Whoa!
More fire!
Nothing is even making it over there.
Nothing's even making it over there.
That was fun.
I'll do the bureau.
I'll do the MIB.
Monkeys in black.
Monkey intelligence bureau.
Headshot They don't do it at the same time though This guy
is out of sync Oh my gosh Engineer Monkey Have you seen the
latest Anikura meta from Meatfest Oh Nikufest in Odaiba last
weekend Gundam Epion is out Mr. Mime Bariano is in What?
No I haven't Can you link me?
Can you like put it in my live tag or my general tag.
Lemo lemo!
Thanks for the 20 gifted!
Qmelia, welcome to membership!
Is that a Tenshi profile picture?
I love Tenshi!
Is that all you got?
Nice.
Ouch.
I'm just gonna keep going, you guys.
Incoming!
gonna keep going what else can we do with these guys maybe
we shouldn't do anything maybe they should just be wall of
fire and that's it but i kind of like the guided manner
spews endless flames and nearby balloons and enhance
enhanced wall of fire
save for necromancy oh
I'm really excited about that one.
Oh.
How much?
You know what?
Don't even tell me how much I spent on that.
Very good.
How are you doing?
We can upgrade Sentry Gun!
One singular upgrade, please.
Dragon's breath.
Holy cow.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, look how cute it is.
This is a little guy.
You can sell it for zero dollars.
This century is getting in my way.
Oh, this is not going to hit anything.
Okay.
Oh, he's popped 14.
Let's go.
Brandon, welcome to Mambushiv.
Thank you so much.
Is that all you got?
Sweet.
Whoa!
Oh my gosh.
Incoming shot.
Come on, make it to the wall of fire.
I dare you, I dare you, I dare you.
Thank you for playing this game.
It is awesome.
I love it.
Mother's Day mint.
Hi, Kiori.
Thank you.
Am I your mom?
What are you doing over there?
Oh my god.
He's looking.
You guys, I think it's an inside job.
I think he's trying to take Ice Monkey out.
I think he was trying to take Ice Monkey out.
Oh my god.
This sucks.
It sucks so bad.
Ah, sounds so nice.
What's the next one?
The Phoenix, right?
Powerful Phoenix wreaks balloon havoc for 20 seconds.
Let's look at the 14,000.
Yes, we have...
I want to see I want to see some get to the wall fire BFB
incoming BFB BFB BFB BFB BFB BFB BFB BFB BFB BFB BFB BFB BFB
BFB BFB BFB okay next time we'll get enough money more banks
maybe
incoming so close bfb incoming and john
nice we're on brown 77 already your druid is stopping them
from reaching the fire zone it's not being so good druid i
really want jungles bounty though oh we're at 9 000 it's not
bad druid is the goat i'm almost like doing it a second you
know what hell yeah we'll get a second one
I will get a second one.
Oh, they made it.
They made it, though.
How Engineer Monkey doing?
He's good.
He's killed a thousand balloons.
Look at this guy producing everything.
Oh!
They were camel.
They didn't die in here.
Hmm.
If I put a village here,
here if I extend the range how far is the range on this one
I don't think it'll reach but it might be good just for
everybody here give
the ice monkeys a village above
them do it above them oh maybe here oh this is actually a oh
but then I wish I could do it down here so I could reach the
like a little bit of these guys too because this one they'll
overlap you know they'll overlap and range but a village can
increase other radius
nah it's worth okay so right here are we in consensus oh if
you are in consensus of this spot say say ye hear ye hear ye
oh say aye aye I
can't tell if it reaches them okay we need more money come
on bank thank you handle
it yay headshot headshot
I just realized I've been playing blooms for three hours.
Oh my gosh.
You guys are like, you don't even understand.
Because I think after stream, if I had done bunny girls, I
would have been like, I just, I'm just going to play blooms.
But now after this, I'll be all bloomed out, kind of.
So I can like work on other stuff.
You know what I mean?
I can like finally be like, okay.
Headshot.
I did my blooms.
I can do other things that I need to finish.
I did my bloons.
I can work on anything else that I need to work on.
Oh, shoot.
Well.
Is that all you got?
Is that all you...
Incoming!
BFB incoming!
Yeah!
Destroy!
Oh, look at that!
They're so cute.
centuries he's trying he's trying he's helping how's my
cookie clicker oh i haven't checked it in a bit because i
like to um kind of like leave it alone so it will harvest
sugar lumps
you guys were already on round 82.
we're already on round 82 with this setup with this so far i
feel like this is kind of his I mean, I don't know how it's
happening, but...
First strike capability.
Ice monkey carry, ice monkey carry.
Now here, do you think I should have another boat or should
I get another submarine?
What do you think?
Because I think I can just fill this up.
I mean, there's only two water units, so...
Siege!
Thanks for the...
Thank you for the 10 gifted.
Thank you so much.
Just upgrade?
I can't!
Just upgrade, they said.
When I can't, I even upgrade.
Waiting for 12,000.
Sub...
Submarine?
Submarines are cooler.
A Gatling straight down the path.
Like this!
Then we can get one here too.
That'd be so awesome.
You're so right.
Oh my gosh.
One here.
One here too.
Locked.
Locked in.
You locked in.
Get her emperor.
Thank you for the five.
Get it.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Okay.
Top.
Oh.
Whoa!
Actually, that's really nice looking, isn't it?
It's pretty nice looking, watching all like the...
Is that all you got?
Oh my gosh, aren't you scared?
Galen Monkey!
Aren't you scared?
Pop!
And then they'll also get the camel, so it'll be good.
Collecting that so we can buy this for each of them.
and yeah let's go do another round headshot after this I'm
gonna buy a helicopter helicopter helicopter
awesome awesome we're gonna do some pushing some moab
pushing can I even fit it here I don't think so.
Aw, it's too far away from anything.
No!
Oh.
Oh!
Yo, that placement is insane.
That placement is insane!
Holy cow!
So we'll go pursue.
We'll do two...
Okay.
That's like pixel perfect placement I feel.
Incoming!
Is that all you got?
Minty, daughter of Minty.
Holy will me!
Not will me.
Thanks for mine!
Is that all you got?
Thank you so much.
BFB incoming!
Incoming!
BFB!
I'm still scared of the DDTs though you guys, I'm scared,
I'm scared.
I'm scared, I'm scared!
When you returned streaming, you mentioned you're still
figuring things out.
A professor I once...
I had once told me I'm still figuring out what I want to be
when I grow up.
Sounds silly, but I hope it helps.
Aww, thank you!
I think I mean...
I think a lot of people are, you know, thinking of what they
want to do.
See OMG incoming!
And it's okay to always be thinking about stuff.
For sure.
But I appreciate your...
You're wanting to help.
Furry, welcome to membership.
Thank you!
When I upgrade this, does it add anything else or...
Oh, just...
calls in the mini command trees oh see look at that we're
already at back at 7,000 nice we can probably get the
necromancer at this rate it's always good to be open to the
possibility of change too yeah I mean is that all you got
there's been a lot of stuff on my mind recently and But I
think I...
Well, I'm not think.
I know I'm an overthinker.
So, some decisions that come easy to some people aren't so
easy for me when I'm just like...
Drowning pool!
Welcome to membership.
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
I wonder if I should put some guys right here.
Just because we can, right?
Maybe I should have a whole team of snipers just...
We can have another alchemist, right?
Let's do it.
Let's throw another alchemist on these guys.
Right here.
And then he can buff.
Buff, buff, buff, buff.
Buff, buff, buff.
Incoming.
Is that all you got?
Round 89, baby!
BFB incoming.
Holy cow.
Wall of fire!
Ring of fire!
Louie, welcome to membership.
Thank you so much!
Glue boy, it might be time for some glue, right?
Well, I don't know if time is the right.
Do glues, do glue guys work?
Do they work?
Do they work on DDTs?
Do the glues work on the DDT?
I question.
Yes?
Okay, we'll put a guy in here.
We'll put him right here.
So, we've written them to Lizaboo.
Glue, glue.
Oh, I need more money.
Thank you.
Glue!
Okay, DDT, do your worst.
DDT, incoming!
Only if they can spot Camo.
What do you mean?
Oh, okay, okay.
So we need them to be able to see Camel then.
DDTs count as Camel?
Shut up, Quincy.
Shut up.
I need an actual answer to that.
DDTs are Camel and Lead.
I said it's strongest.
Thank you for the reminder.
Maybe then we put a little village here.
It's not much, but it could help in a pinch.
Headshot.
Thank you for this every time.
I'll read it in just a second.
Sorry.
Hold on.
I'm blooms in.
Aplosion.
The one last pop.
Mmm.
Where'd it go?
My chat's all wonky.
There's so many carriers you can do.
And you know that you can always switch to something else in
the future.
But that doesn't help decide what to do first.
I don't know.
It's...
I mean, it's a little complicated.
But, you know.
It's fine.
It's all good.
I just take it one afterlife day at a time.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Quincy's got your back, apparently.
Yes?
You do?
You're on my back!
I think...
We'll soak.
Yeah.
It'll be a little more offensive.
It'll be a little bit more offensive.
You can all have some.
Come on.
See OMG incoming.
Oh my god.
He sounds so like...
See OMG incoming!
Wee!
92, baby.
Colin, welcome to membership.
More choppers.
I agree.
Oh!
More choppers, more choppers.
And we can put them right here, too.
Uh-oh.
Is it enough?
It's enough, baby.
It's enough.
It's enough for now.
BFB is incoming.
Come on.
You can all have some.
let's go i usually i i do usually die at that one incoming
headshot headshot i think
i'll be able to get enough from this round
look they don't even make it past the wall of fire yo silver
guy welcome to membership the wild spider whoever idea was
the fire circle you you you you cooked with that and they're
not even like they're just there's three zero zero like zero
three zero it's nothing else I'm wondering would it be worth
like unlocking something else like the like will they do
other stuff as well as the wall of fire so
How close are we to Necromancer?
Actually, really not that far away.
Really not that far away.
Zero, zero, zero.
Ice Monkey giving so much luck.
I mean, I mean like buying...
Oh, I only have Intense Magic, actually.
Should I upgrade the Intense Magic?
Do you think it will do...
What's the one after that?
Oh, the Camel Bloons.
Which I don't entirely need.
but...
No, I am still aiming for the Necro.
That's why I'm not going to buy any other upgrades.
But, I mean, like, buying the Intense Magic, would it be
worth it?
Or is it not going to change anything, I wonder?
Save the money?
Oh, okay.
You know what?
That's fair, too.
Because...
How much is it?
Oh, it's so cheap!
It's so cheap, actually.
Wow.
Wait, is it actually that...
Why is it so cheap?
Oh, water base!
That's right, I was gonna get the sub.
Can I get sub end bolt?
I don't think so.
I think it's one or the other, man.
Yeah.
Only three guys can fit here.
That's okay.
Um, what would I give you?
Oh, I didn't mean to do that.
Ugh!
Oopsie.
I didn't mean to do that.
Since I can't add another guy anyway.
There we go.
Is that all you got?
Oh!
You can all have it!
Come on!
Holy cow!
Awesome!
Because I'm a knowledgeable monkey.
Sheesh!
The wall of fire is so OP!
Holy cow!
And also the druid!
I'm like, should I upgrade him too?
How close are you?
Maybe I should also do like the hard thorns?
Hmm.
What's the one after that?
Oh, the thunder.
Yeah.
Well, it just doesn't hurt to buy it, right?
Headshot.
COMG incoming.
Holy cow.
You know what you need more of?
What is it, Josh?
What could it be?
Absolutely cooked, man.
cooked absolutely cooked this is crazy we're gonna be able
to get the necromancer so soon hopefully hopefully oh oh my
gosh whoopsie what about you oh and then maybe the plasma
accelerator too maybe maybe maybe maybe how much is that one
if i end up getting it 11 000 you That's okay, we can afford
it.
Okay.
I might even get another necromancer.
You know what?
Since we're about to get the necromancer, I will get another
magic monkey.
I'll put him down here.
Perfect.
And...
We're gonna also...
Do that.
Wall of fire!
Headshot
Stop Wait Yippee What
about you?
So close So close, so close Let's go Alright Is that all you
got?
Oh my god, they scared me.
I was like, what are these?
You can all have some.
Oh
my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my
god.
I am the best.
Why were all the attacking balloons going up?
I guess they count for like some back-end support.
Oh, you can change where he summons.
Oh, awesome.
Okay, let's see.
Click to set target.
So like that, right?
And like this?
I don't know, actually.
What does this do?
Oh, is it like targets Camo and doesn't target Camo?
But is it Camo or non-Camo?
Like, you can't do both of them at the same time?
Quincy's now at max.
You want some?
He's maxed on level!
Let's go.
Just priority, just priority.
But we'll still attack the other ones, right?
So it's not so bad.
How are you doing?
We're pretty far from that one, but that's okay.
Okay, what can I get?
Because they got through pretty easily.
They got around to here.
so I'm nervous I'm nervous I mean there's so much we can add
we have all we have so much space
um bigger stacks for the oh for this this one oh and hot
stacks there we go trying to decide what I want we'll take
our money too Upgrade what I upgrade what I have now.
I don't have anything that can like go see like everything
is Everything and I'm waiting.
I can't really upgrade anything that I have right now
Unfortunately
I'm trying to get more of the top path for that guy another
helicopter It's good.
It's good Maybe another ice monkey.
Oh, I wonder what is it?
Yo!
We're doing nothing!
Guy is absolutely cracked.
Absolutely cracked.
Zero, zero, zero, ice monkeys in the middle.
Glue monkey for the wall of fire.
Oh, so like have them like kind of stuck in here?
That's a good idea.
I like that.
We'll even do the same one.
And,
uh...
Oh, wait.
What do you have fit here?
No.
Oh, but he could fit here.
Oh, shoot.
I don't think he's getting...
Oh, oh.
Maybe I messed up.
Hmm.
You know what?
I'm sticking with it.
Get bigger globs.
I did
Run ruined Okay, let's get another helicopter Do I have a
mid helicopter?
No I do not In fact, I'm going to put this one Here I think
you can fit a monkey next to it What, like this one?
The down draft one I guess I could unlock it
other glue needs bigger gloves too no that's when i already
did this one is corrosive though the path is support which
is not bad support is good because you know more we can push
back the more time we can save to to blow them up you know
so maybe two two five zero maybe I can't afford the apache
It's great versus ceramics I think I want to try it, you
know Oh, I can't afford it And then pursue it Incoming DDT
Incoming Oh Yeah I mean I feel like I'm stressing for no
reason, because everything is like, la la la, easy peasy.
You have a mid-blue fellow in the middle.
Yeah, what about him?
What about him, Joshua?
You can't bully me.
He's perfect the way he is.
I have 18 bucks left.
Alright.
Well, I can't actually do anything because I only have $18.
So, uh, YOLO.
Oh, this is the big airship of Doom.
It's big Slow and incredibly hard to take down!
Guys?
You can all have some!
Come on!
Whoa, I just noticed what these look like.
Um, guys!
Oh.
Is that all you got?
Insta monkey!
Yippee!
Let's go!
Oh my gosh, round 100!
Woohoo!
Yeah!
Oh, hi for you!
Oh, we're so close here!
What about this one?
Oh!
Close, close, close, close.
Alright, you know You know what?
Just go for it.
Headshot.
That was it?
That's it?
I felt like that was nothing.
No, I can't get my gatlin.
I want the plasma.
I can't get it yet.
You know what?
Just keep going.
You can all have some.
Whoa.
I'm hearing someone talking on the right.
I don't know who is talking in my ear.
Came back for my break.
Glad to see our blue boy still dead center.
Absolutely.
Look at him go.
He's like, yippee, we won.
Yippee.
Spiked balls.
Do extra damage to ceramic and fortified blooms.
Shoot out a thick layer of spikes over the entire track.
I want that one.
I need a lot of experience though.
Let's just keep going.
Is that all you got?
Uh-oh.
I said uh-oh, but I didn't mean it.
You can all have some.
We'll see though.
Uh-oh.
Uh-oh, for real.
Uh-oh, for real?
Come on.
Uh-oh, for real.
Ah!
Yay!
Oh
man, that was intense.
The fire has breached.
That was awfully close.
It actually was pretty close, wasn't it?
That was pretty close.
Yeah.
But we've reached round 103, in fact, so I am quite
satisfied with that.
Give me one second.
I am going to take us over to our brand new, if you guys
haven't seen it yet.
If you haven't seen it yet.
Ta-da!
And I'm also going to turn off the music because I want to
listen to my own music.
Um...
What do I want to listen to?
This one.
If
you haven't seen it yet.
We moved!
New Made Cafe!
Yeah, I showed it earlier on in the stream, so if you want
like a detailed tour, you can check out then...
Fuck you MVP star creator.
Thank you for the Akasupa.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
Hmm.
So cute, right?
Yeah.
So, uh, it's all, all, all revamped.
Fancy.
For main day.
Well, not entirely for main day, but it just happened to,
um, to kind of work out that way.
I forgot it's 310, happy main day.
Thank you!
Happy main day!
Happy main day, happy main day.
What?
If you're interested in a new theme, there's an Adventure
Time bloons on Steam.
Really?
Adventure Time themed!
Wait, that sounds so awesome.
Ah, cute minto.
Peepo, peepo.
Taimaz, welcome back for one month.
Thank you so much.
Finally, we, I know people have been asking, when is wet 3?
Patience.
Whenever wet 3 happens, it happens.
And if you don't know what I'm talking about, you can check
out some of the videos on my channel.
I did wet, and then wet 2.
And then one day will be wet 3.
Thanks for the stream, Ice Monkey Maidman.
Thank you guys.
Again, I'm so sorry for the change in the schedule.
But thank you for letting me indulge in my monkey
shenanigans.
So I appreciate it very much.
Thank you so much.
It was a lot of fun too.
Yeah.
Wait.
Oh my gosh.
My chat is frozen.
Hold on, was that on Akashupa again?
Happy May Day to our favorite ghostly maid, Valentine!
Thank you!
Happy May Day!
Aw, you guys are so nice.
Thanks for wishing me a happy May Day.
And a happy May Day to you too.
I hope your timelines have been blessed with many wonderful
maid art and fan art.
So, lovely maids that always blesses the timeline.
On days like these, Twitter feels a little less.
cursed right when it's like my favorite is um is uh in
november because when you do 11 like as the date it kind of
in like it looks like ai so that would be e so like in japan
almost every day is like e which means like good blank day
so it'll be like e thought e futamomo no he good thy day or
something like that so november is super duper blessed for
that for for all that fun stuff mint i'm crying i got to see
the northern lights here in oklahoma
how do you see them in oklahoma
So I demand more balloons in the future.
Thanks, Nibbi.
I hope you're having fun.
That explains a lot.
Yeah, good tummy day?
Yeah, yeah.
Good tummy day is another one.
Good day thing, beloved.
It's because of the solar storm.
I saw them in New York tonight.
What?
Solar storm?
I had no idea.
I don't catch up with the news.
I don't...
I don't keep track of anything.
Oh gosh.
Wait.
Maybe I could have seen the northern lights.
I don't know.
It's cloudy here.
Oh no.
I'm gonna go out when the clouds clear up and check.
Yeah!
Wait, do you guys have any pictures?
...
I want to see, I want to see the northern lights.
But honestly, I was like thinking of maybe doing a trip to
see the northern lights.
Because I want to be a little bit more world-travely.
I've never been to Europe.
So I was like, well, if I go to like, I don't know.
I don't know.
like i would want i don't know i have no idea i have to
think of how i can incorporate it into something you know um
like uh like maybe if i went and saw kiwawa and then
traveled to see the northern lights or something that could
work.
Or if Kiowa wants to come with me.
I don't know.
Can you see them in Alaska?
Maybe in parts of Alaska.
There was actually, I saw a video recently about a national
park in Alaska.
I bookmarked it.
Hold on, let me see what it's called for anyone else
interested because I was like, this sounds so awesome.
because it's you have to it's a bit more difficult of a
national park to get to because it's very mountainous hold
on i saved it though because i was like i really want to go
here um but because it's hard to get to it's like you know
it's pretty secluded you don't have a lot of people going
wait what what are some of these videos that i saved and
they were deleted wasn't that oh no maybe i should start
saving them to my phone instead of bookmarking them no way
was one of them it oh i just saved it not too long ago oh i
found it it's called the gates gates of the arctic national
park and it's america's northern most and second largest
national park but it's also the least visited of oh yeah ko
knew it Yeah, it's also the least visited of the national
parks.
But, like, the photos are just so insane.
And I was like, any reason to go to Alaska, baby?
Good guess, KO.
Yeah.
I've been there?
Oh, what did you think, Clockwork?
Did you like it?
How was it?
I want to see Glacier National Park, too.
Yeah.
Got it.
Thanks, man.
Yeah, of course.
Hmm.
The pics on Wiki look pretty cool.
Right!
Happy May Day!
I'm going on a European cruise this summer!
So I hope you can travel more as well.
Oh my gosh!
Where is it going?
That's so awesome.
Cold but very pretty.
I don't mind the cold so much anymore.
I went to Antarctica.
I experienced the cold.
I experienced the...
I don't know.
Is Antarctica the coldest place on Earth?
I experienced the southernmost place on earth.
I went to the ends of the earth.
Italy and Greece.
Woo!
So fun.
Mike Tyson!
Thanks for the gifting!
You went there in the summer though?
Yeah, because they wouldn't let me go in the winter.
Though, if there was like a way to do a...
I would have to, if there was a way to like, I don't wanna
call it an internship, but like, maybe it would be
considered an internship with the scientists that stay.
The side that I went on was the west part of Antarctica,
which is probably maybe the better side to go to right now,
because that's the side that's actively melting, but the
east side of Antarctica is actually growing so we might find
that Antarctica changes shape you know like in I mean it's
going to take hundreds of hundreds and hundreds of years um
if you guys become a ghost you might be able to see it but
it's kind of interesting
Shiraishi went to make content so Glacier growth, yippee,
yeah.
I applied to one of those internship thingies.
I don't think I got it.
No!
That one time my Oshi went to Alaska and saw the Northern
Lights anime play.
Thank you.
If I go, you can bet your butt that I will film everything
and then I can do a best as yet to come song cover of it and
I have to learn Gaelic will sing it and then I will have the
footage in the background just like at the end of MGS1 yeah
you can but your butt that's what would happen what melts
freezes elsewhere cool yeah because you know you whenever
you hear about Antarctica it's always like pretty grim
sounding news but when I learned that At least some part of
Antarctica was growing.
I don't know if it's growing at a rate to...
What's the word?
Like, offset the melting, you know?
But...
There is hope.
Ghosts don't belong in Alaska.
I was busy doing finals.
I forgot about the stream.
No, that's so much more important.
I hope you...
Got them all done and passed.
Yeah.
But.
Thank you guys again for letting it.
For being a little flexible with me and.
Letting me play bloons today instead.
Tomorrow though.
Endurance.
Atlantis non-nasal.
I...
I'm nervous.
To be honest, I'm nervous.
But, um...
I played a little bit.
I, like, played a little bit last night.
And I was like, oh, God.
I think I got to stage three.
And I think there's 99 stages or something in this.
Of course, it's always a good time with the other.
Yeah, thank you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you guys for the funny ice monkey And all the super
chats and everything I always appreciate you guys so much
Endurance stream Yes, endurance stream I came back from my
vacation to Tokyo this month Oh my gosh Otsu Otsu, it's
gonna be rough It is gonna be rough But Let's all, let's all
I'm gonna do I'm, hold on, I am planning on not using save
states at all, so, um, we'll see how that goes.
What kind of a game is it?
It's just, I know you like MGS.
I wear an eye patch and I'm told I kind of look like Big
Boss.
Really?
How, I mean, that's so cool.
Thumbnail though.
Roy, welcome to Mambushif.
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you for the laughs of the stream.
Yeah, maybe a little safe state as a treat.
No, no.
No, no, no.
No safe states.
Nope.
I gotta do it with all skill.
All skill.
Hopefully we make it.
Hopefully.
We will see, though.
We will see.
Get ready for rage.
I'll do my best.
So, with that, I am going to go to sleep then because I got
to be up.
What time is my stream?
I think it's two or three for my time.
14 hours from now.
Sleep tight.
Thank you.
Oh my gosh, you guys.
Well, actually, no.
Never mind.
I'll save this for later.
You'll have to watch the next episode of Find Out.
Otsamito, everybody.
Otsamito.
Actually, you know what?
Since we're here, and it's our first time in the New Made
Cafe, I'm going to let the artist know that I used it.
She said I could.
There's actually one other thing that I commissioned from
this artist, so.
But it's not done yet.
And I was like waiting.
I was like, maybe I should hold out on showing the
background.
But I was like, it's May Day.
So I do kind of want to show my new maid cafe on May Day.
It felt a little perfect.
Bustin!
Also, Anthony!
I saw your stream labs.
Thank you for the spooky number!
Made channel.
Oh my gosh, I missed this!
Oh my gosh, I'm so...
I don't know what's wrong with the sounds.
This is a sound test.
Minto cute.
Minto is extremely cute.
Thank you for the Akadono!
Tell you something.
If there's something weird, I'm sleeping in your bed.
Ow!
Let me tell you something.
Oh.
Mustin' mustin' mustin' mustin' mustin' mustin' See, look,
you're sitting at your table all the way over there.
Sorry, I couldn't give you better seats to the stage, but
you know, it's just, you know, it's a pretty crowded day,
you know.
and things.
Sleeping in your bed.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
An invisible man.
Sleeping in your bed.
Ow!
Let me tell you something.
I'm so sorry about the stream labs, though.
I will see what is wrong with them so that the sounds come
back.
Bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin,
bustin, bustin.
Makes me feel good, feel good, feel Feel good, feel good,
feel good Bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin Yeah, yeah, yeah
Mustin, mustin, mustin, mustin, mustin Makes me feel good,
feel good, feel good, feel good, feel good Dun, dun, dun
Freaky ghost made Freaky ghost man Freaky man, baby!
If you're all alone, let me sleep in your bed.
Let me tell you something.
Sleeping makes me feel good.
I ain't afraid of no sleep.
I ain't afraid of no bed.
An invisible bed.
Freaky ghost bag!
Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin
Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Feel good.
Feel good, feel good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Makes me feel good.
Busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Blues, coolies, welcome to membership.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you Feel good Have a good night Thank you Thank you
everybody Oh What's a mint?
What's a mint?
Bye bye