Is it working?
Can you hear me?
Hello!
Oh god, my voice is so dead.
My voice is so dead.
Oh my gosh.
Just like me.
Living core, thanks for the five gifted.
And chase himself.
Thanks for the 10 gifted.
Thank you.
You are dead.
I am.
So I said just like me.
Hold on one second.
I'm going to refresh you two real quick.
Okay, I think.
Haven't been around for many streams lately.
because of work, life, and football.
But I'm glad to start watching again.
I'm Miss Mint.
Hakuno!
And welcome back.
Thank you.
Oddball boy.
Thanks for the five.
Good to thank.
My flight leaving Long Beach got delayed till Thursday.
You were basically me.
That's when I was going to get back.
It was Thursday.
But now I'm home.
Eevee!
What a mess did Cloud Stryph cause.
He would have missed your anniversary.
I know, right?
I have a convention I'm even doing this weekend.
And I had to contact them and been like, I don't know if I'm
going to make it home in time.
Wait, we can talk a bit about I was gone the past couple of
days.
I was at
MGSKON!
Yippee!
I know, I don't know, maybe if you watch Barry, you heard
some of these already.
She talked some.
Did you see the Nendo's?
Of course I did!
So, I went to MGSKON.
Kiserapture, thanks for the five gifted!
Randall, thanks for the five gifted!
I think I saw Teacup.
Yeah, thanks for the gifted!
Spent all the weekend dealing with your crowd buddies.
Looking back, I'm excited.
Finally, me too, at Anime Fest.
I'm a little nervous.
This, that's this weekend!
Yeah!
We learned things of the 10 gift of it!
So, uh...
It was truly the whole situation with the Cloud Strike was
like...
It is Cloud Strike, right?
Right.
And Draco, thanks for the 20!
Thank you so much.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Yes, okay.
Oh, CrowdStrike.
Wait, wait, is it CloudStrike or CrowdStrike?
I'm glad you had fun at MGSCon.
No, it's been a while, but I wanted to give you an update
about that interview on...
I got the job!
That's my president!
So, it is!
Congratulations!
Was that not a bit?
No, wait.
What's the bit?
I'm always serious.
What are you talking about?
But no, I went to MGSCon this past weekend, which is a
one-day Metal Gear themed convention.
I got to see Maddie!
Oh my god.
The music is so dramatic.
The music, Minecraft loves Maddie.
Good morning, Mito.
And, um...
The timing.
Um, yeah.
Uh, um, I don't know.
Maybe there were some people that had, like, a...
I don't know, a spiritual awakening.
A sixth sense moment.
I'm not sure.
but if you sensed if you had us if you had a little chill it
might have been me but I was definitely haunting Barry
basically the entire time shout out to Barry Barry bug the
better bug better than she's the best bug I've never known a
better bug than the Barry the bug and the audio is so loud
turn down
But, uh...
But, um...
Nice tongue twister.
Say that time's fast.
Barry bug the better bug.
Welcome back, boss.
Happy early anniversary, yippee!
Thank you!
Cloud strife?
Yes.
Basically.
Don't know any other bug.
But, um...
Yeah, I was really grateful because...
Honestly, she is streamed on, she streams on Twitch, but she
streamed yesterday, I believe it was.
Sorry, my time is all discombobulated.
I don't know what day it is.
I don't actually, it's Tuesday, isn't it?
Right?
I actually have no idea what day it is.
is an illusion.
Okay, it is Tuesday.
Well, Tuesday for me, so Wednesday for you, okay.
But I'll explain in a minute.
I was really grateful because Matara wasn't able to make it
to the con, and I was going to be all alone, all by my
lonesome.
And like, Barry talked about how she like stalked me, but
truly I was haunting her the whole time.
I'd be like, Oh, so Barry, what do you, um, what did, uh,
what did you, what did you, what did you, did you have
another thing you wanted to do next?
Oh, you, no, you, you want to do what I want to do?
Okay.
So it was just like she and I being awkward together was so
good.
Um, it's Minto time.
Good evening, Minto.
Good evening.
Do you guys like them?
I have no more slots anymore.
So if we want more emotes, like we're maxed out.
If we want any more emotes, we'll have to switch some out.
Do you know what day it is?
Well, tomorrow is April 30th.
Have fun playing Minecraft.
Thank you, Polly.
You did good, boss.
Yippee!
Emotes are pretty good.
Yeah.
I got so...
So my flight, luckily, was only a little delayed into the
con weekend.
And so I get there.
And honestly, I just have no idea what to do.
I'm just sitting in the lobby.
I'm people watching.
Because I'm like, look at everybody walking around with
their Metal Gear T-shirts.
Oh, sorry.
I'm starting to get emotional.
And all their merch and their bags and everything.
So great.
Why are flight delays so common in North America?
No, no.
It was because of the cloud strike.
The cloud strike.
Got a text saying it might be delayed again.
What flight?
Oh, wait.
Don't actually don't tell me your airline.
Don't tell me your airline because, you know, I don't, I
don't want you But I heard that...
Oh, CrowdStrike.
Thank you.
Sorry.
CrowdStrike.
I am...
I heard that some airlines are doing more poorly than
others, so...
I felt chilly at MGSCon.
I even saw floating UOs and a big sticky...
Thank you, Aura.
What are you talking about?
Wasn't that berry that went off about how good I smelled?
Which I...
She kept talking about how good I smelled.
And I didn't get, like, secondhand embarrassment.
I felt like I was...
I was like, is this how it feels when people listen to me
talk?
I felt...
I felt like too much...
I was hearing too much of myself from her.
and I was really embarrassed about it.
I was like, I was like, no way, this is how I sound.
Unreliable narrator?
What are you talking about?
I envy the bug I will squish.
But, oh, no.
I think, I mean, I think ectoplasm smells kind of good.
Exactly now you understand.
Why do you guys watch me?
That is kind of my whole feeling.
That's kind of what I...
I got a lot of emotions this weekend, but one of them was
truly, why do people watch me?
I think you've all gaslit yourself into finding me
enjoyable.
I swear.
I last you understand, two of them.
E.
Because we're all weirdos.
But I got to meet...
Oh my gosh, I met David Hader for the first time.
I talked about this too in the Twitter space that I did.
But in case you didn't watch that and also stockholed
ourselves into loving you.
Loving you is not easy.
You are horrible.
I've stockholed myself.
Into loving you.
That poster story.
It was so funny.
Oh!
I was like, poster story.
I was like, oh my gosh.
I went up to David Hader.
Like tears forming in my eyes.
I'm like, I can't cry.
First of all, because I don't want to cry in front of him.
Second of all, because I don't want Barry seeing me cry.
I was like, oh god.
And I go, oh my gosh.
but I go up to him and I saw that he had a print of MGS
Delta snake and I was like wow he's so fast and I like the
Delta design and oh I don't know I like it and so I I was
like can I I got an autograph and then I bought that as an
additional autograph and I'm showing oh my gosh after he
signs it after he signs it uh and I kind of was just like
you you you you've made my entire career and he was just
like haha what what I'm like you you I everything shifted at
that moment and and he was like oh what I know right and so
he's signing it and I'm like not even paying attention to
the print I'm just like trying to hold my my composure I'm
just like oh gosh if I if I let one crack you know how like
the dam has cracks and if just a little bit gets through
everything gets through that's how it was gonna be and so
but afterwards he signs it and then he gets up from the
table and walks over to Barry and I he didn't have to do
this, but he like puts his hand on both of our shoulders and
he goes, by the way, you're pretty good.
He said it to everybody.
We weren't special, but oh my god.
What a dream.
David Hater's just a very handsome guy.
Maddie and I are convinced if you've never seen, so
basically he starred in a movie called Giver 2, the second
one, Giver.
And like, he's, he, back then, he was, I mean, he's still
very attractive, but back then he was like, such like a
heartthrob, you know?
He seems very nice.
He was so nice.
He, you can tell he loves what he does, you know what I
mean?
But we kind of, Maddie and I have, like, determined that,
like, he, he is, like, the same level of, like, Harrison
Ford.
Like, in a parallel universe, this guy is, like, Harrison
levels of famous he's like this heartthrob that everybody
loves but in this universe he's just he's just a little too
nerdy to like he's just a little bit too much of a dork
maybe if you like him so much why don't you marry him pretty
sure he's already married
I would throw up every day.
Probably hearing his voice.
Harrison Ford could have gone nerd, but deaf did not.
We met Christopher Randolph, who is the voice of Otacon, who
is just a total absolute sweetheart.
And I know Barry just spilled our absolute spaghetti.
Thank you guys for all the super chats, by the way.
I'm trying to like, I'm trying to...
You talk about me so differently, but you didn't recognize
my favorite character.
Hold on, I have a story for that later.
Can you play the game?
Oh my gosh, stop!
I'm talking first!
What do you mean?
Okay, I'm done.
I'm done.
Okay, I'll see.
Okay, I won't talk anymore.
Okay, let's just play the game.
Actually, I'm stuck on this block and I don't really know.
Do I break it?
Yippee!
That's so unfair.
What?
She won the game.
Why am I losing bricks?
Oh, wait.
around too right so that things don't drop please place
other blocks I'm working on it I'm working on it guys let me
finish my art but um one black out of time yeah
so we met him he was very nice One of my favorite people to
meet was Paul Eiding.
And it's so crazy.
New Journey.
Place 20 blocks.
Oh my gosh, sorry.
There was...
I put a pin on my desk and I thought it was a bug.
a pin from the hand cam.
I thought it was a bug.
And I scared myself.
I scared myself looking at it.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, you guys.
Okay, let me just tell you a little bit about my journey
today, right?
Um, I'm on like very few hours of sleep.
What?
Stop running away from me.
I'm on very few hours of sleep, because I took a red eye.
And, um...
Arigado, Arigado, Choo!
Marl, thank you!
Getting in early on saying happy anniversary your streams,
since your comeback have been the most fun I've ever had
with a VTuber.
Shut up!
No way!
I can't...
I can't wait to see what else you do, because I was on a
conference call with the CEO of CloudStrike.
today he seemed pretty sorry oh my gosh thank you so much
for the big dodo thank you i really appreciate it murl murl
um well yeah i took a red eye it was a which means oh shoot
moss which is a which is a very um very late flight if you
don't know right It means it's like a flight really late in
the night.
And so what had happened was, I was actually checking into
my flight.
And I was like putting in my bags.
Because I had to check a bag.
And I was putting it in.
And it was like, um.
It was like, oh, by the way, we can't check your bag.
There's something wrong.
And I was like, oh, that's weird.
And then when I, and I'm doing this on the app, right?
And when I go back to the app, or when I go back to my
check-in screen, it's like, we're sorry your flight is
canceled.
And I was like, wait, what do you mean by that?
What do you mean by that?
I love red eyes.
I don't.
And so, I was like freaking out.
I was panicking just a little bit.
How do I get underneath?
Thank you.
It's like, hey, by the way, you can make a thing.
And, oh, water.
Oh, water, water, water.
But let's make some utensils, right?
So, I'm like, searching the one flight it like it
automatically rebooked me for some reason thanks rico i
heard that southwest was completely unaffected because
they're still running everything on windows 3.1 which hasn't
been updated in 25 years what maybe i should have taken
southwest then
you mean tools oh
Yeah.
So, you guys, I'm test- hold on.
Let me finish.
Sorry.
I got an amber alert all of a sudden.
It's happening!
What's going on?
Wake up, wake up.
And, uh, where was I?
Yeah, so I'm like, it puts me on a flight on Thursday.
And actual jump scare.
Puts me on a flight on Thursday.
Let's make some shovel, too.
And I was like, no, that's too late.
I'll miss my stream.
I'll miss my anniversary stream.
I'll miss my convention appearance.
I can't do this.
And so I'm like struggling.
I'm like on the phone with them.
for I'm on hold for so many hours trying to get a person to
give me a refund or something there was another flight that
I found that uh but it wouldn't let me rebook it it was just
a bunch of craziness and so I'm like oh my god could I
request a lullaby I'm going in and out of sleep If not a
simple, simple stupid fries works.
That hurt.
Are you okay?
Go to sleep.
Go to sleep, little baby.
Close your eyes.
Go to sleep.
Come have sweet dreams of thighs.
Close your eyes.
Meachies fries.
And you'll...
Oh!
Oh, grass!
Wait, which is the one block?
Oh.
Glad you got home safe in time.
Thank you!
Wait, hold on.
I gotta put on some music.
Um...
um
um what do we want to listen to meantos thighs what are you
thinking about put on lullaby music oh this one's called
smoothie house this is a jazzy limp biscuit people are
trying to sleep shh shh people are trying to sleep everybody
be quiet stop the chat is this it is this the one right okay
good go to sleep little baby think of suckling on a nip just
like when you were a baby and you just suckled the tip
Little baby dreams, baby world.
Think, imagine, put yourself in, as a baby.
Your scream woke me up.
With my jump scare that I thought it was a bug.
Every single stream, I'm left asking myself, how are you
even real?
Well, some people say ghosts aren't real.
It gives me a bit of an existential crisis, you know.
Ah!
Oh my god.
Mysterious traitor!
I can order a cat!
Sorry, I didn't mean to scream so much.
Maybe I should trade...
Oh, I don't have enough dirt.
I don't have anything.
Get out of here.
Get off my land.
Get off my land, please.
Okay, anyway.
Oh, that's my shovel, sorry.
I'm really jumpy.
Like I said, I took a really late flight.
And the day before my flight, all I did...
You guys, I didn't know what to do.
I was, so MGSCon was Saturday.
Sunday, Maddie and I walked around the beach.
We, we, I, I got sunburnt a little bit on my head.
But we walked around the pier and the beach and we just, you
know, so I did walking then and then the day after, then
that was before I even knew anything would be cancelled.
And, uh...
And I, uh...
I'm scared of mob spawning.
I'm gonna turn it down just a little bit more.
And, um...
Touch grass.
Touch sand.
Yeah, we touch sand.
But...
You scream more here than a horror game.
I'm sorry.
I don't really...
My brain is not quite working.
I didn't know what to do.
So I ended up...
I ended up trying to go to a museum.
I was closed.
Oh no!
I can't!
What's step two?
Mine the block 100.
Oh, okay.
I tried to go to a museum.
Apparently everything is closed on Mondays.
Which is really just so sad.
Um...
Oh, I tried to go to tomb museums.
And everything was closed.
So I ended up like just walking.
I ended up walking for like 10 miles.
Like no joke.
Hypothetical situation.
Your OSHA is talking to you about the hypothetical situation
of your OSHA seeing your nipples.
What would you do?
Um...
So, my Oshi talks about, if my Oshi talked about seeing my
nipples is what you're saying.
Sounds like I did something correct.
I did not.
Um, look, Jeff, if you're still around, if I didn't scare
you off.
if I didn't so there was a guy at the convention dressed as
Raiden and I'm getting flamed online for this he was dressed
as Raiden
and he was in a towel with this little Raiden wig on and
everything he was dressed as Raiden and I was like oh it's
just like that scene in MGS too and I was like how is that
how how is me seeing Ryden seeing Ryden in a towel not like
you are correct did he do the cartwheel he should have in
fact how disappointing they didn't how disappointing
How big Chungus life was MGS gone?
Sounds like it was a lot of fun.
Wish I could have gone.
It was so much fun.
I hope I do it again next year.
I'm too embarrassed to hear what Barry said about me.
So anything she said about me was probably a lie.
Just think of, just believe that.
Don't believe on doors lies.
Anything, anything she said about me is the total
fabrication.
We can build trees.
Tomorrow is my birthday Coincidentally the same day as your
anniversary Can I get a happy birthday?
Of course not Happy birthday to you Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday dear Matt Happy birthday to you
So I don't know.
Like I said, I couldn't really listen to her talk about how
much I smelled.
Minecraft music.
Oymal!
Barry literally said, you are the sweetest person.
And everything she says.
I said what I said.
I'm not a good ghost.
I'm an evil ghost.
When will you guys understand?
Ah!
God!
She...
You...
You compared him to getting embarrassed to watching Meryl
turning right in front of a thousand listeners.
Put yourself in their shoes.
Also bury one in a whole existential crisis because of how
nice you were.
Well, that's how awesome I felt, too.
Like, I don't know.
Being...
Being in a place where...
maybe I don't know if you guys went to off Kai maybe maybe
you had like a similar like a similar existential crisis
where you're just like it truly it truly made me just be
like oh my gosh maybe maybe people are just nice you know
maybe people are like when you're surrounded by people that
are you know involved in your fandom and just something that
you really love and something that is so you know you're so
passionate about and you hold in such high regard and you
never want to ever let go and you're so sad that it's over
and you're just like oh my gosh when i have nothing else to
look forward in my life to now or my afterlife because it's
over and you just see how nice everybody is you're just like
just makes you feel like maybe maybe there is some good in
this world
what does this guy have anyway he's got the dirt oh we can
get some copper did we get the copper or do we continue
digging huh why are you what do you mean i can order a
donkey
so true yeah i don't know like i said people are just so
nice like afterwards like even the the head of the
convention she like came up to me She like knew me by name.
I was just like, you're so nice.
And I'm just like, I didn't do anything.
I didn't do anything.
But it does make you think, or like, you know, it makes you
like kind of remember, like, you know, when people are so
poopy online, nine times out of 10, they're not like that in
person.
And it's like, oh my gosh.
Maybe touching grass is important.
Maybe they actually...
Maybe I should touch grass more.
I don't know.
Turns out people love you because you're great.
No.
I was haunting everybody.
I was haunting.
Um, and then also, um, I got to meet Cynthia Harrell, which
I only saw her in concert before, and I got to actually meet
her and talk to her, and I got to tell her that I went to
the MGS concert.
Touchgrass, never!
I got to tell her that I went to the concert because of her,
and how much of an inspiration she is to me, and she's just
such a, she's just such a nice lady.
snake eater she's the singer of snake eater and uh i got the
the crazy thing is i actually got to sing snake eater with
her but it wasn't just me i mean it was like a crowd but
then also um i was invited to a party um with maddie uh
after the con was over and she was at the party and um then
we also sang snake eater again and i was just like What is
this?
What is this life?
What is going on?
I hope you've had a great day.
I've always been a lurker.
I just want to know how you're special to me.
Thank you, Cyber!
Wait.
What's your profile picture?
Is that Hoshino from Blue Archive?
Mention it during my haunting.
Oh, you sensed me.
Developed a sixth sense.
You might want to get, um, like, you might want to go get,
like, blessed or something, you know?
Can you move?
Can you, like, please, leave me alone.
I thought you would disappear or something.
What is this?
Stone!
Stone, stone, stone.
Boom!
Mint experiencing the good of people.
Also, Minecraft being more of a jump scare than usual.
It's because...
You know.
that's because uh things like pop up you know
do not come to european content all the eu wisps want to
dribble you like a basketball for time time zone crimes and
it'll ruin our image no joe back now actually i mentioned
this recently how like um the reason I haven't been able to
do you can blame Matara for the reason I haven't been able
to do so many so many early day uh streams me dribbling so I
thought you meant dribble like you were gonna dribble your
spit on me oh my gosh Lakuna thank you so much for the pink
fancy seeing you play Minecraft Love Black maybe you'll find
a music disc that sounds like vtuber vgm or something what
so glad you had an amazing time at mgs god it got to me too
mgs oh geez looking forward to more minta forever thank you
but um the reason it's matara's fault is because of the
podcast because oh wait which one is it wait which one is it
oh no no Is it this one?
Uh-oh.
Okay, it's this one.
Wait, he's gonna fall.
Never mind.
Um, because of the podcast, she, she...
I have to keep my days open because I'll be like, Hey,
Matara, we gotta record the podcast.
And she's like, I'm gonna stream.
I really wanna stream.
And I'm like, yeah, me too.
But like...
Then she'll sometimes just like...
You know, go away.
Go away.
Love you, Minto.
Thank you.
So you can blame her.
Play slabs around it.
You're so smart.
I was hearing you and Barry talk about it.
JSCON is giving me FOMO.
Oh, anyways.
However, I'm glad I got to see you at Off-Kai.
Yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
you whips crying about time zone and then there's us na
folks very grateful you're streaming at such friendly yes
you timing you asked maria how she would feel if you saw if
wait if her oshi saw her in a towel no i really appreciate
your mint i'm sick oh no i just feel better there are
dribblers like b-ball and there are dribblers
Okay, loved both so stop her!
I don't want to hear this anymore.
Oh, the music disappeared.
Just like a baby.
I'm dribbling like a baby.
Oh my gosh, this is a pain in the butt having to switch to
it.
when do i enter the stone age maybe maybe i can maybe i can
make a stone maybe i can make a stone yes yeah but would you
lose a baby dribbling contest or wait oh no is this the one
oh gosh yes okay oh actually since i just made this pickaxe?
Let's get rid of it first.
Yeah, more stone.
Nah, I'd win.
If there is a competition, any sort of competition, I think
I'd win.
I'm not so weak.
Did you know that mint was a singular leaf?
Are you saying I'm all by my lonesome?
What is going on up here?
Can I...
If there was a competition of any sort.
I'm no loser.
I'm gonna win anything.
How about a being tall competition?
I hate you.
I hate...
This...
It's unfair!
How could you go so low?
Those don't exist.
Tall competitions.
They'll never exist.
Okay.
When I become president, I will make sure of it.
How could you go solo?
Tall competitions do exist.
No?
I never thought I would hear the men say the word hate.
Nah.
I have a lot of hate in my body.
I'm sorry.
Again, like I said, I'm an evil ghost.
Oh!
We got a new guy.
He'll give us jungles.
We can get seeds!
Wait, you guys, you guys.
Can we afford all this?
20?
Okay, that's 45.
Let's just buy it all.
Oh, I was gonna say we had just enough.
Huh?
We can order a sheep.
Bye!
Okay, get out of here.
Actually, no.
Oh wait, he's gonna reset.
Go out.
Go away.
Go, bye-bye.
Bye!
I just lost the spelling competition because that should
have been pro-basketball game.
Barry told us to ask you about the special thing you did.
Special thing?
Hold on, let me message her.
I don't even know what she's...
What's the special thing I did?
Mintz killed a man.
I ran over a baby this morning actually.
I
ran over a baby.
over a baby this morning with my suitcase at the airport and
the mom was like because the baby ran out in front of me or
rather behind me because I was pulling my suitcase and the
mom was like I'm so sorry and I was like I'm sorry I ran
over your baby I
ran over a baby I kept running over people.
I tasted blood.
And I'm a killer.
This is the skin of a killer bella.
Lucky baby.
What's wrong with you?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I thought that was...
I forgot that was in wood.
Or stone is what I meant to say.
Don't worry.
You did the right thing.
Oh, the baby came out of nowhere.
And I mean, like I said, I was pulling my suitcase and he
ran out behind me and I just right over his head.
The
mom apologized to me.
Oh my God, she could have, I could have gotten alive by
that.
She could have been like, you ran over my baby.
Uh-oh, oh, shoot.
Wait, which one is it, you guys?
Is it this one?
Oh, whoo.
Okay, we're gonna, someone said put slabs down for these bad
boys let's do that slab we're gonna put some slabs down slab
slab slab slab bossy killed a child amazing that right there
is why you're the best running over a baby with the mgs
merch suitcase no that's the worst part this bag is heavier
than my actual suitcase because it has all my laptop stuff
So it's even happier!
I had my entire streaming setup!
The baby just took it all like a damn champ.
Kids will just insert themselves in front of moving objects
and ways that defy physics.
It's true.
Oh my gosh.
It was the first thing that happened after I got off the
plane.
And so I've been awake.
I don't know.
Like I said, I did nine miles yesterday.
And then I went to my hotel.
I took a quick shower.
And then I went to the airport after walking for so long.
Wisps are loyal AF.
I ease and guide the child.
Don't lie, we know you don't bathe.
No, it was the most...
Okay.
I got the hotel room scared that I wouldn't be able to go
home.
And it was a pricey...
What the hell is a mace?
What's a...
What are these?
Heavy core, breeze rod?
I've never heard of any of this before.
But um, try auto summary is wild.
What does it say?
It's a new weapon.
Really?
There's actual new stuff!
Onion.
I'm glad you guys like the new emotes and so happy.
Um, but uh...
yeah so i walked and then i took a shower i paid for this
hotel room thinking that i would be there longer and um so i
basically was in the hotel room for like three hours cost me
200 dollars
most expensive shower of my life i bet you gonna have a
great story to tell when they're grown up i got right over
by the one i don't even expect
uh yeah big oof big oof the whole thing just puts such a put
such a damper on everything but in me walking around which i
still even though i didn't get to go home on time um i still
had so much fun yesterday and um walking around and stuff
even because even though I didn't get to go to um even
though I didn't get to go to uh the museums um I was walking
and I was like trying to find like parks to just walk in and
I saw like one that was like called in a memorial park and I
was like oh okay cool memorial park and I go there and I'm
just walking laps and I well first I get there and I'm like
oh this is just a straight up cemetery how how suiting for a
ghost right i was like maybe i'll see some other ghosts here
i don't know um maybe i can socialize like i didn't do
enough this past weekend and um and uh oh my gosh when is
this thing gonna grow he's got the cherry sapling i must buy
prismarine shard we can live without for now a pale but I
walked to the cemetery through the cemetery and I noticed by
one of the graves there's a like kind of a group of people
and I was just like oh I guess you know family you know
whatever whatever a child incident was just an unfortunate
speed bump on an otherwise great trip yes but uh later on
the group of people left and I'm looking at the grave and I
was like looking at it for a second and I was like wait a
second I recognize this it I recognize it from far away
because and this might give it away it was covered in
lipstick marks all over it and do you know what people do
they go to Marilyn Monroe's grave and they kiss it it was
Marilyn Monroe's grave I was like whoa gosh I just we it was
just an accident that I was there I forgot hold on I looked
it up earlier what this place was called because I was also
just like what other what other did you talk to her she
wasn't available you know I mean she's she's a celebrity I'm
mint phantom you know did you kiss it no but um I had to
stop myself from taking a picture of a big boss in front of
it.
I was like, maybe that's a little too far.
But I was looking out who else is buried in that cemetery.
Apparently, it's like the most celebrity-filled cemetery.
Like Jody Fawcett's there.
Peter Falk is there.
Kojima.
I could have done it.
But yeah.
I'm dead too though, right?
I can get away with it.
Guys, I'm just as dead.
Wait, is this a new one?
No.
I'm just as dead!
It's okay when ghosts do it.
Yeah!
I mean, like, come on!
Right.
Ow, go away!
Where were you buried, Minto?
I don't know.
I think...
I don't know if I ever got a proper burial.
Outer heaven.
Good golly.
Shifrugor.
It has been a long time since I died, so...
You know.
Oh.
There goes my shovel.
Can I stop raining, please, for two seconds?
When am I going to get some, like, animals, like sheep and
stuff?
Hmm, indeed.
After that, Jabbar.
Happy anniversary.
Thank you.
Dead men tell no tales.
Are you dead?
Yeah.
I am dead.
You can be ashes on Venom Snake's face.
Ooh, la-la.
I'm glad you didn't eat him up like a cheeto does.
Dead mint tell no tales.
What does that mean?
Like they don't tell stories?
Because what am I doing then?
You're the exception.
Really?
Why are my trees growing?
Do I need more dirt?
Grow!
Um, yeah, I get it.
Sophia!
Thank you for that, thank you for that, thank you for that.
They can't testify in court.
So they're like, dead man can't snitch on you.
Dead man can't tell you where they, how they died.
Stop.
he's trying to think go away please go away you're
embarrassing go they can't rat you out exactly no witnesses
but they didn't think about ghost maids no they didn't now
he won't tell tales dead men tell no tales
He wasn't a villager, he was a mysterious traitor.
He was a traitor.
Maybe you have to water the trees.
Oh.
Why do I go through the things that I go through?
Why do I allow this?
I think being a VTuber has truly changed.
What?
You're back!
We just got a cave shop.
Oh, we can get some gravel.
Let's get some gravel.
We can get some gold.
Beehive.
If only we had to some breeze.
V-tubers.
V-tubers have changed.
Wait, let's get a little...
Oh, wait.
I was going to say let's plant our seeds, but we have no
water.
Hmm.
He must tell his tales?
We hive.
You're so needy, you're so close to me.
Why are you so obsessed with me, mysterious traitor?
Why are you so obsessed with me?
Mushkashte obsessed with me?
There he goes.
When is it gonna stop raining though?
For real?
Sounds familiar.
Maybe he's a wisp.
One thing, though, like, you know, when I do cons and stuff,
even if it's something like MGSCon that I have absolutely no
relation to, I'm just haunting for fun.
I'm not there to, like, you know, be a guest or anything.
Which, oh, I'm so sorry that it didn't work out with me
appearing at the convention.
Like, I had everything set up, and like, five minutes before
the time, they sent me a message and they're like, we're
behind schedule.
We have to cut.
We have to cut it.
I'm so sorry.
And I was like, it's okay.
Like, they were so, so apologetic.
But again, everybody at the convention was so nice.
Like, I can't, I just can't be, I can't, I can't be upset.
So, uh...
But, so I'm so sorry if you were just like, Oh, I wonder if
Minto's gonna show up.
Um, and it was just gonna be, like, a quick little thing
anyway.
But, um...
It stopped raining!
Yippee!
Uh...
Next year, definitely.
How?
Oh, maybe.
We'll see.
Um...
But, uh...
What was I saying?
Even when it's something like MGSCon that I have no relation
to, I truly, I'm just...
Oh my gosh, I'm gonna be...
I was gonna say I'm gonna be sappy.
You know what I was literally about to say?
I was literally about to say...
Oh my gosh, Wisps are just...
The best.
Wisps are the best fandom.
You guys are the absolute best.
And then...
And then what appears?
None other than...
I take it all back.
You guys are absolute freaks!
You guys are such freaks!
What's wrong with you guys?
Why can't you just be normal?
What is absolutely wrong?
What's wrong with you guys?
Why do you say the things that you say?
Why are you so bold and brazen?
Why do you think that you can just say whatever you want?
We learned from you.
You did not learn!
You did not learn to ask people to poop on their chest
because of me!
When have I ever said that?
That Supa is not representation of the majority.
Chat reflects the streamer derogatory.
Don't lump me in with that.
And you know what the greatest insult of that is?
The greatest insult is...
was the amount.
You'll make such a ridiculous demand, such a ridiculous
request.
At that?
At that price?
Oh, at Apple.
Can you get hungry in this version?
Sick freak.
We learned from the best boss.
Yes.
If you want such a prized...
Such a delicacy...
You must pay up.
Lump...
Lump me in with the majority.
So would you reconsider at a different amount?
No, I didn't say that.
I'm just saying it was a little offensive, you know?
We're talking about Mint's secret Cleveland streamer
instructional members video.
Huh?
What does that even mean?
What's a Cleveland streamer?
I just sat down.
You want us to do what?
Do not Google.
Huh?
A Cleveland streamer?
Is that from Idaho?
He's back.
Raw iron!
We need that for real.
Actually, I wonder if I can make a furnace now.
Oh, wait.
Oh, but I can...
Let him cook.
I can burn like this, right?
There we go.
These Supas need to cease.
What's going on with you guys?
I'm gone for like two days.
I wish to feed from the forbidden Play-Doh fun factory.
I googled it.
Don't do it.
That shit literally is sick.
What's going on?
What's happening?
Why are you guys such a...
What are you trying to introduce me to?
You guys, was Minecraft breaking your brains?
What's going on?
We got a call!
Come back!
Thank you for the 50 gifted!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
That is freaky, freaky tonight.
Let's come on guys, let's dial up bang a little bit.
Let's instead talk about murder.
Murder the man!
Murder, murder, murder, murder the man!
No, don't...
Myrtle the man!
Let him live?
No!
I got all that I needed from him.
Time to gouge my eyes out.
You guys scare me.
We got the dripstone!
Myrtle the man!
Messed up, dark, perverted fact.
Thank you.
Chauvet, go to sleep.
But yeah, once the podcast is over, I'll be able to do more
midday thingies.
Right now it's really just kind of because Matara's schedule
is like kind of whack.
Oh!
Well.
Freak Phantom, what is your wisdom?
You two!
Go to sleep, Meech's fries!
Detective Jones.
Thanks for the captain.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Yesterday was my B-day, but Friday will be my last day
living in the house I spent my life in.
Instead of a birthday wish, I'd much rather have words of
encouragement.
Much love from a wisp who's been here since your
introduction video.
Helen!
You really have been around for so long.
Thank you!
Oh my gosh.
I know it can be scary.
Oh.
but you're you are taking a big step in your life and I
believe that you will be just fine and happy birthday happy
birthday to you happy birthday to you happy birthday dear
all right happy birthday day to you good luck you got this
in minecraft where's the music we got the advancement i am
iron let him cook when is this guy gonna gonna grow up This
little sapling.
Unrelated to Fauna Seris, my beloved.
Deep, welcome to membership!
Encore.
Onion.
There
we go.
I like Minecraft music so much.
It's always so calming.
I know when the game is like being so freaky.
Let's see.
Should I get an iron one?
Or should I save it?
Ugh!
I always love your streams.
Well, anything you do, I'm kind of lost right now.
What do you do to make the bad brainworms go away?
Eat the brainworms.
Play Metal Gear Solid.
Yeah, replace them with...
Actually, that's such a thing.
good thing though is replace it with a different kind of
brain worm you know instead that way you don't have you
don't have one brain worm you'll have different type of
brain worm that's a brain worm it could be a really more
dangerous brain worm but worm eater
I like how you can see the sun through the block.
Brainworm farm.
I don't know, because I have lots of brain worms.
I think about lots of things.
I have...
Okay, don't tell anybody, but I might...
I think I have, like, some...
Some of the steam issues, you know?
Oh my god, pies!
It scared me!
in baseball season.
Do you think you'd be a better pitcher?
Wait, do you think you'd be better a pitcher or as a hitter?
I think a pit, no.
Hitter.
I'd be a good hitter.
I think.
I've never played baseball once.
Man, some of us, I said don't tell anybody.
Don't, you know.
I know I'm a 10-side genius.
Perfect ghost maid.
Wow, sometimes I have also problems.
Sometimes I have my...
I do have a little bit of flaws.
Not as much as you guys, but like, you know.
You know.
I'm trying to brisk it.
Oh, I'm about to try a brisk it.
What does this mean?
Trying a brisk it.
Trying to brisk it.
I've been cooking for the past two days.
Can you bless it with your maid powers?
Yeah!
There you go.
Moe, moe, moe, moe, moe, moe, moe, moe, moe.
cute good evening i mean that good evening
oh my gosh we're close to buying more things i want to order
a cat so unfair
don't you have me you have nothing i want leave leave
Oh wait, I can start making torches too, can't I?
Let's make eight.
Yay!
Now it's a little less spooky.
Get off!
She's killed so many people.
I told you I'm a vengeful ghost.
My bagel just did a magical girl transformation into a
croissant.
What happened?
how did this turn into a block wasn't it just bushes just a
second ago how is it change like that
ad ball boy thanks for the five gifted but yeah I don't know
it's hard to say like what else happened at the convention I
talked about it mostly in the in the the Twitter space
Saving out my limited gotcha of bucks for a character with a
huge gap coming out tomorrow.
Can you chaff the desire sensor for me?
Wait, in what game?
What game?
Zazamos.
I, uh, I polled for, uh, Ako today in Blue Archive.
I didn't get her the first time.
Or the second time.
But I got her the third time!
Oh, it's a ZZZ.
Is that game any good?
Is it a Hoyoverse?
I tend to not do Hoyoverse things, but...
The maid girls are really...
You know, they're targeting me, I think.
It's cool.
What?
the gameplay like?
What's the gameplay like?
Definitely Hoyoverse.
There's like furry guys in it and everything.
Simple hack and slash with stages.
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
It doesn't sound like not fun.
Just like kind of thinking like when I like what's so great
about like some of the gotcha games is I can just kind of
kind of play them very casually.
You can skip cutscenes, but that's how you see the
characters, right?
Can't wait for horse gotcha.
Soon till.
Current Limited banner is a made shark girl.
Yeah, I see art of her everywhere.
I see so much art of the made shark girl.
girl people love her i mean the design is really really cute
i can i know why i can see why they would be a fan
big sloppy tail yeah but yeah i don't know i just uh i
couldn't ever get into when I tried.
And...
I don't know.
Maybe it's just like the style of Hoyoverse games for me.
Feel...
I don't know.
I don't know what it is.
I can't just... I can't describe why.
The dailies are easy.
That's good.
In this one.
Zzy, zzy, zzy.
Zzy.
It's more persona-y with action combat.
I never dug Genshin but love Honkai Starbill and Zee Zee
Zee.
Hmm.
Are the stories any good?
Maybe I will try Zee Zee Zee.
But I can't do any more gotcha.
Brrrr!
Hi girly girl!
Hi little girly girl.
What?
Come here!
Pretty simple, up to where I've gotten.
Oh, that's my cat.
Come here!
Yeah, are you gonna jump in my chair?
Come here, I'm making room for you.
Sit in my chair.
No?
Come here.
Oh my gosh, she just flopped on the ground.
She's such a plopper.
Gotcha, anonymous.
really truly try to limit myself to one gotcha and right now
i am so blue archive pill that i i can't look at anything
else what are you doing stinky stinky johnny she's cleaning
herself i think she's okay she might she might want to go
eat soon though i'm doing three kitty love she's just
rolling around on the ground What are you looking at?
What's got your attention?
Is there a bug there?
What are you looking at?
You're scaring me.
Is there a bug?
Stop.
Why are you sniffing the ground like that?
There's nothing there.
She's... She's having delusions.
Is this the lap kitty?
Well, she was supposed to be.
What is...
Summons a trial challenge when dropped into the void?
What is this?
Did you know Niki had a collab with Dave the Diver?
I did know that, and I'm still confused how.
Managed to pull Best Girl Ellen, the shark maid, earlier
today while watching her maid cafe vlog.
So I thank you for having brought me the maid luck.
Of course!
Yippee!
I have minto brain worms.
Hey, stop!
That's my umbrella!
Stop it!
Oh my god, she's chewing my umbrella!
Hold on, stop!
Hold on.
I'm gonna let her out.
She's being a menace.
Stop!
Oh my god!
Oh!
Ah!
Stop!
Stop it.
Stop.
You're gonna put a hole in my...
She put a hole in my umbrella.
Oh my god, no!
This was my expensive umbrella.
No!
That's... That's Venom's arms.
Stop it!
Huh?
She's such a menace!
My umbrella!
No!
Oh, I have umbrella fun.
Thank you.
No, you don't have to.
I bought it last time I was in Japan and I got it at like a
specialty umbrella store.
I was like, I'm gonna splurge on an umbrella.
I was like, I'm gonna splurge.
Oh!
I'm gonna splurge on a nice umbrella.
You chew toy.
I mean the umbrella fun.
Thank you.
She was then attacking his arm.
I got some, I have, I took out like some stuff from a box
that was sent to me from off Kai.
Huh?
Hmm.
She's a phantom minus.
Huh?
Okay.
I need to do more.
I need to start building some stuff.
Expensive umbrella loss or stolen.
$2.7.11 special and I'll have it for life.
I know!
Right!
The haunt in between events are peak.
Let's see.
What should we start building?
Hmm.
Was that her cat?
Yeah, my cat.
My cat's name is Paz.
She's so sweet.
a menace we have some gravel mangrove of proper proper gull
proper goo am I good on food I'm not hungry oh chest yeah
it's a good thing chest let's build that we could start
storing everything let's see ah la la la la la la la la la
la la la once we get some water I swear, I remember like
before when I played this things would like, like animals
would pop up, but we haven't gotten a single animal yet.
Hmm.
A corral for animals.
More platform.
Yeah, I am gonna...
This one is different.
Choo!
When can we expect to hear you voicing a character in a
mountain?
how how what metal gear game i haven't been able to catch a
lot of your streams live but your vibes have made lots of
work is much more bearable so thank you for being so funny
also good night whispering throw won't tell you this but
you're very cute i'll say the whisper cute i'll say it i'll
say it before you i said it first i said it before chovac i
said i said the whisper cute before Chovek even ever thought
the before Chovek even came out the womb I was thinking that
wisps are so cute I said it before you were even a concept
before you were even before you were even implemented into
this into this world thanks Chovek good night no no don't
think Chovek think me
where's your loyalty
Don't think, Chovec!
It was my idea to say that wisps are so cute.
Always have, but no, I kind of want to take it back.
When you guys get cocky about it, I kind of want to take it
back.
Okay, let's start building also maybe a fence.
Chovec by Oshi!
We're as cute as you?
Don't insult yourself like that.
Oh my gosh.
Um, fence.
Except the one area we have for murder.
There we go.
Oh wait, actually we need a few more.
For sticks.
There we go.
33.
That should be, maybe good.
If I do this.
Now, I'm not just making a pen here.
I'm making, like, a whole little outline.
This is my island in the sky.
And no one else is allowed to join.
No one else is allowed in.
No one else can join.
Well, um...
Cute as mint, but taller.
But you play Ace Combat 4, 5, 0, 7.
I would like to play more Ace Combat, yes.
But, please be patient.
Because I'm working on other stuff first.
But eventually, yeah.
Not even Snake.
Snake's not coming in.
Oh my gosh, that would be such a great addition.
Not...
Not solid Snake, but snakes in Minecraft will be so fun.
Shorter is better.
You think so?
I think people are always exaggerating my height, though.
You see, I am not the size of a pinky.
I actually am of normal size.
Oh, my God.
No, he's learning.
He knows that he can't...
That he will...
Okay, we're good.
We're good.
Okay, push, push, push, push, push, push, push, push, push,
push!
I'm a pretty average size I think
I don't think it's cope I think it's you know I think it's
normal Where the shire
What do you call a cookbook filled with French dessert
recipes written by a ghost maid A mont Mont blanc tone
Mont You give off such 9 centimeter energy.
I don't know why.
You're standing at virtual vacations as otherwise.
Yeah, but when I'm standing next to two very, or three very
tall people, of course the perspective is going to be off.
Mean toad baggage.
Let's see.
Let's create like a ledge of death.
Okay.
Let's jump down.
Did something form?
Wait, did you guys see?
Did you guys see something pop up there real quick or am I
crazy?
Did you guys see that or am I crazy?
Maybe I'm crazy.
That means I'm crazy.
I'm so brain dead.
I'm so...
You guys, I'm sorry.
brain that i am today i got maybe like three hours of sleep
of rested sleep you know something did pop up but you're
still crazy okay see see g-man's a real one telling it
telling it as it is something popped up but you know i'm i'm
actually loopy hero brian they wouldn't him in this.
When am I gonna get stuff though?
For like... Like sheep and stuff.
Do I have to trade for the sheep?
I have to get diamonds?
I have to keep going?
We have to keep digging deeper?
Or would they?
That's so evil, they wouldn't do that.
What one block version is this?
I actually have no idea.
It's very different from the one that I did before.
I think it's a little, it feels a little slower.
Oh, oh god.
We can get some string.
Oh yeah, it's 1.21.
You're right, you're right, you're right, you're right.
Oh, we can order a cow!
eventually let's get some string though
what let's order some string and then we murder him I am
keep upgrading buddy keep upgrading know where you going
order a cow order a cow Sounds like a promiscuous website.
Stop moving!
No!
You need to go to the murder...
This area.
Come here, come here.
Oh, look, look, look, look, look!
Something you want to buy!
Come here, come here.
Yeah, yeah.
No!
He knew what it was!
Make him walk the path.
Plank.
If I do attack him, will he get angry?
Here we go.
Slowly, but...
It's fine.
We'll leave him for now.
You missed your chance.
I was too excited for him to be standing there.
What the plank, me hearties.
But yeah, what did you guys do this weekend?
Well, I was gone.
I'm gonna say in advance too I know tomorrow's my
anniversary I don't have much plan you guys I'm really sorry
it's gonna be kind of probably it's kind of disappointing
honestly because it's like my first anniversary but I have
nothing for it
unironically made cafe and TFTI, thanks for the invite.
What the hell?
Wait for you to come back.
There he goes.
Bye.
Went to a maid cafe at MGSCon.
Yeah.
Oh, we were going to make a new shovel.
Went to a convention and got a tattoo in celebration of
someone nine You guys are obsessed with nine centimeters.
Is this like a...
But how long is the...
I mean...
Nine centimeters is plenty.
I'm not shaming.
It's not...
How much you have.
It's how you use it, right?
That's what they always say.
about any context.
In any sort of context.
It's not how much you have, it's how you use it.
I do not use it.
Well, then here lies.
Don't complain.
I choose to use it for evil.
Now that's just not right.
Awesome stream today, Mint.
I'm jumping.
I'm walking the plank!
Oh!
Now we're finally starting to get hungry a little bit.
And let's make some more...
sticks.
And...
and... fence.
Oh!
I didn't mean to do all of it!
Oh my gosh.
Fence.
Oh yeah.
If you were nine centimeter, would you be okay with being,
with, with being in a jar?
No.
I'm a ghost and I'm not okay with being in a jar.
You know how like there's the little ghost canisters that
everybody threatens to put me in too?
I'm not okay with that either.
Thinking more of a cage.
Maybe soon eventually you could put your own Minto in
wherever you like.
Well, not within, I mean, I mean, it would be yours.
I could not stop you.
But I would not want to know.
It's not going to happen to line up with Eva.
great time watching some fighting games speaking of have you
ever played a fighting game i think i've like very casually
played stuff before but nothing ever serious before i
wish the rain would
stop i wish there was a way i could stop the rain la la
because
the rain and the sounds are so loud i don't like them i
think it hard for me to think Womp, womp, womp.
Sagumelon, welcome to membership.
Thank you.
You can turn it down.
I guess you're right.
Like, I'm not used to Minecraft pausing, you know, when
you...
Let's see, weather.
Let's take it down to, like, 45.
Two!
Into the phantom thermos for you bad ghosts.
No!
How's that?
Is it still too loud?
Kind of the same.
Mysterious traitor, how did you get in there?
He's like, good question.
We can buy the beehive!
Huh?
Hold on.
Guess who birthday it is?
Mine!
Fit by far, happy birthday!
look awesome thank you man thank you happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you happy birthday dear wiper happy
birthday to you happy birthday like 20 percent Oh, see,
that's better.
Let's also plant some more trees.
Maybe we can get some more...
Actually, I'm just going to turn the overall sound to, like,
70.
I could do the weather up a little bit more.
Perfect.
The rain is wisps crying because Minto hates ours.
Why do you think that?
The trader has two feet of wood between his legs.
The fence?
What do you mean by that?
Thank you so much for the amazing streams.
You're pretty good.
Thank you!
Let's do some bamboo.
And I can plant that.
And we can get that going.
Because that plants well.
We'll replant this like right here.
I'm gonna keep extending this.
Don't think that just because I put a fence, it's like all
over.
You know?
In fact...
Huh?
I'm just question for you.
When Otacon...
Wait.
When Otacon pisses himself, do you think he changed his
pants or he walked around Shadow Moses with pissy pants?
I think he walked around Shadow Moses with pissy pants.
No, I don't need coal.
I don't need coal.
I want the beehive.
Do I have any more?
No, I don't have any more.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Sir?
I will be acquiring your beehive.
I think...
Oh, nice.
It's already growing.
I think it's quite...
uh well known that like otakon doesn't change his pants just
kind of goes around sopping what you know
throughout all the games every single one
mint please
it's just a pee guy
I didn't even ask the question.
Alright, why should we build on our little island?
There was one version of the one block that I saw that I
kind of wanted to get.
It had like different islands that you could go to.
I think it was a bedrock version.
What is Bro doing over there?
He is staying out of my way.
He's actually in the very best possible place he could be.
He's staying out of my way.
He's causing no trouble.
I think I can get it.
All the little bees are going to come to me.
What's the thing?
Compost.
I need slabs.
Slab.
Compost.
And then we can start.
putting some stuff in to get bone meal.
Such as.
Oh.
Ah.
They can build a cauldron to collect rain.
Is that what that does?
No way.
Wait, I just sold all my iron.
You guys, I just sold...
We gotta dig.
The boss!
You're right, the moss.
The moss.
Takes a while with the cauldron.
But right now, we're not getting anything.
Might be good.
Mysterious traitor new maid cafe employee.
I don't think he's got what it takes.
His head is really big.
His head is huge actually quite is he's quite he's got quite
a noggin
let's see let's try growing i don't want to grow this well i
do but it's just for decoration mostly so if i put a beehive
right here will they come
do you hear that
he's working in there he's working No flowers?
What do you think I'm doing?
Let me get some more seeds.
There we go.
Now there's flowers.
More seeds for the compost.
Perfect.
Come on now.
It's fine.
You hear him?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Everybody okay?
We felt the time skip.
Something happened with OBS.
Disconnected real quick.
All right, straight out a little slow.
Sorry, guys.
You know, it's been a while since I've played Minecraft.
It's been some time.
But we're getting back into it.
We're getting back into it, baby.
How much was the cauldron?
Call, call, call, call, call, call, call.
I just spelled cauldron again.
Am I crazy?
Oh.
How do you...
Huh?
Oh, there we go.
No!
I need seven.
Okay.
You guys, don't judge me.
Don't judge me.
We got raw.
We got it raw.
English is hard, okay?
Nice.
More.
Yeah.
More, more, more.
I hear him.
He wants to come out.
I think he wants to come out only when it's daytime.
Instead of it's nice, lovely night.
Unique New York.
You need New York.
Awesome, awesome.
Whoa.
Judgment.
Woo!
Okay.
We're making, we're cutting through these.
We're gonna get some honey.
It's gonna be great for your ego class.
My ego classes.
Stop!
I, I, I mean, but truly, ghost is my first language.
Are you gonna judge someone whose first language is not
English?
First, making a mistake in English?
Yes!
You're so mean!
Say something in Ghost?
He won't...
You won't understand.
I'll say something, okay.
I'm gonna teach you guys a curse word.
Okay, I'm gonna teach you guys a bad word.
Ready?
Boo.
Don't ever say that around your mom.
I can't believe you just said that on stream.
I know.
Oh, I know.
Can I say that around your mom?
Did a double take when you said honey because I thought I
heard you say the blue archive emoji word while I'm cooking.
The blue archive emoji word.
Why is it getting so loud?
Nihon ghost.
Trader!
Hmm.
We need to get diamonds.
In light of the foul language, I think I need to give you
this before you're demonetized.
No, no, no, it's okay.
That word.
What?
Anyway.
I'm curious.
I don't...
Is it like one of the things in the...
one of the emojis that you like can spam in your guild
anyway the cat bunny word
what cat bunny what wait
i'm so confused you guys confuse me every day i don't know
what's going on?
I'm so confused.
Please wrap it up.
I'm sorry.
I don't know.
Move on.
Why am I getting... Why am I... Why are people... Why are
you
getting...
My weeb card?
What?
Not my weeb card.
If I don't have a weep card, I have nothing left.
If I don't have a weep card, what even is my identity?
What do I even have?
Oh, I need more apples.
We need more apples so we can eat you guys.
Here, let's put down the plants again.
If I don't have a weep card, I just have...
I don't even know.
Stink card.
I don't have that either.
You have that.
Don't get the mistaken with me, please.
Thank you.
I have, well, I was going to say, like, I have maybe a freak
card.
Got my freak card on.
Freak Minto.
Freak Phantom Card.
If I made Freak Phantom Cards, would you guys want one?
Back, way back when I first opened memberships, the first
44, because of course it had to be, because it's very
spooky, got the first people that, first 44 that joined the
memberships got a special card.
Maybe?
Freak, freak, freak?
Don't know.
Too much freak too much freak not enough phantom the v card
wait clearly you made the who's saying v card what's wrong
with you guys today you guys are so freaky um but uh maybe
if i brought those back and did the same thing first 44.
i remember who got the first one and the first one They're
sometimes still in the chat.
They're sometimes still in the chat.
What do you want?
Is it me?
No.
So jealous of the OGs.
What's there to be jealous of?
What I was thinking was the first 44...
Oh, sorry.
I don't think I finished my sentence.
The first 44...
would get it their name filled out by Watashi and then but
obviously there would be more but the first 44 would be the
ones that get it with the hand written I don't know it's
just a thought maybe but having freak phantom cards would be
kind of fun but you already open memberships No, it wouldn't
be a membership thing.
It would be...
Oh, food, food, food, food.
Oh, I forgot about my food.
Wait, don't steal any of my food!
Oh, he literally exploded.
Wait, where is he?
Oh!
They're okay.
Hmm.
We could get a slime ball.
We could get bone.
We don't need the bone.
We don't need any of this.
Go, go, go.
Go, go.
Please leave.
Please vacate the premises.
Spruce for podzole.
I have spruce, though.
What is a podzole good for?
Has this bee ever coming out?
Wait, I don't hear him anymore.
Oh, wait, he did.
Okay, okay.
He's still in there.
I hear him.
Saw that the anime fest schedule is out.
Your schedule for the con is packed.
me.
I know.
It's crazy.
That's why I was just like, oh gosh, if I don't make it.
Crazy, crazy.
It's waiting to jump scare you.
It's a booby.
Okay.
You have an event or two each day.
It's insane.
Yeah, I'm going to still try and put out a schedule for this
week, but I'm gonna be basically streaming in between events
for of the convention so um it's a little it's a little
crazy but uh yeah I'll be there and I'll be streaming also
what was I gonna do oh make a uh we need another pick axe I
don't need this guy to leave.
I need this guy to get out of my hair.
If I kill him, will he be upset?
Huh?
Dead man tell no tales.
Oh!
Kill a villager.
I got an achievement!
So what did I...
I see that means I hadn't killed them before ever.
get some rest, too.
I will!
Thank you.
That means I never killed him before.
That was my first murder.
I've tasted blood.
Do you think they're gonna raise the prices?
You think they're gonna get upset?
Oh!
We're so close to 500!
That means we might get a new...
We might get a new block.
Please.
Step 5.
Alright.
New season.
Nice murder, Minta.
Thank you.
What are we?
Oh.
We're on to and decide.
Not counting the baby.
The baby was not murder.
Though it could have been.
The baby was a freak accident.
The baby was so defense.
I can't believe I ran over a baby this morning.
I missed out on getting a mean greet ticket, but I'm looking
forward to seeing a Vexpo.
Yeah!
Well, if you go to the Minto meetup, which I believe is a
Sunday afternoon.
Is this one gonna grow back?
Or do I have to plant it.
I think I have to plant it.
I wonder if I can make some bad guys appear.
Spilled out a little bit more.
Let's expand.
Domain.
Expansion.
I'm acting like I watched Gojo's bizarre adventure.
There we go.
look at that and we're gonna turn this into our pet play
area this is the pet world right here oh just not that here
they'll have plenty of room to walk probably eventually
and uh what did i say what did i say now they're all heaven
and earth mental owners this thank you what did i say now
you mix jojo with juju no i did Juju's bizarre event.
Wait, no.
Juju took ice.
You made an area specifically for pet play.
What is...
Is that weird?
Pet play?
I was thinking...
I said the pet play area.
It's a play pen for pets.
Yeah, exactly.
What did I say?
I'm just gonna...
I'm just...
You guys, this is it.
I'm leaving all my stuff to you.
Goodbye.
goodbye cruel world goodbye cruel world i don't want to live
i don't want to live on this planet anymore something
something goodbye goodbye goodbye goodbye goodbye wait i
need another chest but you're not living i am in minecraft i
don't want to live in minecraft anymore if i die why wonder
what happens
Haruka, thanks to the gifted!
Why does chat know this?
Chat knows a lot of things that I don't really understand.
Dual flip!
Oh, we're getting some of this other stuff too.
Oh, diorite.
It's Freaky Tuesday.
Please forgive the dehydrated ones.
Again.
I kind of mentioned this somewhat recently.
How like, you know, sometimes when I tell my friends who are
completely out of the VTuber sphere.
Just like sometimes things that are said to me or said in
chat.
They'll be like.
Oh my god.
Like girl.
Get out of there.
Girl.
They'll be like.
What?
Why do you tolerate this?
And I think my brain is seriously like...
I think I'm just seriously like...
So desensitized to things now.
It's pretty bad.
It's kind of like when you go on Twitter in public and
you're just like...
You're so used to seeing...
You know...
Like...
I don't know.
Anime boobies on your timeline.
You just think it's normal.
Then you go out in public and you're just like...
Oh wait.
This is...
This is not what normal people look at.
You know.
Oh, that's me.
Did someone say poopies?
So it's kind of funny just when I hear their perspective on
things.
How they're just like...
What?
What are you doing?
Oh, I thought that said order a ghost!
Wait, a goat?
A pig.
We can get gum powder.
I'm used to seeing people unconscious with blood on them.
Order a ghost!
It's called a Luigi board.
Our own freaky ghost maid?
No, sorry.
That's one of a kind.
Genuine one of a kind.
Huh?
I don't think I need anything here.
Maybe the cactus we could try getting.
How much iron?
Oh, I have quite a bit.
That we can be cooking up.
What's she doing over here?
bleeding.
Look how cute our area is, though, right?
We got so much nice stuff here.
We don't even need a house.
We're better than that.
And now we're getting clay and stuff, too.
What should I build next, you guys?
What should I build next?
Oh, my tummy's starting to hurt.
Why is my tummy starting to hurt?
What shaders do you have?
Uh, nud.
build big shell oh we're getting minecraft music again
do you like it better without shaders see I like minecraft
with shaders but I like it when it's not like when it makes
like the clouds and everything too realistic I'm like no I
kind of like it better when it's you know the clouds are
still like this but it just adds a little bit of of ambient
lighting.
Very lightweight shaders.
Yeah, yeah.
It just adds a little bit.
Preferred a bit cartoony.
Yeah, like there's some that make the grass and everything
so realistic and I'm like, I don't need that.
I just wanna, you know, I wanna have like, again, the
lighting to have like some pretty colors.
even sometimes the water oh yeah oh we gotta make our
cauldron
okay now we will be collecting water right here
okay nice all right guys very good very good just trying to
think of what are the things i could build Let's start
Throwing more moss into here I'm gonna need food soon I'm
gonna need I'm gonna need food I'm gonna starve in Minecraft
I wrote a poem To immortalize a good friend that I met off
kai okay what is a wisp i think i saw one run past me just
now how another could love someone he'd never met before
enough that his legs would take him down a 10 minute run in
two part one out of four amelia
you really put some thought into this
Out of four?
Bro's been cooking.
You've been really thinking about this.
Afkai was a couple months ago.
Oh, part two.
17 seconds ago, we caught a tweet from her.
Stuff for anyone still at Afkai.
I couldn't do it, though.
But he could, for I was not the strongest wisp.
But he could.
He became smaller and smaller down the street.
And I was sure it was destiny.
You really felt so moving.
What's the next part?
What happens next?
I'm invested now.
Me too!
The suspense.
Don't leave me hanging.
When do they kiss?
I'm kind of shipping them.
I'm not going to lie.
Oh, part three.
That he would win a mint card because he was the strongest
wisp.
He would make it from the crowd.
To the Hyatt.
And of course, he'd win our Oshi's offerings.
But 10 minutes later, and I was there too.
It's on a cliffhanger!
And what?
Oh my god.
And then we kissed.
Wait until next month for part two.
I'm expanding so I can put in more trees too.
Oh, it wasn't meant to be now!
It wasn't wispingly possible to be a half-mile head start.
And I remembered that destiny isn't real.
But a few seconds later, when I saw him again, he held up
his phone.
And he was in the center of her new tweet.
I dag it.
Oh my gosh, no, Destiny is real!
What's so funny?
I liked it.
That's why it was funny.
You don't laugh at things that you really like?
Did I grab everything I needed from this guy?
That's kind of expensive.
15 iron ingots for a cactus?
practice.
Hmm.
Okay, get out of here.
I think I laughed too much, you guys.
I think I'm laughing all the time.
That was beautiful, Amelia.
Hopefully, next time is your chance to get the sign if you
really want it.
We laugh and we grow fat here.
True!
Don't mind me just rolling the true gotcha.
You failed, I'm sorry.
I procrastinated so hard writing this.
I had it done a few weeks ago, I spent way too much time
trying to work up the courage to send it.
I'm glad you liked it.
I hope he does too.
He's probably so honored.
I'm glad you felt so inspired.
No such thing as too much laughter.
Sometimes I worry people will take it the wrong way.
Like sometimes I just...
There he goes.
Sometimes I just laugh because I like something so much, you
know?
I'm not laughing in like a...
This sucks.
I'm laughing in like a...
Wow.
That was just so great.
I have no words, but I must laugh.
Going to Japan several months I ever made Cafe Reckons.
I'm looking forward to checking them out.
Yeah!
Have fun, Seymour!
It's about the Tutoroo Gacha.
You mentioned a few streams ago.
It's like...
Ultra rare.
One in a million.
I have no words, but I must laugh.
Uh-oh, you guys, we need more food!
Okay, let's start planting trees.
Tree time.
One in a mint million.
Grow!
Uh-oh.
Guys, we're gonna starve!
We're gonna starve!
Oh gosh, oh gosh, oh gosh.
Okay, don't panic.
Don't, everybody, stop panicking.
Stop panicking.
You guys are making me panic, okay?
Choo!
Don't even try, it's too rare.
Oh, don't test your luck.
It's too rare.
I'm panicking.
No, you're panicking.
I'm not panicking.
Two.
Oh my god, stop.
Hi.
I've never been more called.
Huh.
Let's start.
Okay.
apples.
You're the apple of my eye.
My mom said I'm one in a million.
And I'm sure she meant that you're just so unique and
special.
Possessed to push my locks.
Get out of here!
You'll never find it!
I'll leave the tutu in one one.
piece.
I'll leave the toot-do in one piece.
Stealth camouflage.
You guys, there's no apples.
Don't you, why don't you sell food?
Why don't you sell food, mysterious traitor?
Why?
We're gonna starve.
Let's just keep digging.
Plain the seeds no i don't have any water i can't plant them
i have no water they won't grow what's this we this is
always a team play game it's you guys i you are me we are we
we're a team there's no i in team it's always been us i
always consider you part of the We're all together in this.
We're all complicit in any crime.
I am literally mean to.
That's what you said when I possessed your mom last night.
I don't think that made much sense.
I think I...
I appreciate the effort.
I think I could have botched that one.
What I meant to say.
I think it's dead.
You know what?
I'm not even going to attempt to say what I was trying to
say.
The joke, the bit is dead.
Just like the fans said to Konami.
The bit is dead and you're the ones who killed it.
Good one, Minto.
I don't want to hear it from you.
Alright, let's grab another.
Hmm, another thing.
Another shovel.
Okay, before I was like, no rain, please.
Anyway, please.
Now I'm like, please rain, please rain.
And this is why you're our Oshi.
Why do you have the clown emoji?
There too.
Tyler, welcome to membership.
Thank you!
Why do you have the clown emoji?
We're gonna starve.
The bees aren't coming out.
If I take this down, do they, uh...
Does it destroy it?
I can't remember.
Okay, nice.
Got lots and lots of bamboo, which means we can make lots of
string, and we can also make lots of bamboo thingies.
Bamboo.
Blocko bamboo.
Wow, it's kind of expensive.
Oh.
Uh-oh.
You guys, I can't run anymore.
I'm too hungry.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Bamboo.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no.
I would make more bamboo.
Oh, here.
Oh.
Are we gonna die?
Eat him for sustenance.
The trees do not bear fruit.
The winters are long and cold.
The animals have abandoned us.
I think.
I think this might be it Her small journey Oh gosh I really
hope it doesn't drop an apple Over the edge
This might be it for us Everybody An apple An apple Oh
Sustenance, sustenance We can get more Food!
We need water.
Just a little to hold us over.
We can make it.
We can make it together, everybody!
Believe!
And if not...
I've never tried brains before.
Okay.
Wait, hold on.
Let's plant more trees.
Come on, grow, grow, grow.
Grow, grow, grow, please.
Expand, expand.
There's a first for everything.
I know.
Don't you get, like, certain parasites from... How would you
get up there?
From eating brains, though.
If I don't make it...
Whoa!
Oh my gosh!
It's beautiful!
It took forever to grow!
If I don't make it... Oh my gosh, it grew because my body's
gonna die here!
Oh my god, I'm gonna die here!
Gonna move this so it's not under the tree.
Maybe we'll get some actual water so we can grow some
pumpkins or something!
Melon!
Something!
It grew you a place to rest.
I want to live Please Please girl world Just give me some
fruit Something I don't want to die Oh let's plant another
tree here Just keep planting trees One day They will bear
fruit Food ghost?
But ghosts don't need food, do they?
Yes we do!
What do you think the sacrifice is?
You know, people leave, like, offerings and stuff for
ghosts!
Because we're hungry!
Hungry ghosts!
Sure, you'll find a way to survive sooner or later.
Yeah, you've never heard of a hungry ghost before?
It's real.
Hungry ghosts.
You're next, buddy.
You're next.
People leave out.
Whatever.
Oranges is a popular thing.
Live, mints.
You have to live.
Vern Stortholf Hunter.
How long do I have to live?
What's a ghost favorite food?
Boulogne.
That's up for you to decide, Minto.
No water for crops.
We have no water.
I made some sort of progress.
But I'm not rewarded for it.
Actually, I don't know what progress I made.
Can I eat bamboo?
It's sugar, right?
It's kind of the same as sugar.
sugarcane.
Bulgogi.
I love bulgogi though.
So good.
You guys are making me hungry.
I had the most mediocre pizza last night.
The travel was hard.
I'll be honest.
It was so ugh.
Gosh.
It was like I think that's why I don't know what day it is
because but everything was just so long.
Rindle!
Thanks for the three months.
Bullog knees.
What you...
What?
Bull, bull, bull, bull, dees.
Hope you had fun at MGSCon.
Love ya.
Thank you!
I did.
It's so much fun.
I hope it happens again next year.
Thank you.
If this is the map that if you jump off, you just TP to the
top again.
I know one of these maps do that, but don't do that and
refill.
Oh, wait.
Okay, let's attempt.
This is for science.
We're doing it.
We're jumping off the edge of the world for science.
For science.
It looks like outer wilds here.
Do a flip.
Fall into the void!
We did it!
Yuffie!
Yay!
The void fed you!
Oh my gosh!
We know the strats.
We know the life halves.
What you doing down here?
On the death walk.
Free food.
More food.
Order a horse.
Order a llama.
What are we getting to the good stuff?
Huh?
Gravel.
Gravel gives us a flint.
Maybe we should order some of that.
Do I have enough dirt?
Cauldron has water.
No, it doesn't.
We escape death by dying.
Woohoo!
Well, the pufferfish has water.
Wait, does it count?
Does this count?
Oh!
Oh, God.
Um.
Uh.
He's just swimming around over there.
I'm gonna take away his life source.
Oh, no.
Oh no, no, wait, wait, don't, I can't, I got it, I can't, I
need to live.
Get a second one.
Can I put this in here?
There we go.
All right.
Wait, if I get a, how many do I need to make an endless, an
endless, you know, okay, I'm gonna put it, I'm gonna
meticulously put it here.
Okay, see?
Goodbye.
Now, if he falls off the edge, I mean...
Two by two for infinite.
Okay, okay.
Save him.
For what purpose?
For what purpose do we need this guy?
Alrighty.
Let's do our water...
Right here in the corner.
Okay.
Have to be careful about...
this though okay oh no
let me cook let me cook you need a floor yeah what do you
think i'm doing
all right there's our floor there's our floor ha ha ha ha ha
ha ha ha ha Water!
Sweet water, sweet water!
Let's plant!
Oh my gosh, we're finally gaming!
Let's make a hoe.
Alright, Chet, who's volunteering?
Yeah!
Dun,
dun, dun.
Oh, sorry.
I didn't mean to hit you.
Are you okay?
No, he raised his prices!
I didn't murder him.
He went down with the ship as a good captain should.
If you make a big enough pond, you can fish.
True.
Okay.
Very good.
Let's put this.
Let's move this guy.
Oh, whoops.
Can I fish here in this thing, or is it too small?
Man, I love fishing.
You can fish in any size pond.
Oh, no way!
Alright, perfect.
Now, let's keep one blocking.
I do kind of want to...
here we should start making we should start building like a
downstairs area as well I think I think we should start
building it the downstairs area where
do I want to build it oh wait I can put more of the flowers
down too we'll never we'll never get these bees but that's
okay hmm Put your tools away just in case.
You don't have any faith in me here.
Fake any heat.
Why go down when you can go up?
Well, I do want to build one thing below.
I do...
Below...
Below, I do want to build one thing.
And hold on.
I will do it.
No!
Because I can't...
I kind of want to build a thing below the one block.
Oh gosh, it's so scary, though.
Wait, where's the one block?
Okay, this one...
Okay.
That...
Nope, just kidding.
Uh...
That one.
Right?
That's the one block?
I believe?
Right!
That's the one block, I think.
But yeah, we got water!
finally!
It's okay.
Uh-oh.
Am I gonna drown?
There we go.
We're okay.
Everything is all good.
I even have dirt to replace it.
Perfect.
Now, I will feel less nervous about um oh oops about uh
getting stuff here
hungry ghost festival is actually a holiday here in hong
kong happening next month i remember to leave you some
leftover offering yes thank you that's exactly what i'm
talking about thank you so much maybe people don't know
about hungry ghosts i think we need more food aka might be
time to send me over i'm going over the edge a little bit
you guys might be time to send me over the edge
i don't know why august is such a haunted month
back to the infinite void not again Yes, again!
Again, again!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha Again, again!
Because summer vacation?
Maybe.
There's so much to live for.
I'm not even alive!
But I'm glad I have so much to be dead for.
I'm so glad I'm dead.
Even though it's so much like being alive, I think.
Just like a little extra stuff.
You know?
It's hard to explain.
So much to be unalive for.
You seen that fun with it?
Yeah.
I'm a pretty good time.
Even the dead can't escape taxes.
That's what I'm saying.
I think it's so similar to being alive.
Ugh.
But, you know, um...
When are you guys coming out?
I hear you in there.
And when are these guys gonna grow?
There's taxes in the afterlife?
Ooh.
Oh, buddy.
I don't know how to tell you this, but, uh...
I said it's pretty similar to...
I said it's pretty similar to, uh...
To, to, to, you know...
To real lot to to to the you know I don't want I don't want
to say real life because I feel like my life Even though
it's the afterlife.
It's still real life so What is it?
Oh, no, I'm feeling the existentialism again happening
It's your reality.
Yeah It's my reality
Google how to free myself from both life and death
oh did I oh no just kidding but now being a ghost is pretty
dandy I would say so is this the real life is this just
fantasy oh yeah I'm starting to get sleep with you.
We're almost at 2,000 blocks.
When will we get an animal?
Oh wait, the animal's right here.
Chat's full of them.
I know.
What the...
Where's the...
Pickaxe?
Meow.
Did I get...
Oh no, there's some iron and sticks.
Yeah, where's the...
Oh, I need three.
The world of darkness, Lord, ghosts live in a reflection of
the living world called the Shadowlands, and they do have to
pay ghost taxes.
Yeah, why would I make that up?
Why would I make up ghost taxes?
Pickaxe.
It's death and taxes, not death or taxes.
Why'd you spawn in there?
I want the trial key.
I want to know what that is.
I'm so curious.
So curious.
Enzo, Enzo my man.
Would you rather be a ghost who can't haunt or a maid cafe?
Oh, sorry, a maid.
Oh, I think the music's so good.
Oh, or a maid that can't clean.
I love haunting, though.
I'm haunting you right now.
Would you want me to not haunt you anymore?
If you don't want me to haunt you anymore, I get it.
It's a little freaky.
It's not everybody's thing.
You know.
I'll stop.
I'll stop taking your life force.
I'll stop haunting you.
Don't worry.
Actually, I don't clean.
I don't clean very well.
So you're like, which would you want?
Which would you want?
And I'm like, well, I'm already.
It's a kind of already currently one or the other.
I can't clean very well.
You guys, okay.
It's, it's a, it's, it's called being a maid cafe maid.
It's called being a maid cafe maid where, um, where it just
i i i i like serve in the cafe i don't really do much of
anything else can you cook well i mean like there's like
chefs that do that at the cafe there's people who do that
like i serve i'm serving all day every day and you guys are
whisper you're also my gochidin some Oh, what happened?
Why did I shrink?
What happened to me?
That was kind of freaky.
You can draw some cool stuff on Omelrose.
Yeah!
I'm serving.
Can you slay, though?
Slay!
She's the Van Gogh of Ketchup Joyce.
Why is the...
Why is the potato taking so long?
Maybe I need a pumpkin instead.
Pumpkin seed.
Wait.
I have a couple pumpkins.
Let's just do everything.
Oh, but for the pumpkin I need like sugar and stuff like
that.
too don't i the the wait it's melon the melon can just grow
baby core thanks to the gifted you need to go more cute okay
i'm looking i'm looking at the at the seed oh maybe it's
intimidated if i'm holding this right I think
it grew a little.
Do I have any bone meal?
It grew!
Micmac!
I think it's really gifted!
Maybe I could get some more.
Nope.
That's it.
Oh, yes.
More.
Someone grew taller.
It's me!
I'm a whole whopping 10 feet now.
Try calling me small.
We're so close to 2,000.
Wait, no.
I was right the first time.
There we go.
10 feet, imagine.
uh vtuber actually what scientists would be like there's
like they're like skyscraper size right oh 2000 new recipes
check your recipe book huh huh huh what did i make i can't
did i grab something no they don't like give you any sort of
like achieve anything any bonuses for when you like hit
certain things It's just so sad.
They're just, they're, yeah, Giants are usually like super
duper.
Yeah, Tempe is Amazonian.
Yeah, I think so.
And then like a Giants is like the size of a, like a
skyscraper, right?
Like a tall building.
That can be that.
Free, fly, fo, fun.
Have you guys ever noticed that my sock is a little
transparent?
Have you ever noticed?
Where's my knees?
On my socks.
On my skirt.
There's something...
Okay, I don't think I've ever showed this to you guys
before.
I want to show you something kind of interesting.
Wait, I took this picture.
Actually, no.
I'll just post it on Twitter later.
Actually, I wonder if I could do it right now.
Give me a second.
I wonder if I could do it right now.
If I could show you right now.
One second.
It might take me a second, though.
Oh, wait.
No, I don't think I can.
Wait, hold on.
I don't think I can.
No, I don't think I can.
No!
Wait, maybe I can.
What the heck is she talking about?
I'm gonna see, I'm gonna see.
Yes, you can.
I can do anything I put my mind to, maybe.
Maybe.
Hold on, hold on.
I wonder if it'll work.
Oh my gosh.
I think it's working.
Wait a second.
Putting my mind in the bubble.
Wait, look at this.
It's kind of amazing.
So basically, I don't want to alert anybody, but I'm kind of
stripping.
I don't want to alert anybody, but I'm kind of stripping
right now.
But you'll see.
It's so, it's so cool.
I hope YouTube doesn't get mad at me.
I discovered this the other day.
It's so cool.
Don't get mad at me, YouTube, okay?
Don't get mad at me, YouTube.
One second.
Hmm.
What's going on?
One second.
Now I discovered that.
this the other day and now I'm like...
I'm like...
It's so fun.
You'll see.
In a second.
It's kind of scandalous.
Wait a second.
One second!
You'll see!
You'll all see!
Oh, it's kind of weird because I'm a ghost though.
It's kind of weird because I'm a ghost, though.
This is the longest second of my life.
You guys, look.
I can have...
I can take off my skirt.
Oh, la la.
What if one day I just streamed without my skirt?
You never know.
Oh.
You'd never know.
How scandalous it is.
Easy breezy, beautiful cover girl.
Oh, wait, why did it change from a leaf to a block?
Oh my god, Redstone!
Woohoo!
I thought the whole point of working from home is that pants
are optional.
exactly right but you know i have i can't be off the clock
for you know my gochujin sama ojo sama i can't be i can't be
so lazy oh oh wait are we gonna be able to enchant stuff
when am i gonna get a sheep wait that means we might be
closer to diamonds
what was the goal again of the one block to defeat the ender
dragon I think that's still the goal haven't worn pants and
days love work from home
love work from home oh nice melon seeds we can get a sponge
but what would we use a sponge for hmm hmm If you have 12
strings, you can make a bed.
No way.
I have nine.
Wait, we have a bamboo, right?
Bamboo can make string.
Right, can it?
String.
Can we not make string?
I thought you could make string.
Am I crazy?
Oh, stripped.
Just like me.
Break cobwebs.
Well, we don't have any cobwebs.
Bamboo makes paper.
No, I think the sugar can makes the paper.
Making string is in mods.
Oh, really?
I always thought.
You can make string too.
Oh my god, wait.
I was going to say this is going to fill up, but...
We don't need it anymore.
We do need just a little bit.
more string though yeah you useless you're useless to me
you're useless to me you're useless come here don't run from
me oh aim don't go there we go don't bully i wasn't I was
sending him home.
Duh.
Useless.
Sometimes I wish I could just dig forever and not, like,
think about anything.
Wait, so since we have nothing else, what about, like,
enemies?
Do these guys not spawn either?
Oh, a melon!
Oh, my God!
Hallelujah!
Melon!
Oh my gosh.
Wait, is this thing dead now or will it spawn another melon?
It'll regrow?
Perfect!
Our little island is so cute, isn't it?
I love our little island.
I'm gonna grow a jungle.
Over here.
I don't know if these need more room.
Oh.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm just, like, wishing there was more that would spawn,
though.
Like, before when I played it, they would, like, give you
stuff every so often, or, like, animals would spawn, or
maybe I need to play a different version of it.
Everything's so different.
Like, I feel like this is a little too...
Like, I don't have any animals.
Mavs only spawn 24%.
plus blocks away so if you make a lit of grass platform out
cows might spawn oh let's try that then i don't know how far
out i actually am but
hmm make the platform bigger okay oh i was like what is that
what is that floating away
I think we're gonna have to start using other materials.
Oh yeah, this thing grew so quickly.
Let's see.
We might need to start using other materials.
Might be time.
I'm gonna put the sand away so I don't accidentally place it
and be stupid about it.
Let's just put down some oak planks.
Wait, I want some more dirt first.
so it's a little more cohesive wait are we not going to get
dirt anymore oh oh we got some dirt
you'll get hostile mobs yeah yeah no worries only spawn on
they do only spawn on the grass okay all right then we'll
have to build out autobots build out okay just
a little bit more little bit more just a little bit oh wrong
thing a little bit more hmm hmm it's such i think the
biggest pain is switching between the different things you
know what i mean let's also start cooking some of this uh
gold so we can sell it and dirt so we can build it Okay,
nice.
And light it up, baby.
Light it up, baby.
Um.
Uh.
You.
And.
Uh.
What's it called?
Torch.
Feels so weird playing Minecraft again.
Even though it's, like, not actual Minecraft.
Feels so weird.
Even, like, touching the game again in some capacity.
Okay.
Since I haven't played it in so long.
I think my brain riot was replaced with bloons, honestly.
Also, it's kind of, you know, it's hard to play Minecraft.
I know some people prefer solo, but...
It's hard.
It's hard when, like, uh...
Tunny String?
Turtle Scoot!
It's hard playing Minecraft.
yourself though you know
have you been down the beach ojo server recently i'll be
honest i haven't been on since i went that first time let's
just say you just uh oh i feel a little awkward about it i'm
just like oh i don't know if i'm i feel awkward like
building in there
anti-social mythos i can't i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm so
Anti-social!
Haunting the server.
You're welcome there.
Just go.
They haven't made me feel unwelcome.
You know, not in any ways at all.
It's just, you know, me.
Being like, Oh.
Is it okay?
Also, all the mods do kind of freak me out.
There's so many.
but maybe I should just go in sometime off stream and try
and get used to it a bit more mm-hmm
we as MP streams yeah but I was invited to that so and I'm
not gonna be like let me in let me in but are these I don't
even know if they're Are you still playing them?
Are you winning your block game?
I think so.
I think we're winning.
Oh, Minecraft music.
Bees work.
Rain falls.
Need more dirt.
How far is 24 blocks out, you think?
One.
Two.
Three.
4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15!
Oh, shucks.
Uh-oh.
Yeah, we're gonna have to make it...
We're gonna... We won't fill this in.
We're just gonna have to make it skinny.
We get barely any dirt anymore, though.
Oh, I say that, and they start giving...
You know what's funnier than 24?
I'm not gonna...
Oh, my gosh.
I'm not gonna say the joke.
I think I know.
But you can say it.
You guys don't guess in the chat.
25.
Good one, boy.
eyes.
Bangabab.
Okay.
How much more dirt do we have now?
10 dirt!
And we have none in here, right?
Oh, no.
Oh, shucks.
Maybe I should steal some from over here.
Oh, come on!
Two...
Ah!
What do you buy with gold?
Nothing?
Okay.
All my iron.
I lost everything!
I can't even...
I
lost all my new dirt!
I lost... I lost it all.
I lost it all.
You still have a...
all for a bit of dirt we're going back to the stone age with
this one i know oh my god let's get our wooden picking out
not even stone age wait can i make stone oh we can't we make
it can't make stone stone stone stone stone You're so cute
and also I'm sorry for talking about your sense so much.
Why aren't you super chatting me, Barry?
What's wrong with you?
You paid for dinner, so?
You lent me cash!
Ha ha!
No, gold!
Nothing of use.
Why can't they sell dirt?
I can't even get the redstone.
I don't think I put any of the redstone.
Nope, I didn't put a single redstone away.
Oh my gosh, you guys.
Are we going to be able to work like this?
We're going to have no tools.
They're giving us barely any iron.
Okay.
at least we can get these just a minor step yeah just a
minor setback we'll make it back guys believe that's it by
oh believe it oh my god we don't even get the oh more iron
okay more iron okay we're gonna start cooking gonna start
cooking that iron up let's start Back on the menu, baby.
Of course it is.
You can make dirt out of oak saplings.
No way.
Oh!
I lost all my saplings, though.
Wait, what?
Since when?
I guess I've never needed to make so much dirt before.
When could you do that?
Since when?
Is that...
a mod it is that special i i is this is it for this one
block because oh my god oh my god oh my god we're back to 11
dirt maybe only in one block i think i lost all my torches
too
Infinite dirt.
Oh, I just wanted to close it up.
Monsters, don't worry, don't worry.
Did I lose all my coal?
Why was I holding on to everything?
What's wrong with me?
I didn't put a single thing in here.
Oh, well, here's some coal.
Okay.
Oh, torch.
There we go.
You are EP.
That is true.
I'm very EP.
Maybe the EP is ghost in the Wow, Wow West.
Alright, now while that works, sorry I am the latest stream.
No, I would apologize.
Giving the last presentation of my time as an undergrad!
Finally at my biomedical engineering degree.
Oh my god.
You're so smart.
Congratulations, Sissy McShaggy!
It's the funniest name.
Dr. Sissy McShaggy.
Congrats!
Biomed.
Why are you watching me?
You watch me to make yourself feel better, right?
You're just like, God, at least I'm not as dumb as her.
What a dumb.
rocks.
I get it.
I know.
Congrats, fellow STEM major.
Smart people, do not interact.
Do not watch me.
Do not pay attention to me.
I don't want your judgment.
They're like, did you see that?
She couldn't even spell cauldron.
She tried getting the dirt.
the void what a bozo I've been watching for years it's too
late thank god I'm an idiot idiots rise up
stem majors can't spell either maybe I am a genius I do have
a genius emote guess I should leave then no no you're right
at home you're at home hello fellow dummies fellow my fellow
idiots we gather here today and joyous and joyous
celebratory extravaganza as we grieve our our fellow
smarties for they are too smart and therefore must be
executed.
Time to drain my brain cells for my Oshi.
Yeah!
Get stupid!
You should be a little stupid around your Oshi though,
right?
It's kind of like when you're around your crush.
You gotta be a little stupid around your Oshi.
Okay.
Mint does make me stupider.
Then I'm doing my job.
You should lose some brain cells, you know.
But I'm stupid already.
Then it's working.
Don't worry, Mint.
I've been working in STEM as a testing engineer for a few
years now.
There's plenty of idiots here.
Sounds personal.
Sounds like...
How many...
How far are we out?
Let's see.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17,
18, 19, 20.
Why did he have to appear right there at that time, at that
moment?
Oh my god.
scared the oh my god scared me so bad we can order a cow
though we can order a cow soon i think we just gotta get
more gold and we gotta be able to mine it where was i i lost
cow okay one two three four five six seven eight nine ten
eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen
22, 23, 24!
25!
You can make infinite dirt but you'll lose gravel.
Just make coarse dirt and you can get two more dirt by
breaking it.
I know too much about Minecraft.
Or I can turn these.
Look, it's our jungle tree!
I can turn these into dirt.
I was hoping for another jump scare what are you a sadist I
thought most people that watched were masochists wait okay
are you a sadist or a masochist which which are you
why not both
I'm a normal person.
Both, really?
Pull time.
For my Oshi, I can M.
That's so real.
It's probably the realest thing.
Pumpkins!
It's probably the realest thing you've ever said.
Put this pumpkin away.
Hmm.
I work for a cyber security company and our business partner
was pretty stupid last Friday.
You're smarter than Cloud Strife.
Thank you, Devlin, for the ego boost.
Thank you.
Let's grab some more dirt.
More dirt.
Feels good.
Good.
Hmm.
Normally at M, but your suffering is very entertaining.
Oh, so it's only...
It's only when it's me.
No.
It's hurt Phantom.
What do you want?
What do you want from me?
Do you also like to see my suffering?
I like to see your suffering too.
I don't think we can be M or S with no brain cells.
True?
Where are the cows?
Moo if you're a cow.
Mom.
Genially, really, eternally grateful for your streams.
It's always a blessing to come home to him.
Thank you for being here.
I made love from the U.S.
What are you talking about?
You're too nice.
Thank you, though.
Thank you.
I don't even do anything.
Can I get coal from a wood?
Oh,
yeah.
This one.
What's the chat summary?
Oh, I think it's time.
I think we can actually make some.
Yeah.
Let's remake our stuff.
Iron pickaxe is most important.
Go away stone.
And our...
iron axe and our iron shovel everything stone be gone what
are we in the stone age there we go ah it's so swift happy
to be here for three months happy to have you for three
months thank you thank you thank you nice now we're starting
to get the good we're getting our stuff back everybody.
Minor setback, minor setback, but we're getting everything
back.
Nothing is spawned yet.
Do you think I need to go further away?
Here.
Actually, I'm going to build out a little over there.
Okay, like this.
Give them a little bit more.
Mean comment to balance out all the nice comments.
Well, what's the mean?
What's you saying?
Oh, You, uh...
You...
You have a crooked tooth!
You're talking about my thing!
Ah, ah, ah...
You see it?
Ah, ah...
Grab's tooth!
I have one thing.
You see it?
One block of Mintcraft.
Did anyone make that joke yet?
Glad you made a safe window.
Thanks, Road.
Cute thing.
Thank you.
I love deformed teeth.
I love teeth that are messed up.
It's my favorite thing.
Oh, sorry.
Very finally messaged me back.
I don't know if I can say it, though.
Oh, I'm lagging a little.
I don't think I can say it.
The special thing.
She was like, I was like, what's the special thing I did?
She's like, did I say something like that?
You were cute.
There's something else, but I can't say it.
What happened to the right fang?
I never had two fangs.
I always just had one fang.
Because my teeth grew weird.
And I died weird.
Guys, I love my one tooth.
I love my one messed up tooth.
Why are you weird?
Wow, weirdo.
Takes one to no one.
Oh, that sounds like a self-report.
The tooth is real.
Oh, Minecraft music.
Snaggle tooth.
Got him.
You guys, when did they start?
Little cow, cow, cow, cow.
Where are you?
You, you, you.
Little cow, cow, cow, cow.
Why won't you come home?
It's still not grass?
Oh.
Needs to be grass.
Can't just be dirt.
If I do this, will it happen faster?
Miss Mint Phantom, what's the pink thing?
Oh,
I can't use it.
Check the bio.
We're in the plains, baby.
I
got a pink thing
While I at MGSCon But not at MGSCon Just while I was there
You know I can spot Okay It's gonna spot You gotta just hold
I won't end stream until we get a cow Where is the cow It's
oh Step 7.
2,500.
Alright.
What do we get now?
Oh!
Where's the diamonds?
Why don't we get any diamonds?
We're getting deep sleep with no diamonds yet.
Emeralds.
Nice.
Was the pink thing one more brain cell for chat?
I need it more than you.
Oh, what can we buy?
Really enjoyed hearing your MGSCon stories.
So happy your brain rot is thriving more than ever!
Yeah!
Glad you're able to get home all right and good luck with
the upcoming con.
Thank you, Miss Consanity!
Thank you so much.
String!
What were we needed?
What were we trying to get string again for?
What were we trying to make?
We needed 12 string to make something.
What was it?
Oh, a bed!
I don't have so much iron though.
Should I waste it?
Do you think?
You think I should waste it?
Hmm.
We don't technically...
Diamond!
Oh my god!
Wait, what do you sell?
What do you buy?
dive in yeah keep growing keep growing keep growing huh I'm
gonna I'm gonna make more room for activities oh where's my
hole where's my hole where's my hole here I'll just make a
wooden one.
Your Metal Gear brain rot is contagious.
I know it is.
Oh, wait.
How do I get more seeds?
Mint's life depends on finding a floating cow.
The stakes have never been higher.
How do I make more seeds?
Oh, the crafting.
the slices okay let's let this grow let's let that grow and
then okay okay i only have this is as much iron as i have
thank you for your business oh let's see bed oh whoa one two
You guys, we don't have enough!
Wait.
There's some in the chest.
There is.
Oh, you're right.
Thank you.
Two.
One out of 11 diamonds to go.
Also, 10 out of a thousand.
A thousand.
What?
Curse.
Welcome to my bishop.
Thank you.
Bed.
Wait.
Oh.
Oh, oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, bed, bed, bed, bed.
The Paris Olympics is starting this Friday.
It is?
Good night.
I don't know the last time I watched the Olympics.
I kind of want to watch them go swimming, though, in that
nasty river.
I don't want to watch it happen.
And be like, ew.
I can't believe they're doing this for real.
They approve the eSports Olympics?
What's the eSports Olympics?
They should compete in Metal Gear.
No, there are people that are actually insane with Metal
Gear.
I know one of the guys.
His name is Apache.
And he can literally play the game.
blindfolded.
He can beat Metal Gear Solid 3 blindfolded.
I don't know how people can do that.
At MGSCon, he did a run where it was all invisible enemies.
And he was still able to know where they were.
Their entire life training to swim in poopy water.
I saw that was crazy.
It's so crazy!
How is that possible?
I just...
How do you know where they walk?
So crazy.
But the fact you can do a blindfolded two is just...
It's the whole thing.
Blows my mind.
People are...
Speed runners are so cool.
Get out of here!
Go, go, go, go, go, nasty, go.
I have got what I wanted from you.
I need nothing else.
I need no more from you.
Diamond!
2024 Olympic gold medal for balloons.
I want to play balloons because I want to play the maps.
I saw some people created a Minto map, so...
Minto my Oshi!
Bogi here back home after being stranded for a while.
No!
Got a new job, getting ready for my courses and still
watching my Oshi!
Thank you for sticking around.
The silliest, coolest ghost!
Thank you for sticking around too!
Good luck with your not being stranded.
anymore and more diamond this much diamond has never
happened to me before
I watched games done quick that's my Olympics the gaming
Olympics I love gaming Olympics who is that MGS streamer
player that would do MGS 3 runs in the monkey mask with the
torch I don't know I don't know.
Does anybody know?
Doki is not here to steal.
She's, why would she even?
I asked her, I want to, I asked her for, I was like, can I
get on your server?
I was like, I want to play on your server, Doki.
So maybe one day you'll randomly see me if you play on
there.
And I'd still like to make my own.
I haven't given up that, that idea.
I just, um...
I think for a lot of things, I might wait until after the
Patreon is over, because that takes up currently so much of
my mental bandwidth.
So, but eventually in the future.
Having it.
That server is a war and a half.
Wait, why?
What's going on in there?
All I saw was, like, some...
She sent me...
Like, it showed up in my timeline, too, but Doki was just
like...
Like, apparently we got married on the server.
Property values skyrocketing?
Well, I get exclusive property.
I get an exclusive spot.
Zy, no!
Thank you for the 50 gift.
Thank you so much.
It was a beautiful wedding.
Why wasn't I invited to my own wedding that apparently
happened?
How many people went to this wedding?
What were my vows even?
You were there, kind of.
She knows.
Doki is the one who sent it to me.
Doki was just like, look at this.
I was like, what's going on in your server?
Okay, let's see.
Oh my gosh, the grass is taking so long.
the spread the gooners gooning I recently became a big fan
thank you your videos help after a long day of work thank
you can't wait for work content Logan thank you so much
thank you it's like 70 people thank you for the raid thank
you so much I hope you had a good stream just realized oh
you got a put some stuff away.
We don't want to...
Wow, I have so much lapis.
We don't want another incident.
Murphy, thanks for the five gifters!
As the cult leader on the Doki SMP Tehepero.
Doki, thanks for the gifting.
Thank you.
Oh, Orca.
I would say never but also...
Yeah.
So that's what I'll say about that.
Please change immediately.
Alright, let's see.
Let's make our seeds...
We might...
I wonder if we'll have enough to...
enough diamond...
to...
Where is the guy?
to get a cow where is he oh what are you doing up there
a cow wait six six i think we have six you guys i think we
have six
wait should we wait okay you guys we could cheat mode and i
can end stream right now or we can wait for the grass
No, stay with us!
I'll see you tomorrow.
With all my exciting things that I have and have not.
I hope we'll see you on Doki's server, that'd be really fun.
Yeah, I'll ask her again about it.
Wait for grass.
I'm kind of tired though, you guys.
Okay, we'll wait for the grass a little bit longer.
What's tomorrow?
My anniversary.
I'll have been streaming for one whole year.
As of tomorrow.
I finally get to celebrate my one year anniversary.
I never got to celebrate it before I left all those years
ago.
One whole year.
Never got to celebrate it.
So, you know.
Better late than never.
Because I came back on the same day that I graduated.
Right?
And now...
So it's just like I picked up when I left off.
Kind of.
12 months total.
Non-consecutive.
Yeah, pretty much.
Yeah, it's kind of crazy.
Glad we can now.
Yeah, I know, right?
I do, I do, I'll make sure, I'll try to make it fun.
Even though, like I said, sorry, I wish I could offer you
guys more.
I wish anything was ready.
I wish, I wish I wasn't so slow and bad at stuff.
So I'm really sorry.
I feel...
Quite guilty about it.
I probably shouldn't have gone to the convention.
I should have.
I should have taken the time to get everything ready and
stuff.
Ooh, a more sand.
Wait, did I lose my sand before?
No, I still have the sand.
Wait, where do you go?
Oh, what the hell?
Get out of my bed, you freak!
Why are traitors laying in my bed?
Get out of my bed!
It's me.
Don't apologize.
I'm so keen.
What do you mean by that?
You had fun at the cons.
It was worth it.
Anti-negative thoughts, Beam.
Ah!
Get out of my bed!
Wait!
Oh my gosh.
We lost the cow!
All we want for you to do is do an anniversary is hang out
with you watch you sing funny ghost song well all my vods
are like privated right my old vods so if you haven't seen
those before um be prepared i guess be prepared it's gonna
be bad
i'm gonna see baby me too long long ago
If most of my friends weren't all taken up by NSFW...
Sometimes you guys
just...
Chat says the darndest things.
From the MC Wedding Camera Man, it's an honor to know you
heard about it.
kneel i saw it on twitter i did see it
um i'd send an aquasupa to tell you how proud i have to
watch you doing all these conventions and being the best
that you can be keep it up are you guys have i mean your
name is literally a kinky cadaver like you but seriously i
think we need to bring shame back a little bit I think we
need a little bit more shame in our lives
Let's see Let's cook this And let's make a new pickaxe
It's barely It's growing at a snail's pace You guys Absolute
snail's pace Shame Shame So says freak phantom
King shaming is my king King?
Lulu Kachoo!
Welcome to membership.
We appreciate all that you do.
Mint combo ghosty.
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
That was the flower girl at the moment.
There's a flower girl!
Yeah, let's try widening it a little bit.
Let's plump her up.
Oh, look!
It's spreading more.
yeah all right more more grass more grass more grass more
grass more grass more grass more grass does it grow at night
grass grows at night Tuesday welcome to membership thank you
touching grasses okay question no if someone touches grass
would you consider that normie behavior even if it's like
even if it's like yes right like if someone has a hobby and
it involves touching grass i believe that's normie behavior
moo not really what do you mean Do they do it voluntarily?
Yeah!
Also a library of fanfics.
I want to write one.
Oh my god, Tuesday!
Thank you for the 20 gifted!
Thank you so much!
What the heck?
Yay, we leveled up!
Like if someone's having a life equals normie, that's how I
feel.
What if it's like a weirdo hobby?
What's a weirdo hobby?
Because
like...
You can't shame me, I have no shame.
I ship Vulgan and Yandras.
Brave.
You're so brave for admitting that.
V-tubing?
No, like... Okay.
Like say your hobby...
Say your hobby is running, right?
Like you run.
But, like, you care really deeply about, like, stats and,
like, the nerdy side of things.
Does that still, but that's still considered a normie hobby,
right?
Taxidermy?
Poor mint is too far gone.
Still normie, just lame.
Aries, thank you for three months!
It's athletic, right?
Fitness equals normie.
I believe that, too.
Thank you guys for justifying me.
I feel so justified right now.
I can't stand hearing these bees and they're not doing
anything.
They're acting like they're so busy in there.
Like, leave.
Get out!
Asking the least normie chat.
I don't know.
I feel like...
Sometimes I'm like, why do, why the people that aren't as
deranged as me watch me?
You know, like, I feel like I appear or rather like...
You wouldn't...
You wouldn't understand.
Unless you're, like, on the level, right?
You're fun?
I like the chaos.
You just don't get the nuanced weird?
No, no, no.
Still North.
Athletic is Normie.
One year, Annie.
Oh my god.
She knows eight months.
Sent right now because can't watch tomorrow.
Thank you!
Thanks for...
Boom.
Thank you for still being around.
Dorky and cute.
Any hobby is a Normie hobby?
if you're casual enough.
You think so?
Sailor Moon!
Thanks for three vans.
Two!
Oh.
Thanks, Zahi.
You always brighten my day, Mint.
Woo!
Thank you!
Am I a powerful and passionate otaku?
I don't have the power to do the same.
You do!
What are you talking about?
Everybody has the power.
You have the power.
Just...
Just, just do it.
Just be into the, just like the things that you like a
normal amount.
Or sometimes an abnormal amount.
That's all.
Where is he again?
Oh my god, no wait.
Why does he keep spawning up there?
You can confidently say that you have made me more deranged
over the years.
Just want to celebrate with you.
Don't beat yourself up.
such are just bonuses.
What's more important is spending time with Binto.
No!
Guys, you're gonna make me cry.
Come here, sweet child.
What do you have to sell for me?
A donkey.
Guys, we can get a cat.
Bring me a cat.
Farm villagers.
orders.
Order a mob.
I just got back from my normie hobby, drinking a liter of
beer and guzzling glizzy and then passing out for two hours.
Can you moi moi kune my meal?
You already ate it!
The music is a paid actor.
The magic is gone!
Yeah, what kind of glizzy?
10 out of 10 hobby.
What a freak.
Gosh, I thought I was a freak.
Your hobby is glizzies?
I think it'd be kind of fun to learn how to do the...
Oh, whoops.
How to do the...
What's the word?
You know how, like, there's hot dog eating contest?
There was my grandmother's birthday, so I made her baked
Alaska.
What's a baked Alaska?
And torched the meringue right in front of her.
Very normy, but now I get to spend the rest of the night
with Mint.
What's your grandma?
What about your grandma?
Don't worry about being too slow.
We're not providing enough for us.
Every stream with you is a blast.
We're glad to be able to hang out with you.
Mint love.
Thank you.
Grandma's gone to bed.
Granny's getting scammed.
Ice cream cake, which you torch the top of.
Ah.
That sounds awesome.
Ice cream covered in whipped cream and then baked or
torched.
Look at you guys.
It's getting closer.
Soon.
Then we have some melon for food.
Did you guys ever believe that if you ate the seeds, it
would grow inside you?
Like a tree?
I'll be honest.
I...
purposefully ate.
Yes.
No, I was normal.
Every kid believes that.
But I think too much seed at an amount is poisonous.
Or was it a puppet?
Can't remember.
That's understandable, too.
Well, how about now?
If you eat a seed, will it grow inside you?
I think it might, well, maybe the stomach acids.
I think it could a little bit though.
I still believe that.
That's what I'm saying.
Just take an anacid and then eat the seed.
And it'll grow.
Probably.
It needs sunlight.
What?
But seeds are buried in the ground.
Why does it need sunlight?
My tummy is nice and warm.
They just need a warmth and love.
To be cared for.
acid no acid in your tummy believe you mean they don't take
like 50 tums or something just down the whole bottle eat the
seed wham bam thank you ma'am you got yourself a watermelon
you're a proud parent of a watermelon is that safe are you
gonna take advice are you gonna take life advice from a
ghost?
Are you gonna take life advice from someone who's dead who
died under mysterious circumstances?
Yes.
From a VTuber?
Would you listen to any advice from a VTuber?
Actually, there are some very smart VTubers out there.
I got the most useless mob, but I think it's kind of worth.
Actually, it's not useless.
It's a companionship thing.
I'm lonely.
Gotta get both sides.
She wants us to be ghosts.
I just said I was lonely.
Oh.
Whoopsie.
Who's...
Sionio!
Thank you for the vibe.
I believe that gum would stick all over my stomach.
But gum, that actually doesn't digest for like...
There's our cat.
Our cat.
Wait, they don't love us.
Our cat!
Could you give a moi-moi?
Hey, whoa, whoa, stay back from the...
Stay away from the edge of the world, cat.
Give a moi-moi-cuntier multivitamin.
Oh my gosh.
You are being healthy.
OYSIC NARE!
MAHE!
Kiu!
Flintstones.
Granddad.
What do you have?
Hamethist Shard.
We could buy this cow, I think.
Wait, do I have Do we have enough?
I think we can buy this cow!
Let's go fishing.
I need fish.
Kuntaks.
Gone fishing.
Nice.
Mool.
Oh,
come on.
Fishy business.
Please bless the sleep aid supplement as I try.
And fist fight the sleep paralysis demon.
Okay, I read that correctly.
But at first I did not...
At first I did not...
At first I did not read that correctly.
Let me get my...
My cat first.
Is that OK?
Oh, what are you doing, over there?
Pssps, pss, pss, pss.
Pss, pss.
Pss.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I have more.
Come here, cat.
Cat.
Whoa, whoa.
Oh, cat.
There we go.
Okay, come here, cat.
Come here, cat.
Get in my bed.
Get in my bed, cat.
Yeah, yeah.
Go that way.
Get in my bed.
Nice.
Yippee!
Don't push him off.
So we could buy a cat.
Wait, 22.
Oh, I don't know about you.
We might...
Okay, it might be a race at this point.
Okay, look at this.
I'm gonna... Okay, watch.
I'm gonna order it.
Okay?
Now it's a race between the grass and the man.
That's...
It's a race.
It's on.
It's on, baby.
Let's put some stuff away.
Okay.
Actually, let's get some bone meal.
Grass versus ass, exactly.
Oh my god, oh my gosh, I just realized it's so late.
Chill Minecraft evening.
Do I have any more iron in here?
Nope.
I'm starting to feel a little sick though.
Like a little woozy.
So that's why I'm gonna wrap it up soonish.
Meow.
Go sleep, ghosty.
I will.
Once we get a cow, I'm a ghost of my word.
I am a ghost of my word.
I said I will not end stream until we get a cow.
What's the series goal?
I want to defeat the Ender Dragon, but I also really want to
see...
I don't know if I'll be doing this weekly or anything like
that.
But I also want to see...
Whatever the hell this thing, what was it?
Where'd it go?
Wait, what is this?
Oh, Wolf Armor!
Wait, I need an Armadillo!
There's so much stuff that they've added to this game.
I'm
gonna get rid of him Why are you what is what is what is
what are you What are you being refreshed upon It's creeping
me out Leave Please leave Okay
They added cows Wait Weren't cows always
He went night night Yeah Yeah Yeah He was refreshing himself
at the composter.
That's disgusting!
That's nasty!
Oh my god, it reeks!
What did he do?
He composted!
Oh my god.
Disgusting.
He added soil to the thing.
Oh!
That's so awful!
Right in front of me!
You sleep a block away.
put i don't put i don't put piss and shit in there i put
little moss it's different that's not my toilet
there's a whole void
moss has bugs in it so
it still rots look if we're gonna get into the very
specifics of minecraft i've murdered several people it's a
doggy dog world out there okay and sometimes you know you
have to live next to your toilet
he's trying to help you with composting look at all these
diamonds Wow we have so many here I'm gonna start making
some of this copper maybe we can uh what can I make with
copper you could put the bed anywhere else You guys are so
judgmental.
You guys are so judgmental.
What if I like it?
Oh, wait.
Leave the bud.
Hold on.
I want my cat to sleep with me.
Come here.
Come here, cat.
Oh my god.
The purrs of a cat are like the best thing ever invented.
The best thing ever invented is making a cat purr.
I didn't know it would do it did that I know it's so cute
it's so cute oh did you bring me some cocoa beans my cat
brought me cocoa beans nature's ASMR it's true it's true
How?
Don't ask, how?
Rude?
Are you sure those are beans?
Toe beans.
Bed right next to a tree might not be the best plan.
Might wake up to a rate of spiders.
Oh, yeah, let me get rid of my gone fishing, sorry.
Toe beans.
I love Paz's toe beans because since she's a tortie since
she's got like she's not completely black one of her one of
her toe beans is pink like her one paw and then the other
paw her toe beans are black.
So it's really cute.
It's so cute.
She's so cute.
He's such a bad cat.
Forties are very cute.
Huh.
We're really digging through this.
We're almost at 3,500.
Oh!
Is he on top of my cow?
Oh, he's in my...
Well, guys...
Moo!
We did it!
We got a cow.
Where are you going, cow?
Cow, cow, cow, cow, cow.
Cow, cow.
How did you get up there?
No, no, no, no.
Go back inside.
Go through.
Okay.
I'm going to go.
I'm going to put him.
I'm going to lock him up in here.
We're going to lock him up.
Perfect.
There we go.
He has enough room.
Probably.
And then also, we can drink his milk.
Oh, I lost my bucket.
I lost my buckets when I died!
Oops.
Yes?
What?
Excuse me?
You're so close?
We could order a wolf.
Male cows don't have milk.
We can drink her milk.
How do they...
How do they mate them?
Hold on, let's make another bucket.
Oh.
Milky Way?
Delicious.
Why is my cat on the ground?
Why is my cat...
What did you do?
Why are you on the ground?
Get on the bed.
Get on the bed right now.
Yeah.
There we go.
Freak Phantom drinking his milk.
You wouldn't?
You wouldn't tell me you wouldn't.
You're telling me you would not drink the milk of this
precious cow that was delivered from the heavens.
Anyways, guys, thank you for tonight.
I'm so sleepy tired.
I've got to go to bed now, and I suggest you all do the
same.
Oh my gosh, it's been four hours.
Holy cow.
Yeah.
I'm gonna head out.
I'll see you guys later.
Thank you for um, for watching, hanging out with me,
welcoming me back home.
Sorry if I was a little low energy.
Just because, you know, it was it's me being tired.
I've been up for so long.
But I'm going to get some good sleep.
Why don't you eat the puffer fish?
Oh, okay.
Did I lose the puffer?
No.
Whoa.
Oh.
That was crazy.
Oh, I think I'm about to die, though.
Let's eat some watermelon.
Oh.
Oh no!
Uh...
Guru Guru.
This is how I die.
A sad Victorian child.
Getting the black plague.
You discovered it.
You discovered my lore.
And now...
I have no other reason to be here.
you discovered how I died I am truly satisfied I'm seeing
the light I can finally rest in peace now I can know I will
no longer be a sad Victorian child who died of syphilis
plague
everything Goodbye, everybody.
Goodbye.
Oh, sorry.
Oh, wait, hold on.
One second.
Um.
What
was I doing?
Oh, okay, there we go.
Okay.
Um.
Now go.
Go into the light.
To the love!
There you go.
Come on.
That's all right.
There you go.
Downside's all right.
It burns.
Go outside.
Touch your eyes.
Be a normie.
Feel.
Don't be normal.
Oh, hold on, I also hold on to you.
Hold on, hold on to you.
Hold on.
Oh, oh wait.
Yeah.
It's me.
You're probably wondering what I'm doing here to get one
nice look.