I'm Fred No-Ben.
Invisible Ben.
Freaky Ghost Ben!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Welcome.
Do you see what is next to me?
Do you perceive... this?
It's quite quiet right now because it's in like this... I call it trailer mode.
I don't know if it has another... whatever.
It's my Apache slot!
Yippee!
Oh my gosh.
My stuff is kind of all over the place.
So attract mode.
Demo mode!
Sounds like the most sense.
But I kind of like attract mode.
Attract mode is... wait, that's real?
Attract mode is an actual phrase?
I've never heard that before.
It's just like...
Oh my gosh, thank you!
It's like a... how to say?
It's like a... she gives you a little like...
She splashes a little ankle like...
Mmm, don't you wanna try...
My...
Where's...
Mmm, mmm, mmm...
Ooh la la, baby!
Actually, this is really strange because...
Because I don't think before I ever did a hand cam.
Because, you know, for me it's a little difficult as a ghost.
But I got some special gloves.
Thank you!
I know almost nothing about the Apache slot other than the cutscenes and it playing at a convention once.
This is a whole new and unique experience.
I know!
I'm so excited!
Paid actor?
No, no.
I got some ghost gloves.
Because usually if you see...
Like if I'm trying to show you my hands on stream, you won't be able to see, you know?
Because I'm a ghost.
Like it's see-through.
But I got these like special ghost gloves that kind of hold my ectoplasm in.
So, we'll be a-okay, baby!
Yippee!
Also, I will need to test some audio stuff with you guys.
I want your opinions.
Because there are three...
Thank you for the donation, Zaku!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Pachinko.
There are three sound options that we can get for you guys hearing the machine itself.
Oh my god.
Oh my gosh, I'm so nervous!
Thank you!
Thank you guys for the donation so much.
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
That machine looks so cool.
It's very cool.
Honestly!
If anything, it just looks amazing, right?
Like it's just so well...
And so, so well.
It's so well.
It's so pretty.
It's so good.
It's not good.
It's just...
Even without playing it, this thing's rad.
I know, right?
Like the details on it are kind of insane.
Also, it's really cool because...
Let me show you.
Like this...
Hold on.
I'm waiting for it to light back up.
I'm sorry about the lighting.
Um...
I...
It will get better.
I wanted to make sure you could see.
Uh...
The...
Of course, the...
Um...
The slots themselves.
Uh...
It was a little tricky.
I had to go through a couple different cameras.
Um...
I tried to see if there was a way to output the screen itself.
But also, then you wouldn't be able to see the slots.
So, we kind of had to have it in camera mode like this.
I currently...
I got my...
Um...
Stop talking about my hand!
I...
Um...
What was I saying?
Oh my gosh.
You guys made me forget.
Um...
Uh...
What was I saying?
Oh!
I...
I got my GoPro.
Actually, to work as like a webcam.
And it has the best kind of...
Oh my gosh.
Ah!
It's so good.
Oh my gosh.
I screamed.
Don't scream!
Boo!
Thank you!
Almost too spooky to handle.
Real...
Real ghost activity.
This is actually...
I tricked you guys.
This is a real phasmophobia stream.
Oh my gosh.
Um...
But yeah.
So, sorry that it is like a camera like this.
I wish that I could output...
Maybe in the future I can find a way to do it.
If I become so technically illiterate.
Um...
But...
Again...
Of course, we're wanting to see the slots themselves too.
Also...
Um...
Just...
I don't know if I can...
If there's anything like legally...
Yeah.
Like...
You know...
Obviously, this is a gambling machine.
But...
I will not be paying any money as I have this nifty button right here.
Yeah.
That...
Oh!
Oh gosh.
It started.
Uh...
That if I press it...
It inputs...
It inputs credits for me.
So...
I'm also sorry.
There is a slight flicker.
I know I'm apologizing like so much.
But...
You know...
I...
I really...
I did my best to like put up...
Put the optimal set up for your enjoyment.
Also, look at this!
Bla-la-la-la-la...
Bla-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la.
This is one big screen.
Isn't that crazy?
It's one huge screen.
It's so awesome.
Yeah!
Um...
I will be picking up the camera and kind of like zooming in.
Oh!
You can see him!
Just a little bit!
This is what it looks like.
My perspective is a little cropped Also, for people who are just like, this is pachinko.
No, this is patchy slot.
Because it's not pachinko, it won't be like...
You know what I mean?
It won't be all the little balls falling and being noisy and annoying.
No, it's actually quite quiet, which is...
I mean, you probably can barely hear it right now.
Which brings me to my next thing.
Thank you!
I can't believe we kidnapped a cute girl to represent you, Mint.
No, I swear!
This is a ghostly hand.
Just with ectoplasm gloves on.
Or ectoplasm...
What's the word?
And hands.
Kabuki-cho pachinko ASMR.
No, thank you.
Okay, so...
We have three options.
For your listening pleasure.
One!
Is just like how it is now.
Right now, there's like no music.
I will... let's see.
Let's add some cash money up in here.
You can probably barely hear it.
Barely, barely, barely hear it.
I'm just gonna put in a ton.
Yeah, simp!
Okay, we maxed that out.
So, I'll also give you kind of a rundown of a little bit of the stuff.
One thing you can't see is right here.
My hand, hello.
On the side here.
This is kind of hard to see because I have my lights out.
So you can see the screen better.
But this is like a walkie-talkie kind of thing.
And then on the side, there's like a light up exclamation point.
It's so cute.
Anyway, okay.
Yeah, you can hear it.
Okay, so this is a little button to control a menu.
The menu kind of changes...
How to say?
The...
It changes...
It changes one.
You can change...
There's some points where they'll like say like, push button one, push button two, push button three.
And someone will be like, middle, right, left.
And you can change the voice.
You can change it to like Snake or The Boss or Siggint.
Oh my gosh.
Thank you for the Akadono.
Arigato.
Arigato-chu.
Thank you.
You're the reason why I'm getting into Metal Gear now.
So I'm really excited.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
But there's also...
You can change the mode.
So there's like advanced mode, normal mode, and classic mode.
I honestly...
I have no idea the difference.
They are all difficult.
I have no idea.
Of course, we have our little lever here.
We have the payout button right here.
And of course, our...
Our clicky-clacky buttons.
So let's try.
All right.
Oh my god.
Wow.
Great start.
Oh my gosh.
Doesn't it just look so good though?
Oh my god.
Snake looks so awesome.
Okay.
I'm going to keep going until something...
Oh.
Okay.
We got spotted kind of.
So this is...
This is a good point to test the audio, I'd say.
Because you can hear.
Also, I can't let this run for too long.
But I'll let it run for too long just right now because something kind of cool happens.
If you let the slots keep going, keep going.
But this is a good point to test the audio.
So.
This is the first audio.
It's really mostly...
It's just my regular mic.
But I do have another mic set up over here.
So you can hear.
You can hear the game a little bit better.
But if I play my mic and this mic at the same time, obviously there's going to be an echo in my voice.
We can't hear the audio.
I know.
It's not on right now.
Thank you.
But if I have only this mic on, it kind of sounds like an Xbox mic.
So I'm going to turn on this mic now.
So you can hear.
How is that?
It's pretty good.
Probably you can hear my voice twice.
But if it doesn't bother you guys, we can keep it.
Because obviously I want you guys to hear my voice.
It's loud.
I'm so sorry.
It's kind of spooky.
And then if I turn off my mic and I only have...
It's still loud?
Sorry.
If I only have this mic on, I sound like I'm playing Xbox Call of Duty.
So which one would you guys prefer?
I'm going to put up a poll, actually.
That'll help me the most, I think.
So, poll.
Which mic?
Which?
Mint only?
Mint and Pachinko?
Xbox mic.
The way I actually...
It's kind of funny.
It's kind of funny how...
This is actually the webcam mic.
I intended on having like...
See?
Ah!
The sorrow comes and he's just like...
He says, stop the reel.
Stop us from spinning.
It's so spooky.
I love it.
But...
This is actually a webcam.
I intended on having like a webcam kind of like giving a more close up image.
But in the end, my webcam was kind of shit.
So it just didn't do a good quality.
So I'm really sorry.
But this is the best I could do.
And what I had.
Yeah.
That was cool.
Right?
It's so cool.
Okay.
So we managed to escape.
Now, you are going to see all of this a lot.
This cut...
These cut scenes you are going to see so many times.
And I bet you are...
I bet you were going to see a bunny.
Oh, never mind.
Oh, the tree was in the way.
Wow.
I was wrong.
I saw a bunny so many times.
Okay.
We're walking down.
This is what I mean that not a lot happens in this game.
Also, I see...
I see that the result is mint and pachinko.
Double.
Okay.
So we're going to keep it like this.
I'm so sorry if it's distracting for some of you guys.
But...
Yeah.
We're going to keep it like this.
Dang.
Lost the shot.
Yeah.
The tree was in the way is what he said.
The tree was in the way.
So we're going to bet.
We're going to do this.
We're walking down the pathway.
A whole lot of nothing is going on.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, my gosh.
What is it?
What could it be?
It's going to be...
I don't know.
A chance.
Yeah.
It's a chance.
Oh, my gosh.
He gave me a chance.
You guys.
Oh.
We upgraded to blue.
I have no idea what that means.
Our loot box in Metal Gear.
Can you imagine?
It may be this.
Oh.
Pasha.
Oh, dang.
Of course, the one time...
Look at that.
It's going to be...
Isn't it so cool?
Gosh.
It's...
Oh.
Okay.
Place your bets, everyone.
What do you think we're going to get?
I think we're going to get a fork.
What do you think you're going to get?
What do you think?
The screen broke.
I know.
It's so cool, right?
A cigar?
A ration?
I think we're going to get a fork.
But if we get a ration, that would be pretty awesome.
I'll...
Okay.
Out of all the times I've played this, I've only...
I'll give you guys a clue.
I've only gotten a fork and a ration.
I've never gotten a ration before.
I have never gotten a cigar or an ammunition box or a key or the mystery ever.
So, streamer luck.
Come on.
Streamer luck.
We got a fork.
That's okay.
Next time.
Sokolove.
He's going to say...
What?
Oh, my God.
I'm breaking all expectations today.
It's a fork.
Let's go, baby.
Oh.
We upgraded to gold.
I have no idea what that means.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Are we going to...
Oh, wait.
Now we will see the bunny.
I think.
What?
Oh, my God.
What is going on?
No way.
Oh, my God.
Oh, oh.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Did you see that glitch?
Thank you for the doughnut!
Based on lore, would this ghastly form be akin to venish...
Venish?
Ven...
Oh, the ven...
Venum punish steak or big boss.
So, I'm absolutely jealous you got your hands on such a legendary trophy.
I know some people...
Good.
What does that mean?
I know some people have wondered how much this cost me.
We can continue!
Oh my gosh, you guys, we can continue to the next area.
Now, these parts are so cute because like... okay, you'll see.
Here we go.
The progress!
Camouflage is a mystery.
Oh my gosh.
Mic peaking?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Okay, I'm gonna turn it down just a little bit more.
I'm so sorry.
This is still experimental.
I was trying.
Okay.
Oh!
Wait, so we're trying to get Sokolov.
This is the Sokolov.
Okay, next.
Good, good.
The music is so cute.
And... continue!
Next!
Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice.
Okay, okay.
Wait.
Why are we...
Why are we suddenly inside the building?
Okay.
Last game!
Oh my gosh.
What?
It's on fire!
I'll be honest.
I've never seen this.
Get him!
Get him, Aslan!
We're getting back to our mission!
Yeah!
Oh my gosh.
No way!
First try!
We're getting back to our mission already?
Oh my god.
Maybe.
Sokolov won't refuse to stay with you.
Okay.
Let's go save Sokolov.
I guess.
Sokolov, real!
Okay.
I don't think you can choose a guy.
I think it just kind of...
We're just gonna attack him.
Alright.
Okay.
Come on, Snake.
Take his butt down!
Great!
So cute!
I love Tiny Paramedic.
She's so precious.
Okay.
So...
If we do all of this well, if we complete this Virtuous Mission well, we'll get the actual, like, cutscenes of the game.
Which is what I really want to show you guys.
Thank you for the dada!
Thank you!
Okay.
Took that guy down.
Easy peasy.
Great!
Come on!
Oh my god!
He's got the knife!
Okay.
Hold on.
Let's try again.
The timing...
was not right.
Yes!
Okay.
Mic desynced.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I'm doing my best, you guys.
Okay.
Here we go.
Take
his butt down!
Getting better at gambling.
Good.
Okay.
We at least made it.
Yosh!
There is a button here?
I'm not quite sure what it's for.
It does say push, but I don't know ever when to push it.
Oh no!
So loud!
Chuuu!
Thank you!
Even Mint is surprised by the patchy slot going off script.
There's a lot.
Oh, I have to add more friends.
We've already spent...
It goes up to 50 credits.
And we've already spent them.
Isn't that crazy?
I don't know actually how much...
I don't know actually how much it cost to play this.
If anyone has any better insight.
I always fail this, you guys.
I always fail this.
$20 per credit.
Does the pachinko machine come with some sort of developer mode that lets you automatically get alternate scenes?
If it does, I don't...
I don't know.
You guys, my luck is coming in real clutch here.
Look how cute he looks!
Okay...
Come on, Snake!
Don't miss!
Oh!
I told you guys.
I'm sorry.
I think...
Now we have to go back to the very beginning.
No?
Okay, yup.
We're back at the very beginning.
Your eyes jump!
Thank you!
There is...
So basically...
When I...
When I was setting up yesterday for this...
I did have to like...
I did have to kind of do some stuff because when I hadn't turned it off in the two months that I was gone...
Um...
Like there's like a thing with the RAM.
I had to like clear the RAM.
Um...
And like there's like a system key and then I press the reset button and turn the system key off and it was like this whole thing.
Oh, oh sorry.
I still have money!
Oh, it sucks that we went back to the beginning.
Um...
I want to hopefully...
There's two things I want to show.
First is a boss fight.
Whichever boss we can get.
And second is the um...
If we can get big boss mode.
Um...
Actually, I do want to show...
There we go.
I do want to show the menu too if I have a chance.
Oh!
No, no, no.
We'll take this guy down.
Ooh!
Nice!
Your soup.
The sheer amount of effort you went through to stream this is so funny.
What do you mean?
I paid for Streamlabs Pro to make you look at my Oshis.
Stop!
Wait, I missed it!
I'm sorry!
Snake!
Bajamin!
Oh, here we go.
So this is the menu that I was talking about earlier.
Um...
So this is like the kind of mode.
There's classic, normal, advanced.
We're just on normal.
Yeah...
Oh!
No!
Okay.
Just kidding.
I can't show you the other things now.
I can't show you the other...
Oh!
Here we go.
Okay.
This is the um...
Sinabi Custom.
The Navigator.
You can have Major Zero.
You can have...
Oh!
I thought there was Sigand.
But I think I remembered Sigand just because he's here.
You can't actually have him talking for you.
Obviously Snake, Ocelot, and the boss.
I think I had it set to the boss.
But who do you guys want?
I don't think we've heard...
We haven't heard them doing the...
Yeah.
But which one do you guys want?
Ocelot?
I saw Ocelot the most, I think.
You sound so goofy.
This is...
The game just looks so beautiful.
Also, little Snake down here will sometimes be dressed up different.
Sometimes he'll have his shirt off.
Sometimes...
Sometimes he'll be wearing a beret.
And the tree was in the background.
We're Snow!
I don't know what this is.
I have no idea.
I don't know at all.
I think it helps when you go into like the Virtuous Mission and stuff.
Hi, Paramedic!
Oh my gosh!
Oh!
The lighting!
Oh, that was kind of crazy!
Um...
This is... This is...
I think for...
Here, I'm gonna make a pin real quick about, uh...
Hold on.
About my mic situation.
There is double mic.
So...
Um...
You can hear the game better without me sounding like I'm on an Xbox.
Is it peaking so much though?
Um...
Yeah, I mentioned that we voted for it.
I will...
I voted it was the best option.
Sorry!
If it's weird.
LMAO!
It's not peaking that much.
Okay.
Pin message.
Just close echo.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm so sorry about it.
I... I was... That's... I was very like... I was very much like, I don't know which option to choose.
Like...
I want you guys to be able to hear me better, but also hear the game so clearly as well too.
Okay.
These guys are...
do something.
Sorry!
Sorry, Soru!
I'm... I'm gonna stop it!
Hold on!
Oh.
They're so stupid.
We're just crouched behind a tree.
These guys are idiots.
Oh!
It's glitching again.
Okay.
Interesting.
Oh.
Um...
Uros.
Oh!
Tiger tribe.
Okay.
Nice.
I wonder when we'll see the body.
...
I have been given the gift of prophecy.
Um...
Oh!
I was gonna say earlier.
I keep forgetting.
Um...
Wait.
Former slot mathematician here.
You should get more cutscenes if you bet max credits and max...
I don't know.
Oh, I do max bet every time.
And I... I'll just add all the credits.
Oh.
We're gonna shoot this guy.
We're gonna shoot this guy this time.
Or...
We're gonna throw...
Um... something to distract him.
Oh!
We shot him!
Oh my gosh!
Nice!
Streamer Luke.
Pew!
Oh.
Why does it every time that I try to make the noise it doesn't work?
Um...
Oh!
This is the one where he beats up the barrel!
...
Chance!
We got to see Vulcan!
Vulcan looks so good in this game.
It's crazy.
Um...
Sorry.
I keep getting distracted with what I want to say.
Um...
People might be wondering how much this cost me.
Usually...
I know we're at yellow.
I don't like to... you know...
I'm not trying to... I don't want to like...
brag.
I'm not trying to brag or anything!
Do we get to see Rykov?
Rykov is here, yes.
We do get to see him sometimes.
Um...
But...
It was about...
With shipping...
Um...
I can't remember exactly.
I think it was about like...
1400 US dollars.
So some people think like it's a correct...
I mean that is a lot of money.
Don't get me wrong.
But like it is not maybe what some people think.
And...
To be fair, like this thing...
I mean it's very nice.
So...
Um...
Oh!
Okay we get to progress you guys!
I don't know why!
I don't know why we're progressing but something happened!
The progress.
Camouflage is still a mystery.
That's okay.
Also I love down here like the...
It's like the title screen.
It just looks so cool.
Okay we're in a different place this time.
Cheaper than my PC.
Yeah!
Like it is like...
You know...
Less expensive than some gaming PCs so...
Okay?
Doing so well?
Sorry.
I get so used to just like...
So I gotta build up a little suspense really.
Okay.
What?
I didn't even finish!
No way!
I didn't even get...
I didn't even...
The game is rigged!
Uh oh.
Are we in warning or...
You can get caught by the way.
And then there's like a...
Up here there will be like the...
Countdown and everything.
Pasha!
Every time!
Back to blue.
See I told you guys we would be seeing this cutscene a whole lot.
Oh!
Oh my gosh!
Is there something inside?
Please don't get crushed!
Please!
Oh my god!
It's my destiny!
We in the boss!
Oh come on.
I don't know.
Pasha!
Oh!
Shit!
Uh oh.
We stepped on a stick.
Oh we are so suspicious.
Who is it?
Oh my gosh.
It's okay.
Everybody...
Calm down.
Woohoo!
I like how we are like non-lethal mode the whole time.
Never thought I would watch slots.
I like how he calls them annoying guys.
It's just like...
He's burning the papers.
Oh my gosh.
What is this?
We are green now.
We are green.
I don't know what that means.
They are annoying.
Yeah.
They are extremely annoying.
Segen!
We are red now!
I don't know what that means.
Oh!
Oh come on.
Come on.
Come on!
Loot boxes...
hate me.
Oh.
Sokolov is still burning those papers.
What is this?
If none of this makes sense to you guys, it doesn't make sense to me either.
I have no idea how this works.
I have tried looking up like...
if you get this combination, if you get this combination, but like...
I don't know.
Triple blue seems common.
Yeah.
What is this?
Who is this?
Hmm?
What is this?
Paramedic.
She is looking at her body again.
You know?
They don't make walkthroughs for slot machines.
This is the...
This is the walkthrough for anyone else who owns a Metal Gear Solid patchy slot machine.
We are seeing these guys quite often now.
Haha.
Just keep putting in credits.
Okay.
What do you guys think we are going to get this time?
Two!
Thank you!
Gotta feed the patchy slot.
Wait.
Okay.
What should you guys think we are going to get?
Fork?
Key?
Key!
Oh!
We got a ration!
Good to you guys.
Oh!
Another chance at the loot box.
Please.
I hate this.
Just a box.
It's literally just a box.
Is the tree in the way?
Oh!
Ten!
Alright guys.
Come on.
Thirty percent camouflage.
Oof.
That's okay though.
That's okay.
Come on.
I just want to show you guys the box battle and how unfair it is.
It is so unfair.
It's absolutely...
Ah!
Oh my god.
He got on his knees for us.
Bring him to his knees.
Snake.
What does Haten mean?
Haten means progress.
We can continue forward.
Development.
I truly don't understand.
Why?
Okay.
Oh!
Yeah!
Virtuous Vision!
Okay.
Cool.
I really want us to get to the actual...
Because when you get to the real Virtuous Mission, you can...
You can see him doing the...
He doesn't do the flips in this.
Which is actually a sin.
But!
How far have you gotten?
It's hard to say.
Because sometimes when I do this, I'll...
I'll get to...
I'll get to a boss fight and it will be Ocelot.
And sometimes I'll get to a boss fight and it will be...
The Fear or something.
I've never seen the Fury and I've never seen the End.
So if we get to either of them...
Lucky day!
You would think that...
I love this 7.
It's so awesome looking.
You can kind of see it a little bit better.
It's got like big boss art.
It's really cool.
Here's... ooh.
Yes.
Virtuous mission.
Oh wow!
There's playing cutscenes in the back!
I just realized.
Oh my gosh!
I never noticed that!
Are those cutscenes from...
Those don't look like...
They're remade.
Those look like...
Yeah!
That's from the actual game!
What!
That's cool!
Okay.
Sorry.
Hold on.
Oh.
The colors are so pretty.
Okay.
We're good.
I think.
Okay.
I have money!
Don't kick me out!
Good!
Oh!
Can you hear us a lot?
I don't know if it makes a difference.
You can do it out of order too.
But I don't know if it makes a difference to make it like a better chance if you do it in order.
Good!
Okay.
It's not great, but we're getting good.
Not gonna lie, having my arm out like...
having my arms out floaty, but like having my arm like this is kind of a workout.
Okay.
All right.
Come on.
Take him out.
Nevermind.
Take him out with a great Tony the Tiger!
He's...
Ah!
All right.
This is... Okay.
Chance two!
All right.
Let's try and get stealth maybe.
Oh!
Three in a row.
Okay.
Come on.
Tony the Tiger buff.
No!
We're back at the beginning!
Oh!
Can you see?
Wait.
You can't see.
He's got his shirt off.
I don't know why he's naked now.
He's a naked little man.
That's creepy.
Because he's a naked snake.
No, that's solid snake.
I'm surprised we haven't... I haven't had the...
Max... Maybe I should keep...
It won't let me max bet, so...
Yeah, I'm eating.
Oh.
I love how she calls.
She's like, hey, you eating?
No, that is not solid snake.
Oh.
All right, guys.
We got a ration last time.
What do you think we're gonna get this time?
Also, it's not...
It's not like whenever I stop it.
If I can be, like, here, and I stop it, and it'll still go to fork.
So, here I'll...
Here I'll try, like, on ammunition.
Oh!
So, it's a skill issue.
No!
Okay, that was... Oh, it's glitching again.
That is... That's awesome.
That's not...
Something happening.
Or not something wrong with the screen.
It's part of the game.
Is it okay?
Can you even call this a game?
You were saying.
Okay.
Shh.
Hush.
Oh!
Pshaw!
Yeah!
Okay.
I got one, at least.
Oh!
Is it just a box?
This is a game?
You think so?
It's a pay-to-win game.
True.
Nothing.
No.
That is... That is not a skill issue.
Yeah!
Oh!
Come on, baby.
We are Tiger Stripes.
Okay.
Come on.
Come on!
Just a box!
Box!
Oh!
Chance?
Chance.
Oh!
Mister!
What could it be?
Oh!
They are looking around for me.
Trying to find me.
We are back to Sokolov.
It's just a fever dream of scenes.
Everything is all over the...
We are back in the woods.
What is going on?
Why did Vulcan come out?
We have no idea.
He is doing his little thing.
What is this?
I just don't understand.
It's all over the place.
It actually is.
Usually it doesn't take this long to get to like a boss or something.
I think my luck is actually just bad today.
Oh!
Okay.
We are throwing the...
What is that?
Magazine?
Okay.
Still just a box.
Someday.
Oh!
Today.
Right now.
Right now!
Oh.
Never mind.
You are so... Just look the other way.
All you have to do is look the opposite direction and you would have seen...
Oh!
Danyda!
Thank you Ocelot for your direction.
Thank you.
Basically he is saying like...
I thought I saw him around here.
Like he was definitely somewhere around here.
No one here.
They are idiots.
180 IQ.
Not stopping this stream until she beats the boss.
This is the stream you guys.
Oh!
Sorry Ocelot!
I was not listening to you.
I was not even looking at the screen.
I was not paying attention at all.
I'm so sorry.
Okay.
Here we go.
Ocelot is gonna get us the mystery thing.
Because he loves snakes so much.
Right now!
Alright.
Ocelot.
Ocelot this... Whatever you...
Whatever you decide for us will be...
Will decide your true love.
Okay?
Oh!
Oh my god.
He knows...
He knows that snake loves to eat.
True love.
Oh my god.
He loves us for real.
You are a simp.
Ocelot.
Didn't think we'd actually see this thing in action.
PogChamp.
I know her.
Me too.
Oh!
What is this?
I don't...
Ocelot know... I don't know if like...
He starts giving us direction.
Like if the game feels bad for us.
We're not getting any wins.
So Ocelot is like...
Hey I'm coming to help you.
Her actions taste horrible though.
I think it's better than eating a dead rat in the forest.
I'm just saying.
An uncooked rat.
Hmm?
What is this?
Pity pole.
Okay.
See?
I was down here.
And it still went to fork.
Rigged.
Oh?
That is...
Space snake.
Oh my god.
Hahaha.
Oh no.
They're starting to multiply.
They're hanging out.
Oh gosh.
It's a party.
We were not invited.
Ocelot got the rations because snake is a snack.
So true.
A fork.
Do you think he'll see us behind the tree?
Will we be spotted?
I love that they're just like...
Yeah.
He's definitely here.
I definitely think I saw him.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's go, sir.
Snow.
They're just chilling.
Yeah.
You guys, my luck is kind of...
I'm okay.
He's like, how you doing?
I'm good.
How's your condition?
We're stabbing him.
Oh.
Thank you.
Oh my gosh.
Paramedics saved us from the jungle.
Finally, we can continue forward.
Hahaha.
Eventually, we get there.
You just have to spend enough money, obviously.
Finally.
The progress.
Mysterious camouflage.
Okay.
Team.
And there are different locations too.
It's not always...
This area.
So, I'm wondering if we'll see that as well.
Last game.
Okay.
Let me out.
Paramedic.
White girl, save me.
Hahaha.
Save me, white girl.
No.
Hahaha.
Alright.
I'm gonna press it on ration.
And we'll see what we get.
Oh, I pressed it on ammunition box.
But it still went to fork.
Okay.
Save me, white girl.
Hahaha.
Oh.
Okay.
Oh, there.
We got the same thing twice in a row?
That's kind of interesting.
Yeah.
This is...
This whole thing is Mendo.
Please get me out of the forest.
Please.
The jungles of Russia.
I'm so sick of it.
I don't want to see the jungles of Russia any longer.
Please.
You got forked.
At least we have enough forks to share the single ration with awesome.
Hahaha.
Oh, we took him out.
Alright.
Oh!
We
got bullets!
There's jungles in Russia?
Yes, according to Metal Gear Solid 3.
There are jungles in Russia.
Isn't that the most fascinating thing?
Oh!
It's Zero!
Oh, Zero.
Monday night.
Oh, she's responding.
Tiger strike.
Bullet.
Hahaha.
Okay, you guys.
Alright.
Okay.
Oh, this one's fun!
Because this is the one with the dogs!
So, uh...
If we make it out, we get to jump off the...
Okay, come on.
Alright.
Let's go!
Nice.
Next.
Nice!
The sound of the dogs is so sad though.
Bow-wow.
Hup!
Weep-weep-weep-weep!
Oh, my god.
Let's go!
Bow-wow.
Bow-wow!
Oh, my god.
Please.
Please, Sokolov.
Can't we just leave him?
We could just leave him, right?
We got the bow-bow virus.
Nope, not yet, not yet.
Good.
We need more bullets.
Hmm.
Oh wait, I forgot this was just the one to choose the guy.
Not yet.
Okay, I think you have to get it in the first try to get great, right?
Oh, nope, just kidding.
I proved myself wrong again.
One last... one last guy.
Okay, alright, here we go.
Alright, come on.
The audio fixed.
Oh, was it out of sync before?
That's so weird.
Is this better now?
Oh, I'm so sorry, I didn't realize.
I thought... I thought you meant like there was an echo in that like you could hear me twice.
I didn't realize that it was like a delayed echo.
It was double for me when I joined the... I'm so sorry.
Oh my gosh, it must have been really awful to listen to.
I'm so sorry.
That's so... yeah, I'm so sorry about that.
It must have been so annoying to listen to.
It's
been two times enjoying my...
Cha-da!
I was hoping that I could like channel my energy into that.
Look at Tiny Ocelot, he's just so goofy looking.
Oh!
Okay, okay.
Okay, come on, Snake.
Snake.
Snake!
Snake, don't miss!
Snake.
Snake, please.
Oh my god, please.
Please.
Please to god, Snake, we need to continue.
Please, Snake.
I'm begging you.
I'm on my knees, please.
Snake!
Snake, don't miss!
Don't miss!
Yes!
Also, you can't tell, but my credits have not gone down at all, which is very impressive.
12 hour stream, let's go.
It already has been an hour and we haven't barely seen any of the game.
You know what?
Actually...
Hold on.
I think... let me try changing the game mode.
Next time I have the option to go to the menu.
Let me... let me try changing the game mode.
Because maybe being on normal is kind of messing some stuff up.
Do you own this machine?
Hi, Hana!
Yeah, this is my... this is my patchy slot machine.
It's my baby.
Hold on.
It's got a light up, so we can go to it.
Thanks for the donut!
Double mint is fine, but this works too.
How much time have you spent playing this exactly?
Probably less than you'd imagine.
Like, I'll, like, every so often, like, you know, do it.
Or I usually turn it on when I, like, if I... I say when, but it's really if I have company over.
Because it's kind of like, you know, it's kind of like a...
What's the word?
Strange thing to have.
Oh, no!
The echo's back!
Is it better if I just do this?
Thank you, Zero!
Is it better if I just do that?
It's worse?
Wait, way better.
What's the echo?
You guys are so weird!
I think the echo's better than mine.
Okay.
I'll trust Hana's opinion.
Hold on, I'm paying out.
There we go.
Okay.
Classic mode.
Let's change it to classic.
And now we will retry.
We will retry.
Do you ever just get up in the middle of the night and just go one more spin?
It's a...
There are definitely times when I am playing on it that I'm just like, okay, I'll end on a win.
And as you can tell, that's not easy.
I don't even think there's a true way of beating this, you know?
Like, I don't even know if you can fight the boss.
Though I do know you can fight the four bosses.
Or the four, like, you can fight the fear, the fury, the end, and the pain.
Look at this.
We're just, we're hitting nothing.
It is...
Oh, the tree is in the way.
Oh my god.
Take him out.
Have you changed the difficulty inside?
Is there a way to do that?
I'll be honest, this thing hasn't really... it never came with an instruction manual.
It came with a piece of paper.
So I, uh...
Can you die in this?
You can do boss battles, and when you die, you just go back to this area.
It's like the beginning, you know?
But yeah.
I don't know, actually, how to, uh...
If there's a way to change the difficulty on the inside.
I don't know.
Load the last save.
Okay, guys.
I'm guessing key.
Key!
I'm gonna press it on ammunition.
Damn.
It's actually really easy.
It takes, like, less than a minute.
If you have both keys, I can tell you how...
I do have both keys!
I do!
This is the one to open.
And then this is the one for the...
For the... uh... what's it called?
Key.
What's it... um... hold on.
Something... something key.
I don't remember.
Though I don't wanna do it right now, obviously.
Because I would have to open this up.
And it's gonna disturb my setup.
But I would love to know how for the future.
Because...
Oh.
Nevermind.
Why would you tease me?
Oh!
Snow!
One day.
But I kind of like... I don't know.
Maybe I'm...
Oh!
Snow again!
Didn't we... I don't understand.
I don't...
I just... I don't understand.
The mechanics.
I don't get it at all.
I don't understand.
Why do we get snow and then we get snow again?
What is the point of the snow?
Why do I get camouflage?
But it doesn't do anything.
Why do I get camouflage and then when I go to...
When I go to... uh...
The Virtuous Mission?
My... my thing is at zero or question mark?
I don't get it!
It's so confusing!
Oh, I messed up.
What?
Hidden modifiers?
It has to be there, right?
Don't move.
Why did an extra weapon disappear?
Please.
Just something happened.
Snow!
Oh, my god!
It's just like Oops.
Animals!
Animals 70%!
We just got this!
We did it!
We got animals!
We got it!
Oh, what did it do?
Who knows?
The tree...
Push?
I've never had to push!
Wait!
We skipped!
What?
Oh my god.
It's never lit up like that before.
It's so dramatic, I know.
Why did it happen?
I have no idea.
What's going on?
Okay.
Come on.
All right, snake.
Get a...
Tony the tiger!
He's... great!
Yeah!
That's two for two.
That's two for two, baby!
Okay.
Works every time!
Works every time.
Lady, look.
Tiger!
He's...
Just wanted to let you know that I'm starting off my birthday watching you play Metal Gear Slot, and I can't imagine a better way to spend it.
Marika, happy birthday!
Oh my god, Asel!
Hello!
Long time no see.
Here we
go.
Now I want Frosted Flakes.
Um...
I... I have a distinct memory of, um, Frosted Flakes from, like...
You know how, uh...
Well, at, like, some...
Great!
At some, uh, like, hotels and stuff, um, in the United States...
Like, when... If they have breakfast...
Uh...
You can get, like, the little cereal boxes.
Um... Yeah, the mini boxes!
Yeah!
I never would, um...
I never... Uh, my mom never got Frosted Flakes.
Well, she really never got, um...
Like, any kind of, like, sugary cereals like that for me as a kid.
There was one cereal that she would get that, like, I very lovingly call, um...
Cardboard O's because they just had no flavor.
I think... I think those kind of messed me up for life.
Because my pa... my taste palette has been very directly influenced by Cardboard O's.
So...
Cheerios?
No, no, no!
They were, uh...
They were... They were Cheerios from, like, one of those health food stores.
Okay, come on.
Oh, gosh, you guys.
I'm not feeling...
I don't know.
I'm feeling nervous.
Oh, I'm sweating!
Snake, please!
Please.
Please, Snake.
Please, God.
I'm not gonna look.
Oh.
Ugh.
Choo!
Open machine.
Turn switch under small key off.
Put in small key and turn.
Turn on switch below key.
On back of door, look for red number with button behind small plastic sliding door.
Push button to change difficulty.
One through six.
One hard, easy six.
Continue.
Oh, my gosh.
It's so funny because I know exactly what you're talking about with the...
With, like, the buttons and the keys.
I'm like, oh, okay.
I know where those are.
Yes, yes.
You guys, this is so pathetic.
I know.
I finally... I finally can show you my patchy sla... I mean, final... I mean, oh.
I can show you Apache's... Apache's slot machine that...
I've had this for a while and I've... I've always wanted to show people.
And...
It's going crazy.
Sorry.
There's also supposed to be a volume control.
There is.
Actually, I haven't turned much down because it usually was very loud.
Anyway...
What was I saying?
But my game... My game is camera shy.
It's getting... What's the word?
You know when you do poorly when people are watching you?
What's that word?
Performance anxiety!
Yes.
Performance anxiety.
Stage fright.
Oh.
Bullets!
I mean, you love Metal Gear, so shouldn't you be thrilled for the excuse to just keep playing it indefinitely?
So true.
Godzilla!
Oh my gosh, these guys are so stupid.
No!
Come on, animals.
We're making out in the jungle with this one.
I don't... You guys, I don't think so.
Oh, oh!
Chance?
Wait.
There... Before in the background it said chance, but this time it didn't.
So maybe the chance is under the...
No?
It's a mis... I don't know.
What?
What just happened?
Oh?
What
is this?
Suddenly Grozny.
I know.
Oh, we get Sokolov again.
What is this?
This guy.
Two.
After choosing difficulty, go back to front and push knob down a few times until the red number turns to zero.
Then just turn small key back off and you're done.
Thank you.
Thank you, Dave.
I appreciate it.
We never met, but I'm happy to see you're back.
Thank you.
I hope you're here to stay.
I'm looking forward to seeing you more often.
Thank you so much.
Okay.
What do you think, guys?
What do you think?
Sokolov is very inquisitive.
Oh my god, yeah.
I... It drives me... Like, you're the one burning those papers.
What do you mean you don't know what's on it?
Fork?
Cigar?
This is like a... What's it called?
Family feud?
The board says cigar!
All on fork.
Well, minty fresh Kyle, it's your minty fresh day.
You better go play the lottery, buddy, because who would have thought we would get fork again?
Oh my god, paramedic is so cute.
Even when she's looking at my insides.
Don't look.
Don't look at my pelvis.
You'll see my sciatica.
Or not my sciatica.
You'll see my scoliosis.
Oh my god, it's paramedic.
She's like, I love that curve of your spine, snake.
Boo.
Boo!
Bullets!
It can't work every time.
Scoliosis in your pelvis?
No!
Ooh, I like the effect it has.
Ooh, that is so cool, right?
It's such a nice machine.
It just looks so good.
Unfortunately, mine is a little cracked up in the corner of the snake.
You can kind of see, like, the breakage a little bit.
Um, but if I were to want to get it fixed, I would have to send the entire thing back.
And they would have to replace this whole panel.
It would be, uh, it's more of a pain in the ass than I'm willing to deal with, so...
Tiger.
T-T-T-T-T-Tiger.
Are you planning to buy more machines?
No, I don't need more than one, unless I get, what, Metal Gear Arcade?
I don't know if I'm that crazy, though.
Here's another trick.
There's a hidden set of patterns on the snake that tell you when to push the buttons to get streaks.
But you can only see it if you equip the...
Stop lying to me!
Don't lie!
It's ugly.
It's ugly when you lie on the internet.
Hahaha.
Don't tell lies!
It makes you go bald!
Bald isn't ugly.
But if you like to have hair, then it would be kind of sad.
I'm just saying.
Oh no!
My hair!
Is the audio doubled or is it just the room?
Yeah, unfortunately there's like some strange audio issues I'm having.
What a scuff stream to have as my first actual stream back.
This is so... I'm so sorry.
What is this?
Bald likes Sokolov.
I think Sokolov's... I mean, yeah, he's a little bald.
I think Sokolov's bald!
Hahaha.
It's a perfect stream.
I'm loving it.
You guys are just saying that to make me feel better.
You're just like, we can't say bad things or else she'll ghost us.
Oh my god.
Curve of your spine.
Ooh, baby.
I don't know why it makes him look so old.
Oh, sorry, you can't really see it, I guess.
It gives him like these weird smile lines.
I guess they're on a skull, huh?
I don't know.
I'm a ghost, not a skele- I'm a ghost, not a skeleton.
Skeleton is old mint.
It would be really fun to...
Oh my gosh, what if we find my grave and we dig me up?
Oh my gosh.
You guys, what do you think I'm buried with?
It's kind of embarrassing.
Oh my gosh, what if you dig me up and you find my skeleton?
Oh my gosh, what if you grave rob me?
What if you open up my grave and I'm just gelatinous?
Decomposing.
I love hearing you have so much fun playing with the slot machine.
I'm eating Mike Tyson's butt!
Thank you!
Let's do it!
Very wormy.
Oh my gosh, we're never making it out of the Russian German Ghouls, you guys.
I'm afraid to say.
I changed the game mode, but I don't think it changed anything.
The legend.
Thank you guys for all the donations.
I really, really appreciate it.
The man, the myth, the legend.
For those who are wondering about memberships, I don't get a monetization until I post three videos.
So this is the second one.
And then it says I need more watch hours too.
So I guess maybe sometime next week we'll get it.
Hopefully.
Maybe.
I don't know.
I still don't know what to do for memberships.
Kind of, I think...
Oh, sorry.
I was thinking so much and I just ended up pressing buttons.
Levyman, thank you!
Thank you so much.
Because for memberships, I do plan on maybe doing some streams.
I'm going to put it at like a lower tier though because of the podcast and having the Patreon.
Because Matara and I will be doing like some extra streams and games and things on there.
So that's a little bit more of my priority.
So my memberships will be probably like tiered much less.
But yeah.
So I do obviously still plan to do stuff with memberships.
And then there will be the emotes if you guys want that.
So less than $5.
Less than $5 is what I'm thinking.
Yeah, like either $2 or $3.
So mm-mm.
Make them $44?
Are you crazy?
I thought you said four.
Four makes sense because obviously it's a spooky number.
But not 44.
But yeah.
Four, four, four.
Four, what a deal!
No.
Simple.
Will we get out of the jungle when Delta releases?
Yeah.
Maybe the game, maybe my patchy slot is feeling like a little insecure.
It's just like you're going to abandon me once Delta comes out.
You're not going to love this snake anymore.
You're going to love other snakes.
He's going to be even more high def.
He looks so good though.
Oh my gosh.
He looks so awesome.
He looks so good.
Everybody looks so good except Eva.
Sorry.
Eva in this, something about her just looks a little off.
Like her hair looks a little wiry.
Her face just looks a little off.
I don't know what it is.
I don't know.
Sorry, Eva.
Grave robbing membership stream.
If we dig you up and find your skeleton clutching a suppressed H&K MK23 in a bag of cursed sand.
What is this a reference to?
Eva, my wife.
I love Eva.
I think I'm very excited to see how she looks in Delta because how I and also Ocelot looks a little weird in this too.
So it's not just her.
The two of them look a little weird.
Like hold on.
Hold on.
Give me the menu.
I'm going to pay out.
Not that it matters.
We haven't done anything.
Okay.
Um.
Because you can see.
No.
Get me out of here.
Okay.
Never mind.
Um.
They have a picture of Ocelot which is why I wanted to bring up the menu.
He just looks a little goofy.
Welcome back.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Oh.
Hello.
It's okay.
Oh.
What is this?
How does the boss look?
She looks perfect.
Oh my god.
She looks...
Like her and Snake.
I feel like they had the most love put into them.
I mean the boss...
The other boss is looking too.
But...
Her and...
Oh.
Her and Snake looks stupidly good.
They look so perfect.
What is this?
Just so much.
I'm going to throw you into that for sure.
Fire.
If you don't say something else, please.
I think I'm turning into the Joker.
Oh my god, no, please!
Don't say it.
Don't you dare.
There's an Umineko patchy slot for 250 right now in Nara and you're making it really hard for me to not hit buy.
That's not a bad price at all.
I think with this patchy slot...
I can't... I have never played any other patchy slot games before.
Well, patchy slot is true.
I have tried like a pachinko machine at a convention before a long time ago and it was whatever.
I don't even remember like what anime series it was, if it even was one.
But I feel like a considerable amount of effort went into went into this one.
I don't know.
There's just a lot going on and obviously you have like the HD graphics, so it just feels like a lot of love.
Not love.
Maybe that's the wrong word.
A lot of something.
Effort.
Effort went into this.
Sorry, I'm trying to choose my words carefully.
Going, going, going.
That's what I'm trying to do.
Please, let me through.
Oh my god, finally.
Something has happened.
Oh my god.
Please.
Please, please.
Let me, let me go somewhere else.
The game pity me for once.
Oh my god, I'm so sorry.
I'm so tired.
Don't say it.
What is this?
He's gonna say it.
Snow!
Oh, this is like probably the worst round we've gotten so far.
If I get the chance, I'm gonna maybe change the game mode again.
Okay, guys.
What is this?
This is gonna become a meme on my channel.
Like everybody, something happened.
What is this?
Alright, everybody.
Place your bets.
Cigar.
I really want the cigar.
I don't think I know what he says when he gets the cigar.
When he gets the fork, he says like, I don't need this right now.
H&K MK23 is the SOCOM pistol from the game.
Are you sure you're a Metal Gear fan?
No, I knew that!
I didn't know what the bag of...
the bag of...
dirt or whatever they said was.
I didn't know.
What is this?
Alright, cigar!
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, he says I don't need it right now.
Ration, he says like, not bad.
Ammunition, I don't remember what he says because I haven't gotten it enough times.
And cigar and key, I have no idea.
And then obviously the secret.
I have no idea.
Forked!
Get forked again, nerd!
Tiger's draw.
You guys, I'm starting to lose hope.
I'm starting to lose hope, please.
Ammos, he says ocelot, my love.
Really?
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Another chance!
Chance, chance!
Forked.
Again.
I'm getting forked in the butt here, man.
Oh, oh, oh!
Okay, come on, come on, come on!
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on, come on!
Boo!
Mama!
Tiger's draw.
I think because it's like the worst result.
Okay.
What did that mean?
I don't know.
I don't know anything that goes on in this.
I literally just push buttons and I pray.
I pray something is going to happen.
Can I get the menu again, please?
Okay.
Paramedic, please.
Oh!
We haven't gotten this one.
Oh, no, we got caught!
Oh, no!
Paramedic!
It's going to go into caution after this, though.
Oh.
Bullets!
Nice, nice, nice.
Nice, nice.
Let's just go to the other side.
Nope.
Just a tree.
The tree is in the way now.
That's what I get for...
for cosplaying a tree.
He took offense.
Alright, get out of here.
Run away, you losers.
Oh my god, the music is so awesome.
Okay, now we're in caution.
What is this?
If it goes well, there's a chance.
I think the umaku part is difficult.
He's... he's...
so thick!
My god!
He is... he is...
I'm so... how thick did they have to make this tree to allow him to stand behind it?
Like, this guy!
Look at the size of him!
I can't even...
I can barely fit my fingers to his length!
Like, it's crazy!
Oh, dang it!
Oh, I just realized it was on.
Uh oh, I missed it.
We're still in caution mode.
The music is so awesome, right?
Absolute unit.
That's what I'm saying.
Snake been eating good.
Fit your fingers where?
Like a...
To... to...
Like a... like a ruler, right?
What did I say?
Wait, now I'm scared.
Wait, what did I say?
Does the bottom screen do anything?
No, it's all one screen.
It's just for decoration.
So, um...
But, when, uh...
When we get theater mode...
If we get theater mode...
It will be on the whole thing.
So, that's really awesome.
Um, that's when it shows, like, the...
It plays Snake Eater and shows, like, the scenes from the game while you play.
Crossing my fingers.
Safety!
Yeah, I'm hungry.
Okay, you're not gonna do anything about it.
It's pretty cool you own something like this.
Thanks.
I like it too.
Snow.
Yeah, we're picking snow...
in this location.
Makes absolute sense.
Come on, streamer luck.
I don't think there is...
I don't believe anymore.
I don't believe in stream...
streamer luck anymore.
I think...
Hold on, I'm gonna take a sip of your water.
How do you progress?
Is it all random?
I think so!
I think it's all random.
Um...
I see a wind coming soon.
Psycho Mantis?
Yeah, everybody, hydrate!
Drink your water.
We've been sweating trying to get these winds.
You know, but...
you make sure you're hydrated.
Chill!
When you're having a bad day, are you more of the type of ghost to go to the bar and drown your sorrows and booze?
Or the type to haunt elevators to try to lift your spirits?
Boo!
Increasing the patchy slot luck?
Thank you!
Thank you, Amelia!
Oh my god, how did you predict that?
Here he is!
He's not gonna say it though.
Nevermind.
I posted it in a tweet.
But I basically said, you're just gonna be getting a lot of this.
And when the exciting stuff happens, it's fun.
But it is a lot of this.
Please get the menu.
Please, can I get the menu?
Can I please get the menu?
Please...
Actually, I'm gonna pay out.
Oh wait, I'll do it after this.
Pay out.
If I...
If I go to the menu now...
Okay, let's try...
Wait, what are we on?
I think we're on...
Okay, we're on normal mode.
So let's try classic mode.
Again.
We tried it before.
But let's try it again.
I don't know, maybe it'll help a little bit.
We had a lucky streak at the start.
I know!
It started so strong!
You'd think that the game would just start to pity me at some point.
Snow...
You switched it to classic?
Yeah, we were on...
Oh, you were on classic.
Oh, I was?
We started on normal then moved to classic and then now on classic again.
Oh, wait, so I should I should switch it to normal now.
I should switch it to normal now.
Sorry, I thought I was on classic.
Or normal before.
Try advance.
What if it's so difficult?
So this is why when some people have asked me, like when I say oh yeah, I have this Metal Gear patchy slot, people have asked me before like, have you beaten it?
And I'm like, no!
Because this this is what I get every time!
This is what I'm dealing with!
Hi, paramedic.
Oh my god.
Look at the curve.
Oh, we're blue now.
Okay, this is looking good.
Right?
This is all different.
Well, not different, but oh!
We got some bullets.
Okay.
This is looking different.
This is looking good.
You keep getting so close.
I feel like it.
This game hates me.
Come on, please.
What the?
Yeah!
Oh my gosh.
Okay.
I don't remember what this is.
And I can't read it.
I can read it, but I don't know what the...
what it means.
Someone Nihongo Jozu more than me can read it?
Someone help.
Pull out the translator.
It's too blurry?
Oh yeah, you probably can't even see it.
Ha ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
It's so...
Oh yeah, because it's highlighted?
There you go.
Ha ha ha ha.
I hate kanji.
Sorry.
Ha ha ha ha.
Navi custom?
No, that's not the one.
Ha ha ha ha.
Kanji is the enemy.
It's still too... wait, no.
Someone... that's it.
I'm just gonna...
Jozu!
Try plugging your controller into the second slot.
Okay, so is it read how I thought it would be read?
But I don't understand what it means.
Okay, I'm just gonna try clicking it.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, I clicked the exit button.
Wait, okay.
Oh!
That's right.
Yes.
It shows you the different... okay, so if you get any of these combinations, you get to try again.
And if you...
I don't understand what the seven or three... like, they've been...
I don't really understand what they mean.
Like, I guess maybe credits?
I don't really get it.
I have no idea.
The odds?
Yeah, but like, I don't know.
Um...
Multipliers.
Oh, maybe.
Maybe, maybe.
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
Okay.
All right.
Oh, we're in the underground this time!
Okay.
Oh.
Hahahaha.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, just your imagination.
Just your imagination.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You were wrong.
Nothing here, nothing here.
Are you kidding me?
Hahahaha.
This is...
This is so cruel.
This is painful.
Why are you guys even watching this?
Why are you watching my pain and my suffering and my losing?
...
We like pain.
What is this?
...
Insanity is doing the same thing over and over and over again Insanity is doing the same thing over and over and over again and never changing.
No!
...
I am a symptom of evil!
Nanda kore wa imou?
That's not even the right quote.
Whatever!
It doesn't matter!
Isn't this supposed to be pay to win?
Oh, hi snake.
He looks so cool.
Nanda kore wa?
Isn't this supposed to be pay to win?
Hornet Strike!
Very cool.
Yeah, take him out.
Okay.
Oh, never mind.
We got demoted.
Okay guys.
Cigar.
Get forked.
Fork!
Oh!
We're red now and I don't know why.
Doesn't even matter how hard you try.
Okay.
Maybe the game feels bad for me now.
We're back in the underground.
Our camouflage is 30% which is not great.
Thank you for the dono.
The greatest engineer of the USSR's nascent space age looking at his own blueprints.
That's what I'm saying.
It's your... they're your papers.
Why?
Why do you not know what it is?
Okay.
Alright.
Come on.
Please.
What?!
But I got three in a row!
.
If you're a ghost in your pain, does that make it the phantom pain?
Yes!
Literally rigged.
Oh my god.
This is me.
Can you... I kind of want to see him like in the family guy dead pose.
Game.
It's rigged.
I know.
What?
I've never seen that before.
Why did that guy just fly across the screen?
I don't know.
What happened?
Okay.
Wait.
What?
One of those annoying guys.
Yeah.
Get forked.
This game is so rigged.
Nice.
Okay.
That's closer to the family guy pose.
Fork and bite.
Oh.
We're progressing maybe.
Where's the jackpot?
I don't know.
I don't know anything anymore.
What was that?
I've never had that before either.
What is going on?
Behind me.
I was so shocked he said something else I don't even know what he said.
Oh
my god.
We can finally progress.
He actually remembered.
The progress is none.
Okay.
50% camouflage.
Alright.
Okay.
It's 50-50 chance you guys.
And honestly.
I'll be honest.
50-50 is never on my side.
Please.
I just...
Okay.
Nice.
Thank you for the donut!
Thanks for sharing your brain rot with us.
Thank you!
Okay.
Come on.
What?
Oh my god!
What's going on?
Oh push!
Oh shit!
I missed it!
Sorry.
I didn't mean to curse.
No!
That was too close.
I was too slow!
Okay.
I have to look at this machine.
I can't look at it.
There's a slight delay when I look at it through the computer.
So.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Alright.
Come on.
Come on!
Oh god.
There's a timer here.
Five.
It says last game down there.
Do something!
Oh.
Yeah!
Oh my god.
Nice!
Push!
Oh dang.
Dang dang dang.
Okay.
We only have two tries left though.
One more?
Uh oh.
Oh no.
One!
Two!
Three!
Push!
I did it!
Uh oh.
Suddenly we're back here.
What just happened?
What?
The cliffhanger.
What just happened?
I think maybe we lost because because we didn't get the helicopter.
This is the Metal Gear experience I remember.
Hope you have a good time.
Thank you.
What is this?
The jungle.
In the jungle.
Our jungle.
I'm gonna die and sleep tonight.
It's the colonel.
I mean not the colonel.
It's the Major.
It's Wait.
Down here it turned to the Major.
Instead of Snake.
Why?
Wait.
I'm so confused.
Oh!
Exclamation point.
Something is going on.
What is going on?
What?
Me too.
I don't know.
What is this?
Ch-ch-chance!
Okay.
Thank you.
Oh.
Okay.
Wait.
What?
What's going on?
Oh my god.
Please.
What's going on?
What?
You guys.
What's going on?
No.
Please.
What happened?
No!
Everything is happening all at once.
I'm so...
In the jungle The mighty jungle The mighty jungle The lion sleeps The lion sleeps tonight The lion sleeps tonight The lion sleeps tonight 5,
6, 7, 0, 9 5, 6, 7, 0, 9 5, 6, 7, 0, 9
Let's go.
Okay.
The escape!
I think we can do this one though.
We don't need camouflage.
Right?
We're running for our lives.
We don't need camouflage.
Right?
We're running for our lives.
Okay.
Chance.
Chance!
Nice.
Stupid dogs.
Bow wow!
That's a lot.
If you loved me, you'd let me go.
Oh.
Again?
Okay guys.
Let's survive this time.
Okay.
Yeah!
In
the wrong order on accident.
Two.
Thank you!
Oh.
Okay.
Nice!
Yeah!
Okay.
It's okay.
We got three chances, I guess.
For the...
For the helicopter.
Okay.
I'm sweating.
Nice!
Yes!
This big snake!
Come on!
Oh!
She's coming.
Come
on.
Come on!
Oh.
Okay.
One more.
I can't do anything!
I can't!
NO!
THERE IS A PROBLEM!
YOU'RE STICK!
PLEASE!
WE NEED TO...
This game is hard.
I know.
It really is like so tough.
When I try to describe to people like...
When I try to describe to people like... it is not easy!
Get it?
Maybe it's just me.
I have no idea.
We're stuck in a loop.
Are you going to eat?
Oh, Snake thinks about his food.
Oh, a grenade!
Oh my gosh, we're actually getting stuff though.
This is good, right?
Oh no, not the progress, please.
Oh, please.
Oh no.
I don't even know what's happening.
Me neither!
Nice!
I'm going to become the Joker.
I think the game is actually feeling bad for me.
I think the game is actually starting to pity me a little bit.
No more progress.
90%?
Nice!
Oh, nice.
Okay.
We live in Apache's... Apache's society.
Oh!
I've never seen this guy before.
Am I in Fortnite emoting?
Wait!
What is this?
Stop.
Oh my god!
Here it is!
Yes!
Oh my god!
Bonus!
Please, please, let me get big boss.
Please, please, please, please, please.
Oh my god, please, please, please, please, please.
Oh my god, bonus, bonus!
Let's go!
This is what it looks like?
This is so awesome, right?
Come on, come on, come on.
What is this?
Okay.
Good.
What is this?
Come on, give us the great.
Oh, oh, oh, please.
Oh god, oh god.
Okay.
No.
I see it.
I see it in there.
Regular bonus!
Oh!
Oh my god, look at the intros and stuff.
Isn't it so awesome?
Thank you, Eva.
See, she just looks a little off.
I don't know what it is.
It's just something.
The new eyebrows?
Maybe that's it.
Maybe.
Oh, major zero.
His neck here is insane.
But he looks awesome here.
Here, I'll shut up a little bit so you guys can hear the audio a little better.
What neck?
I don't know.
The Jinju dirty in major zero.
Oh my god, what he says.
He said to the... I felt that.
No!
Remember the basis of CQC?
I punched the slot machine as strong as ghost.
Thank you!
Thank you, Acelot.
I'm making like little intros of everybody.
I love.
I love the N's Japanese voice.
I love it so much.
He just sounds like the perfect old man.
He looks so good.
Oh my gosh.
I've never actually have seen his models so much.
His hair looks like an actual...
He looks like a scarecrow.
It's so stringy.
Sorry if the quality is kind of bad right now because it's so much flashing.
Where is my gay cat boy son?
Patience.
Hopefully he comes home, actually.
Because these are random, too.
You don't always get the same characters.
He looks so cool!
He looks so good!
Oh, his eyes!
Oh my god, he looks so high.
I can't wait for Delta.
This bonus version music of the MGS3 is groovy.
Yeah, it's cool.
I love bonus time!
I've had this
one before.
Oh my god, he looks so good!
Oh my god!
Oh my god, sorry.
Oh my god, oh my god.
Nice!
Maybe...
Oh my god, sorry.
I was so...
He looks so good!
Oh my god, oh my god!
We got it, you guys!
We got it!
It only took... two hours!
Oh my god.
I'm gonna go a little slower so it plays as much as possible.
But he never was.
He never was.
Oh
my god, he looks so good.
I can't wait for Oh my god.
This is exactly why I bought this machine.
Oh, I love it.
Oh, the walking with the switch between the scenes.
It's so good.
Oh, man.
Sorry, I'm not even looking at chat.
I just can't stop looking.
You look so goofy.
Oh, she looks so perfect.
Oh my god.
Oh gosh, she looks so perfect.
Oh my gosh, she looks so good.
Tense!
Rank up!
I don't know what that means.
Rykoff looks so cool too.
Oh, she looks good there.
And then I have to repeat so that you can get all the... hopefully see all the scenes, you know?
It's just... it looks so good.
It looks too good!
Oh, it looks too good.
Wait, I think this is a repeat now, so yeah.
Okay.
Alright, so we got everything.
Wait, it says last game 46.
No way.
Oh my god, we have 45 more turns?
Yeah!
You know what?
It took us this... it took us this hard to get here.
We can watch it as many times as we want.
But I have to do this patchy slot part or else it doesn't continue.
It'll end up like... the music will end up fading.
It was worth it.
Rykoff looks so cute.
He looks so cute.
Oh, what are we getting it?
Mystery!
Truly the big bonus.
There is one other mode.
Like, this is the theater one, but there's one other one.
I can't remember what it's called.
The day you go through the rain.
It's a day... the... the... the... the bees.
I'm in it.
I'm still in a dream.
Snake Eater, yeah!
Yeah!
Oh, sorry.
I know.
Sorry.
Here you go.
You can see it.
I shouldn't put my hand on the screen so you can...
I'm like, look!
Isn't my machine so beautiful?
Isn't it so pretty?
Aren't the cutscenes so nice?
With my hand, like, blocking everything.
Oh, Snake looks so awesome.
Oh!
Mystery!
Nice.
Oh!
Come on!
Shoot!
Dang.
Oh, I'm so glad we got this.
Oh,
I'm so glad we got this.
Oh, I'm so glad we got this.
Two!
Thank you!
You have surpassed even the bonus.
We award you the title, Big Bonus.
I know!
The Big Bonus came out of nowhere, you guys!
We had regular bonus, and then they awarded us Big Bonus!
Maybe the game loves us after all.
I feel like if we weren't watching you...
watching, you would smooch the screen.
Which is okay.
I would too.
Yeah, maybe.
Maybe.
Oh!
I'm sorry.
I can't get over how cute Rykov looks.
Like, if there was a... good remake.
Not a good one.
Well, if there was a... like a new...
rather, a remake of MGS2, I guess.
Would Ryden look like that?
He'd be so cute!
Yeah, like a Delta remake.
Not that I... oh, oops.
Sorry, Ocelot.
I wasn't paying attention.
Um, not that I want that, but...
it's fun to see how, um, Ryden would maybe look.
Okay, we only have 16 left.
Look at our total get!
It's so small!
Come
on, big bucks!
Come on, big, big bonus!
Big money!
Now!
Click the link for money!
Oh!
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
Now you can see, like, the close-up of it.
It's very good.
The art is so awesome.
So, um...
D sjaba-de.
Everyone just... oh!
Oh!
Last 3 games.
Okay!
Okay.
Uh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, okay!
Two more, two more.
Okay.
You go through the rain, ba-bam.
Oh!
Double snake dream.
On a trip, ba-da, ba-ba.
Oh, a different seven.
Ba-ba, ba-ba, ba-ba.
Last one, Kim.
I get a 140!
Whoosh!
Snake it up!
And... oh, here it is.
Okay, here we go.
You can see it's the whole thing.
It looks so good.
It just looks so good.
The thing is, he doesn't flip here.
It's actually quite disappointing.
But it looks so good.
Oh my god, it looks so good.
I have to keep going real simple.
It looks... oh my god, it looks... oh god, it looks incredible.
It looks... it looks way too good.
Like, it almost looks like it's not a game.
It almost looks like real footage sometimes.
Like, it's kind of scary.
The graphics on a slap machine.
I know, right?
It's crazy.
It looks so good though.
I think I have to keep going or else...
He's just gonna fall forever.
Okay, alright, Snake.
Don't flip!
You won't!
Good!
He's just... he's just...
He's free falling!
He's going forever.
He's... he's... he's...
Okay, Snake.
How... how big is the atmosphere?
He's just still going.
He's...
Okay, Snake.
We get it.
You can stop.
Alright.
Do something.
Pull the parachute.
Snake...
He's...
he's going to fall forever.
Oh my god!
Snake, please!
Snake...
Oh!
Okay, we need this one!
Fox is still hunted.
Fox is not still hunted.
Oh!
Sorry, I didn't...
Oh my god!
What...
Let's go!
He's gonna fall forever!
Okay,
move on!
Oh, he's gonna...
Oh my god!
Time to fight, baby!
Now you're going to see how truly evil... how truly evil... this Patchy Slot game is.
You are going to see... how evil... this game is.
Truly.
Truly!
Like... oh my god.
Oh my god.
I can't believe we're here.
This is the best.
And I'm glad it's Ocelot.
Honestly, I do want to see the fury and I do want to see the end, but I'm glad for viewing that it's Ocelot, you know?
So you guys can see Ocelot nice and close in this whole scene and everything.
All right.
Oh my god.
Okay guys, prepare to lose.
To battle.
Okay.
So...
All right.
He has three bars.
Keep that in mind.
He has green, yellow, red.
Okay.
He has three.
Three bars.
The tumbleweed.
Okay.
Three bars.
Nice!
See how much damage that did?
Do you see how much damage that did?
Okay.
Where are we?
It did like, you know, like... you know.
Okay.
Three bars.
Right?
And that's how much damage?
Okay.
Oh, this is my life bar.
I forgot to mention.
I have four shots.
So if he hits me four times, we start the whole game over.
Okay?
And he has three bars.
Do you understand why now I've never beaten this game before?
Do you understand?
I've never beaten a boss battle.
Ever.
I don't think there's a way to heal.
If there is, I have no idea what it is.
If there's a way to heal.
So, um...
KERATINE!
All right.
Stun grenade.
Not bad.
Advantage.
Nice, nice, nice.
Nice, nice, nice, nice.
Hmm...
I think it would've been even better... Why is it even already?
I think it would've been even better if we got the orange next.
Why does Acelad's voice fit him so perfectly?
Oh!
Nice!
Nice, nice, nice, nice!
Rush, rush, rush, rush, rush.
Rush, rush, rush.
Rush, rush, rush, rush.
Okay, nice.
Oh my god, wait.
Rush.
Rush, rush.
We're back to even, okay.
Okay, we're about a little under 50%, or rather a little over 50% for his health.
And we still don't have any hits on us, so that's a tumble win.
It's not so bad.
Nice, okay.
Three tumble wins.
Nothing's going on.
Oh no, oh no, please.
Also, I don't... look at him go!
Look at him go!
Oh my god!
Uh oh, uh oh, okay.
I don't know how to block attacks.
So...
Oh, oh god.
Okay, that's one hit.
Nice!
250 over.
What does that mean?
I'm so tense right now.
Truly the Dark Souls of slot machines.
Good.
Come
on, Ocelot.
Come on, Ocelot.
Ghosts are proud creatures.
Oh no, we didn't even attack him once!
This game is so cruel.
What's the strategy here?
Uh...
I wish I could just pay more money.
Like, I don't know why it... why it, uh...
I don't know why you can't, like, continue the fight.
You know, why it has to take you back to the very beginning.
Is the most painful part.
But, I got to show you the scenes and we got to a boss fight.
So I feel very fulfilled in what I was able to show you guys today.
Even though it took two hours to get there.
Uggggggggggggggg.
Ugh.
Ocelot?
I don't think there's a way to avoid the attacks.
Please,
please, please!
Please, please, please!
Please!
Guys, I think we're in trouble.
I think we're in trouble.
Nice!
Ooh!
Yes!
Big damage.
Spin to win.
Ooh.
Oh!
Nice!
It's looking good!
Oh my god.
I don't, I don't even know if I've ever gotten this far before.
No second.
I am not daijoubu.
Please.
I'm, I'm, I'm literally losing my vision.
I'm going unconscious.
I'm... I think I'm... I think this is it for me.
Yah!
Does money heal you?
No!
I have max credits!
Uh oh.
I'm not gonna turn into the Sorrow.
I'm gonna turn into the Joker.
Snake
dies.
Cause I'm already dead.
Your money has no power here.
Yeah.
Oh no.
Oh, I think it's over, you guys!
I think this is it!
Everybody say...
Sayonara.
You can see Snake's face in slow-mo.
Never mind.
Ah.
Real footage of...
Mint phantom gameplay.
Milk your solid gameplay.
Hahaha.
Ah.
Thanks, Ocelot.
Wait, continue zone.
Save?
Wait, what?
What do you mean?
Woah!
Woah, that's crazy!
Wait, what do you mean save?
Oh, and also we're... we have our little... the little...
Woah, that's crazy!
Wait, what do you mean save?
Oh, and also we're...
we have our little...
um...
Oh, and also we're...
we have our little...
um...
Oh, and also we're... we have our little...
Oh, and also we're... we have our little... um...
Oh, and also we're...
we have our little...
um...
Oh, and also we're... we have our little...
Oh,
and also we're... we have our little... um...
Ready?
Say it with me!
Get... full!
Rationed!
Get... rationed!
Four big bonus.
Why are we still here?
Just to suffer.
Every night I can feel my fork in my cigar.
Even my bullets.
The progress I've lost.
The hours I've lost.
Won't stop.
Nanda kore wae.
Big bonus.
What a thrill!
Ocelot, why are we still here?
Oh, we got it!
Okay!
Everybody say it with me!
Sorry.
I instinctively pushed it very quickly.
Gosh, Ocelot is just hand-holding the whole time.
He won't let me impress how I want to.
He's like, come on!
Migi da manaka!
You know?
Oh, Eva!
Oh, never mind.
Eva does not respond.
Yeah!
Nanda kore wae.
Nanda kore
wae.
It's time to get...
Forked!
Yeah!
And with that, everybody, I think...
I think that is all of...
the...
Metal Gear Apache slot.
I'm going to keep chatting after this because I don't want to end just quite yet.
What do you guys think?
What if...
What did you guys think?
I have no idea what's happening, but my brain likes the sounds and colors.
Cool machining.
Thanks!
An interesting concept.
I think...
having...
a battle through...
slots is...
actually something only the Devil could conjure up.
I think it is so evil.
Um...
But other than that, I do like watching Ocelot spin his guns.
I understood nothing.
You know what?
Yeah, you could watch this and be like...
This is...
the...
the most...
Oh my god.
Nanda kore wae.
This is a truly...
This is Metal Gear Solid 3.
I don't understand anything that's going on.
Will you ever do another podcast?
Cheers to Ocelot's dream.
I think...
it's...
What's the word?
I think it's going to be exactly the same as here.
We may be...
I mean there are some events that we haven't gotten before.
I think it will be mostly...
the same exact thing.
Yeah, I'll have to check the difficulty later.
For sure.
About every two to three streams ended with a few games of Patchy Slot.
See, that would be difficult because I had to move my Patchy Slot.
My Patchy Slot is usually over there in my room.
And I had to very painstakingly drag it closer to my computer.
So that wouldn't really work out.
Because... yeah.
Oh, I can disable the echo mic.
You're right.
Thank you.
There we go.
So... how large is it?
It's very large and very in charge.
It's very heavy.
Yeah, it's...
Okay, so... let's see.
This is my arm.
And it...
This is the top of the machine.
And it doesn't even go to like the middle.
And it's... it's...
Hold on, let me measure how thick it is.
Thick.
Maybe... hold on.
It's like this...
This thick.
Wait.
It's like...
You can't show these guns on YouTube.
It is kind of like a refrigerator.
Yeah, it is.
It does kind of feel like a refrigerator.
This is cool though.
I don't think I've ever seen this before.
Or if I have, it was a long time ago.
So...
Yay.
Let's see.
I have this.
And...
I see...
You've been wearing this.
It's very nice.
If I have to describe it...
It's very similar to the most popular one.
I will be wearing this.
Feels like... feels while trying to figure out what we all just watched since this is probably the most folks have seen of the patchy game.
You think so?
I don't know.
I wish I could have shown it off better, but my luck tends to be poor.
So I truly apologize, but it is quite fine.
Like it's not something that I could typically sit...
Well, that's not true.
I think I could typically sit and do it for...
Sorry.
For like an hour or something.
Hour two if I really wanted to.
But it's like so...
It's... it's...
Maybe not the most super duper exciting thing, right?
Here, I'm gonna actually do this.
No!
I wanna go back to...
Well, maybe it'll go... maybe it will...
I don't know what to call it.
Wait, there's continue zone right here.
I don't know what that is.
I do not know.
Anyway.
Sorry if I'm making weird faces.
Sorry.
Okay.
Did you read the manual?
It didn't come with a manual!
It didn't come with a manual.
Okay, give me one second.
I'm gonna set up...
Well, quickly...
Hold on.
Pew, pew, pew, pew.
Mm-mm-mm-mm-mm.
Oh!
Grr.
I'm okay.
I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
We can just leave it on in the background.
If we would.
Okay.
Oh, what the hell?
Why am I asleep?
Uh-oh.
Hold on.
Oh.
What did I get?
I think I did break something.
I think I broke my brain.
You know, I'm just trying.
I think I'm.
Oh no!
Wait, wait.
Hold on.
Uh.
Oh.
Why?
Woo.
Oh.
Uh.
Okay.
I don't know how to work my body.
I don't know how to work my body, you guys.
Maybe I should... Can you guys hear the machine still?
I'm gonna put on some music.
Let's see.
A little.
You can hear the birds chirping just a tiny bit.
Key.
Do.
Very spring time.
I use this BGM all the time.
You're a simp.
Thanks for showing off your Pachisot machine and for all the work it took to set this up.
Stream has been really special.
Special is a word for it, isn't it?
That is a word for it, right?
Maybe you're supposed to ignore the 1, 2, 3 and risk it for the biscuit.
I don't know.
Why would they tell us to 1, 2, 3 then?
Oh, snake.
You good?
That always seems to get you blues or yellows, which I think are the lowest value spins.
Maybe... I don't know.
What's the fork count at?
Truly...
Unforkable measures.
Ugh...
Is this your craziest Metal Gear item?
Probably.
The other thing... I kind of wanted to show it off in the background, but I couldn't fix it in a good way.
Was my... I have a snake standee.
Like a life size... Well, maybe not life size, but I have like a big...
Snake standee from...
From when they sold...
What was it?
I think it was MGS...
I can't remember actually.
It was one of the... It was one of the...
Advertisements in...
Europe though.
I think... I'm pretty sure it was MGS2.
But like, what's the...
What's the...
Oh my gosh, my brain is...
Is... I have a lack of...
Ectoplasm...
Happening.
Is the standee bigger than you?
No, no, no, no.
I can say that was the best VTuber playing Apache Slot stream I've ever seen.
You must watch those a lot.
Truly.
You must watch those all the time.
It's a big market.
Everybody out here is saying...
VTubers playing Apache Slots.
It's the new...
The new...
Meta.
There was some...
Hold on, I'm gonna like zoom in a little bit more.
There was some... I did want to like...
What's the word?
I wanted to talk some more about like my...
Hashtags and stuff like that.
I know it's kind of probably not the right stream to do that but...
Even I was... I was like...
At first, I was like...
I don't need an art tag.
Whatever.
But then...
I think I need an art tag.
I feel really sad leaving my old tags and stuff.
And then I also kind of want to talk about like...
Fan names.
Sorry, it's like the most random time to talk about this, isn't it?
But...
Oh!
And if you haven't seen...
Where is it?
My schedule for...
Well, tomorrow!
Tomorrow I'm playing Zoombinis!
Oh gosh, my voice...
My throat is still healing so I can't do high notes right now.
But...
Yeah, but...
On...
Tuesday I'm playing the new Chilla's Heart game.
Because I'm a VTuber, you guys.
And I have to play it.
I have to.
I'm so sorry.
But also...
I kind of like those like games where it's like...
Find the anomaly.
I think those are kind of fun.
It's mandatory.
I can't say that I'm truly...
Been...
Resummoned until I play it, you know?
And then...
Monday is the podcast.
A release day.
So...
Instead of a stream, you can listen to the podcast.
Probably...
Pretty much every Monday I'll have off.
Just because that's when we'll be releasing the podcast.
So...
Um...
Yes, yes, yes.
Uh...
Wednesday is when we record the podcast.
So I'll have off that day too.
And...
Uh...
Thursday is Facade.
Which is a game that I've...
Uh...
I saw a video on it recently and I was like...
Oh my gosh!
I forgot this existed!
Um...
There's like this other old Flash game.
I think on Newgrounds.
Called...
I think it was like The Negotiator or something.
Um...
And...
Uh...
It always...
I don't know if it's the same person.
It's a classic.
It is.
Yeah.
So...
The Negotiator.
Yeah!
You guys remember it?
Oh my god.
I reference it all the time.
And I don't think people realize.
Anytime...
Well...
Um...
Like...
I'll be like...
I'm gonna blow this place to hell.
And...
That's why I'm referencing...
The Negotiator.
Oh man.
So silly.
Um...
And then on...
Friday, Tomodachi Live.
Um...
I was thinking maybe we can make like a bunch of...
Silly characters.
Of course like Snake.
Or...
We can...
We'll have you guys decide.
We can make like whatever silly characters we want.
And just have them in.
And then...
Saturday.
Metal Gear Saturdays.
With the Twin Snakes.
Um...
I say Metal Gear Saturdays.
I mean we might go after Twin Snakes.
We might go into like...
Acid.
Um...
Cause I have not played Acid yet.
Though...
Oh!
Thank you!
Thank you for the AkaToro!
Thank you so much!
Um...
I meant...
Quick reminder.
It's not a day off if you work that day.
Hope this helps.
Um...
I don't...
I mean...
But it's...
I don't consider it.
You know?
It's like...
I don't...
Um...
Memberships will be open on Tuesday.
Right?
I have no idea.
That's up to YouTube.
That's not up to me.
Wah!
Hi man!
Hi!
Thank you for the AkaToro!
Thank you!
How do I say...
Wait.
Osos!
Thank you!
Jinuko!
Kyun!
Oh my gosh.
Long time no see.
100 plus player.
Tetrio win.
Hahaha.
Metal Gear Twin Snakes let's go I remember.
Spoiled myself by accident one time with this game.
Hahaha.
I can't wait.
I can't wait to play Twin Snakes.
Um...
And then...
Probably Sunday I'll do a Guerrilla stream.
Um...
Honestly, I just didn't know what to stream that day.
So I...
I said Guerrilla stream if I come up with something.
Maybe it's Tetrio but I'll be honest you guys.
I haven't gotten better at all at Tetri...
Thank you for all the donuts.
Thank you guys.
I haven't gotten better at all at Tetri.
I, uh...
Um...
I'm gonna get my butt white whooped.
Hahaha.
You're Osu!
I'm glad to have finally gotten the definitive MGS3 experience!
Thanks, Mint!
This stream was definitely more fun than you seemed to think.
I'm glad that you'd say that.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Sorry, girl, but there's at least one Mintomo.
Mintomo!
What is that?
Thank you.
That won't wipe your ear.
No, stop.
Thanks for all the donuts!
Thank you, guys!
I'm vacuuming your butt for that comment.
No!
Don't Luigi me!
To the heroes of Tetris for the privilege to wipe your butt in mine.
I'd wipe someone's...
No!
Oh, man.
Why?
Why is my brain like this?
Thank you!
Mint brain, don't say wiped.
Don't say wiped.
Absolutely do not say wiped.
Mint mouth, wiped.
Oh, stinky.
Thank you, thank you.
Chuu!
Cool piece of Metal Gear franchise you showed off today.
Thanks for the stream!
The new Being Haunted could be this one.
Yay!
Yeah, all it requires is giving me a little bit of your life force.
Is that okay?
Batae funds.
Chuu!
Mmm!
Mmm...
Thank you!
I can't believe I got this invested over watching someone play slots.
It got a little intense sometimes, for real.
It got pretty intense in some sections, I was feeling the pressure, the actual pressure.
Unrelated but I really love your Ace Combat games collection.
Thank you non-John Ace Combat Team!
Yeah!
I'm so jealous that you have even older Ace Combat, though.
I only have PS2 era, sadly.
I've gone to so many used game stores.
Unfortunately, so many of the ones that I have are in those GameStop-esque boxes.
I only played 7, and when I did, I was like, oh my gosh, I think I love this.
I struggled a little bit with following the story, so it almost felt...
Hold on.
I can't say it.
Wait.
It felt like if I were to have played Metal Gear Rising before the rest of the Metal Gear series.
You know what I mean?
So it's like I really wanted to know more about the rest of the lore.
That's nuts.
I know, right?
Who would do that?
Play the games in release order, you idiot.
So yeah, I've just been kind of collecting them.
I haven't played any of them yet.
Excited.
JPEG dog lore.
Yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
7 is a new story, but knowing...
Well, I think it was like...
I know it all takes place...
What's it called?
It takes place...
Like, you know, more about the Belkan War and stuff like that.
Like, there's obviously...
There's a lot of lore that didn't feel...
Like, you know, what was it?
Stonehenge and everything like that.
Strange Reel!
Yes, yes.
It all takes place in Strange Reel.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's from 3, right?
That it takes place in...
Strange...
Reel?
Or 4?
Wait.
I can't remember.
3 or 4, right?
It's 4?
Wait, from 2?
I thought 1 and 2 were like...
Kind of...
Mostly separate.
Is that not the case?
Am I misunderstood?
Don't worry, I still have my Membu card.
If you open memberships back, I'll be joining back.
Thank you!
Thanks, Shun.
I hope you're doing well.
I really enjoyed the stream today.
Thank you, Mike Tyson's butt.
I hope your butt gets thoroughly wiped.
In a good way.
In a good way, right?
Thanks for the means.
Thank you, Shunvoi.
I'll go grab a coffee to stop about 3 avons.
No, thank you so much.
I hope everyone is alright this afternoon.
I don't like to back down from a challenge, so...
Thank you for the stream, for sharing the machine.
I've not seen such an extensive look at it before.
And man, what could have been with the Fox Engine remake...
I know...
When you get the theater mode...
Sometimes, like I said before...
Before it started playing with the bonus or whatever...
Sometimes it will let you choose.
Theater mode or...
There is another mode.
I think the other mode...
Takes you directly into...
The...
Like the quote-unquote story part of the game.
So I think it starts you on the helicopter.
But with this, we got both.
So I guess it worked out, honestly.
But yeah...
Seeing the...
Seeing the cutscenes...
Just...
Monkey!
Oh, Ape Escape!
Yeah, we got to do Ape Escape.
Me so cute.
Yeah!
Yeah, Mint is adorable.
Stop it.
Stop.
Oh my gosh.
Stop it.
Come on.
I mean...
I mean, it's like...
I'm a maid.
Like, I have to be cute, right?
But like...
Come on.
Oh, okay.
Let's talk...
Fan names.
In this very...
Okay.
Sorry.
I should have done this...
Last time.
I don't know what to do.
I refuse.
I just want to be cute.
And that's...
Yes.
T -Error.
No.
Am...
Not...
Great.
Are you good?
Are you Meh?
Yes.
I don't necessarily want to get rid of the name Fandom, right?
I don't want to throw away everything that we came up with before.
But I do think that having something a little bit more concrete...
Because you can't say, I am a Fandom.
It's more like, I'm part of the Fandom.
You know what I mean?
I think Boo-ties.
Boo-ties?
Like bow-tie, but a Boo-tie.
Fandom is good?
Boomers.
Boo-champs?
I don't know.
I haven't really thought of it at all.
Because I kind of just came in thinking that I would have everything the same as before.
So I'm just like...
I think Boomers.
Choco Minto Art?
Wait, that's so cute actually.
I think... I think Boomers feels a little too...
Like, any ghost Vtuber could have that, right?
As their fandom.
I think we gotta come up with something a little more specific.
There was Wisps before.
Like it was Fandom, and then...
If you were in the Fandom, you were a Wisp.
But...
Hmm...
Phantoms?
Phantoms in the Fandom?
Like this?
Phantoms?
Insane in the Membrane?
Phantoms in the Fandom?
Mint Busters?
That's kind of cute actually.
Wait, Mint...
Mint...
Mint Busters?
Fantomies?
That's kind of cute too.
That's pretty cute too.
Hmm...
I'm seeing if I see any others that I really like.
Thank you for the dough, Noel.
Mentos.
Oh my god.
This page seems to have some instructions in a forum for the Metal Gear...
What?
Really?
Since our time was cut short, what are the chances of a return to Trials and Tribulations to play this game?
This is the main cafe...
Wait, that's the DLC, isn't it?
We'll see.
I can't just play the DLC episode.
I have to play everything all over again.
Dead Cell.
What?
That doesn't even make any sense.
I kinda love it but...
I don't want everything to be a Metal Gear reference, you guys.
Not everything can be a Metal Gear reference.
Boots?
I don't get it.
Like dudes?
I'm not feeling it.
Sorry.
Fandom with the mods as wisps and us as memboos.
Well memboos is the membership though.
Okay, shut up you.
See, and part of me wants to keep things...
The same as before too, but like...
We have to be honest.
Things aren't the same.
Things are a little different than they were before.
Can we just keep wisps?
But you don't want anything?
You don't want something more... specific?
To...
Me?
I'm so egotistical.
It has to be related to me, you guys.
No, I'm just kidding.
Mintomo?
Buh... Buh... Brigade.
Oh, like brigade.
Ugh, this is all... I think no matter what I choose, I can't make everybody happy.
So I think I just gotta choose what I like the most.
Cause...
It'll still be.
Like if it's... you know, it's...
You are awesome.
Min... min...
Min... te... min... te...
Min...
Min... tes...
Sotens.
Oh!
Mintesotens!
Like a Minnesotan?
Like Minnesota?
Like the... the... the state in the United States of America, Minnesota.
That's wild.
Why...
That's actually crazy.
Uh oh, I think my chat froze.
Are you guys still there?
Oh, okay.
It froze on YouTube.
YouTube has been freezing so much for me recently.
Don't know if you said this before, but are weekend streams always early?
The upcoming weekday streams are a bit too late to catch for me, unfortunately.
Ah...
Ah... I didn't say before.
Weekend streams, I typically do a little bit earlier.
Um...
But also in the weekday, I'll try and do some midday stuff as well.
So, uh...
There will be a mix of stuff.
My schedule's never truly consistent, unfortunately.
I'm sorry.
I'm all over the place.
But, uh...
But there will be times that will be good for EU watchers.
If there are any.
As well.
So...
Yeah, sorry that I don't have a set...
I don't think I've ever had really a set time where I'm just like, Okay, guys!
Every day!
7pm EST!
Catch me here!
No, sometimes...
I don't know why.
Sometimes I'll be like, Today's 7.
But tomorrow is 6.
I don't know why.
It's...
Maybe just because I try to do a little bit of variety.
For people who are just like, Oh, I can't make the 7pm times.
I can only do the 6pm times.
So...
Yeah.
I'm fine with whatever you choose.
Can I get some of that dripping chocolate?
I feel uncomfortable.
Well, I'm gonna try and reset my...
YouTube.
Okay.
You're a suit.
There we go.
Thank you.
You mentioned.
Let's go.
Okay.
The fanchies?
Wait.
That's so cute.
Actually.
I'm gonna go...
I'm kind of leaning... towards phantomies.
Because it sounds close enough to fandom.
I think phantomies, maybe.
Because it's like phantomies...
in the...
See, for me, when I say like, hey...
I'm a wisp.
It doesn't feel, to me, so much like a...
Like, it just feels like a description.
Like, you guys are wisps.
But like, you're a phantomie wisp.
I think.
Right?
Like...
It's more like a...
My wisp type is phantomie.
And memberships are the members.
Sounds like the buttriots.
Hmm...
So I think we'll go with phantomies.
If you guys are okay with it.
Phantomies in the fan...
Fandom.
For those who still like fandom.
Of course, you can still use it.
Of course, of course.
Okay.
It's been decided.
I lay down the hammer.
Okay.
I feel so...
I don't know.
I don't know how to feel.
Like, I feel so...
What's the word?
Maybe...
Not like...
It's like almost guilt.
You know?
It almost feels like...
Like a guilt.
But...
Don't think that...
You know?
Because we're making a few little changes.
Sometimes...
This happens to other VTubers as well.
Where they have to change their...
Fan names for whatever reason.
So...
Um...
Will they be redesigned?
What?
The Wisp design?
No, no.
It's still the same.
So...
I don't mind?
Okay.
Thank you, Splagoon.
I don't know.
I just got so many questions from people being like...
What?
What do I call myself?
And like...
I think...
You know?
Like I said back then...
We came up with stuff.
But...
It was kind of like...
Multiple things.
I think we need to settle on...
Some more definitive...
Stuff.
You know what I mean?
Something a little...
Like...
I don't know.
Wisps is still fine.
But...
I don't know.
Am I overthinking this?
Am I over thinking this?
Maybe I'm overthinking this.
I don't know!
Am I?
Yes?
Shall we just keep it as...
Shall we just...
Should we just keep it as Whisp?
You know what?
Okay.
Yeah.
What do I do?
Pull?
Okay, pull.
I don't want this responsibility.
You decide.
If you don't like the poll result, then you know what answer you really want.
That's true.
I just don't want people mad at me.
You know?
I don't want people being like, oh no.
She's changed too much.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm overthinking it.
Can't please everyone.
Yeah, I know.
I know, I know, I know, I know.
And I know this is probably not even that big of a deal.
It's just a fandom.
But...
It was because...
I get so confused when it's like, you have the wisps.
You have the fandom.
You have the members.
You have this.
You have that.
And, I'm like, I can't keep up either.
And,
I'm like, I can't keep up either.
And, I'm like, I can't keep up either.
Okay.
Well, Fantomys seems to have the consensus.
Not by much.
I will give it that.
And not everybody watching... Oh!
There's more votes coming in?
I was gonna say, not everybody watching is voting.
Hey guys!
No, I'm just kidding.
You don't have to vote.
It's okay.
Oh!
More votes coming in?
I'll just keep it up.
Well, we'll keep this up and then we can decide hashtags.
Flip the W and rearrange the letters.
And you have what we really are.
Simps.
Stop!
No!
Okay.
You're...
a simp.
Um...
Um... Okay.
Hashtag.
So, I need an art tag.
What was that?
Choco mint art.
That was cute.
I have to make sure no one's using stuff though.
Um... I guess we can keep my...
current one as like...
It's still a general tag.
It's even written as that.
So, we can still keep it as that too.
Um...
No, we're not...
Why you guys have to say...
Fant...
Art.
Mint paste.
Simps rise up.
The will of the wisps is phantomies.
Stop saying fart.
Stop.
Stop it.
Stop saying fart.
Stop.
Ghosts can't even fart, you guys.
This is...
This is not even accurate.
Stop saying...
fart, please.
Not with that attitude.
Ghosts are all fart?
What are you talking about?
What is ectoplasm?
It's like a little more gooey.
Ghost post?
Oh my gosh, wait.
Hashtag ghost.
But it doesn't have to do with art.
I think that's the hardest thing.
It's probably also taken.
Snakes just been... I think snake is lost.
He can't find his way through the forest at all.
Fan art?
Oh, that's kind of cute.
Like that?
Wait, that's actually so cute.
Wait, that's...
Wait, it's probably taken.
Let's check.
There's like...
Some yaoi parry.
Thank you, thank you.
I don't think I can use this.
There's like some yaoi parry.
Oh my god.
These get a little graphic.
It's just some guys.
I don't think I can take...
I don't think I can use it.
I know what will fix it.
You're a snake.
I wonder if this is actually...
We just do fanfart!
It works!
Wait, I have to see if this is taken.
This is fun.
Fantography?
Wait, that's so cute too.
This is what you wanted, isn't it?
I feel like this is probably taken, but we can check.
It's hard being a ghost.
Because there's so many other ghosts.
Oh, this one doesn't seem to be used very much.
Maybe?
Oh, with an F?
Like that?
Mintography?
You guys are going crazy.
Phantom paint?
This one's a little punny, right?
It's kind of fun.
Yeah, this one... wait, Latest.
This one doesn't seem to be used at all.
Well, a little bit, but you know.
It's hard to find a hashtag that's not used at all.
And you know what?
This kind of fits in with the theme of the general hashtag.
Since it's...
Shinrei Shashin.
Which is spirit photography.
That's what it means in Japanese.
Mint sightings?
Wait, that's so cute too.
I like that for like...
If you ever...
Like... well, I don't...
Well, if you get like the merch and you like take a picture of me somewhere.
But I guess that works with the Shinrei Shashin too.
You can probably use the other hashtag for it.
If you take a picture of me?
NSFW tag!
I like fantography, though.
I think that's good.
I think we can go with that.
I think I'll go with the fantography.
Do I...
Do I have to...
Because why are you so fast with that?
Maybe it's necessary.
I don't know.
So that certain things don't show up in the fantography.
Only fans!
Oh my god.
Like this?
Like that?
I feel like that has to be taken though, right?
Please no R18.
Is this $100 enough?
At least maybe any R18 is untagged.
The fact that you donated!
I don't know for that.
Also, only fans is definitely taken.
Do not... I don't want to look at it.
I'm just afraid that if people draw stuff that they'll put it in the art tag and then it'll show up mainstream.
Not safe for Mint.
No!
I don't think having a tag necessarily encourages it.
It's just so that if it does show up, it's in its own place.
I think.
I don't... I don't know.
Maybe we don't need it.
I don't know.
Not everyone has one, so it's not so necessary.
Hmm...
Oh, I think you're in the raid!
I'll think about this one.
I will think about this one.
I still... I feel weird about it.
I don't know.
Especially with people just coming in.
I'm like...
Let's just get this off the screen real quick.
I think I... I have the live tag, Minto Live.
And I have the general tag.
And I have the art tag.
I think that's good enough.
Anything other... like if it's not art...
You can put it in the general tag.
And I think it'll be okay.
Cosplay tag?
I don't think I need one.
I really don't think I need one.
I think you can put cosplay in the general tag.
Because I'll still check it.
When you have so many hashtags, it's hard to check all of them.
So... yeah.
Memes in general tag?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just put it all in the general tag.
Unless it's art.
Cos for art, like I like to... you know, obviously I go through it for...
For...
Like thumbnails and stuff like that.
So...
So we'll have art... live... is...
Minto...
Minto... live...
As it has been... always?
Busted makes me feel good.
I think that is probably already used so much.
I do like not save for Minto.
I think that's really funny.
My keyboard no do JP?
Copy and paste!
Copy and paste.
Probably you could do it in English if you wanted to, but...
Hashtag...
Minto... live...
I wonder...
The last thing...
Oh!
I was like...
You guys would think I'm stupid.
Oh!
It's mint olive!
I searched... Hashtag... Minto... live...
And it... I clicked latest and it was a soap...
And it said mint and rosemary and I was like...
Mint!
That's me!
Even though I searched...
Even though...
Even though I searched mint myself...
First time here and love the MGS3 gacha experience.
Thank you!
Thanks for being here!
Oh man...
But also it's mint and rosemary extra virgin olive oil soap.
I was like...
Mint olive!
Is the hashtag.
Hashtag... Mint olive!
That's so funny.
Mint olive...
But yeah, okay.
Those can be the hashtags.
Um...
And then...
Uh...
Yes.
Fantomys is still winning but it...
It went down a little.
I still don't know what to do.
Maybe I'll sleep on it.
I'll sleep on it!
And I'll make a tweet about it.
So that we can...
We can...
Maybe I'll ask Google.
I'll say... I'll give it...
You know, I'll spin a wheel.
But I'll make a tweet about all this.
Being like...
Here's hashtags.
It's just these three.
And...
Here's the fan name.
Yeah.
We'll see.
Ask Matara for her opinion as well.
Yeah, maybe I will.
Because...
She...
I tend to ask her for...
Like her opinion on...
Things a lot too.
Anything else you wanted to discuss with us?
No?
You are dismissed?
Class is dismissed?
No, no.
I just wanted to hang out too.
You know.
I feel like...
Since I've gotten back...
I mean last stream...
Maybe I didn't talk so much.
It was like...
Me answering things...
And then singing.
So it was less talking.
Matara Miller.
That's perfect.
Because...
That means...
Um...
She...
Will die.
Maybe by my hands.
After I finish...
Um...
Sucking her soul.
You know?
Soul sucker.
She...
She's...
Will die.
That means...
repair...
It's possible.
I take...
That must be offer.
Counseling...
You know.
I cient some technology.
What do we have in here?
Joss bar them now.
More, more.
More building materials.
Like Slippers.
But Joss?
There isn't a holding flat.
I mean...
Ocelot killed... Master Miller?
Kazuhiro Miller?
What are we supposed to call your cat these days?
How do you know I have a cat?
Oh my gosh, I'm gonna try and give my cat a friend this month.
It was never explicit.
It was explicit.
It was implied.
Yeah, I think it was implied, but it was never like...
Hi, my name is Ocelot and I'm gonna go to that house and I'm gonna murder him in the dark.
No, it was a...
It was a little bit like...
Yeah, we'll see each other again.
Oh, my cat!
That guy is stinky!
Oh my gosh.
He...
Let's see.
Stinky.
He is very stinky, my cat.
He's kind of the worst.
Don't have him!
He's dirty!
He went outside and he rolled in the dirt!
Today!
And all the pollen!
But, oh my gosh, it was kind of crazy.
Because I had gotten my cat shaved...
Uh...
A long time ago now.
I got him shaved because his hair was getting really long and matted and stuff like that.
So it was like forming knots on his chest.
He couldn't reach it.
And to lick it and stuff.
And so...
I shaved him.
And...
After I shaved him...
He was...
He was like super scraggly for the longest time.
Like his hair just was not growing back.
He uh...
He had like some patches grow back.
But like overall his hair was just like...
He looked like an old grandpa.
Did he look like a sphinx cat?
No, because he still had hair growing.
It just was not a lot.
It was like really ugly and terrible.
It was like...
It would like stick up.
It was just so bad.
But when I came back from Japan...
He's...
So much of his hair grew back.
I was like all it took was me leaving.
For him to become...
A regular cat again.
And he's like really soft now.
And I'm like...
I can finally pet you again without feeling disgusting.
I was stressing him out.
Probably because everyday I'm just like...
Grow!
And he's like...
Don't put pressure on me!
Why are you so mean?
I...
I say it lovingly, okay?
I say it lovingly.
He was stressed he would shave him again.
It might have...
It might have actually like...
Really freaked him out.
But I...
I mean...
Having the...
The knots gone was really important.
Because that hurts!
That hurts him!
So...
Yeah...
Hair tonic with the nip.
Thank you!
Hi Mint!
Thank you for the fun stream!
Fun fact, Catnip...
Is in the plant family...
As Mint!
Really!
Is that why you guys are so addicted to me?
Obsessed.
You guys are obsessed with me.
Thank you!
Bye!
The awkward in between phase applies in for other species.
Crazy.
Yeah, he felt like he was like going through a strange puberty.
But he's all good now.
Yeah, yeah.
He's all good now.
It's not...
His hair is not as fluffy as before, but that's fine.
Because if it were, then it would be getting knotted again.
So...
Yeah!
Yeah, yeah.
Maybe we need to add cat ears to the wisp design.
Maybe we need to...
You're a simp.
A simp.
I hope to see you at off-camp Mint!
Would love to show you my Ace Combat merch with you though.
Oh my gosh, yes!
Wait...
Do you have a lot?
It might be a lot to show you.
It might be a lot to bring, right?
Okay.
My...
Do you have a friend in mind?
No.
I do not.
But basically like yesterday, I decided it.
I was like, okay, this month is going to be the month.
I have to get him a friend this month.
I don't know why.
Hmm.
I don't know why, but like it's...
I've been trying to get him a friend for a really long time, so...
Um...
Okay.
I think I'm going to stick with Wisps.
I think I just decided, because I've already said Wisps several times now.
Are you still thinking about this?
Sorry.
I'm an over-thinker.
Okay.
Get out of here.
I like Fantomys too, but...
I have an idea.
Yeah, I have an idea.
Wait, actually, I don't know if I'll have my old settings for memberships.
Greatest anime betrayal.
Yeah, I think wisps are cute.
I can be like, you guys are my little wisps.
It's simple enough that it's fine.
Even though it's like just a regular word, but that's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
Do both?
No, no, no.
That's why I was so conflicted to begin with.
Because I already had multiple stuff.
It's like calling cats.
Oh my gosh, it's perfect!
And we can put cat ears on you guys for real!
Oh my god.
It's perfect!
Now I feel so much better.
My cat's looking here now.
Yeah, it's perfect.
So cute.
For your YouTube kittens.
Come here, my little YouTube kitten.
What is that noise?
What?
Oh my god.
Not safe for work, Takumi.
NSF Wisps.
That's kind of funny too.
I'll think about it.
Hold on.
I just realized I had a message.
Do you know what you're going to make your member icons?
Or do you already have one?
I already have stuff.
I'm hoping that YouTube will...
Has saved my old stuff.
I think I still have it though.
From before.
But I'm hoping that they saved it so that when I turn monetization back on, it's all the same.
Otherwise, it's going to be a little annoying, I think.
I don't trust YouTube.
You know what?
I don't know if I do either.
It could all be wiped.
If that's the case...
Wait, like...
Where even is my...
Okay.
Wait, emotes?
Okay, I have my emotes.
I don't know where my...
I don't know where the membership, like, tier pictures are.
Maybe I don't have those anymore.
Uh oh.
But I still have my emotes.
If you guys want to see them.
They're quite old.
So they're...
They're...
They're quite old.
So they're of, like, my older model.
But I have this one.
Pien.
I have...
This one.
Doya.
Your soup.
Fan name is Wisp.
No ghosticles.
Stop!
Cease.
Doya.
I have this one.
Yeah!
Zinzo.
Bye.
Ama Ibu.
Aipa.
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-dai-i-ga.
D-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da.
I have...
W.
I love you.
I have...
Oh god!
Wait.
I have...
What is that?
A master has...
gone outside.
I don't remember what...
I have...
And I have...
Wait.
This is just...
This is literally...
This is... this is just...
Oh, but opposite.
See?
Some things truly never change.
Can I bite my lip?
Hold on.
I think I can...
Oh, wait.
Hold on.
Wait.
No, I'm just smiling.
I'm just smiling.
Will we get chili mint...
back during Halloween?
Maybe.
If I'm feeling spicy.
Yeah.
Chili mint.
Struggles to bite lip.
I...
I thought I could bite my lip.
No, I'm just smiling.
I'm just smiling.
Oh well.
Yeah.
And then...
I had some more...
that Emory did.
But I don't know where they are.
Maybe they're in a...
hidden folder.
I have almost everything.
So...
I'm working on a newer version.
Wait, no!
Actually...
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Oh, and if anybody wants it...
This is the old one.
My old headband.
There you go.
It's like nothing has changed.
Yay.
Oh, wait.
Hold on.
I can actually...
Oh, gosh.
Oh, my gosh.
I can.
One second.
Here.
Put it on you guys.
You want it on?
I lost my Ahoge because I'm not an idiot.
Let's see.
Oh, wait.
I don't know how to...
Wait.
Oh.
L M N O P Q R...
There, I found it.
It's kind of...
It works a little bit.
We're matching!
We're matching.
Wait.
Maybe if I make it a little bit bigger.
I don't know how to turn it.
Wait.
How can I turn it?
Is there a way to turn it?
I don't know how to turn it.
This works.
I guess.
Yippee!
Slay, sister.
Slay.
Control?
Oh!
I got it.
Thank you.
That actually worked.
There we go!
It's a little bit better.
Aha!
So cute.
Extra Lacy.
Yeah!
And it's got my old ghost.
New ghost.
This is you.
This one right here.
Well, not you exactly.
Is he moving on his own?
Oh!
I think he's actually a ghost.
No, there's a...
Hold on.
I have the wisp.
I have the wisp design.
Still.
Uh...
Hold on.
Please hold!
Please hold.
Wait.
It's somewhere.
Where did I save it?
Why can't I find anything?
Ever.
Why am I so unorganized?
Holding?
Yes.
Hold.
Oh!
Maya, I hope it's okay if I show these.
This is so long ago.
Oh my gosh.
So...
Um... Yes, of course.
Okay, so the left is what I drew.
What kind of outfit I was thinking.
And Maya!
For those who don't know, Maya actually helped come up with the way I look now for my second outfit.
So she actually came up with it.
Uh...
So this right here.
This little guy there is you.
That one right there.
That one.
On my right.
Yeah.
So...
I'm so grateful to Maya because she gave me so many...
I sent her my ugly stupid poopy drawing and she made it look so perfect and cute.
I was so happy.
Needs cat ears stat.
Yeah, we'll add cat ears too.
So you can be...
Yeah.
Um...
She made everything look so perfect and cute.
There were so many designs that here I...
Is it okay if I show...
I don't know if I ever showed these before.
I can't remember to be honest.
Um...
I think I sent.
Feel free to.
Okay.
Thank you.
I love you.
I love you, Maya!
Looking forward to the mint organizes her hard drive stream.
Yeah, for real.
So I gave...
Oh, these two.
Oh, gosh.
The left one is so cringe.
I can't...
Art is so bad.
Oh, God.
Okay, don't look at it.
But she gave me so many variations.
Like, look at all these hair styles.
And dress styles.
And...
Um...
I think I ultimately settled on ten.
As you can tell.
But there's so many.
Um...
I also really like six.
I think it's so cute.
So, uh...
Yeah.
So...
So many.
But definitely, um...
Three.
Three is really cute.
Five is really... Wait, I think five and...
Oh, no.
Five and six are...
Just a little different.
Those are longer.
But I ended up really loving the wavy hair.
So... Yeah.
Six had the old hairstyle.
Uh...
A little.
It's just, uh...
Yeah, it's my old hairstyle.
But with the twin tails on the sides.
Mm-mm.
And...
Uh, it's kind of similar to this one that I drew, too.
Um...
With, like, the little hair sticking out.
And, uh...
Yeah.
One day I'll grow my hair out.
Eventually.
The wavy hair was so last minute.
So I'm glad you liked it the most.
Yeah!
Thank you!
You're a genius, Maya.
You're a genius.
Little hair pokies.
Long hair mint.
Yeah.
Maybe?
Who knows?
Can ghosts even grow longer?
Oh, go- Can ghost hair even grow- Yeah!
Of course!
I just have to...
Um, you know...
I just have to consume more life force.
And then, uh...
Do you wear wigs?
Will you wear wigs?
Yeah.
I just have to consume more life force.
And then, um...
Easy peasy.
Increase the ectoplasm.
Exactly!
Exactly.
So...
Maybe one day.
We'll see.
We shall see.
Us Momo already offered ourselves one so we could do it again.
Getting Momos to sacrifice themselves to summon me?
I was like, wow.
I'm feasting!
My friend Rifticus is- I remember Rifticus is bawling over that there are no ponytails.
Not yet!
Not with that attitude.
Gosh.
Are we tasty?
Momos?
Yeah.
Yeah, the momos were delicious.
You're awesome.
Thank you for the donut.
She hates us.
Ugh.
But yeah.
It still feels very weird to...
be here.
It feels very strange.
But that's okay.
I'll get used to it.
I'm sure.
And hopefully...
Hopefully you guys stick around.
We can all hang out still.
And, you know, have a good time.
And hopefully you guys enjoy the podcast.
And, uh...
I simp!
Oh wait, sorry.
I was reading...
I realized I was reading that last donut.
But I never said it out loud.
I can honestly...
Oh my gosh, thank you for all the donuts!
I can honestly already imagine the fanart of you floating in a moonlit night in the middle of a forest with my cat ears.
Wait, I don't have the cat ears.
You have the cat ears.
Surrounded by dozens of different colored glowing whiskers.
With your own cat ears whiskers.
Oh, with our own cat ears.
Like Slime Rancher.
The Momo-wisp path seems like it works.
Tara gets to eat the body and mint the soul.
Yeah!
It's a parasocial relationship.
Cashing in some life force for twin tails.
Can we get Hime cut twin tails?
Oh my gosh.
Um...
Oh sorry, yes.
Symbiotic relationship.
A paranormal relationship.
Parasitic relationship.
My...
My last outfit was a little...
Was a little...
Uh...
What's the word?
Um...
It was meant to be a Hime cut.
I wonder if that came across.
Kind of.
It was Hime cut but with short hair.
But maybe it didn't come across as a Hime cut.
I'm not sure.
I've saved so much money while you were gone.
Oh no!
Keep saving!
Cat tails is glow sticks.
What?
You're like waving your tails around?
That's kind of crazy.
My last outfit here or in heaven?
Oh!
My last outfit here.
This one.
Jump scare!
It's so funny.
She came out of nowhere!
Oh my god!
Old mint jump scare.
What are you...
What are you doing here?
I thought I killed you.
Why are you here?
What do you want?
What do you want, old mint?
Funny old.
Old!
But yeah.
I don't know.
You can kind of maybe tell that it's a Hime cut.
Maybe.
Mint 1.0, my beloved.
Yeah.
Jump scare.
She's the old mint, but she's from the past.
So doesn't that make you the old mint?
Wait.
She's...
She's the old mint.
Oh.
Wait.
I'm confused.
I heard someone mention my obsession with ponytails.
Ponytail mint win.
I don't know.
I have to first even see if I'm staying.
And get a new outfit then.
If all of that...
One step at a time.
Though if I get a new outfit...
I already have an idea.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Anonymous, thanks for the donation.
Do you still have that?
So I was a French maid who fell in love with the prince and I got killed in the 14th century.
Yeah.
My very extravagant lore.
It's what turned me into a vengeful ghost.
You know?
But...
I don't know.
Maybe I was exaggerating a little bit.
I couldn't possibly get close with a prince.
I don't know.
Is that a light novel?
I was a French maid and I fell in love with a prince but I got... ended up dying in the 14th century.
And now I'm a ghost.
Destined to search the afterlife for all of eternity.
Vengeful?
Yeah.
I'm a vengeful ghost.
I've always have been.
I've always been a yurei.
You are a ghost.
I guess we could put the cat ears on.
If it's for you.
Put your cat ears on.
Meow for me kitten.
Meow.
I may have missed it but what is your cat's name?
Boo-taro.
How do you feel about fan-made or fan-commissioned live 2D or 3D models?
If you want to!
Oh my gosh though.
That's like a lot though, isn't it?
Stinky.
Boo-taro.
That's the first thing that came up in my brain.
Kind of like buta-yaro.
Because he's so stinky.
He's also boo-taro.
Boo-taro.
That's right!
Boo.
Yeah, like boo.
Yeah.
Sir stinks a lot.
Boruto's dad.
Don't worry, the game I want isn't on sale yet.
So I can spare this.
Stop!
Welcome back to the mint phantom from the maidmaid channel.
Thanks Gonzalia!
It's been a while.
Hello.
Play the Ghostbusters game PS3.
Why?
Is it any good?
Is it something you suggest?
Oh my gosh, I can't wait for Zoombinis tomorrow.
Zoombinis was maybe...
So as a kid, I only played like...
a handful of those edumatainment games.
Right?
And one was Zoombinis.
That was my favorite.
And the other one was Freddy Fish and the haunted schoolhouse.
Out of like those like...
Freddy Fish and the...
There's the car.
And then there's like that one kid that looks like Danny Phantom.
But out of like...
that whole...
edumatainment...
cinematic universe...
I only owned that one single...
Freddy Fish haunted...
haunted schoolhouse.
Pajama Sam!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Putt-Putt!
See, I don't know their names because I never owned the games.
I only...
I only knew...
Freddy Fish and only because...
I was interested because it was a game about...
a haunted schoolhouse.
I was like...
He's just like me!
I was like, oh my gosh.
I'm rooting for the ghost, baby.
But um...
Yeah, so...
I would play that...
all the time and I would play...
Zoombinis all the time.
Like, I've played...
I can probably quote more...
Zoombinis than I...
think is healthy.
Welcome back boys!
Thank you for the Hakodate!
Thank you!
Could you get close to a prince if they were...
a cute girl?
Or if they were a...
hot old man?
Hi!
Where?
What?
I was saying...
Like, if I'm a maid, there's not a way...
I'm gonna get close to a prince.
They're so princely, you know?
Like...
Sounds like a webtoon though.
Sounds like a webtoon I might even read.
I used to have the Littlest Creature games.
And the Wishbone one.
I don't know those ones.
I don't know if you're familiar with either...
but Wishbone was my favorite thing.
Wishbone was the dog...
the detective dog, right?
I watched it a little bit.
FLEENS!
You're not...
Well, whatever you are...
MAKE ME A PIZZA!
Oh my gosh, I love the pizza guy.
I love when he goes...
MORE TOPPINGS!
Oh my gosh, I'm gonna be...
I'm gonna be so obnoxious tomorrow.
I'm really sorry.
I'm gonna be so...
awful tomorrow.
I'm gonna be...
Oh my gosh.
Yes, Zoombinis!
So will we.
LET'S GO!
I'm so excited!
I've been wanting to play...
Zoombinis on stream for like...
3 years.
So I'm like...
It's my favorite Ejipitava game from a kid.
From when I was a kid.
I'm so excited.
When I was a Wiiwisp.
Oh my gosh.
Welcome back!
We missed you while you were in heaven.
Oh my gosh!
Beastotboy!
Hello!
Oh my gosh.
Thank you so much.
Yes!
Oh my gosh.
You can play anything now.
I know!
It's actually...
The freedom...
The...
It's kind of overwhelming where I'm just like...
When I was trying to...
When I was thinking of the schedule...
For next week, I was like...
Like I don't...
Maybe I shouldn't just start off...
With all the things that I wanted to play.
But in the end, I kind of...
Did that.
Now what changed?
In heaven, you know...
It's a little bit strict.
Because...
You know, you gotta follow those heavenly rules.
All those...
You know, you gotta be a good, pure soul.
So...
Zoombinis was not good and pure.
Apparently.
More toppings!
Big question.
Do you prefer...
Hot dog or pizza?
Probably pizza.
Yeah, probably pizza.
Oh my gosh.
Zoombinis.
And then the narrator, he's just like...
The Zoombinis...
Are off.
Are going to the...
Promised land.
The Zoombinis...
Why are they going there?
I don't even know.
Fatal Frame Ace Attorney Waiting Room.
Maybe we will play Ace Attorney again.
We can do...
Some of the newer ones.
Oh...
Jeez.
Stop spoiling the game.
Okay.
I'm so sorry.
Oh my gosh.
I can't wait to play Zoombinis.
Isn't it weird that I'm this excited about it?
Isn't it strange that I'm just like...
Let's go!
Children's game!
But I just loved it.
Oh...
Actually, my favorite quote from the pizza guy...
And I quote this almost daily.
Is...
There's something on that I don't like!
Yeah!
Oh my gosh, it's so funny.
Thank you!
Can't wait to see... play older Ace Combat.
Yeah!
I can't wait to play that too!
So much... so much we can do!
Oh my gosh!
And honestly, I'm really super duper excited about the podcast because...
Besides the Metal Gear episode, there is one episode that I think...
May surprise some people and would be like...
So I'm... that's something that we're... that we're cooking so I'm just kind of like...
Actually, I mean we're cooking several things but something in particular that I believe...
We can...
You know, really do so I'm just like...
So...
Super duper excited with the stuff with the podcast.
It's just kind of an exciting time like I'm...
You know, happy to be back and I'm happy to be...
Able to do so much with you guys so...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh...
Yeah, that one, that episode.
I can't even say when it will be out because I have no idea.
We have a sort of plan.
This game sounds super familiar.
Did you know if this game was ever part of a real arcade?
I don't... I don't know.
Also speaking of real arcade, please play Granny in Paradise some day.
It's about an old lady rescuing her cat.
It's 10 out of 10.
I will look into that.
Thank you.
You are a simp.
Welcome back.
Thank you.
Ghostbusters PS3 360 game is really good.
And has all four original Ghostbusters actors reunited for one last time.
No way.
Really?
So after Ghostbusters 2, it's basically Ghostbusters 3 before we actually got more Ghostbusters.
What?
Wait, that's actually so awesome.
It's really good?
Hymen, how is it going?
I'm good.
Thanks for stopping by.
Have you played Devil May Cry before?
I haven't.
We can play that too.
Minta, I don't mean to alarm you but I'm starting to worry that Snake isn't going to fight his way out of the jungle.
Part of me is like worried.
What if it like...
You know how like if you leave a screen on for so long like that image will burn into the screen?
I'm like concerned about that a little.
I really wanted to get to like the...
I really...
Oh, we got forked again.
I really wanted to get to the...
Oh my god, we got...
What is this?
Again.
Wow, both in a row.
Did you see my hand?
No, you didn't.
You saw nothing.
Anyway.
Shut up Sokolove.
This isn't about you.
She manifest this because I think I...
I think I got...
I think I got some energy from Zoombinis.
So I was able to, you know, partially...
have a physical fight.
What is it called?
Oh my gosh, I don't even know my own ghost terminology.
Yeah, corporeal.
An apparition.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
How do I get back to demo mode?
Oh, I think I know why.
It's because I have all these credits.
I have to get rid of the credits first, but I'm like stuck at 50.
I see now.
I moved all my stuff around.
I'll just do stuff while we're talking.
Don't mind the background.
What the?
Again?
Okay, hold on.
Maybe we can beat this one this time.
Maybe we can beat... Maybe I can beat this one this time.
Nice!
What are the
chances of getting that?
I think I'm stuck on credits forever.
I think the game just said, yeah, you know what?
You will get unlimited money.
You don't have to pay.
Can you imagine if this happened in the actual thing?
Like in the actual arcade, if you just could play forever?
She's so good.
Wait, did I?
Oh, come on.
What are the odds of getting that?
If it's 50-50, I'm gonna pull my hair out.
It can't be 50-50.
It has to be more, right?
Look at him go.
Oh.
Sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I screamed.
Now we have hints.
Now we have hints on how to beat Ocelot.
Are you kidding me?
Now there's hints?
Sorry, guys.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't think I was going to win.
I didn't mean to hurt your ears.
I'm so sorry.
Wait, we're back at Ocelot, though.
Oh my god, wait.
I can
only, like, understand a little bit.
I think they want me to continue.
Advantage.
Okay, yeah, the rush.
Chuuu, thank you!
Audio doko?
Oh, I turned it down.
There we go.
Is that better?
Great!
Safe?
What is happening?
What is going on?
I have a safety zone now?
Oh my god.
What is happening?
Oh, they're getting a safety zone.
Save data.
So that's what I'm doing while it's, like, retrieving the save data.
I was like, hello?
Am I going to go into the bite?
No way.
Oh my god.
Highway to the safety zone.
We're back where we were before.
This is absolutely insane.
I don't have my stuff set up, so I'm sorry that I keep freezing.
Hold on.
I'm going to, like, go down here so it doesn't look as weird, maybe.
He has less HP.
Yeah!
Oh my gosh.
Okay, guys.
This is... this is... this... this is how we like to stream.
And we have the safety zone!
Nice.
Yes!
You know what?
I will.
Nice.
Oh, that did a good amount.
Wait, my safety zone is going down.
Why is it going down?
Uh-oh.
Do it, Palpatine boys.
Palpatine.
Oh.
It's like he talks a lot.
He's just excited, Snake.
He's just really excited.
Oh my gosh.
Thank you for the Hakodoro!
Damix, thank you!
Glad we have cat ears now.
I think we needed that extra pair of ears.
I'm so sorry, guys.
I feel really bad, for real.
I feel so bad.
Oh, he's shooting!
But because we have the safety zone...
Oh my god.
I don't...
Oh.
I hope we get another rush.
Oh!
Yes!
Oh my god!
Rush, rush, rush!
Oh my god.
Oh my god!
Wait, you guys.
This is... this is...
No way, no way, no way, no way.
Oh, I'm getting my hopes up.
No, no, no.
I'm not gonna get my hopes up.
Oh my god.
Oh my god!
I'm not... I'm not gonna... I'm not gonna... I'm not gonna...
I'm not gonna...
Oh
my god.
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh my god.
Oh my...
Did you see the amount of damage?
Oh, that just did.
Because we're at... we have the advantage.
Okay, we're back to even, though.
Oh my god, this is insane.
Oh my god!
No way!
Another rush!
No,
no, no, no, no.
No way this is happening.
Oh my god!
Ksao, ksao, ksao!
Oh my god, Stank!
Stank, you're killing me!
You are doing it!
Oh my god.
You guys, you guys, you guys!
Oh my god, oh my god.
No way!
Oh my god, I'm gonna cry.
This is so crazy.
Come on, Stank!
Oh, here they come.
The bees.
Oh!
He found us.
Oh my god, thank you for the donation!
Oh my god!
Oh my god.
Awesome!
Oh my god, Stank, thank you for the donation!
You're really back.
I'm out of the country right now, so I can't watch too often, but here's a donation.
Thank you!
It's not as much as I used to do, but it should cover the three years of membership if you would let that continue.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I will do it on my own.
Stank, thank you!
I'm back!
Hisashiburi!
Sorry.
Oh my gosh.
Yeah!
That's what the push... it says to push.
It said push, so I pushed it.
I paused it.
I can't believe we clutched that, you guys.
I cannot believe.
Wait, so now... are we gonna be in the forest?
Or...
Oh!
Oh my god!
Oh
my god!
Oh my god!
We're in a new area!
Oh my god, I'm gonna cry!
We're talking to you!
And she's just... she's just talking!
Streamer Luke, for real.
Oh my god, this is a first.
This is an absolute first for me.
This is an ab... this is an absolute first for me!
Oh my god.
And it's still just as... I still have unlimited credits!
The music is so epic.
Why is it so cool?
We're just walking through the forest.
But it's a different forest!
It's a different forest!
It's a different jungle!
I was here!
Oh, the end!
Oh my god, wait!
Are we going to fight the end?
No way.
Wait, remember how I said... if you were here...
I said earlier at the beginning of the stream, I've never seen the end...
I've never seen his fight before in this.
So I'm like, yo, I wanted to see... oh!
What the... oh!
Nice!
Good job, Snake.
Oh!
What is going on?
What is actually happening?
What is happening?
CQC time?
Yo!
Hold on, let me do this too.
I'm going to end the poll.
Do you think the first part was like the tutorial?
No.
Wait!
Oh?
Oh, come on.
What?
Oh!
Okay.
I didn't get the boss fight, but, you know...
I got 30 Gs!
Let me fight!
Okay, we have to keep fighting these guys.
We have to keep CQC-ing.
And getting so many codec calls.
Thank you!
You're pretty good.
Let me.
Let me fight!
Let me...
Hello, Sakeyn.
Even though I don't like you, I don't like Paramedic either anymore.
I don't like any of these guys anymore, but, you know.
Let me fight.
I want to
throw a gun.
We have an explosion sector.
Very friendly to ghosts.
Let.
Me.
Fight.
Let.
Me.
FIGHT.
We're so good at CQC, you guys.
We're like the best ever.
We've walked so much.
Lookit, we keep getting straight walking.
We're just walking, walking, walking.
We're a walking crew.
I'm bloodthirsty.
And I'm just flipping all these guys.
They never see it.
Never see it coming!
Come on.
Hold on, Perrin.
Oh, oh, I need a tip.
To battle.
Keep going.
She's gotta taste her blood.
Oh.
I did it out of order, but that's okay.
Is it double audio?
Yeah.
Sorry, I do that.
I have a, uh...
So sorry that it's a little distracting.
Oh!
Hello!
Hello, sorrow!
CHANCE!
No.
No, no, no.
No, no.
No, don't put me back here, please.
No, God, please.
Please, God.
God, no.
Oh, okay.
Oh!
I don't know what this means.
So there's, like, things written here on these buttons on the walkie-talkie here.
It says Transsaber is the first one that's green.
The second one is Sensor Sonar, but it's red.
And the third one is Emergency, but it's green.
Oh!
What's going on?
I can't see.
I don't know what it is.
Oh!
Big, big boss time?
No!
Oh, wait, he's saying new things now.
Okay, I think we're still in.
I think we're still good.
God, how long do people just sit here and play this to be able to get to this...
to get this far?
Endless Sokolov.
We just gotta keep getting through the woods.
Back to flipping guys, yeah.
More tips.
Yeah, but, like...
It's like...
Yeah, I get that the...
So it's like...
I get it, but it's just like...
How do I...
It says the tips, like, the colors are...
Like, you'll get the better stuff based on the color, but I'm like, how do I get the colors?
I don't know.
How do I get the...
You know?
Like, they don't...
They act like it's not just pure luck.
And also, this thing is rigged as hell!
I keep getting the same thing over and over again!
Like...
Skill issue.
Yeah, basically.
Oh, now we have the sensor, but we don't have the trans...
Oh, wait, the trans...
The trans saver is blinking.
I dropped it.
That's interesting.
I don't know why it's blinking like that.
But now!
He just said that...
Oh!
Now we have the sensor, too.
Oh, cool.
Thank you!
I usually just lurk, but I can't stay long, so when I wish you an amazing day, thank you for being a fantastic person and for the amazing time watching your stream.
Your...
Your name is so crazy.
S-L-I-D-3-3-F-E-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V-V.
Thank you!
Fox.
Fox!
Well, I wonder if the trans saver goes red when we're using the codec.
Uh-huh-huh-huh!
Uh, baby!
Okay, please.
All right, snake.
Okay,
keep going.
What the...?
What the...
Oh, look!
Gotta head to bed.
Good night!
Don't worry.
I just kinda wanna see if we can get to the bomb spam.
If I lose the next one, then we'll call it quits.
You know?
I just wanna try one more time.
What the hell is this?
It's the actual game!
It's the actual game cutscene!
Oh my god!
Pause!
Win!
Can't believe you used your ghost skills to grab a hold of luck!
This is... oh my god, the music?
Did you know there's actually a song?
There's a soundtrack for the Pachislot.
So, uh...
If you like any of the versions of these songs, you can actually get this CD for it.
I don't own it yet.
But after this song... oh!
It's so good!
Maybe I'll get it.
Okay, so Big Boss Time is 8 out of 30.
Okay.
That's what it says.
Yay.
Oh my god.
Remember the Alago!
This is so ISO.
I don't know what's going on, to be honest, but it's kind of fun to see the scenes.
Yo!
This is so ISO.
I'm so into this now.
Safety Zone!
Big payout.
Big money, baby!
What are you doing?
Don't be so... crazy!
It's interesting that... these scenes are from... I guess they just didn't... have... maybe... I don't know what's the timing.
They... didn't get to...
Fox Engine.
Interesting.
Okay, we only have three more.
Oh.
Thank you!
I have my...
My Hidari from Migi memorized now.
Thanks.
Thanks for the Nihongo Jozu.
Nihongo Jozu, listen!
Yeah!
Me, there you go!
And don't forget the Manaka.
Manaka, in the middle.
I didn't think anyone would get this far.
Me neither!
Oh my gosh, last?
Oh my...
Oh my gosh, look at them!
They look so good!
Oh my god!
Look at them!
They look so amazing!
Oh, I've never seen this visual before!
I've never seen this visual before!
Oh my gosh!
Oh my gosh.
See the whole, like, codex set up on it?
Like, this is so cool!
Oh my gosh!
I've never seen this visual before.
Yo, they look so cute together.
Wow!
Oh my god!
You can't see, but the exclamation point on the side here is also lighting up rainbow.
Second movement!
Oh my god!
Wait, this is also...
Oh my, you guys!
No way!
But also, why is this also...
From the... this is also original cutscene!
I thought I was under the impression that the whole thing was Fox Engine.
Solid time?
Wait, what is this saying at the bottom here?
Oh my gosh, that's my favorite part about Metal Gear Solid when he says, It's solid time!
Do you guys know this song?
What is this song?
Oh, sorry.
But I was under the impression that everything was Fox Engine made, so...
Oh my gosh.
This is the most unexpected development imaginable at the end of this stream.
No, this doesn't sound like Donna Burke.
This is amazing!
Why is this so...
Okay, I'm definitely buying the soundtrack now.
I feel like crying!
It was so beautiful!
It's so beautiful!
Oh, we can do it again.
Because we still have...
We have 40 out of 60.
This song goes hard!
It does!
I did not expect this to happen at all.
I'm so shocked.
This is so... I'm so happy this happens for the first time on stream.
I can't believe.
Oh my god.
Sorry.
I feel like there might be people who will watch this just wanting to know more about the patchy slot.
And will just hear my obnoxious, like, screeching.
My Banshee screeching.
And my annoying commentary.
Scissors!
Okay, I'm gonna be quiet so we can get more of the song.
I love this!
It's so good!
Sasuga Metal Gear.
No matter what kind of Metal Gear it is.
It has amazing music.
Even as a patchy slot.
That's...
I need this song!
Oh my gosh.
Oh my god.
It's just so worth everything.
I'm so thankful for the Dodo.
Don't worry, this is the exact experience of what I was hoping for tonight.
Man.
The most obscure original Metal Gear song.
If...
Correct me if I'm wrong.
Like...
I don't recognize this song.
So...
Oh, it's over.
But if it's...
But if it's a patchy slot exclusive, that's like insane.
Title is become the big boss second movement.
And seems to be a patchy slot original.
No way!
Oh my gosh.
Where are we now?
Sound Forest?
I don't want to stop now.
This is like a cutscene.
Oh my god.
I literally, like...
I put my like...
I gasped and like...
Put my hand over my mouth.
Oh my god.
Oh I just want to hear him say the...
The...
When he...
He says...
Like...
Oh, he's like...
Sunei.
But he say...
Ah...
Sorry, my brain is like...
Let me hear you.
I'm literally melting right now because the way he says the snort, like, ugh, I'm dying right now, I'm sorry, I'm like, actually, oh my god, I can't think, oh my god, the bird!
How does this fight work, though?
This is the same as Ocelots.
I'm sorry, I'm, like, actually losing my mind right now.
Oh my god!
Okay.
Thank you for the donuts, you guys!
Singer's name is apparently Sa... Sa... how do you say that, though?
I don't even know Apache Slot soundtracks were a thing till now, but, like, adding it to your collection, Min, thank you, Pinkerton, thank you!
Watching Min making MGS Apache Slot history with this stream.
Oh, here, here, here.
Hippie!
Oh my
god!
Oh, I get goosebumps every time!
Every time!
Oh my god!
Sorry.
I'm not reading all this.
Wait, I think I actually...
Okay, wait.
Oh, okay.
It's saying that I can, like, okay.
I can, like, pause by pressing push, and I can skip the movies.
We're fine, we're fine.
I don't need it.
Oh, one... okay.
This is just what to read.
It says, like, while you're waiting, read this, or whatever.
We have one more thing to do until we...
until we move on.
Okay.
We're good, we're good, we're good, we're good.
Oh my god!
Oh, he's so leafy!
How do I still have 50 credits?
We're finally at the end fight.
Oh my gosh!
It's the end, guys!
Time to leave!
Also, I noticed that there are two more...
Have you guys seen that there's two more slots?
I wonder if you can fight the boss, and if she's all five.
I wonder.
I wonder, I wonder.
Just skip the pain.
Yeah, that's the funny thing, though, is I've fought the pain before.
But, like, in a... like, it just skips around sometimes.
But the end?
And the fury?
I've never done.
So I'm thinking...
Oh my god!
Watch out, Snake!
You're just standing there!
You're just a sitting dog!
What are you doing there?
Standing man emoji!
You look so...
The bird looks so cute.
Oh my god, your aura's showing up!
Snake, don't just stand there like an idiot!
This guy's so dumb!
Ouch!
Sorry, I...
I was adjusting, and I, like...
You know when you, like...
Ouch!
Like you...
Um, catch your fingernail and, like, lift it up?
Bro is confused.
He's just... Bro is just as stunned as I am.
He's just like, how did I get here?
He was just like, literally an hour ago...
Or two hours ago, I was just... I was just, uh...
Listening to Sokolov, like, repeat the same phrase over and over...
I was walking through the same forest for two hours!
How did I get here?
I don't know how far I wanna go with this.
Because I just noticed the time.
And I've been streaming maybe a little longer than I intended to.
Which is fine, because I'm having so much fun.
Snake T posing the end.
The bottom screen is so cool.
Also, no more mini-Snake.
Yeah, you're right!
He's gone!
Also, for those who haven't seen...
It is one big screen.
So, it just kind of like...
In this part, it just kind of like fades.
You know, it's just like a fade effect.
But it's really cool.
And it's like, one big thing.
Uh-oh.
Wait!
Our safety zone!
Thank you for the...
Oh, sorry.
Thank you for the dodo.
Also, do you own the machine?
I do own this machine, yes.
This is my own personal machine.
So, I don't have to pay...
Oh, okay.
I feel like this fight will take way longer than Ocelot, so...
Maybe...
Maybe we'll die before I...
Before we get to do anything.
Yeah, so I don't have to...
I have like a little button down here.
That gives me unlimited...
Or not unlimited, but I can just press it and give me as many credits as I want.
So, I don't have to spend real money on this.
I already spent enough money to buy it, so...
Oh?
I'm getting really bad luck.
It's really cool hearing Snake talk so much though.
He's asleep!
Come on.
Oh!
Yes!
Searching?
Battle mode?
Oh my god, it's so cool.
This is it.
That's it.
Oh, no.
No!
We had it!
This one's...
This one's tough.
But he's not shooting me either.
But I'm out of the save zone.
Uh-oh.
They gave me the donut!
Imagine dropping a save and coming back two weeks later to see the head defeated, but if Patchy's locked more...
I know, that'd be crazy, right?
Uh-oh.
Oh, Snake, why are you just standing there?
You big old dummy!
No, Snake, please!
Snake!
Uh-oh.
Oh!
Oh, god.
Ugh.
He's so...
He's so dumb sometimes!
I don't think...
Honestly, we might get a save on this, but...
I feel like we're just gonna end up dying.
If we die, though, I wonder if it will take us back to the very beginning or back to, like, this area, you know what I mean?
I don't know.
I wonder... I wonder...
He tanked that.
Oh, again?
So soon?
Snake!
Help me, yo!
Oh my gosh, Snake.
You're not... ooh.
He attacked so soon, we didn't even have a chance...
Oh!
Come on, search!
Search, Snake, search!
Use your eyes!
Thermal goggles!
Thermal goggles, Snake!
Why does he hit if you roll matches, though?
I don't think there's a way to...
Unless you get, like, a perfect... I have no idea.
I wonder if there's, like, a very, very specific...
...match that... like, match-up that you have to get, because...
But it's also rigged!
It's not letting me get...
...anything to avoid it.
Unless it's this one, let's see.
Never mind.
I
saw it.
Lock on, lock on, lock on!
Come on, Snake!
No, no, no, no, no!
Okay.
I can do it!
That does big damage!
More, more, more!
I can do it!
Oof.
Big damage, though.
Uh-oh.
Oh, is this the end for us?
Get it?
Beat it.
Is this it?
Snake.
Oh!
Ssss...
Ah!
You slippery... you slippery snake, you!
Good, good.
Yes, yes, yes, see the footprints!
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Okay, okay, search, search, search, search, search!
It's here, okay.
Oh, no.
We lost him.
It's okay.
Mint's poor ghostly heart.
I'm... my... I think my blood pressure right now is kind of insane.
Because I'm so... like... like... so happy and so...
Like, shocked and so... nervous?
Oh, no.
Snake.
Oh, no!
Snake!
Snaaaake!
It's over.
Okay, here's where we figure out.
Here's where we learn if we start over from the very beginning.
Or... if the game is a little...
If the game is a little, uh...
What's the word?
A little kind to us.
Kojima actually intended this to be a three-week long gambling sequence.
Oh!
Jesus, that... and Vulcan!
I didn't even... for some reason, I didn't even...
consider fighting him either.
It did save!
Yo...
I think we're back at the beginning.
Yep.
We gotta get boss time again, I think.
Okay, are we gonna get forked?
Let's get forked one last time, you guys.
Get forked!
Oh, wait,
no, no, no.
I just wanna go to, like, him walking around again.
Okay, there we go.
Alright.
Alrighty, guys.
Well, that was...
That was an intense run.
That was kind of insane.
That was...
A lot.
So much.
Holy cow!
I did...
I...
I said that I really wanted to see the end battle, and I got to!
And I wanted to show you guys the theater mode, and I got to!
I got to show you guys Ocelot Battle!
And I got to show you how cruel it is, and then I got to show you how we beat it!
Oh my god.
That was so intense.
Secret song 2!
Yes!
The song!
The original Patchy Slot song!
I'm gonna go listen to it after this.
Tomorrow is Zoombinis.
You're a soup!
Thank you!
What insane luck for you to be able to beat Ocelot.
Enter a new area, discover a Patchy Slot exclusive OST, and face the end on your first Patchy Slot stream.
This has been so much fun and I'm happy to see you having tons of fun.
Thank you, man.
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
Oh, hold on.
Let me turn off the echo.
Sorry.
There we go.
I feel so fulfilled right now.
I can't...
How are you supposed to...
Like, okay.
Obviously...
Obviously, like, it's saved.
But...
How are you supposed to, like...
Continue and...
Actually beat it?
I'm so curious about every inner workings of this machine.
There's still so much that I don't know.
It's so fascinating.
So much fun.
What a purchase I made, eh?
What a purchase.
Konami amusement card?
No, there's nowhere to, like...
Tap it.
Not that I can see.
Chuu!
What is this?
Patchy Slot was actually so much fun to see.
Thank you for the stream.
Welcome back.
Thank you!
Chuu!
What's the stream meant?
Will you...
Will you be doing an MGS karaoke?
If so, don't forget to add a new song.
And I...
I would like to do an MGS karaoke.
There's not a ton of songs I can sing, but...
A while back, I made a mint Minecraft skin.
Totally not because I wanted to cope.
Wait, I have a question.
Is it this one?
Oh, that's so tiny.
Like, a while back?
Like, how long while back?
This is from...
October 31st, 2020.
Wow!
Halloween!
Thank you!
It's another one?
Okay.
Just post it in the tag again.
So I can see it.
I want to play Minecraft.
But I'm trying to figure out how...
To...
Because...
I want to maybe play in like a...
I don't know.
In a Minecraft server with maybe like other wisps.
But...
Well, probably memboos.
Like, probably you need to be a memboo to gain access to it.
But Minecraft doesn't let you...
It's part of their like...
Or rather, it's against their rules to play it like under a paywall.
So I wouldn't be able to play Minecraft in members.
So it's kind of like...
I don't know yet.
Play in single player.
I guess we could always do that too.
Yeah.
There is, of course, always that.
Yes, yes, yes.
Don't we own the server?
What server?
The non-exist...
There is no server.
It's completely non-existent.
I have...
I have to...
I have to buy Minecraft.
I have to buy Minecraft first of all.
So...
I got to do that first.
I don't have it yet.
Yeah, yeah.
You're a simp.
Vic Boss.
You're pretty good with this patchy slot.
Thank you.
Mint love.
I really never thought I'd have so much fun watching someone play patchy slot for five hours.
Thanks for the stream and welcome back, Mint.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, thank you.
Really, really appreciate it.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
A server without a nation.
Lots of people have Patreon servers.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know if Matara would be interested in doing a Patreon one.
Because...
First of all...
The Patreon will only be for...
The podcast length... so once the podcast is up, kind of dead server?
That wouldn't be so good.
And so if I am staying longer after the podcast, of course it would be good to have something that I control.
Skin posted on the tag.
Thanks for the skin tag!
Also, you played with the Ryusei Nova in a horror... That is true!
That is true!
I did play once.
Wait, then do I own it?
Wait!
Do I own Minecraft?
That's so true, I did...
I might have Minecraft.
I actually...
Okay, I vaguely remember...
Wait, uh oh.
I might be in trouble though.
I vaguely remember...
Okay, this is all coming back to me right now at this very moment.
I kept getting emails...
In my Mint email being like, Hey, don't forget to migrate your Minecraft over to Microsoft account.
And I was like, Ah!
I'll do that later.
I...
I never did it.
So...
It's gone now?
Wait, but...
But I bought it, so...
If I just remake the account...
Wait...
Wait, so I have to buy Minecraft a third time?
No way!
Okay...
Okay, I'll buy it.
I swear so many people own Minecraft multiple times.
Why?
I bought it though!
I mean, I guess it is my fault.
They did warn me.
They did send me a lot of emails.
Minecraft...
No!
Tag is...
Oh no!
Stop!
No Minecraft funds.
Oh, don't worry.
Thank you!
Chu!
Thank you.
Number servers are fairly common and it would be pretty cool.
I think.
Haha.
Not that I like Minecraft or anything.
You forgot to add an extra haha at the end of that.
Haha.
Hmm...
I feel like by now...
Probably someone's going to be like, Someone took like mint phantom.
So what am I...
I have to come up with a new username.
Haha.
Hmm...
We'll think of something.
Would love a member server.
Yeah, maybe we can do that.
Member server.
But I would play...
Um...
Not a members, obviously.
But normal.
Haha.
Mint phantom FPS VTuber real?
That sounds like a...
I don't know.
That sounds like a name that someone who shits themselves would take, you know?
Haha.
I don't want that kind of image.
True.
Haha.
Anyway.
I had a lot of fun today.
I hope you guys did too.
Thank you so much.
I'm sorry that it took me so long.
Five hours to get to the really exciting bits.
But um...
Haha.
Um...
But I had so much fun.
And uh...
Haha.
I hear seething in the universe.
Do you?
I'm unbothered.
Haha.
Couldn't be me.
Um...
Thank you guys for watching.
And uh...
See you tomorrow for Zoombinis!
Okay.
Otsumito!
Otsumito.
Oh.
You know what?
Actually I realized this um...
Yesterday.
Or not yesterday.
Well yes yesterday.
But like after um...
The karaoke stream.
I think because I went from karaoke.
Or from singing the last song to ending it.
Like you know I used to end my streams...
With playing Bustin.
So...
I don't know.
But...
I'm kind of also afraid of...
Uh...
The content...
Whatever...
Police...
Con...
Uh...
You know...
Haha.
Especially because I still have a strike on my...
On my...
Uh...
Account.
But...
I think maybe...
Maybe I can do it?
I don't know.
I'm kind of afraid of uh...
Yeah the content ID.
Um...
Cause actually my uh...
My Bustin cover is even...
Um...
It doesn't have a strike.
But it is partially blocked according to it.
I don't even know where.
Where is it partially blocked?
Let's see.
Where are you blocked?
It has been partially blocked in some countries and or regions.
Yeah but where?
It doesn't tell me where.
Um...
How old of a block?
Long, long time ago.
And I never got... I never got like... even in the past when I... when I would play Bustin, I never got like content ID.
But I feel like maybe YouTube's stuff has changed a little bit in the past three years.
I think you're good as long as you don't watch another BWC video.
Oh my gosh.
We talked about that, Matara and I, in the latest Patreon... in the next Patreon episode, so...
We looked up some of those spy animals and how terrifying they are.
Just singing acapella?
Okay.
I wonder... I wonder... oh wait, do I still have my instrumental of it?
Maybe somewhere, right?
Maybe somewhere.
Oh, wait.
This is the mix.
Oh!
I do still have it!
I'll just sing it myself!
Can you hear it?
Oh, it's kind of quiet.
Why is it in one ear?
It's like so in one ear.
If there's something strange, sleeping in your bed.
Let me tell you something.
If there's something weird, sleeping in... why is it only in my right ear?
Ow!
Let me tell you something.
Busting makes me feel good.
Busting!
Bustin' bustin' bustin' bustin'
Ever seen things sleepin' in your bed Yeah, yeah, yeah yeah an invisible man Bustin'!
Sleepin' in your bed.
Ow!
Let me tell you something.
Yeah!
Bustin'!
My right ear busting, ear busting, right ear busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting,
busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting,
busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, b Freaky man, baby!
Wait, when does the next part start?
If you're all alone, let me sleep in your bed.
Sleep?
I ain't afraid of no bed.
I think.
An invisible bed!
Freaky ghost bed!
Bustin' and bustin'.
Bustin'
Makes me feel good Yeah!
Yeah!
Bustin' Makes me feel good Feel good Feel good
Bustin' Makes me feel good Feel good
Bustin' Oh, wait, hold on.
I have it on loop.
Okay, thank you guys!
Thank you!
What's Bustin'?
What's Mint?
Have a nice day!
Master and Miss!
Bye bye!
Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin' Bustin'
Oh my god!
Oh, I forgot to tell you guys!
Okay, I have this crazy story!
Okay, hold on.
I'm gonna tell it to you real quick.
Okay, so anyway...
Bustin'