Hello everybody, welcome to I Am Part-Time Worker!
I just noticed the crowbar.
Oh, I thought that was a gun.
No, I think it's the checkout thing.
Part-time maid, no!
Full-time maid.
Part-time worker.
ghost scan gun half-life crowbar yeah hello minty fresh
hello i'm ready to watch part-time Ponti's piece.
That's a throwback.
No way.
Meat cheese fries.
Part-time crowbar.
If it's not a crowbar all the time, what is it the other
half of the time?
If not a crowbar all the time.
Wait, hold on?
Okay, never mind.
A noodle.
Just a bar?
Just a bar.
A bar crow.
A bounty hunter?
Huh?
Anyway, I don't know much about this game.
I've seen like minimal clips from it.
In this game, you're living your grocery dreams.
be able to find out if I, if being a grocer was my calling.
Working at a grocery store, I mean, this is a convene, but
it could have been my calling and I could have maybe lost
out on the opportunity, you know?
I don't know.
So here goes to the maid cafe, please haunt this convene.
Amen.
Oddball boy, thanks for the vibe, gifted.
Ryan was fired last night.
Now he's a part-time cashier.
We'll see for sure.
I could have been a natural.
Did you see me?
You'd see me at the...
Behind the counter.
And I'd just be like...
I was going to say...
You know, in...
It's so funny.
Like, at some stores in Japan, the girls...
The girls, like, take the...
If you think of a nasally voice, crank it, like...
another times 10.
And that's what they sound like.
Famichiki, kudasaai.
Hi!
But like, so if you go, it's really like the trendy kind of
places.
I say like, like, Shibuya 109.
You'll like, go around there and they'll be like, irasai
masai, goan kudasaimasu, like exactly like that.
That's exactly like what they sound like.
How immersive.
So, I don't know why they do it.
I don't know why it's like a...
Why that's like the fashion girly voice.
Anyway, DLC voice.
back anyway let's play there's stories to this ho ho ho
looking forward to your customer service stream today oh
customer Johnson yes you would know customer service
wouldn't you best of luck on dress you know thank you I
don't think I'll still be streaming when she comes out.
But just in case, if anybody plays Blue Archive, if I'm
still streaming when Dress Hina is released on Blue Archive,
please let me know.
And I will.
I will roll for her on stream.
I'm so excited.
We'll do.
Okay, okay, okay.
I got into Blue Archive because of you.
Do you like it?
It's actually such a good story even.
Hyper Miracle.
Hyper Miracle Positive Girl.
Thank you for the time gifted.
Are you part-time workerman?
I don't know what the class of...
I'm a...
I'm a girl boss.
I'm my own boss.
Oh my gosh.
I wonder if there's like VTuber MLMs where I can be like,
Hey girly.
Do you want to become your own boss?
Do you want to work your own hours?
Join my company, obviously.
S-C-A-M?
Oh.
Society can always make it.
No.
Hmm.
I need to work this.
I need to workshop this.
Pyramids?
Pyramids scheme?
No, no, no.
We're in infinity scheme.
Oh, those dentsy!
Thank you for the five gifted.
Thank you so much.
Can I have a karage kun red, please?
Karage kun.
The way you are working, you certainly seem like a one woman
company is
that a good thing you see that oh she no cause getting a
live action series on Amazon Prime yes I did see that
because one of my one of my well she's not an idol anymore
but I really love her her name is Anna Chan she'll be
playing memcho she plays memcho and I remember when Anna she
dyed her hair blonde and I was like what are you doing why
why did you do this and then i was like oh it's for memcho
okay i'm not mad anymore i was like no because she's always
had iconic like black hair bob and it was so oh it's so cute
and then she went blonde and i was like no of course i still
supported her through it but i was secretly a hater
Anonymous mooks?
What's that?
Minto, don't eat all the jellies in the store.
You can't.
Okay, I won't eat all the jellies.
Love you, Minto.
Thanks for the stream today.
Thank you.
Thank you for the super chat.
We would support Minto if you went blonde too.
You wouldn't.
She stops being an idol to pretend to be an idol on Amazon
TV.
Yes.
Shall we get started?
Prologue I am a part-time worker!
Oh.
I like the music so much.
Ipatz!
My name is Ipatz.
I'm just an ordinary civilian.
I recently moved to the city.
Ichigeki.
I heard that it is generally unsafe and that many residents
are a bit...
A little bit confrontational.
Gyal mint.
Mintpatz.
Not to be confused with Mint Pants Today is my first day Of
part-time work I have to go now So I won't be late Day zero
part-time Day one Jobless man The job location Is just past
the downtown core Okay Whoa Whoa I'm headed to work Is this
a horror game secretly?
Okay What the?
Why is running weird?
I'm holding down shift, but nothing's working.
The sensitivity is...
I wonder if I could turn it down.
Oh, there we go.
There we go.
Sushi!
What's...
Is my work down this really spooky place?
I hope not.
Okay, good.
Oh.
Oh, it's bustling.
Okay, hold on.
Let me see if I can turn...
Oh, sensitivity.
Here we go.
Maybe like this much.
Why is there double music?
Oh, that's so much better, I think.
Oh, this is why young people these days.
Damn it, shut up!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Oh, gosh, I'm getting like chill as art vibes from this.
Am I in the red light district?
Oh, oh my god, he's drunk!
I feel great.
Never mind, he's great!
Okay, okay.
He's feeling good.
He's feeling himself.
Oh, Okonomiaki.
I don't know, the last time I had Okonomiaki.
I can't even read that.
Would you recognize the Red Light District?
Um, I've been...
Well, I've accidentally walked into, like, a street.
love hotels once before this guy's hair what is going on oh
it's like he's his hair is alive it's like it's got little
it's made of bugs you know oh my gosh you know those um
Kazuma Kiryu is somewhere around here true oh gosh kabuki
job um it was on accident I swear I swear do you guys know
those like toys that are like it's little magnet pieces that
you move around and like you give little characters beards
and hair and mustaches and stuff like that that's what his
hair looks like to me woolly woolly is that his name not
etched oh gosh this guy is i don't think he needs help at
all like
got oh man whoa oh god I'm in oh god oh man we can see from
his perspective oh man wait hold on
oh man oh man wait why do I have to be like there there we
go oh Man!
Oh, sorry.
Every time I go out of the game.
Every time I...
Okay.
Oh, man.
Oh, that's a Bokonomiyaki around here.
Oh, new person.
Hello, hello, hello.
Wait, are you not from Exit 8?
Or...
Yes, isn't this the guy from Exit 8?
I swear!
But his...
He has hair this time!
Ah!
This place is wild and wait!
Oh, this is the guy from earlier!
Oh, I don't...
He still feels great, though.
Oh my god.
Okay.
I also...
I should get to work.
I should go to work.
He still feels great.
He's living his best life.
Let me know how the audio is, by the way.
If it's okay.
Oh!
Loading.
This is the convenience store where I will start working
part-time.
I have to go say hello to the manager first.
Okay.
This is supposed to be Shinjuku.
Oh!
Do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-dodo-dodo
do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do.
a little messed up.
It's Florida.
Oh, okay.
Um, hello.
Oh, it's you.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Oh, my God.
My coworker is not okay.
Yes, I'll do my best.
No customers are here yet.
So you can take a look inside the convenience store before
you start your work.
When you're ready, take your position.
Okay.
His hair is really greased down.
We're looking around, everybody.
Oh.
We have our hair.
Hair stuff.
Wow.
Toilet paper.
We got, wait.
I think this is actually the brand, like very close to the
brand that I actually wear.
Because they're the only ones that, the pink ones are the
only ones that fit me.
That's so funny.
Adios, okay.
Thank you.
More hair stuff.
Okay.
What magazines do we have?
Cause gal?
Wow.
Okay.
Neko Gumi.
Nero Neko.
I'd buy every one of those.
So cute.
Okay.
Oh, we got manga and everything.
everything too, all right.
Where's the adult section?
Literally, like right in here.
It's where they usually sell Playboy and stuff as well.
Oh!
This is the restroom.
All is well.
I'm getting, I feel like I'm in a Chilla's art game, I'm not
gonna lie.
I'm a little scared that it's gonna turn bad on me.
Coffee.
Snacks.
Oh no, I mean tea.
Hit!
What are these?
Oh!
It's energy!
Jelly!
Um...
I'll take...
What is Akashi's flavor?
Anyway.
Wasabi flavored potato chip.
chips lots of snacks what's these ones oh just health stuff
what's in here oh ice cream oh yeah this is so nice best
zero caro caro bito love that vivicorn thanks for the gifted
okay oh wait what's in here more ice cream nice they're
stocked i'm i'm this is easiest job ever everything is
already so stocked we'll be we'll be fine oh what have we
got bananas apples uh eggy some bento sandovi chi i love
tamago sandal
some onigiri hell yeah My favorite, I don't remember which
place it has, which place it is, but it's a tamago, it's an
egg sandwich with, but, but it also has, um, ham and
cucumber.
It's my favorite thing ever.
I don't remember which one it was.
Maybe it was Family Mart.
Lucky, I think I'm, oh, get into position.
What about the Odin?
Oh, it's just, it's just a big old...
Okay, there's not much go there's I mean there's a lot going
on in there.
It's just wait hold on I'm not ready yet.
I gotta meet my co-worker.
Oh Nina I guess you're the new part-timer I'm done for
today, but it's nice to meet you Yes, nice to meet you too.
They Do they allow mini skirts at work?
Okay Uh It'll be a tough job, but good luck.
Okay.
I like this guy.
I swear, I think this is the same exact layout as the
Combin...
I mean, I know it's like Combin' is like, you know...
Oh, I forgot the back room, too.
Don't smile at me like that.
He looks like a...
He looks like a Ken doll.
Why is one of it...
I think he...
Oh my god, he's just so shiny.
Oh my god.
oh my god he uses the most amount of gel
I'm about to look in here I think this is the exact layout
of the one convenience store um oh was there did I imagine
seeing something over here okay um the chillas art game but
I like I said I know it's like a convenient convenience
stores are pretty similar you know but...
Thank you for your hard work!
Oh my gosh, she just...
Stormed out of there.
Good night!
Thank you for your hard work!
Otsukarishama desu!
I'll leave you to your cashier duties.
Actually, I've got some important things to take care of.
But I have not been trained!
I'm sorry, but you'll have to take care of things on your
own.
But I haven't been...
I'm going to be on my own for my first day?
Don't worry.
It's a simple job.
I'll give you instructions over the phone.
So take it easy.
All right, then.
Please take care of everything.
Oh!
Oh no, manager's eye!
Where are you going though?
Where are you going?
Oh, I must protect it.
Wait, what is he protecting?
What is he protecting?
Huh?
What do you mean by that?
There he goes.
I'm stuck by an invisible wall.
Well, there's stuff out here, too.
Coin lockers.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
How do I answer the following?
How do I, oh.
Chocolate sauce on his head.
Can you hear me?
First, hold the item scanner in your hand.
When the customer brings an item to you, the scanner.
Pretty simple, huh?
Okay, scan.
Nobody's here, though, right?
What's up, Min?
Good luck with the new job.
Hopefully nothing weird happens.
Scan.
Oh.
Oh, okay.
That's how I scan stuff.
Okay.
I, like, lunge it.
Oh, my god!
Every time Min says, did I see something, I remember the egg
in Outer Wilds.
This guy looks normal.
Ping pong.
Oh, my goodness.
You're doing well.
Why am I still on the phone with you?
Working the cash register adds to the store.
is good rating.
Oh, my stocking.
I mean, monitoring work is going well here as well.
Now let's deal with the troublesome customers.
Equip a weapon and beat them up?
That's what it says.
It's not just me.
I get to attack people.
Oh, that's what the crowbar is for.
Who's a troublesome customer?
Wait, who didn't?
Oh, that was me.
Litter!
Any troublesome customers around?
Oh, how are you?
Are you a troublesome customer?
This guy looks like bad news.
This guy looks like some bad news.
I'm being judgmental.
What are you doing?
Are you trying to pick a fight?
Ah!
I'm part-time walker!
Oh!
You're doing well.
I'm breaking my guard.
Letting troublesome customers loiter adds to the store's bad
rating.
Customers are not, in fact, always right.
Oh my gosh, that lucky guy.
Everybody stand in line.
So beat up the troublesome ones.
Oh my gosh.
This game feels so personal.
I'm done.
with my work i'm feeling lazy now let's go out for a drink
is this place not 24 7.
oh just kidding actually i have to go because i got a call
from hq next use your store scan skill you'll be able to see
the movements of all the troublesome customers who are
hidden in seconds what you can't use that it's an essential
skill for convenience store workers mea mea whoa i just
solved the vision some bad news.
This guy looks like bad news.
Get out!
I don't even know what he was going to do.
Oh, he was smoking.
No smoking on the premises!
Looks like you've mastered storage skin.
Now you're a full-fledged convenience store worker.
You've got it from here.
This is actually how it is on the JP language setting.
Oh, thank you.
I think that's the dev.
I'm ready.
Okay.
It's taking some time.
Now we can start work approximately 15 minutes,
approximately 30 minutes, approximately 60 minutes of work.
Wait, is this like real time?
It's like an actual hour or like a 15 minute game?
Yes!
Real time!
Yeah, we'll do the 60 then.
Work until the end of the day.
Okay.
But there were some other question marks things.
Hello!
Oh.
What a peaceful, quiet evening.
You.
Hello, person.
I think I'm just, you know, I think they're fine.
Oh, that person's jazzy.
Hello.
Ooh, they got a nice little trot going on.
Ping pong.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, oh, okay.
I'll pick that up.
Don't worry.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
What are you doing?
Are you...
No loitering.
Oh.
Why is everybody throwing stuff at me?
Oh my gosh.
There's already so many people here.
Okay.
Why are you...
What the?
Where'd the bad people go?
Oh my god.
Stop throwing.
Everybody's rude.
Cone mad.
Bye bye.
Is he actually gonna buy something or hello?
Oh, oh.
Beep.
Yes, yes.
Oh, nice.
Tits.
Oh, this guy...
What do you want?
What are you doing?
Dude, you're not allowed behind here.
Are you being a loiterer?
Where is all the people?
What is that person doing over there?
What are you doing here?
Get out of here!
Oh, maybe he was fine.
Um...
I'm sweeping... Just stand on him so they don't notice, you
know?
Ping-bang!
I like how I scan this, but they don't pay.
Yeah, what are you doing?
What are you getting?
Pink pants, huh?
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
Oh, that guy is walking way too slowly.
Hey!
No slow!
What the?
Who's laughing at me?
Um, I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming!
Okay.
Why?
He was a slow... I don't know.
He was giving me a bad vibe.
Wait, who's laughing at- Wait, we have three people- Why did
you just throw my- Oh my god.
Ah!
I'm part-time Walker!
I'm sorry.
Don't throw your stuff at me, rude!
We still have two sillies around.
Well, oh sorry, I just realized the chat is like...
Oh my god.
This guy over here!
Hi!
I'm part-time Walker!
Why does this look like high guy?
It won't open!
One second.
I'm gonna move you guys over just a little, just a tad.
So you can see our points and stuff.
Yes?
There you go.
That should be better.
My apple!
Hello!
Sorry, sorry for the wait.
Don't worry about it.
That guy looks really sussy.
this piton worker i don't know anymore oh sorry hold a
second what's that get okay hello hello oh just oh why why
do you shrug at me get out of here weirdo no running no
running you're in no running no running in my store people
are stressing me out you guys this is Okay, okay.
Beep.
Thank you.
Pet time worker.
I'm pet time worker.
Yes, 来来来来来。
来来ません。
Oh, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
Are you embarrassed?
Maybe you should buy some water, guy.
All you bought is Chuhai and Cola.
Turn it down just...
Oh, excuse you!
What?
What was that?
Did you just...
Did he just give me a middle finger?
Everybody's so rude to the part-time workers.
They don't know what it's like.
You must work...
I believe everybody should work retail, you know, at least
once.
Oh, it was an okay sign?
Oh, okay.
Hello, hello.
Maybe he was just like, yeah, this is the good stuff.
Maybe they were really impressed with the store.
Uh-oh.
That guy's hair is too yellow.
Did you just go, oh, my bed.
I dropped the thing on the floor.
Hello.
Oh, maybe he's normal.
Do you need hair supplies?
Okay.
Fizzy water.
Okay, you're normal.
Alright, get out of here.
I judged him.
You guys, I misjudged him.
And I should have judged this guy because he threw all of
his stuff at me.
I don't have to, like, restock stuff in this game, right?
Pew!
Oh, there's so many people here.
Whoa!
Hey!
No!
Matt, you picked that up!
Oh, you!
Your thing, it fell in front!
Two more things.
What?
Oh my god, wait, where's the...
Where's the one more thing?
Oh, here.
What?
She's throwing on both sides.
Hello!
No, okay.
Oh!
What will you do for your next trick?
This guy is just trying to rob us!
Look, you say it's heavy, but like, I got it if I screwed
up.
I was able to take care of it with just a crowbar.
This guy is weak.
One more thing.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, my God.
There's a whole line, you guys.
He's dead?
I sure hope so.
Oh.
Oh, what did you do?
Why is everybody like flashing me?
Uh-oh, we have a little crazy cookie person going on.
Where are they?
Cookie person, where are you?
Over there?
No.
Oh, that's not my property.
I don't care about that.
I don't own the parking lot, do I?
What are they doing out there anyway?
Are you eating the dirt?
Earthy?
Why was I right?
Actually, what is wrong with him eating dirt?
That's his prerogative.
Look at this guy.
Teeny weenie here.
He's so small.
Oh, someone's mad at me.
Why are you mad?
Isn't because I took too long?
Eating dirt is illegal.
Oh, this guy.
Hey!
Quick, march.
What a jerk!
I hope you choke on this gum.
Asshole!
Hello.
Thank you.
Oh, oh, he did too.
I called him a teeny-weeny, but...
Short people, am I right?
He's actually so nice!
Have a good day.
What the?
Is it this guy?
Oh.
Oh, maybe not.
Maybe he's just a slow walker.
Who is...
I think I gotta get rid of our dirt eater, you guys.
I think I gotta get rid of the dirt eater.
I'm gonna whack him in the ass.
I am part-time walker.
Woo!
How many points would you give me for that?
Where's the...
Where's the other silly person?
It's not you, are you?
Is it?
It's not this guy, is it?
Rip dirt eater.
Wait, where's the other one?
huh are you stealing from me there's one more item oh here
this guy what are you doing delicious i'm perch i'm wow yeah
oh my gosh oh everybody's really eccentric here another one
Troublemaker.
Have a good day!
Oh, it's a person of... What is...
Whoa, you got a lot of stuff.
Yeah, very good.
Very nice.
Just a normal day.
What is... What's, like, the most... Or, like, like,
what's...
The craziest person you have ever had come into your work
before?
If you, like, worked retail or a restaurant or anywhere.
Thumbs up.
Ah!
this guy's sorry it took so long sorry now we have two crazy
people hey what are you doing over here man sleepy i'm
part-time worker i'm part-time worker wait no that's the guy
walking away oh he's in the back he's in the back
He's outside!
Excuse me!
What are you doing?
Oh, so sitting is a crime now?
This guy's just chilling!
I'm sorry, guy.
Gotta get your toesies.
No, feet out!
I managed a game stop for like a decade before going to
school.
We don't have time for all the stories.
I wish I had a crowbar.
The guy came in right before...
What did it happen?
on price?
Oh my god.
Wait, did you say before a blizzard?
I'm still in a dream.
Dirt, you.
Toes out is a crime.
It is in Japan, actually.
Never wear sandals in Japan.
Oh, you're back!
Oh my god.
Who's laughing at me?
Cookie.
Oh.
Look at me.
Yeah, look at your face!
Nice!
I am part-time worker!
Where is the other person?
What?
How is this a crime?
Oh my god, she's awesome!
This isn't a crime!
She's a nice place to practice!
This isn't- Oh, there's- I am part-time worker!
You guys, our reputation is going down the drain.
Oh, you?
What are you?
What are you doing?
Stop it!
Stop searching!
Oh, oh my god.
Yay.
Oh, oh!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wow!
What?
What your fingers soar?
Oh my god!
Oh,
public!
This store is insane.
This store...
This door is absolutely insane!
Uh-oh, we have a line.
People are going to start getting mad at me.
Ping pong.
I'm telling you, the way this guy is walking, he's going to
mug me.
This guy's about to...
I think this guy's about to...
Oh.
Oh my god.
Wait, wait.
This is an actual crime.
Get out of my...
Anyway, continue scanning.
I was asked for pepperoni, but was, did you say it was
vegan?
I think that lady is causing trouble.
The lady in pink, yeah, we'll get her, we'll get her.
You?
Oh my gosh, you just eat my apples!
Grandma!
This isn't home!
I'm not afraid to hit the elderly!
Okay, whoa, you got a lot of stuff there, buddy.
This is a convenience store, not, you know...
Not your grocery store.
Okay, all is well in the neighborhood.
Rip Grandma.
You know what?
Yeah, Rip Grandma.
She was not cognitively there.
I think she's lived enough life on this earth.
This is not Aeon.
No.
Yeah, thumbs up.
Thumbs up.
Oh, my bad.
I was just...
Oh, my gosh.
That guy is back there.
Drinking my drinks.
Hello.
Hold on.
One moment, please.
So sorry about the blood.
Anyway.
Beep.
Zoro?
That guy.
Yes, yes, everybody's getting noodles.
Please, eat something healthier.
What's wrong with this guy?
Nothing's wrong with this guy.
Okay, maybe something, maybe a little something's wrong with
this guy.
Give him a knuckle sandwich.
I wish I could use my fist.
The crowbar is fine, but...
Sorry, I didn't realize this game would be so intensive.
But I, uh, doesn't Chibi Binto have a crowbar?
You're right!
Uh-oh, we got...
Oh, what?
This is not a crime.
This is a show!
Yeah!
Let her spin!
I'm partying with her!
Where's the other crazy person?
How did I miss that?
Oh, wait.
How am I supposed to...
Wait.
Huh?
Why were they...
Oh my god, he's there!
Wait, how am I supposed to get that other person?
I am part-time walker.
Oh!
Oh my god!
I'm a superhero!
Oh my god.
No!
Get out of my store!
Oh gosh, I don't...
I don't think we have the insurance for this.
Oh, God!
No!
You know what?
It's fine.
Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry, sir.
You've been waiting so patiently.
You've been waiting so...
I don't know where the other person is.
I think it was really far away.
I don't think...
Oh, hello.
Bucket.
Hello.
Why are you mad at me?
Look to your left this guy look at this body oh all he's
doing this is not a crime i am part-time worker so you know
what this place is this place is like so strict this is i
guess typical nihon right hello thank you for waiting thank
you for your patience
Oh no, okay.
You bought a lot of hair.
You bought a lot of hair stuff for someone who's literally
bald.
But okay.
Oh my god!
Was that you?
Get by.
What does that mean?
What does that even mean?
Don't shame him.
Maybe he just likes how it feels on his head, you know?
It's for his friend, obviously.
Wow, the ceiling is not fixed, but...
The rubble has been cleaned up, which is pretty nice.
We have someone around, and I don't know where they are.
Get by!
Like, what does that mean?
Um...
Oh!
No exercising!
I'm part-time Walker!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Is this...
Oh.
Wait, hold on, sir.
Actually, I can't use my scan, so...
Is that the person?
Ew, what's that sound?
Ah!
Hi, Guy, get out of the water!
I'm part-time Walker!
Oh my gosh!
That's stranding!
Hold on, I think it's over here.
I'm rooting for you.
I love you.
Daiski!
I am part-time walker!
Tain, ikido!
It's basically saying like...
Live!
Whoa, wait a second.
I don't think you're supposed to be... They don't know.
How would they know?
They don't know.
I'm part-time worker!
So I did find out...
Oh.
Hey!
You're not a part-time worker.
Welcome!
Get out of my...
door hello excuse me you've been waiting so patiently
i hear other music oh my god they how is this how how was
this neighborhood real i had a video game store had someone
move a ceiling panel to crawl into the store what that's
wild
Wait, the music's kinda beautiful.
Oh my god!
Is that me?
Oh, sorry, sorry.
There's a ghost!
Who's throwing stuff now?
That guy!
Oh my god, okay.
We have...
You guys, we're in trouble.
Hey, hey.
Are
they gonna go make some mochi or something?
Oh my god.
I am part-time worker!
Oh, he's done!
He's out of here!
What?
Thing one or thing two?
I am part-time worker!
This is impressive!
Oh.
Oh!
Oh my god, Hanabi!
It's not the 4th of July!
I'm part-time worker!
Oh.
Oh my god, she haunted our store!
Boo!
Woohoo!
We'll let her go.
She haunted our store!
Don't mind the lights.
It's just our resident ghost.
Okay.
Oh, Komen's back.
Oh, she's also coming back.
I think she likes it here.
If our... If our...
You know what?
Honestly, a place being a...
a haunted spot.
That's like a novelty, you know?
What's going on?
Do I kill them?
Oh, we have an actual Karen now.
Okay, hold on.
Oh, uh, this?
Mem?
It'll bring more, um, it'll bring more customers if they
know that it's like, people will start coming just for the
novelty of it being haunted, you know?
Don't we all wish we could crowbar Karen's?
Oh.
I guess I have to get rid of her, don't I?
It was an honor meeting you.
Why are your eyes when you...
Are you even real?
Oh, whoops.
I tried to scan her.
What?
I'm a ghost!
Oh my god.
You guys, we have too many...
Ah!
I wish I was dead.
We have a guy over here, bench pressing.
What did the robot do?
Uh-oh.
Wait.
Who else do we have?
Being a nuisance around here.
Oh, you!
I am part-time worker.
The...
Are you...
What are you...
What are you doing?
Oh.
Oh, okay.
I'll check you out.
Check you out.
We have three people.
If you bite it, you bought it.
Well, I'll check you out.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, gosh.
We're losing.
We're losing credibility points.
That guy's just grilling on the street.
That's...
That's unsanitary!
We'll get it.
We'll get him.
Hey!
Coming through.
Sam Bridges.
Sam Bridges, I didn't get any deliveries!
The slow-mo into like the fast is so disorienting.
I don't like it very much.
Oh!
Uh...
This person's just laying on the ground.
Oh!
It's the thumbnail!
I'm gonna cool you down.
I am part-time worker.
Oh, my guide.
I'm part-time worker.
Hey, what are you doing back here?
The office work.
Yeah, this is pretty much it, you know.
Oh.
What?
What are you cutting down my tree for?
Spray them with herbicide.
No!
The city needs trees!
I am part-time worker!
Damn.
What are you doing?
I put up a fucking flag!
I can't be mad at him!
I am part-time worker!
She's got a...
a caboose.
Okay, excuse me, Sorry, it took so long.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Hi, thank you.
Hi, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi.
Maybe, what are you, why are you shrugging at me?
You need better, healthier habits, buddy.
I am the booty.
Can you blame me?
Banana flavored?
What were those chips?
Hmm.
Oh my god.
I'll get her in just a second.
Banana chips.
But they were like banana.
I don't think they were banana chips.
I think they were banana flavored chips.
Jackseptic guy.
Lady, I think you need a rest.
Ping pong.
Oh, come on.
Everybody's so rude.
Everybody's so...
Rude, get out of my store.
I'm sure it will get a lot of attention.
I am part-time walker!
Nobody saw that.
Delicious.
I'm part-time walker!
Alright guys.
Oh, where are you going?
You're not allowed to sit at a seat anymore!
What is this?
I'm part-time walker!
This is a dictatorship!
I swear!
You're not allowed to do anything!
Don't push him.
I like our skylight.
Oh, I feel at home in this corner.
Okay.
I don't even know what to say.
You should sit, not sleep.
I guess so.
Uh-oh.
That guy coming through, he's trouble.
That guy is gonna be trouble.
That guy's going to be trouble.
What?
There's a whole car!
Who's driving in?
All he's doing is smoking.
Ah!
How
will I financially recover from this?
Ah!
Oh.
Everybody ignore the construction.
Oh my god.
Ma'am, I will get with you in just one second, ma'am.
There's two of them in a row!
Sleepy!
New door.
Yeah!
Just, it goes perfectly with our skylight, you know?
Hello!
Yes, yes.
Thank you.
Thank you for shopping here.
All your money will go towards our new...
Our new building.
Did that guy just... That guy did not walk through the door.
That guy literally walked through the hole in the wall.
I see him over there.
I'm not gonna let you.
What are you gonna do?
Make mochi or something?
I won't let you, old man.
I am part-time worker.
I won't let you.
Come out.
Oh my god.
I didn't make fun of you.
I'm so sorry.
Oh.
Wait.
Sorry I had the wrong person.
Oh my god.
Is that guy?
bad or not he's just standing there she called me out I'm
sorry I called you a tiny weedy oh there he goes I guess he
didn't have anything you guys I think people are getting
weirder and weirder
we're halfway through I think no standing what are you gonna
do smash my I'm curious what he's about to do, though.
He's walking.
Oh.
What are you about to do?
Don't smash the wall.
Ah!
Now I have a third door.
Oh, uh-oh.
Sorry.
Sorry, so sorry, everybody.
Hi.
Where's your stuff?
Oh, sorry.
You got really impatient.
Hi.
Oh, oh.
Oh.
Where did he come from?
Where did he go?
Cotton eyes.
Joe.
Do you want to drink with that or?
I guess penguins don't have money.
He walks with such swagger.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, okay, good.
I'm glad that the, um, oh, okay.
Have a nice day.
Hello.
Who is being a nuisance?
Is it that old man?
Oh my gosh, old people are such a nuisance.
Oh, bucket.
I know you can't see.
It's not your fault.
Thank you.
Matara, don't listen.
Oh gosh, we're getting docked.
Oh, don't be mad at me.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's my first day.
It's my first day, please.
Oh.
Oh my god!
I'm part-time worker!
Not the Fami Tiki!
Wow!
Hey, hey, hey!
What are we wowing about?
What are you doing?
No running on the premises!
Oh my god.
You do camp!
It's warm.
Shiny days!
It's not the mountains!
Oh my gosh, I can't believe we have a new entrance and
people just use it.
Hello.
Oh, I just watched that guy walk behind there.
What the hell?
I just watched him walk into the back.
These people have no nerve.
Like, no shame.
Nothing.
They're just like...
Just like, yeah, I'm gonna...
No.
Oh, what's the word?
You know when...
Oh.
Is that a Tengu?
It absolutely is.
That's a normal thing.
Oh my gosh, thank you.
Penguin was a manager.
You can see in the employee room.
He was clearing out the experience.
fired product you're right Felix you're right wait does that
mean I would have gotten fired how do I like oh gosh we have
a lot of people okay okay oh oh we're getting we're getting
bonked we're getting bonked excuse me excuse me excuse me oh
no sitting no being in the back rooms oh I was so drunk I
couldn't move at all.
No!
No laying!
I am part-time worker!
Who else is around?
Phew!
Oh.
Oh, wait.
Oh!
This person again!
No having fun!
I am part-time worker!
Okay.
All is well.
Hello, hello.
Oh!
Sorry, sorry.
Sorry, it took so long.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Okay.
Everybody loves this place!
We have so many likes on Facebook!
Ping pong!
I worked at a 7-Eleven before and I can confirm it's pretty
trash working there as a retail- Wait, like...
Japanese 7-Eleven?
Or somewhere else 7-Eleven?
Ping pong!
Ping pong Guy with a backpack Oh!
What is he gonna steal?
We'll get him in a second.
We have so many people to take care of.
Oh, shoot.
What is he gonna steal?
Sand bridges?
Hello!
Wow, that's a lot of junk food you got there.
Okay.
Thank you!
Do you think he's coming back?
I can hear someone walking back there.
Oh!
They really just use the new entrances.
They don't even...
You don't have to judge them too?
No, I'm not judging.
I'm not judging, I'm not judging.
One second!
Canadian 7-Eleven.
I am sadly Canadian.
I'm sorry.
I'll be in Canada.
I'll be in Canada this weekend.
Wait, we have two people?
You are not!
Oh.
What a convenient sensor.
I think I'm...
I saw this guy.
What are you doing?
He's just standing and giving a middle finger.
Yes.
You can't even...
Oh my god.
This is obscene.
This is the worst one yet.
I was just holding up my finger.
Two of them.
Oh my gosh.
We have a long line.
Looks like Ryden's back there.
Hello.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you so much for being patient.
Hi.
Dozo.
Retail workers with crowbars is too powerful.
I feel really powerful.
Wow, we have a long line.
Oh, gosh, you guys.
I'm going to get fired.
They're going to be like, you have not served enough people.
Oh, my gosh.
Hi, hi.
Oh, cookies.
More cookies.
Ice cream.
Okay.
She's having a good night.
Unigiri.
Yuhi.
Hi.
Oji-san.
Oh, I keep forgetting to read the banana chips.
Hi.
Come in, don't stop coming.
So far, everything's very quiet.
What's that guy doing over there?
Also, another guy with a backpack.
What is he gonna steal?
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
What is he gonna steal from us?
Don't jinx it.
I know there's a guy that just walked back.
He's gonna get, he's gonna do something silly.
Hello.
Hi.
Hi!
Okay, next!
Uh-oh.
Time to go be the silly police, everybody.
That's more like what this game is.
We're the silly police.
Where was he?
Where'd he go?
Wait, where'd the backpack man go?
I saw him.
Huh?
Is that him over there?
Glad we have it.
Oh, no?
Huh?
Lady eating?
Oh.
I am Koutang Walker!
Now we have another one.
You!
I don't know where you're off to.
You haven't technically done anything wrong yet, but...
Oh!
Oh my god.
Two of them.
He's putting broccoli on...
I must plant broccoli.
There's dirt on the other side!
Saa!
I am
Perch, I am Walker!
Another silly?
Is it you?
Oh, yep.
I am Perch, I am Walker!
Why would you put broccoli on the seats, though?
Hello, please, uh, one moment.
I have two silly people around.
Oh, you're eating hair products!
Are you outside, or are you in my...
Oh, no, you're outside.
One second.
I'll come get you just a second.
I'll help you in one moment.
Come on!
Go!
Bye!
Wow, they're leaving like, little love notes for me.
Makes me feel so bad.
Hi, I'm so sorry.
Oh, what?
Do we have more silly?
Oh, you!
In front of my face, have you no shame!
I'm a hard time whacker!
Um, let's see, where's our other guy at?
Is it you?
No, you're just slow.
Oh, this guy's whacking the trees!
I'm going to cut down and spray them with herbicide!
Why do you hate the environment?
Minecraft.
Grandma!
Grandma, what are you?
What are you hitting, for real?
Grandma!
What are you?
This is obscene!
Grandma!
Sorry, my depth perception.
My depth perception.
Okay!
Wait, there's one more!
You!
Oh my god.
No.
I'm sorry, lady.
You have six things.
No!
Not the microwave!
I'm part-time worker!
Oh my god.
I just saw that guy up here.
What the?
Get out of here!
I am part-time worker!
Oh my god.
What are you doing?
Where are these guys coming from?
Oh.
He's bench pressing.
Oh, my God.
Vandals everywhere.
Not even.
I can't even.
I can't even poop in peace.
Guy in a speedo goggle in a swimming cap while you were
shopping.
Swimming on the ground aisles.
Wait, no way.
Are you serious?
Are you kidding about that?
Oh, my God.
gosh they don't stop coming wait i think i just saw no i'm
getting bonked but i don't see where they are at all oh hmm
what i am part-time walker oh oh uh did i get her too or on
accident wait what are you doing stop beating
It's really revving up.
Get off your phone!
Double kill.
No carons!
Oh my gosh, they're flipping me off again.
I don't even want to see the second one!
There's just one left.
Oh wait, I think he's in here.
I wonder if they have any underwear.
What?
Perfect!
They want my underwear.
Girl, this lady's been waiting forever.
She's like, I have two things, please.
Please help me.
We have three!
Three silly people.
I wouldn't put my underwear in there.
Oh my gosh.
Four silly people!
Nice ass!
I am pouch and whatever!
Uh...
Oh, everybody's just lingering around.
Sleepy.
Yon, I'm sleepy.
Wake up!
Oh, don't throw your crotch in me.
In me face.
Where was the other one?
I have one left.
Oh, there he is.
Wait.
Oh, I think he's in the back room.
Okay.
I'm part-time worker!
Wait, still one guy?
Oh, you!
I'm part-time worker!
Ah.
Okay.
He was sleepy.
No, he's fine.
I actually helped him sleep, you know?
I helped him sleep.
He'll be sleeping real good now, you know?
Hey!
I just saw that!
I just saw that guy walking to the back.
you bitch come here come here another one where are you at
oh no grilling on the premises peace
and quiet oh my god there's no customers what did that where
What is that guy doing?
I was going to say, there's no customers.
There's no...
What are you doing?
Oh, okay.
You're just leaving.
I got you.
Don't mind the blood in the aisles, everybody.
I've killed everybody.
Where are you going?
Say sorry.
You're only sorry because you got caught.
Earthy.
That's my dinner, too.
No eating my dinner.
Hello, hello, hello.
Sorry for the wait.
Wow, that's a sweet, huh?
Have a fun night.
Is it that lady?
Is she the problem?
Oh, peace!
Peace!
One more.
Oh, oh, oh my god.
Everybody here is insane.
Work on your technique.
Is it you?
All right.
It's hair medicine.
Oh my gosh.
We had a little bit of, we had a moments to rest and that
was it.
Oh my god.
Oh, wrong thing.
Here we go.
Boo!
What are you doing?
What are you about to do?
What are you...
I caught you!
Red-handed.
What are you doing?
Can I get this guy?
Dang.
I'm- I've tasted blood and I want more.
Where are they?
Where's the other?
Time Walker
Wait there's one more Oh my god Nothing like skipping out on
the toilet What does that What does that mean?
Hello sir, thank you for being so patient Thank you Hi Thank
you
Oh my gosh We have a long line now guys Oh Okay, maybe
please learn to put your belongings down more gently so they
don't fall, you know.
Hi!
Okay, nice, Onigiri.
To my left?
Nothing to my left.
We're good.
We have no troublemakers right now.
The guy who is sleeping on the shelves?
Well, he's changed his ways.
You know?
He's changed his ways.
He's mended his issues, you know?
Shift is almost over.
I know, right?
Crazy.
I'm learning the real retail experience.
I've worked retail.
Okay, um...
You tried.
You're currently dancing and spraying hairspray.
Absolutely.
Whoa!
How'd you carry all that?
But this guy is a fun guy.
Oh, okay.
I'm gonna say.
Okay.
Wow.
Peach flavored potato chips.
I'd try it.
Okay.
Yes, sir?
The way he like slid up was so funny.
Do you like the beach?
I just watched that guy trip outside.
Oh, one moment, sir.
I must take care of some riff-raff.
No sitting!
I am part-time worker.
Where?
You?
I'm part-time worker!
I like how he increasingly gets like more and more upset.
Where's the other one though?
Oh, I hate punishing this guy.
You're so awesome!
I support what you do!
I'm part-time worker!
What the?
You dropped your sensor.
Grandma!
Yes?
Ah!
They dropped their sensor.
What's there?
Destroy all robots!
Grandma's a rebel.
Feels just like home.
You'll...
Suit your shade.
Let's do it again.
More?
Oh, where?
Oh, you?
Why does getting rid of that guy spark joy?
I'm part-time worker.
No!
Wait, what's that?
What's that sound?
Stop!
Why are you all so upset?
Oh, oh, oh, inside.
Get out of here!
What were you looking at?
Oh gosh!
Oh my god, everybody's coming out at the end of my shift!
Um, uh, you?
I am part-time worker!
I'm part-time worker!
I'm part-time!
Oh.
Tick-tick!
There's so many people over here.
Wow, this is a popular area.
Dancing on the compute!
Oh, sorry.
Whiplash, for real.
You guys...
He put up a fucking flag!
Well, sorry about that.
I know it was a tough day.
Yeah.
It's true that you have to deal with troublesome customers,
but if you don't like it, that's fine.
You can just beat them up.
Take care of yourself.
By the way, I'm going on vacation.
I mean, a business trip.
Could you take care of the store for a month or so?
Is that in real time?
I'm counting on you, part-timer.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Yeah!
Okay, I'm definitely quitting this job.
I'm part-time.
Wow, it's the best ending ever.
I feel so validated.
Ha!
Aw, I said that guy, his lip color didn't...
Good shopper.
Oh?
Oh, we missed some.
Ordinary people hanging around a convenience store.
A mystery.
Stray, stray person.
Penguin cute.
Voluntary restraints.
Broccoli.
I'll never allow plants.
Reading in bed.
Catfire.
Idiot.
Female ghost.
Woo!
Kick cash.
Safe cracker.
Open muscle.
Do you want to Eat it up, destroy!
A pawn from another store.
I wanted to know if it was extra.
Stuffed toy!
Robbery!
Fireworks!
Leaving a restaurant without paying bill!
Damn flag!
Write jointly.
People who were made fun of on the internet!
Soup!
Fascinating use of hips!
R18!
The strong old man!
Revolution!
Living in a corner.
Dynamic entry.
Superhero.
Huh, I'm stumped.
Live shopkeeper.
Push-up.
Running along a wall.
Cigarette in the restroom.
Uncle Wallbreaker.
Yankee.
The worst brothers.
People who can't open the door.
Bench press.
Sleep.
Drunkard.
Smartphone in the restroom.
Noisy person.
Underwear thief.
Person who keeps peeping films.
Baseball boy one.
Claimer.
Baseball boy two.
Chef.
Shoplifting.
dance warming up exercises person who lost a key a robot
that says the right things taking a break people running
around screaming dumbbell earthy this is a wild Stoplifting.
The end.
So there were a few that we didn't, that we actually didn't
get.
Huh.
Hmm.
Piano Man was good.
I don't, we ended up, I don't, oh wait, well we did kind of
get rid of him.
There were a few that we didn't get.
Should we try again?
Yeah, I was thinking maybe like the 15 minute round.
Let's see.
Oh, let's see.
Hold on.
Picture book.
Living in a corner.
These names are so funny.
Hold on though.
This one.
Bad.
One second.
Oh,
I'm a little...
I'm a little off, but...
Female ghost!
It's me!
It's like the pop-out type.
Oh, yeah, I guess I should fix that too, right?
Once I get...
I'll even...
try to align it as perfectly...
as...
Oh.
Poshibou.
Yay!
Ready for something kind of cool?
Boo!
Now it's the pop-out type for real!
I'm tiny ghost!
Big, big ghost!
Haunted checky.
Oh my gosh!
This is like a checky for real!
Wow!
Oh my gosh!
Okay, how do I go back to normal?
There we go.
Ghost checky.
I love Dam Flag.
That might be my favorite one.
Dam Flag.
See, this one's a mystery.
I also like this one too.
The middle finger one.
Um...
Two...
Three...
Oh, it does say R18.
Oh!
Three...
I think it's just three or four, maybe.
Oh my gosh, we only missed three!
Do you think we could get them maybe in the 15 minutes?
Maybe we should try.
What's my score?
Yay!
What site asking for a friend?
DL site.
Let's try it.
Let's try the 15 minutes and see if we can get the 3.
If not, maybe someday.
Work until the end of the day.
I'm back here.
Gosh.
Feels strange being back here.
Oh.
Wow.
We have all our...
Everything is back...
There's no skylight!
Everything's normal.
Wow.
I'm just a normal, normal worker, you know?
Oh, the teeny weeny.
Little guy.
That's my little guy.
I never made fun of that little guy.
Feels too normal now.
Yeah.
Actually, I am going to make fun of you.
You have no shoes on.
What's wrong with you?
What's that guy doing over there, huh?
I'm nervous about him.
Why is he over there?
Shorking.
Oh, boy.
It's already started.
Oh, wait.
Oh, my God.
Goodbye.
They haven't even given us a second to...
Oh, my God.
Grandma's already getting ready for her casket.
Grandma, you have so much to live for still.
Oh, what do you want?
What are you about to do?
Worn out.
Not on my watch.
Go to sleep.
We have a guy eating dirt and a guy taking out the tree.
Let her die.
Well, we already lost the window.
Hello.
Sorry for taking so long.
You're like really bald.
Like, you just...
This guy looks unnatural.
What are you doing?
Don't do it!
What are you about to do?
So close.
We almost saved it.
What?
You're too close to me.
Oh, my bad.
He was actually a good guy.
He was making me nervous, you guys.
It was his man bun, you know?
It's making me nervous.
I don't know.
Is it her?
Yeah, she's eating my chips.
Oh my gosh.
I'll take care of your stuff in just one moment.
Personal space.
That's what I'm saying.
Oh, it's just a little pile of rubble.
My poor microwave.
Let's hope for some new crazy antics.
Okay, we got our cooking man over here.
Oh, wow, already three?
Fried rice!
Um, uh, where's the other ones?
Oh.
Just people laying down, people chilling.
Is that a crime?
Is it a crime to be chill?
No more microwave lunches.
Grandma, you're not allowed back here.
Yes, but no.
He's just chill like that, you guys.
He's just chill like that.
Thank you.
Hi.
I like the okay, but they're usually, I like the potato one.
ones you know oh there's a lot of people okay um oh where
are they oh they're just oh another another bench oh no this
is the manga reader how can you even read with that mask on
oh wait i i saw them i saw them sitting maybe they were
sitting inside oh gosh not having the back though the wall
destroyed is so inconvenient actually oh look you're right
here no growing mushrooms oh oh he's angry you know what i'm
saying you know sorry sorry sorry please leave ping pong oh
this guy needs to sleep you want some sticks yeah get them
sticks and chalky You want that chalky?
Ping pong Die!
It's an old manga trope.
What?
Growing mushrooms in the corner?
Is it really?
It's not that old, right?
It's not that old of a trope Oh my god!
No flash photography!
Paparazzi!
Paparazzi, paparazzi!
I barely even noticed you there.
Why do you need hairspray fuller?
You're his Oshi?
I'm so fast and efficient, aren't I?
Uh-oh, there comes the robot.
The robot's coming on in.
Cold brew.
There you go.
What the?
Where?
Why is everybody so obsessed with me?
I'm part-time wacker.
That guy looks like he's up to no good.
Oh, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it.
I knew you were up to no good.
He was like stalking around like a creep.
Oh, hello.
If it's so hard, why don't you just stop working?
Oh my god.
Ugh!
Get out of here!
Something's going on around here.
The robot does say right things, though.
It's true.
Isn't that his name, the robot that says right things?
I'm not saying!
Oh my gosh, I just remembered.
I'm going to be in Japan soon.
I'll be able to get...
Hey, why are you looking sussy, huh?
Oh, sorry.
Sorry.
He was, like, looking around, like he was doing something.
I don't know.
I can get jelly, and also I can get tomato ramen.
Uh-oh.
Wait, actually, let's let that guy destroy the back wall.
Not gonna lie.
Where's the other two people?
Oh, uh, not on my watch.
Let me speak to your manager.
Quick march!
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
What is quick march?
Oh, he's angry at me.
Catch up, ramen.
No!
Different.
I'm excited about it.
What do you want?
Oh my god!
She just walked back you with such confidence.
It's actually a It's so good.
There's like a chain that like has tomato ramen.
Who am I missing?
Oh, the guy that is about to break the wall!
Right?
Where'd he go?
Oh, three of them.
Thank you!
Oh, what are you doing?
Let's play baseball.
You, target.
I'm part-time worker!
All I was doing was playing baseball with you, man!
Isn't that what you wanted, man?
Oh my god, the pained look on his face.
The crowbar!
It's just another bat!
It's just... Wow!
Running man!
Ah, why?
Is this guy gonna break the wall or what?
Oh, he's gonna put up his flag.
I put up a fucking flag!
What an idiot.
Oh, piano man.
a song a piano man he's taking his damn time that's what he
is
do i have to get close to him thank you thanks for the back
door oh my god there's just debris everywhere hello excuse
me oh sorry i didn't notice it amongst all the debris you
know But it's that this guy's a good guy.
Stay positive.
You think you can do yoga here?
Uh-oh.
Um.
What do I do with the penguin, you guys?
Oh, broccoli!
No, I don't want to be healthy.
I guess I think I have to take Piano Man out.
Wait, where are you going?
What are you about to do?
He was normal.
Isn't this guy normal too?
He just runs out, doesn't it?
He just stands there and then he runs away.
I like the piano though.
Preemptive strike.
Why was he walking towards the back?
Oh, oh, there he goes.
He ran somewhere.
Thank you.
Oh!
I lose so much.
Oh my goodness.
I didn't even realize.
Oops.
Depth perception.
It's okay.
I'm not going for scoring, everybody.
We're just, uh...
Oh my god.
We're trying to get the new people.
I am part-time walker.
Jojo was plus zero, I think, because there's, like, good
guys, and then there's bad guys.
Like, good, there's good.
What the?
Oh!
What were you doing in there?
Oh, my God.
Wait.
Why do you look so happy?
I am part-time worker.
He looks so satisfied.
What are you doing?
Oh, you're just...
walking never mind no he was in there for a long time depth
perception oh wow so fast oh the flag lost thanks for the
one gifted thank you oh let's play baseball you the ball oh
sorry your head looked like a ball to me where are you going
Hmm, we still have two.
Three.
Go into the garbage!
Have a nice day!
Oh my god, five!
Five!
Anybody in here?
No?
Oh my god.
This guy checking himself out.
This guy doing...
What are you doing?
Oh.
I don't think we got any of the new ones.
I'm surprised your crowbar has no blood on it.
Oh, ah, man.
I don't think we got any new ones.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
with troublesome customers but if you don't like it that's
fine you can just beat them up i will beat them up i will
beat them up hmm jojo what do you mean jojo i am proud same
rapper that one wasn't new unless me beating them up was new
piano man would have been in no we have piano man He was
already listed, wasn't he?
Is there a way to skip this?
Oh, oh, nope.
Oh,
I can't skip the credits.
The R18 guy?
No, we got him.
You have to not bonk the good ones.
Let's see.
This one.
Oh, press Y to close.
Penguin.
There we go.
Penguin cute.
Still three.
Yeah, we still didn't get the new ones.
No piano man.
No, I could have sworn I saw him in here.
Because I didn't take him out before, right?
sorry it's hard to like read chat if you're like telling me
something i'm not really reading chat because it's kind of
one of those games where you're just like running all over
the place you know oh maybe oh maybe i thought he was listed
because uh i saw the people with the blue and red this guy
see this outfit oh you're right oh okay okay okay ignoring
us for a part-time job yeah you bonged both times oh okay
okay okay well i didn't realize that like to uh to get them
listed also that you had to not bong them so that's my bad
that's my bad what was the other ones though this is such an
epic picture a good wallbreaker oh and the jojo might be
good oh yeah so both of them are fine so that's two but
what's the last one i feel like maybe then we've seen all of
them right hmm maybe we've seen all of them if there's one
more maybe i accidentally balked someone that i didn't mean
to the guy blocking you
i said the coolest thing ever in chat earlier too or two
body let's see Are there any other endings?
I don't think so.
I don't think there are.
Seems to be a one ending thing.
Unless you have like zero points.
What?
Can you get negative points, I think?
There's a guy that bathes in the water tank next.
Oh no, I had that one.
I did get that one.
He can't be a good guy, right?
I did get that guy.
He's in here for sure.
I got that guy.
That guy...
That guy I had him earlier.
What else is there?
Beat everyone.
Beat up everyone, Minto.
You can't get negative points.
No way.
We did get him.
Yeah, oh, there he is.
Soup.
Good soup.
I've never seen the R18 guys stay there long enough to
leave.
before he looked so satisfied too as he was leaving he was
just like yeah that was good what a thrill going on going on
those kinds of sites at a convenience store pc that's crazy
the guy that throws the food over the counter oh you think
that the guys that are rude customers you think they count
Because we know the two.
We have what, three that we haven't been able to get?
It's three that we haven't been able to get.
It's Piano Man, Jojo Pose, and...
Maybe the guys that throw the thing?
Okay, let's do another 15 minutes and see what we can get.
The guy who stands next to you uncomfortably.
No, but I...
Don't think I bonged that guy once before.
All right.
Last round.
One more time.
All right.
Teen guy read Ayami Sensei's work.
I don't want to bong him then.
He's a man of culture.
Ju Shimatsu Tencho.
He really is a manager.
Why is it?
Why is it Juimatsu?
Like Osomatsu-san.
Hello!
Ha!
Got your gum?
Already?
What is this guy doing?
What are you doing?
You're the bad guy, right?
He's just like checking his shoes out.
Oh!
Uh...
Is he...
Ah!
You are the bad one!
Oh.
This is new?
Worn out.
No, he's fine.
This guy's fine.
He's just taking... That's what the bench is for!
Oh.
Okay.
Bye.
Bye, Grandpa.
Oh my... There's nothing going on in here!
Nothing's going on in here!
Hi!
I run a well-fed establishment!
Hello, sir.
Wow.
I don't think I've seen that model.
That character model.
Okay, we're...
Oh, uh...
Uh, we're getting a few new things.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
I don't mean to be so close to, you know.
Ping pong!
Okay, thanks for that.
Oh, well-fed?
I meant to say a well-oiled...
You know how like a oiled machine.
Oopsie.
Boop.
That guy didn't take anything, right?
Oh.
Ah!
You're rude!
Quick merch.
Oh.
You guys?
Uh...
Ah!
Look at me!
Oh my god, he just filmed me killing a person!
No witnesses!
I'm partying Walker!
Hello.
Oh my god.
Grandpa.
Grandpa, you have to...
Oh, actually, you're a young guy.
You're a young guy.
Ghosts don't appear on cameras.
They do!
What are you doing?
Are you gonna go eat that dirt?
oh he's gonna whack my tree I'm gonna whack you smoking guy
hey oh he's the flag guy grandpa looking at oh my god oh no
that's not you huh oh oh ping pong
Sometimes you pre-bonk everyone.
Yeah, but sometimes I like to see what they do.
If I...
Also, I don't always recognize who's the bad guys.
Sometimes I like to see what they do.
Ida shimasi.
Sleep forever.
Oh, forever.
Is it him?
Okay.
Wow.
He's really ganky.
Okay.
Donald, thanks for tuning, man.
Thanks.
Oh.
One second.
One moment.
Yeah.
Oh.
Lady!
Pasta!
Who am I missing?
Oh.
Hurry, hurry, that's...
That's property!
That's good property!
Whoa!
Lost thanks to the five!
Gifted!
That guy is definitely dead.
I, like, got right on this neck.
Sorry about the way.
Oh, yeah.
All right, we need JoJo person back, and we need a piano
back.
Ping pong.
The way they apologize, I apologize, it's so funny.
Parkour is very dangerous.
Yeah, I could...
If they get hurt on my property...
They could get mad at me, you know?
They could...
They could sue us.
They could be like, I got hurt on your property.
Even though it's my fault.
I'm gonna sue you.
They could say that.
Lemon Karubito.
What's wrong with you?
Everybody knows Melon Sabo's flavor.
Ah!
I can't hurt you or else I'm going to get a bad score.
I hope you have a prolapse anus, sir.
Anyway, hello.
Beep.
The robot.
Oh, that's the guy with the bat, isn't it?
It's fine, he comes over to me.
He comes up to me.
Hey man.
Oh, there's a guy giving me the finger even!
Hey, chill out.
I'm trying to check out somebody, okay?
Chill out!
I'm part-time worker!
Proportional response.
Of course!
I am part-time worker!
I'm part-time worker!
Oh,
the guy that's gonna destroy the wall.
Yeah!
Oh, flag!
Do it.
I dare you.
Hello!
Sorry for the wait.
One, two, three, four, five.
That's just a guy smoking.
Two, three, oh.
Sorry.
One moment, please.
You delinquent!
Money!
What do you want?
He doesn't even say anything.
What do you mean money?
Like, count the money?
Like, what do you want?
with the money.
Count it.
Um, you know.
Spend it.
Receive it.
Oh.
Oh, this is the guy that's...
You know what?
Why can't I...
Why can't he work here?
Wait, that car.
Isn't that the one that drives into the window, or am I
crazy?
I think it is.
Um.
Let me see, do you have eyebrows?
No eyebrows!
I'm part-time worker!
Let's go take care of this car real quick.
Well, we have a new...
The ghost is back!
Hey, I'm Dragon.
Thanks for the time.
No, no, no, no, no.
Thank you.
Nice.
Staying healthy.
Chonking.
The piano!
And the Jojo!
Okay.
I see the Jojo.
Hello, Jojo.
I'm not gonna...
I'm not gonna bonk you.
You're fine.
You're just standing there.
Oh!
Okay.
crime stay positive
a penny thief i am part-time worker stay positive hello sing
us a song a piano man oh my god oh my god
I don't know where the other...
Our other weirdo is.
Where's the nuisance?
It says we have one nuisance, but I...
Oh, there he is.
Is the evil ghost?
No, she's not doing anything yet.
There we go.
See?
Now she's a nuisance.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Boo.
Oh, yeah.
How'd I walk?
What was under her dress?
Yoga lady's fine, right?
I have to train.
Okay.
Isn't yoga lady alright?
Piantis?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I see him going in there.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh.
Oh, I thought he was going to smoke.
It's only legs, no details.
Like, left for dead two zombies.
I'm part-time worker Oh, starting to ramp up a little bit
Okay, so now Oh, I put up A fucking flag
Good Why is this guy bad?
I don't understand Oh, hey, come on out Shrink!
Nano- he's literally like nanomachines.
Ah, yeah, yeah.
Here's the nanomachines guy.
All right, Senator.
I killed a senator.
Goodbye.
How did I stay?
Oh, my God.
This guy just smoked- Oh, my God.
This guy just smoked- Nanomachines, son.
You're not a superhero!
You're...
outfit is stupid.
Why?
Who wants superhero wears vans?
Oh.
Hey.
Oh my god.
Chill out.
Time worker.
Where are you going?
Oh my god.
Is it him?
No.
We never see the R18 guy doing his business.
You know what?
That's probably for the best, isn't it?
That's the third time we've had him.
And the first time I didn't know what was going on Because
it was all yellow
Yeah A lot of troublesome customers Yeah, yeah Do you want
to?
I don't know I just want to see what he's looking at You
know?
Everybody, let's go to karaoke after this instead I propose
We all instead go to the manga cafe And the karaoke I am pro
team worker!
What if he's still in there?
I mean...
Yeah.
Had an explosive time!
Wait, it's not letting me...
Press Y and... Oh, there we go.
Okay.
Okay, let's see now if we got them.
That hurt to say, doesn't it?
Mint, please.
Okay.
Picture book.
Fool.
Strong old man is so funny.
Hmm.
I'm stomped.
The shirt on this guy is everything about it.
It's so funny.
This game is so silly.
Oh, enigmatic pose!
Yeah, we got it!
Minus two.
Two what?
Or, yo, wait, we had yoga before, didn't we?
Yankee.
Fireworks.
Stuff toy.
So now we'll see if we only have one or not.
Robbery.
Street piano!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, I think we might still have just one then.
Shoplifting, baseball, baseball two.
What does claimer mean?
Oh, wait, we're close to the end.
People running around screaming.
We got him!
He's claiming.
Yay!
We did it!
Yippee!
I don't know what the third one was at all, but...
The last one was the person sitting on the bench.
Oh, was it?
Wait, did I miss him?
I...
Maybe we just never got him before, though, because...
We must have not have gotten him Because there's no way I
would have I don't remember bonking a guy Sitting on a
bench, you know But I also don't remember seeing Oh him
Ordinary person sitting on a chair
Yay we did
it everybody Good job, good job, good job What a fun game
What a fun Um and creative game.
The dev has a good sense of humor.
That was so fun.
I hope you guys enjoyed going to work with me and all that
fun stuff.
Weird game.
Yeah, fun Baka game.
Yeah.
I didn't know so much about it before.
So I now understand.
I now understand.
um hold on i'm looking at some these are some older sorry
for i didn't hear the donos earlier get by also dressina
gotcha fun gawa thank you so much for the dressina wait is
she up not yet right not yet right soon right soon right
soon right not yet right
no not yet Not yet, not yet.
50 more minutes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
In an hour.
Maybe I can talk for 50 minutes.
I can talk for 50 minutes, maybe.
Thank you for the Trishina Gacha fun.
Hopefully I don't have to use it on that.
Try Princess.
you okay barn thank you i wasn't there at the time but the
boss at my first job was taking the trash outside and came
across a guy squatted on top of the commercial size garbage
bin he looked at my boss and calmly said sorry dude i got
the runs postcard signing will you guys let me sign
postcards for real will you guys let me sign postcards for
real yeah while i while i wait for an Okay.
I'm gonna quit the game then.
Hold on, give me one second.
Oh wait, uh, give me one second again.
Give me one second again.
Oh wait, I have no desk.
Where's my desk?
There it is.
Or table rather, not a desk.
manual labor game wait menial actual menial labor keynote
stream quit the game there we go give me one second to pull
up some music and then we can then I can sign stuff while we
wait here I'll actually I'm even going to write a thing at
the bottom um
oh wait uh let me do this ta-da
Um, reassigning postcards until dress hina gotcha.
Oh, music too.
My bad.
My bad, my bad.
Since we went from jazz, let's keep on the jazz run.
Um, there we go.
Sorry, I'm late for work, boss.
No worries.
I'm just docking your pay.
A little bit.
Thanks for the exciting Take Your Whisp to Work Day Mint.
Yeah!
Did you guys ever do that as a kid?
Well, like, the Take Your...
Oh, wait.
Did you ever...
Well, actually, do they...
If you have kids...
Do you have kids?
What if we do?
Do they still do...
take your child to work day so will you be a part-time
worker
i'm too riseless to have kids but i visited my dad at work
fun i think i did that the take your child to work once
before but um my mom and my uh my mom and my dad actually
worked at the same place and it was kind of how do i
describe um It was Like Kind of construction-ish So I didn't
do anything I just sat in the office and like Didn't do
anything Because they were like you can't go in the back
You'll You'll lose a finger Probably Alright let me grab my
My postcards are right down here
I have about maybe like 200 here so I could probably finish
signing this whole well actually maybe a little more than
200 yeah I don't know I don't think I can sign and like oh
gosh I already messed up I don't think I can sign and talk
at the same time it requires too much mental capacity right
because i have to like think about how i do my signature or
else it ends up being i mean i mess up all the time and it
ends up being kind of ugly all the time anyway but if anyone
curious i'm signing patreon a postcard for the patreon i
have this sick um what's the word my my my um ring finger is
like, it's gonna be so strong by the end of this.
It's gonna have the sickest callus.
Like I even, my skin started breaking.
It's okay if mine's ugly, okay.
Talking between signatures.
I've already signed five since I first started.
I've already signed a couple.
He'll be able to fit so many rings on it.
Or none, my, It's gonna be so...
It's gonna be so beefy.
You know?
It's gonna be like, the strongest ring finger to ever exist.
It's my fault, though.
I should have signed these, like, because basically I'm
taking a...
Um...
A few.
I mean, I say a few.
I'm taking about...
2,000 to Matara when I see her.
Well, I say to Matoro.
But I'm passing them off when I see her this weekend at
Otakuton.
I'm saying, okay, put it in your suitcase.
You're a responsive idly-d-d-d-n-l.
I hope it fits.
I basically was just like, don't bring a lot of stuff.
Bring your biggest suitcase.
And, um...
But that's just two months.
And that's including the recent ones that we have to...
that i had to do which was kind of hellish because i was
just like oh my gosh i felt like i just signed all of these
and now i'm having to sign all of them again how much do
postcards weigh well that's why i was gonna bring more but
one i don't think i can sign i was like maybe i'll bring
three months worth but i don't think i can sign that many
and again it's my fault i should
I got these.
I came back from anime expo and I had them.
They had been delivered So I've had them for some time now,
but I was like, huh, I'll get to it Who's your personal
favorite Metal Gear character?
Personally, I love us a lot I also love us us a lot's
forgotten twin brother brother
I thought you weren't signing the replacement ones.
Oh, no.
We signed them.
Or I signed them.
Why?
Did Matara say we weren't going to sign them?
Did I sign all of them for...
Top blue archive characters?
Koharu?
Chiri no...
Hina.
Okay.
you both said it
Kana's your fave Kana's so cool
Kana's really cool I like her also her her attack is really
good basically what she does is she like you target a
character you target like a little I don't know how do I say
a villain and she uh arrest them and then it builds up and
like does a giant explosion and it's so helpful serika my
beloved i always call her azunyan because she looks just
like azunyan from from kaon only only kind of recently did i
like call her start calling her serika
So true.
So true, Bessie.
You're in a safe place.
Safe space.
I love Baselite so much.
They do look alike.
It's just that trope, you know?
The black-haired, twin-tailed and, but also, like, her
uniform, too.
She's got, like, the the little bow tie, the blazer and the
red bow tie, and, you know.
Did you know Ayami Sensei has a character in Blue Archive?
The reason Mint's hands are like that is because her heads
got tired from signing postcards.
No, honestly, I feel like I can sign like my hand doesn't
get so tired.
It's just a matter of speed, you know?
Does she?
Yeah, Shimiko!
Shimiko is Hayami Sensei's but I feel bad I wish she was
more popular of a character I'm pretty sure she's also just
a one star so it's fun seeing you multiple days at a-fives I
don't know why I thought I should do a cart will for you on
Saturday ups I was fine with it I think staff was just like
hey buddy what are you
so funny oh my gosh everybody yeah i should talk about
animate fest huh it was so fun i was at a con i did a
convention appearance this past weekend apparently it was
like their last year or something for the convention which
is pretty crazy but uh i'm it was so funny the amount of
people that were just like i don't really know who you are i
just came to see you I don't know who you are, but in your
bio on the website, it said you liked Metal Gear.
So I was like, what?
Someone came up to me dressed as Snake and was just like, I
found out about you like 30 minutes ago.
Crazy.
If you watch me, thanks.
Cool to see you on the panel.
That's sad.
What that is, it's last year.
Yeah.
I don't know what the dealio is.
but I'm honored to have been part of the last year of a
convention that's been going on for many many years I would
like to go to Texas for real one day I've been trying to you
know I've been doing a lot of events and stuff but I've just
been my main goal is to try and go to as many new places as
I possibly can because not not just for me because you know
some of them are digitally but just because i know not
everybody could go to california four times a year so
i careful i hear they have cowboys there g-ha oh that
signature was not pretty sorry so sorry my signature's
getting meanwhile me stuck on the east coast i i'll be
honest i tried to get um so for like the podcast right some
of our convention appearances was um kind of because
matara's involved it was a v show jo uh trying to help us
out and reaching out to cons and stuff as well and i was
like please more east coast conventions for us but a lot of
them also fall within or fall out of the range of the
podcast so can't really do much about it can't really do a
podcast thing when it is out of you know we end the podcast
in September so um that's kind of why it didn't work out
Oh!
Okay, I'm done with this.
I grabbed little stacks at a time, so done with this little
stack.
Oops, there we go.
Let me grab another little stack.
Sad but understandable.
Yeah.
But also I'd like to go more outside of the US as well.
Just places I've never been before.
Brazilian in shambles.
I don't even know what we're waiting for, to be honest.
I just like spending time with you guys.
Aside from Japan?
What do you mean?
No, I just mean events and stuff.
I just mean events.
But my time's going to Japan.
I mean, I'm going to Japan.
Oh, gosh.
Am I going to Japan next week?
Ah!
I'm going to Japan next week Oh golly I'm going but it's all
for work It's for work you guys It's not Oh gosh Busy busy
No pleasure
But I'm excited because There's some people I'll be meeting.
I asked Ayami Sensei if she wanted to do an off collab.
So we'll probably be doing that.
I'm just saying if there's Mintomito somewhere in Southeast
Asia, I'll probably fly there.
Hey.
Wins, thank you so much for the peek.
Anime Fest was my first con, and you made it a blast.
Shout out to your super fans that showed up.
I got to take fan group photos and say, better for you.
It was an amazing experience.
That's so sweet.
I'm so glad you had fun.
Please don't feel obligated to stream often while you're
there.
I'm going to do my best.
I kind of don't know how the first week will go while I'm
there.
But I definitely know after the first week I'll be free.
Until Annie-sama.
I'm so excited for Annie-sama.
You guys, I'm going to be seeing Ogura Yui.
the first time live oh my gosh i'm so excited oh my gosh if
you don't know ogura yuri is my she's my like say you oh she
i love her so much i've never been able to see her before
i'm so excited oh gosh and dempagumi will be performing and
uh i i got I got tickets for, um, just a, not every day.
But, um, oh my gosh, it's my first Anisama, too.
So I'm very excited.
Very, very, very excited.
Isn't she the VA for Shiroko, too?
She is!
Yes, she's the VA for Shiroko from Blue Archive, which is
why I love Shiroko.
But also, I just like Shiroko's character, too.
came for Shiroko, stayed for everything else, pretty much.
I did all three days of Anisama in 2022, it was fun, but I
fell asleep every day.
Yeah.
Aww.
I don't think I could do more than three days, I'll be
honest.
It's also a lot on just that much noise and stimulation and
everything, like every day, would be it so much the current
time fgo even is scotty getting a holy grail and creating an
endless summer so you're saying i need a holy grail to make
a mint and matara endless summer podcast prb no please at my
suffering don't do this to me why are you making me suffer
why an eternal summer with matara don't do this to me please
plan learn to astral project to see minto at cards i'll try
to come to you i don't know where you are but i first got
exposed to you ui ogura from ui kaori me too actually space
guy right welcome the moment membership thank you oh and
thank you for the 10 gifted thank you so much thank you
thank you yeah i love ui kaori
i love them so much.
I used to do wait, I just arrived back.
Did she say yes?
Oh?
Huh?
What was I going to say?
you know, before I did this maid cafe, I did some maid cafes
at anime conventions.
And so I learned Yui Kaui dances.
My favorite one is puppy love.
Hi.
Say no.
Poppy love.
Papapipi love.
Phantom!
Thanks for the five gifted.
Thank you so much.
Can't wait to see you at Otaku Tan this weekend.
See you there, everybody!
See you, see you there.
Do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, puppy love.
Pop, puppy, love.
What time is it?
Okay, 30 more minutes.
I think I should be able to get through these.
I hope so.
Because I was going to sign these once I finished stream.
just signing them now.
Thanks guys for keeping me company.
I missed Otakutan.
I used to go every year before COVID?
Why don't you go back?
Unless it's like a distance thing or money thing.
I get it.
Oh, but I won't be able to... I won't be able to stream me
polling.
Is that okay?
Do you guys mind?
You'll just hear my reactions.
My disappointment.
You'll hear my disappointment.
For me, it's distance and money.
Other side of country, and I'm broke.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
But other side of country, that means you're West Coast,
right?
That means you get a lot of stuff.
I feel the West Coast gets so much stuff.
The Napping Koala.
Welcome to Mambushab Thakku.
What a koala.
T-Name.
The price of the highest Patreon tier?
I believe it's $25.
And that's what gets you the postcard.
Sorry.
Checking stuff for Otaku-tan, actually.
Meanwhile, us Midwesterners.
I'm sorry, Joshua.
You can still get the postcards?
Well...
You'll get it starting from the, when you join, right?
I know we're late with sending them out, I'm so sorry, but
we're basically doing it like, we're checking each month, so
each month we'll get a batch, you know?
So, um, this one, the one I signed for before was, oh gosh,
April, and then I'm signing for May, and then, you know,
we'll send it out to the May people.
and then
I've only gotten one so far yeah because we've only sent out
one
I think you know had it been not signed it would have gone
out way faster but it's hard to actually have us meet up you
know because
essentially I'm going to be um probably taking a couple
stacks to otakuthan and handing them off to matara and then
her signing her side and then shipping them when she can and
then um the next stack i'm gonna take with me to japan so
i'm gonna be holding on to them for like a whole month until
i see her and then um doing that and then probably the last
batch i'll ship to her after i'm finished signing them
because I guess we met up or rather we didn't meet up as
much as we thought we would and other things other times
like for anime expo we thought we would um well honestly
they didn't come in time for anime expo which was my fault
because I was in charge of ordering them and uh you know I
was yeah but our postcards will have traveled the world
pretty much right I have social anxiety for big gatherings
like conventions.
Maybe I can rope an older brother into going with me to one
somewhere.
It's definitely more fun to have someone with you, right?
Than to go by yourself.
But, you know, if you were to go to a con with other wisps
there.
Like if, say, if you would all go to a con where I'm
guesting and other people were going to come to see me.
I'm sure you would make friends.
Or even other VTuber communities are usually so nice you
know and very welcoming I think come
to South America if I get invited to a place I had someone
at anime fest they came from Mexico and I was like I'll try
and go to a Mexico convention or somewhere I don't know go
Go to Brazil.
This has a great big fan community, as big as her heart.
Like the Grinch.
Her heart grew three sizes that day.
Japan?
Maybe one day.
I'll be big in Japan.
maybe one day purple Helios thanks for the membership thank
you though you know I feel it's like I don't know I always
go back and forth with like
how do I say growing bigger as a content creator so I can
get more opportunities and reach more worldwide and things
like that but
Also, you know, I feel like that kind of mentality is a lot
of pressure.
And I feel quite comfortable where I'm at.
So, Kevin, welcome to membership.
Thank you.
I don't want to become someone who, you know, and obviously
I do think about like, wow, numbers and subscribers and
things like that.
But I don't want to become someone who focuses.
is only on that kind of stuff.
Mint's U.S.
Tour win?
I need to see Mint in Minnesota.
What's in Minnesota?
Cows?
I don't want to see some cows.
Otsumito!
Thanks, Ring!
If you're gonna leave.
20 more minutes.
Oh no, maybe I won't finish this stack before.
Before time.
After the podcast, are you going to Any more sub-tears for
the cafe?
No, I don't think so.
Like, memberships?
Nah.
I am entirely comfortable.
It was nice to meet you at Anime Fest.
Thursday was my first ever meet and greet, and I'm glad to
know I'll never be forgotten for my balls even in front of
everyone.
Working realto has forever changed me.
Thank you, Magic Doodoo Johnson.
I really appreciate it.
Give us higher tiers.
Why, Anthony?
Why do you want higher tiers?
Can there be a membership tier where we watch Nacho Libre
once a month asking for a friend?
Only if...
No.
Yeah.
Yes.
I literally watched it from the Patreon and you missed it,
Raymac.
That's your fault.
Oh my gosh, you made me miss out my signature.
No, it's ugly.
I like making the little ghosty's eyes so derpy.
Came back from a con Sunday, your tricks help a lot.
Really?
Thanks, Solace.
them so happy what what was the most effective okay here's
the post con survey what was most effective konnichiwa
konnichiwa hope the ugly one is sent to me and they're all
ugly don't worry
but sometimes i do um instead of like eyeballs i do winky
eyeballs so uh some people get a special
In fact, this one will be a winky face.
Oh, this one's so cute, actually!
This one's really cute.
Ayami-sensei got it.
Eh?
Thank you, guys!
Oh my god.
Ayami-sensei, I love this.
Teen Girl Squad.
The ugly one!
I had so much fun with Ayami Sensei.
Our panel was so much fun.
Mama, thanks for the five kids!
Thank you!
Thank you.
Hot dog.
Mine has a winky face.
Wait, really?
Victor?
Does it actually?
You got a lucky one then.
You really did.
Did you just say you can't eat Japanese?
Yeah.
I cannot eat the Japanese language.
It's not even Japanese food.
It's the Japanese language.
It does.
Let's go!
Hot dog!
hot dog moment
did Iami get more Baha blast actually both of us were there
digitally so but we want to go back that's why we were just
like oh it's the last year of this convention well hopefully
hopefully another Texas convention will invite us hopefully
minty birch kyle thanks for the hot dog hot dog can my
signature have a freckle um well i don't know if you'll get
it though it's the gotcha who knows which one you'll get
come to san japan if they'll invite if they'll invite me i
have to maybe i do have to become more popular i have to be
more desirable you guys I have to become more desirable My
signature I have a frog What's something What's something I
should draw on this postcard Something silly Hmm Not my
regular signature What's something that I should draw
Something silly This is the real SSR Frogbird
I could draw a drawing I can try drawing Frogbert.
Okay, hold on.
What is a frog?
Oh, here, here, okay.
Okay.
This is a real SSR.
This one's from Frogbert.
I got a reference picture.
I'm drawing it now.
I'll take a picture.
I'll take a picture of it before I...
Before, you know?
Or should we wait and see who...
if someone gets it.
I think Frogbert would write with his left hand, so.
Oh, God.
Writing with my left hand.
What?
I'm going to draw a little fire, too.
Yeah.
It's going to be funny if they don't watch this, they're
going to be like, what the hell?
They're going to be some, like, some Matara fan who barely
knows who I am.
It's going to be a Momo instead.
They're going to be like, what is this?
I really hope someone, someone Canadian gets it.
Oh, gosh.
It's so ominous.
I'm putting it off to the side.
I'll take a picture of it later.
Oh, not knowing Minta.
It's okay.
A lot of people don't know me.
They can't see ghosts.
They don't have a sixth sense.
I'm manifesting it.
Everybody will now be wondering who gets the elusive
frogbert signed postcard.
Every Momo knows you're her stinky wife off.
Blah.
That is a bro moment.
10 minutes.
I think I can get through this little stack.
I'm about halfway through the whole stack as a whole.
Which is, each stack is 250.
yeah I wish you blessed gotcha luckos lady thank you thank
you thank you thank you oh I forgot to change them summer
special this week or today today was the new episode I
wasn't in it because we we wouldn't have had time to record
together since she went to LA and I got stuck in LA.
So, you hate her?
Yeah.
Ten minutes for the server to crash.
Don't say that.
Escape from LA and all.
But I did eventually escape.
did you escape from LA like you hear a snake actually I
should have made more escape from LA jokes but I also
haven't seen escape from LA I've seen escape from New York
maybe we should do a double double feature watch along
member stream double feature escape from New York escape
from LA or I could do it on the patreon i have to do a
patreon stream
my roommate showed me escape from new york a few years back
he doesn't even like mgs i mean it's a good movie you don't
have to like metal gear to like it i think though my
favorite um i mean i do i do like it but i uh what is it
david carpenter I like the thing so much more.
Yeah, Kurt Russell, he's so awesome.
Oh, such a cool actor.
John Carpenter.
What did I say?
Did I say David?
Sorry.
I said David.
Who the hell is Davin?
Spooky doogle.
Welcome to membership.
Thank you.
David.
Sorry.
I just got snake on the brain.
John David Carpenter.
The effects on the thing are just amazing.
I know.
Gosh.
And like the atmosphere.
and everything love it I love it David Carpenter and John
Hader oh god what is this alternative universe I'm getting
Mandela effect what if that was really I was like no guys
it's David Hader and John Carpenter you're like what no it's
always been John Carpenter and wait I mean David Carpenter
and John Hader what are you talking about mint you're going
crazy you're taking your crazy pills Mandela effect
Sometimes Sometimes Mandela effect feels too real though
Like the bear and stain bears Baron stain bears And also
like the one that's like The fruits of the loom I could have
sworn there was a cornucopia But there never was Why does
everybody remember the cornucopia then?
The fruit of the loom gets me so bad I know I know And I
read those bears like every day when I was a kid.
I was obsessed with them bears.
Made mint and mint phantom?
What?
It's always been made mint.
Never mint phantom.
I'm just like, are we crazy?
I don't think I do remember a cornucopia.
The cornucopia was a thing.
It was a knockoff brand.
Oh.
pancake thanks for watching have
a good night thanks for hanging out if you're heading out
thank you so much for hanging out why is it made mint
instead of mint made because i'm i don't know i'm the maid
who is named mint
i just really wanted to hammer in the fact that i was a maid
i guess
Mayoshi is made channel it's so funny because when I get um
when I get spam emails to my email they'll say like like
there's a ridiculous amount of people that call me made mint
rather than like mint phantom but my um but the spam like
it'll be like a spam sponsorship or something and you know
they're very obviously like spam it'll be like we want to
sponsor you for products will you advertise prada on your
things like that i'm like okay this is you know um but uh oh
gosh my signature is getting really sloppy i'm so sorry um
but they always i know most of the time when they're spam
when they put like my full legal name my full youtube legal
name prada phantom
win actually though I got a pretty cool email the other day
of like a PR package that somebody wanted to send that I'm
extremely yeah it's literally space ghost is dear made mint
channel mean to mean to phantom like they do that every time
it's so funny I got I got I don't know if it's I hope it's
legit I I'm like, I don't know if it was legit.
I hope it's legit.
I give it my address.
But, um...
Okay, I just grabbed the other stack.
Five minutes!
Yippee!
I verified.
Or rather, I tried to verify.
I was like, what's their LinkedIn?
And I looked at the website.
But some of them...
Some can be pretty tricky.
Like, some of the spam ones.
So that's how, like, people end up getting, like, hacked and
stuff.
and the the little hold on this thing where is it oh no did
I delete it already the little brick the little brick the
brick mint that I'll be selling the one that I announced
during my anniversary stream I almost thought that one was
spam too I was just like huh what is this oh my gosh my
signature i'm sorry everybody i almost thought it was spam i
was like this isn't real
if it's not english it's spam mint probably no how many
times does it happen oh my gosh every day i get um spam
emails i get more spam emails than i get real offers but
that's okay I hope you have a great day.
I drew an art of you.
Yippee.
Cyber.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for the Super Chat.
Thank you for the art.
Thank you.
Is that my tag?
The funniest one I've ever gotten.
Here, I'll go check my email right now.
Let's see what's in there.
Let's see what's in my email.
Private email.
Pravity, my new.
Whoa, my God.
Matara Khan is spamming my inbox.
I have one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Eight emails from Matara Khan.
It's for stuff like, it's for the, it's for, it's for our
talkathon to add it to my calendar.
But that's so funny.
Let's see.
Oh, I need to respond to that.
Um.
Uh.
I don't know.
I don't know what the funniest one I've ever gotten is.
Hmm.
I don't know.
Crypto.
Oh, I get it.
I get it.
Sometimes like AI collabs, they'll be like, do you want to
promote our AI app?
And I'm like, no!
Leave me alone!
I wanna promote your stinky AI app.
Stinky.
Yeah.
I want Mint to be my GPS assistant boy oh my gosh did you
see someone like put out a uh a a miku voice for ways that's
crazy it maybe will make me start using ways my mom once
used ways it was the first time i had ever seen someone use
it when i was driving with her and it was so annoying i i i
wanted to tear out the middle console i was like shut up
ways is so oh Oh my gosh, I hate it.
It'll be like, you missed that turn.
But that's okay.
And I'm like, shut up.
What are you talking about?
Oh my gosh, they're so annoying.
It's like this stupid toxic positivity thing that just
drives me crazy.
It's so annoying.
Sounds a bit passive aggressive.
It was like, it didn't seem condescending.
can't remember it now because it was like a long time ago
that um that I heard it but it was just like some things
would be like hey just letting you know that you're gonna
want to turn and like five five miles I don't know I'm like
shut up what do you mean wrong way baka would you prefer
regular toxicity no just give it to me straight just give it
to me straight turn in in two minutes or 500 feet or
whatever not minutes what if it was snake's voice or oticon
well that's just unfair of course i wouldn't of course
negative toxicity gps it is yeah be like where the hell are
you going dummy what the hell are you doing idiot you made
the wrong
who taught you to drive yeah what if there was like oh
actually i was gonna say what if there was a gps app that
like you it just told you directions but you didn't know
where you you were going and you just went to a random place
but i was thinking that's kind of like the randomodica right
did you guys ever do that it was like geocaching but not
Randonautica would just Mint Way's voice pack Turn now Just
kidding Me to turn Tish it better Dressina Oh my gosh Oh my
gosh Oh my gosh Oh my gosh Oh my gosh Oh my gosh Oh my gosh
Oh my gosh Oh my gosh She's live Oh wait Wait Wait Wait
wait oh my god oh my gosh also summer swimsuit hoshino
wait but swimsuit hoshino is so cute okay here I go I have
one free tenpool recruit okay here I'm gonna turn here I'm
gonna turn off the music and see it can you hear that Can
you hear that?
Okay.
Oh, I also have some free one recruit tickets too.
Okay, we can hear?
Okay.
Okay, here I go.
I'm using my free temple.
Oh.
I'm drawing a sad face.
Ugh.
Okay, skip.
Okay, I'm gonna use all my free tickets.
So this is an individual one.
Awesome.
You nerd.
What did I get?
Oh, oops.
Oh, it's yellow.
Wow.
ID.
Okay.
Recruit one.
Oop.
Pink!
Blue.
I love drawing the faces.
We need pink.
Kotori.
Recruit again.
Come on, Arona!
Pink!
Blue.
Okay.
by the way, so.
Kotama.
Okay, this is my last single free pull.
Oh, sorry.
Oh.
Oh, it's gold at least.
Hanae.
Okay, back to ten pulls, back to ten pulls.
Okay, second ten pull.
Ink!
Flip!
Blue!
It's the coveted...
It's the coveted nine blue one, one, two star.
Okay, recruit again.
Two!
You guys!
I got two, I got two, I got two, I got two!
Ah, first one!
Yuzu!
That's okay.
Oh, second one!
No, it's not her though.
Wow!
Oh my gosh, I finally got Wakamo though.
Oh my god.
Oh my gosh, sorry.
I finally got Wakamo at least.
Oh, that's okay.
Kind of worse.
Okay.
Third one?
Or fourth?
Fourth ten-pole?
Blue?
I've been winning Wakamo for a while though, so that's good.
Recruit again.
I'm below 20,000 now.
Blue!
Oh gosh, it took all my luck in the, what's it called?
In the free units.
Oh!
It flipped!
Please.
Oh, here we go.
Why can't we see the screen?
Because it's on my phone.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, it's on my phone.
Okay, I'm at 18,000.
Okay, six times.
Six times the charm, baby!
Oh!
Oh, it's actually pink!
Oh my god!
Yo!
Come on!
First one!
Small shun.
I got Rumi.
Rumi.
Okay.
At least it was somebody new.
Out of three, only one of them was new.
That's so rude.
There were three of them!
Okay, I'm at 17,000.
Boo.
Hina, please.
Hina, come home.
Hina, come home!
We're crude again!
Oh, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink,
just one.
That's okay.
It's better than none.
Oh, come on.
Hina come on!
Hina come on, please!
Please!
So I can also pull for swimsuit.
Hina come on!
Small shun.
again
why am I getting here so many times it's only two times but
still pig pig pig oh I dropped my phone in excitement okay
it's on the ninth one here we go shut up Yoshimi
oh come on please please come home here
it is here it is red winter
it's medu but i didn't have her before either so
what is this look man i've gotten what three new how many
how many 10 how many how many i'm at 94 10 pulls but how
many new characters How many three stars have I had?
This is insane!
Oh my gosh.
Okay.
I'm at 13,000 still.
I can do a little bit more.
Why he the white?
Blue.
Yeah, 94 poles.
Oh!
It flipped!
And I got two!
What is happening?
That's... Oh my god.
Oh, please.
He the...
First one?
Wait, who is this?
Oh, I got, um...
Track suit, Haruna.
I didn't have her before, so that's nice.
Please, please.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, one more, one more.
yes on the flipped one oh my gosh it showed up as blue oh my
god oh my god oh my god nice nice nice i might be able to
spark for uh for oh i should know at this rate
We did it!
Yuffie!
Oh, Hina secured.
Spark?
No, I still have to have 100 more pulls.
I don't know.
Should I...
I still have 12,000.
I still have 12,000, but maybe I should save it.
Hoshino swimsuit is really cute, though.
Okay, I'm going to try it once for Hoshino.
for Hoshino.
I'm gonna try once.
Blue.
Wow, I got four.
Four.
Two stars, though.
Maybe, okay, one more.
One more.
Okay, this is it.
For real.
Blue.
Oh, okay, never mind.
Blue Archive.
So, yes!
The banner is 6% right now, worth sparking.
I mean...
Congrats on getting dressed, Hina!
Thanks for sharing your luck, managed to get her in 80
polls.
Wow, thanks for bragging.
Yeah, but I don't want to spend all my gems, you guys.
Did you need anything else from this banner?
I've gotten so many new girls.
Let's see.
Let me count how many new girls I've gotten.
Uh, how many new girls did I get?
Let's see.
Um, uh, oh, uh, where is it?
I got one, Wakamol, Meru, two, Haruna three, Dressina four,
Rumi, five, five girl, five new girls.
And then, oh, I'll keep, oh, no.
You know how it was from the previous banner.
But 5 new girls is really good.
Got Hina and Hoshino after 280 pulls.
Save for Shiroko Terror.
There's no good units until next fest, so you have six
months.
I guess that's true.
Wait, wait.
Isn't Mika coming back soon, though?
I don't have Mika.
I thought Mika was coming back soon.
Oh, she's next fest.
Oh, okay.
All right, let's pull, baby.
Let's keep pulling.
Hoshina!
Blue.
You can borrow my Mika.
I already do Oimo.
Actually, I don't think you have her as your character.
You do?
Oh.
One more!
Next one!
Blue!
I got used to seeing pink so often.
Skip,
skip, skip, skip.
I'm at 7,600.
Alright, next!
I'm drawing a picture.
Full blue.
Oh my god, all three of my two stars are...
Oh gosh, what's her name?
I can't remember her name.
I don't use her.
The red-haired devil girl.
What's her name?
Junka!
Next!
I'm gonna end up using all of them at this rate.
Pink!
I'm gonna end up using all my gems at this point.
Junko's very cute.
Serena.
Simika!
Sensei's daughter.
It doesn't count as a daughter.
I'm so used to VTubers.
Here it is.
Sakura-ko.
Is Dress Hina already out?
Yeah!
I'm at 164 polls.
Got both Hina and Hoshino within 40 rolls.
Stop bragging to me!
Stop bragging!
This is so messed up.
Pink!
Please.
I've been a good sensei.
I do all my dailies.
Oh, it's the second one.
Okay, we can rip off the bandaid.
Oh.
Someone new though.
Oh!
Oh.
I got dengue.
Oh, my bad.
Sorry, dengue.
I don't...
I'm like...
Sorry, I'm like, who?
You guys have 4,000 left.
4,000.
Next one.
Blue.
I'm scared to pull.
You should be.
bath.
This is a blood bath.
Mama-y!
Alright, I can do two more pulls.
This is it.
Don't brag unless you intend to send her money to keep
rolling cowards.
Oh yeah, it does have a pity system, but only after 200
pulls.
So Oh my god, I got the 10, the 9 blue one.
Alright, last one.
Wait, I'll be able to spark for her though.
At this point.
Here it is.
Blue.
And flip.
Nope.
I'm gonna get so many ellips though.
Yippee!
I got so many elves you guys
I can spark for her I have 402 left
Secured Hina and Hoshino in 13 Thank you for your energy
Stop bragging!
Keep pulling for your own pride Thank you Stop bragging Oh
gosh.
Very confused.
Sorry, I'm polling in Blue Archive right now.
It's a special event.
How many did I have saved up?
I had...
20,000.
Maybe 23,000.
Nima...
Polling fun.
Thank you.
How many polls is that?
About 200.
200 of them I want Poshido Should I pull Or should I Should
I buy I got 150 more Because I Since I I pulled so many new
students Now I pulled six new students It's not bad And then
I also From the previous banner I pulled custom So out of,
in the past week I got one, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight.
And then also I got Dress Akko, so nine.
And also Makoto, so ten.
In the past week I got ten new students.
But my luck has always been very bad so I don't have very
many three stars.
You don't deserve summer hoshena.
What are you talking about?
I'm banning you Oimo Buster.
Fuck off.
Fuck you.
Get this out.
Get this bitch out of my chat.
In timeout for 24 hours.
I
hear you're bullshit.
Goodbye, Oimo.
I have.
You don't even understand.
Like, I just got the achievement that was, like, pulled,
have, or have 93 star students.
my luck in this game is shit okay you don't deserve her what
are you talking about i still don't have shiroko regular
shiroko i can claim her i have i have 221 of her elephs but
i'm just waiting for the day i pull her are you free to play
mint ah not oh i do the monthly the monthly package you the
little bit every day and then you also get the extra um the
extra what's it called uh scrimmage tickets and the extra
bounty tickets do you have koharu i had to use a ticket on
her i had to use a ticket on her i didn't have her i can't
believe you killed oi mo good
I know.
What level are you?
I'm only 75, I think?
76?
Oh, nice.
He can't back out on stream.
Hashtag Oimo did nothing wrong.
Also, she showed her BA room yesterday.
It was not as bad as you made it out to be.
You're just an Oimo hater.
What are you talking about?
She had to have added more stuff.
Are you kidding me?
She added more stuff.
added more stuff.
What do you say?
She said that I didn't deserve Zuboroshino.
I spent all my gems.
How much is it for Carrier Boy here?
Oimo said she rolled three, three stars in 200 polls last
fest.
She also said, please forgive me.
It's because I have so few.
It's because I have so few three stars to Get out of here,
Carrier Boy.
Oh.
Oh, gosh.
They're so expensive.
I never looked at these prices before.
Oh, my God.
What if I spent $65?
But I don't get it.
If it makes you feel better, it took me 19-10 rolls for
Summer Hoshino, so I just went ahead and pitied for Hina.
That's basically me right now.
I'm like, maybe I should just, I mean, I've already sparked,
like, I can, I can recruit her without buying.
I can just like, hmm.
The packages are expensive.
$65 for a moment of joy.
It's not joy.
It's disappointment.
It always is!
I have 204 recruitment points.
I can get her right now.
I saved 21 gems and had the pity for Dress, Akko.
No!
But the free pulls!
The free pulls!
I think I'm just...
gonna
even the free pulls didn't save me I'm so sorry how was
anime fest?
A blast!
It's so much fun Safer made me Dory and Momoy Oh
Okay I was gonna spark for Akko since they gave us 100 free
rolls but then she showed up on roll 200 Yo
No not Momoy
Okay, you guys, I'm gonna, I'm just gonna spark for Hoshino.
I'm gonna spark for Hoshino!
I'm pressing the button!
It feels so...
Come here, Sensei, it's really cool here.
Yay!
I got her Yay Hoshi no
Well I have all the units For the fest now Sorry that's
Chido no Imagine you do single pole and she pops up?
Okay, I'll try.
One single pole.
Let's see.
Nope.
Wait, Mary?
What if it flips?
That'd be crazy.
No, I'm just kidding.
Haruka.
How many elves do I have now?
I'm so curious.
Let's see.
Shop.
My eligma.
I have 7,206.
I got Dressina 20.
Shut up, Raybag.
Shut up.
I never spend them ever.
I never spend them.
I hoard everything.
Like for my...
for my um my normal tickets like just the regular currency
thing that um i have 200 million i have 212 million hoarder
oh she yeah i never also i never also use like the uh what's
it called the select you know how you can do that oops i
pressed the wrong thing Did you hear Arona?
Hold on, she'll say my name.
Wait, hold on.
No, Arona, say my name.
Don't embarrass me now.
Never mind.
You heard it?
You heard the Minto Sensei?
She's camera shy.
What's it?
You know, when you can level up your character, I always
just...
the Blu-rays and things, I always just save up for them.
I never use the selectable ones.
So maybe that's why I'm like a little lower leveled and
stuff, but you know, I like to save up everything.
But now I have a dress Hina.
And I can put her right next to swimsuit Hina.
And regular Hina.
Wait, what does she look like when you pick her up?
Wait, hold on.
What does she look like?
Let me just go into a random mission.
Where is she?
Hina.
She's so cute.
Her little...
Irene, welcome to Mamu's show up.
Listening to my ghost Oshi, giggle, and drool.
Lila, Slyha, she picks up.
Marina, Blue Archive.
Blue Archive, please sponsor me.
I'm your targeted audience.
She's so cute.
Look at her go around.
Hold on, my other favorite is Koharu.
Where are you, Koharu?
.
I can't wait to pat her head.
Oh gosh.
Okay, I'm going to go.
Wait.
I'm going to go to the cafe.
Can I summon her?
Oh no.
I don't have any.
I can't invite her yet.
Okay, I'm going to invite.
her and then I'm going to give her I'm going to give her the
big stuff and I'm going to get her recollection and then I'm
going to be so happy
there's a special animation I've seen this special animation
if you use dress Akko and dress Hina at the end I can't wait
for Shiroko Terror maybe then I'll maybe once maybe once I'm
going to put the music back on maybe once Shiroko Terror
comes out if I haven't gotten I don't go by then.
I'll just pull for her.
Or I'll get her, you know.
I pulled Hoshino swimsuit on my second temple.
I'm so happy for you.
I'm going to be, I'm going to a famous hot dog restaurant
this weekend.
I'll make sure to leave you one as an offering.
What kind of toppings do you want?
Onion, onion, onion!
Yeah.
Oh, sounds delicious.
What's a famous hot dog place?
Kifumi dies, kid.
Oh my gosh, Jelly's trying to butt doctor.
Kifumi's pretty cute.
Going to the gym for the first time, I'm like, eight months
tonight, can you possess me and go for me?
No.
If not, can I get some encouraging words instead?
Work, work, work!
Get those gains!
Minto gains!
Ghosty gains!
Your space is ghost.
Ghosty gains, ghosty gains.
Costco is most famous.
Oh, my favorite character in Blue Archive.
I have three.
Chedino, Koharu, and Hina.
Mintogains.
Yeah.
It's a place in New Jersey that does deep-fried hot dogs
called Rippers.
That sounds amazing.
Wow.
Thanks for accompanying me during my part-time job.
I don't work retail, but it was fun hearing you beat
customers of.
It's also my birthday today!
Can I get a happy birthday?
Of course!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday dear suburb guy!
Happy birthday!
luck on the membership and with that i'm going to end the
stream thank you guys for hanging out with me for for all of
all of my polls and everything streamer luck is questionable
but i will see you guys uh tomorrow i have double stream um
one afternoon stream for me and then another um i'll be
streaming on uh on uh well i'll be on i think berry's
channel i think wow swimsuit hoshino's so cute i just got
her too i'm so happy for you at berries yeah yeah i think we
were before we were still trying to decide but anyway
otsumita have a great night good luck with all your gotcha
polls and i will see you guys later Bye bye!
Thank you for hanging out with me!
Thank you, thank you!
Thanks for the one dream!
Thank you!
For the Akasupa earlier, thank you.
I will probably have to use it for Shiroko Terror.
So...
Thank you guys so much!
Bye bye!