Can you hear it okay?
That part sounds a little quiet, you know what I mean?
Yeah?
No?
Stop it.
No audio?
Stop!
I know you're lying!
What do you mean no sound?
Actually?
Wait, what?
Oh, you can't hear the game?
Wait, actually?
Now you can.
Really?
The game is actually silent.
So I'm just laughing to myself?
Quietly?
Huh.
Oh!
I see why.
Okay, hold on.
Restart!
Redo!
Welcome
back!
Master!
Lady!
Say a mint?
Say the line?
Say the line, boss!
For old time's sake.
Kept you waiting, huh?
Oh my gosh!
Oh my gosh, you guys.
Welcome.
Welcome, welcome, welcome to...
The Twin Snakes, baby!
I was gonna say the most controversial...
Metal Gear game, but actually I don't think so.
I don't think it's the most controversial one.
But you know, it is one that...
I think a lot of people are...
I don't know, I think more nowadays it's more like...
What's the word?
It's more...
Beloved by people than it used to be.
I think nowadays more people are like...
Yeah, this game kind of owns.
Because of how crazy it gets.
You know?
I think...
So, for those unaware...
This is a...
Quote unquote...
Remake of Metal Gear Solid.
First game.
Thank you guys for the silver chance!
Thank you!
Gaseous steak.
I have a confession to make.
I've never played Twin Snakes.
I'm a fake fan.
So I'm looking forward to this.
Awesome!
Me too!
It's my first time actually playing it.
I have seen some of the cutscenes.
But not all of them.
So...
Very much looking forward to playing it.
For realsies now.
But it is a...
Remake of Metal Gear Solid 1.
So the first game.
But it is made in the Metal Gear Solid 2 engine.
And so it's gonna look like...
All kind of fancy and new.
And...
And it's...
It's different.
It is.
It's...
It's different.
Alright.
Thank you guys for the silver chance!
Thank you!
Glad you're playing this.
I actually got into VTubers because of this game.
The VTuber had a sultry voice like Sniper Wolf.
But was replaced by a nerdy energetic lady like EE.
What?
What do you...
They were...
What do you mean they were replaced?
The best explanation I've seen is that MGS1 is what really happened.
While Twin Snakes is what Snake tells people happened.
You'll understand.
No, no, no.
That's not my favorite theory.
My favorite theory...
Is that...
Metal Gear Solid...
Okay, so there's several theories, right?
First theory...
Is what you just said.
That Snake is retelling the story.
The second theory...
Is that this is Raiden's VR missions that he went through.
Because, you know, in Metal Gear Solid 2 you learn that he went through VR missions of Shadow Moses to kind of learn how to be like Solid Snake.
The third...
The third theory and my favorite...
And my favorite...
Is that this is Otacon's retelling.
Of Shadow Moses.
And that makes the most sense to me.
I think this...
I think this is Otacon being like...
Oh my gosh.
And then Snake...
He like...
Jumped off the missiles and blew up the Hindy.
It makes entirely...
More sense if you think of it as Otacon being like...
It's literally just like my Japanese anime.
Because he thinks Snake is like a superhero.
It's so great.
Otacon left off in the...
Left in the part where he peed.
What's under special?
Oh, I do also want to say...
This is my first time ever playing on a Gamecube.
I did have a friend when I was a...
When I was a...
A little...
A little ghost.
Who...
Had a Gamecube.
And didn't let me play.
That kid was a jerk.
Um...
I still hold it against him.
I would...
I would sit there like...
Because he was one of my few friends that was in my neighborhood.
And so...
Um...
I would go to his house.
And he would sit and play Animal Crossing.
And I would just watch.
For...
For a long time.
He was always...
Just playing by himself.
Ugh.
Yeah.
Friend in quotes.
But I also just didn't have one growing up.
So...
Um...
And then I...
I don't know.
I just never had an opportunity to play one.
So...
The controller...
The controls are very new to me.
Extremely...
As of...
As of like 30 minutes ago.
And I bought this Gamecube just to play the Twin Snakes.
Um...
But because I have it now, we can play more Gamecube games.
Yippee!
But I bought it literally only for this game.
So...
Um...
Yup.
So...
Yeah.
Um...
What else?
Uh...
Yeah.
So let's...
What is under special?
I'm curious.
Um...
Oh my gosh!
Wait!
There's dog tags!
In this?
Just like in Metal Gear Solid 2?
The briefings are in full 3D?
Oh yes!
Yes!
We will be watching the briefings.
Don't worry.
Because there's one part that I really love.
That Snake does.
There's photo album too.
I don't know what this is.
It looks like a gun.
Previous operations.
Oh my gosh!
Otacon's pee!
Okay.
Let's do the briefings.
I think they're quite long.
Like the original briefings, right?
I'm not sure to be honest.
So...
It's been a long time, Snake.
He's got pants!
I should have known you were behind this, Colonel.
Let me know how the audio is by the way.
Snake.
Let me know how you feel.
Okay.
I can't remember what I want to hear in this.
I'm just going to leave you to your decision.
Thanks, bro.
And let's go back to the briefings.
That's what I'm saying.
Damn.
I always wanted a gun.
That was a good one.
And why are you still here?
I was in the army with you.
That was a good one.
We had a good time.
I think we can always join the army together.
I think so.
Good.
I'm glad we're back.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Thank you, Obi-Wan.
You can change, move the cameras, I can.
Is there a way to zoom in?
I don't want to accidentally skip the cutscene.
Ew!
Don't touch me!
Who is this?
I'm Dr. Naomi Hunter, the unit's chief medic.
An expert in gene therapy.
Are you military?
No, civilian.
I've been sent here from ATGC.
Pleasure to meet you, Snake.
Don't worry, this injection won't hurt a bit.
Don't touch me!
Oh!
Ah!
Oh, God.
I found out how to zoom in.
What's the shot for?
What's wrong?
You don't like shots?
No, I do not.
Snake, listen up.
Doesn't go any closer.
Camera A, how do I change it?
About five hours ago, an island in Alaska's Fox Archipelago, called Shadow Moses Island, was occupied by special ops soldiers.
What soldiers?
What is she doing, anyway?
Next generation special forces, led by members of Unit Foxhound.
Foxhound!
They've presented Washington with a single demand, and they say that if it isn't met, they'll launch a nuclear weapon.
Take off your pants!
A nuclear weapon?
Also, how's he...
I'm afraid so.
What hairstyle is he gonna change?
You see, the island is the site of a secret nuclear weapons disposal facility.
Foxhound, hijacking a nuclear weapon?
Five nights in.
Now you understand how serious the situation is.
This is actually FNAF, you guys.
You have two objectives.
First, infiltrate the nuclear weapons disposal facility...
...and rescue the two hostages.
That's a suit!
Oh my gosh, that's so cool!
...and Kenneth Baker, president of Arms Tech.
Okay, I know those guys.
Those are some heavy-duty hostages.
Secondly, you're to investigate whether or not the terrorists have the ability to launch a nuclear strike...
How do I get to the other camera?
Oh, let me try a trigger.
...and stop them if they do.
Oh!
Any questions, Snake?
Questions?
I haven't even said whether I accept this mission.
Oh my gosh, so cool!
You can make up your mind after you hear more about the situation.
Welcome back, thank you!
Next one?
Oh, here we go.
Oh my god, the music is so awesome!
We will know if this is really a retelling...
...or if Snake's dumpy is still as chonky as it is supposed to be.
I think it is going to be as chonky, right?
Next one?
Infiltration.
The insertion method.
So cool!
Wait, what if I do Z?
Okay, it doesn't.
The disposal facility includes a hardened underground base.
Thank you!
Even with our most advanced intelligence-gathering equipment, we can't tell what's happening inside.
Oh, Colonel!
Colonel!
Oh!
So, someone needs to penetrate, gather intelligence and report back.
Yes.
Sounds like a spy method.
No one...
What's the insertion method?
No one even lats...
No one even bats an eye at it.
Sounds like a spy method.
Not the hand...
...the handgun.
The handgun.
The facility is equipped with sonar detection capabilities.
They'd be able to hear our engine or propeller noise.
And then...
God, it's so goofy.
You'll launch a one-man SDV.
Launch.
Launch?
Same as a torpedo.
Only this has no propulsion device of its own.
Bond.
James Bond.
After the SDV gets as close as it can, dispose of it.
From there on, you'll have to swim.
You want me to swim?
Swim.
In sub-zero Alaskan water.
Oh.
That suit represents the latest advances in polyphonic technology.
Sorry if I'm switching around so much.
The nuclear weapons disposal facility covers the whole island.
Wait.
I'll instruct you by coach...
I think his dumpy is there.
You guys?
Anyone going with me?
Look at that.
As always, this is a one-man sneaking mission.
One -man sneaking mission.
Weapons and equipment OSP.
Yes.
Why are you even here?
This is a top-secret black-off.
Yeah, we get out of here.
Don't expect any official support.
He's cheeked up.
I'm embarrassed to look down.
I'm embarrassed to move the camera down.
We got our time.
That was my favorite part, though, of the briefings.
That I know of.
Where he goes...
Seems like a spy movie.
And he does his little handgun and nobody laughs at him or nobody makes a comment or anything.
He just...
Everyone's just kind of like...
Snake.
And then he's like...
Uh...
What's the insertion method?
It's so funny.
What's the time limit?
Oh!
Jeez!
24 hours.
So exasperating.
They say they'll launch after 24 hours.
This is so goofy.
Yeah.
Did they say what the target will be?
So far.
I love this game for different reasons than one, you know?
Like...
They did the countdown.
You know?
Okay, so it's not 24 hours.
Gosh!
Are you okay, Snake?
Why does it just stop there?
Oh my gosh, so funny.
Wait, how do I go back?
Oh, there we go.
Okay.
Oh my gosh, I can't wait to see...
Unit Foxhound.
I can't wait to see what they look like in the...
I'm so excited.
Person in charge of the operation.
He's like, bro...
He's like, no, you can't be serious.
What is... oh.
Hey!
Hey, no smoking on the job!
She actually tried.
She's still trying!
Get him.
Get him, Naomi.
Oh!
Come on.
Reach.
Just go in.
If you determine they possess nuclear launch capabilities...
Oh my god, the spread.
Yo, Snake!
I suppose there isn't that much reason to worry.
Yet.
Is the National Security Agency in on this?
The Power Stats.
Yeah.
And so is the D.I.A.
The Defense Intelligence Agency.
The D.I.A.
Get him.
Get him, Naomi.
I'm starting to have a bad feeling about this.
They'll be sending us some support.
We don't need desk jockeys.
We need a nuclear weapons specialist.
Of course.
Yeah.
A nuclear weapons specialist has already been assigned to us.
Oh.
Oh, she got him!
Oh, yeah!
You get him.
You show him, girl.
That, you know what?
Respect.
She went for it.
She girl-bust her way.
Let's see.
Support crew.
She's talking about Nastasha, right?
Where is she?
Let her come in.
Enter the room.
Romanenko.
Oh, there she is.
Kinda.
Let me see.
Let me see her.
Come on, Snake.
She's built up an impressive record as an advisor for the nuclear emergency search team.
Contact her if you have any questions.
Nastasha.
She's also an expert on high-tech weapons.
A female.
Where is she working from?
Her home in Los Angeles.
Oh, she's in LA.
California.
Ew.
California's a lot different than this place.
California, boo.
Ew.
Roy Campbell.
Our guy coming out of retirement.
All of us coming out of retirement.
Colonel.
Oh.
You're retired.
Why are you involved in this?
Because there aren't many people who know Foxhound as well as I do.
Wait, if I...
Is that the only reason?
Oh, yeah, baby.
I've been saving dreams for a long time.
I don't know anything else.
I guess even though I'm getting a little old, I still love to be in the field.
Why are you...
Why are you look...
Why are you standing like that?
Oh, my God.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Tell me the real reason.
Oh.
Okay, Snake.
Sorry.
Oh.
Take it.
Come on.
I'll be frank.
A person very dear to me.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Is being held hostage.
Who is it?
What?
Don't act surprised, Naomi.
Meryl.
Don't act surprised.
Pikachu surprise.
She's like, why you have someone in there?
Oh, my...
Actually, I don't even know if she does know about Meryl being in there to be honest.
Actually, not sure.
This is so fun being able to move the camera around so fast.
What was your niece doing there?
Several soldiers were reported missing the day of the revolt.
Meryl...
My niece was one of those called in as an emergency replacement.
Aww.
Oh, he's got a picture of her in his pocket.
She looks like you.
She's my little brother's girl.
...and since then I've been watching after her.
This is kind of messed up.
A personal motive, Colonel.
That's not very soldierly.
Oh.
I'm retired.
I'm just an old man now.
And I'm your friend.
Well, if you were merely my friend, you wouldn't have pulled me out of retirement either.
I've always been a friend since the fall of Zanzibar land.
Zanzibar!
Haven't you had enough of a moody bastard like me?
No.
That's the part of you I trust.
Zanzibar land.
Please, Snake.
Save my niece, Meryl.
She's just here.
Awkwardly standing.
Alright.
Okay.
But I have two conditions.
Name them.
One.
He's got that...
No more secrets between us.
He's got that Gollum posture.
I'm a complete disclosure at all times.
Snake, your gamer posture, please.
And two.
I'll only accept orders directly from you, Colonel.
No cut-offs involved, okay?
Oh, my precious.
Snake.
That's why I was...
He's back!
What?
He's not Colonel anymore.
I am not a Colonel anymore.
Okay, Colonel.
Just a retired old war-horse.
Nah.
Naomi, what are you doing?
Why are you looking like that?
I understand, Colonel.
The way he scooted closer, so cute.
Why are they doing that?
We're stealing this together!
Ah, yes.
We have 19 hours left until this nuclear warhead explodes.
You know what?
Or until they launch the nuke.
Let's just kick back and relax on the bed a little bit, you know?
It's fine.
They're so cute!
Oh my gosh.
They're like actual bros, you know?
It's so cute.
Hanging out with the homies.
Oh, so cute.
Naomi's third wheeling?
Yeah, just a little bit.
I'm invading their privacy!
Hold on.
It's like Naomi walked in on the wrong scene and doesn't know what to do.
Oh!
Oh, look at her!
He's...
Ah!
Don't sit like that!
Snake!
Snake, you... you... hey!
It's a combination of nanomachines and an anti-freezing pathway.
Help, please!
Wait, he's like sat up like that!
When he's talking about her being naked!
Oh my god!
Snake!
There are different types which will replenish the supply of adrenaline...
Nanomachines.
... and sugar in your bloodstream.
Now I don't have to worry about food.
No, that's Snake's worst enemy!
Or it's his worst fear!
Not eating!
No, drugs.
A class of drugs which will help improve your mental functioning.
Mmm.
It'll make me smarter, huh?
Anything else?
Oh my god, the tension here.
It's a type of stimulant.
It'll keep you alert...
Now, he's even looking away!
He's like, now I'm third wheeling.
That was quite a cocktail.
Anything else in there?
Those nanomachines will also keep your codex batteries charged up.
Poor Roy.
Oh!
I guess I can call you when I'm ready to go on a diet.
Stop!
Why are you doing this, Snake?
What?
The tummy rub.
The Snake tummy rub.
Thank you so much for the donut.
Thank you.
I guess I can call you when I wanna go on a diet.
Okay, last little bit.
Well, I say little bit, but it's quite a lot of bit.
That's okay.
Such a goofy old man he is.
The tension though.
Wow.
Okay, let's talk about the hostages.
Now we know the meaning of the twin snakes.
The chief of DARPA and the president of an arms manufacturing company.
Mm-hmm.
What business did they have at a nuclear weapons disposal facility?
Let's try this angle a little bit.
Ooh.
The truth is that secret exercises were being conducted at the time the terrorist group attacked.
China.
Look it.
Must be extremely important exercises if those two were directly involved.
Were they testing some kind of new advanced weapon?
I'm not privy to that information.
Do we know exactly where they're being held?
Why is he pointing his fingers?
Seriously.
Um, actually, do we know where they're being held?
I can't with the finger guns.
Oh, gosh, sorry.
I know I'm not paying attention, but also at the same time, I know most of this already, so it's fine.
It's more interesting to look at the visuals, you know?
Um, actually...
Do they really have the ability to launch a nuclear missile?
They say they do.
They even gave us the serial number of the warhead they plan to use.
He's doing it again.
Draw me like you're French, girl.
Was the number confirmed?
I'm afraid so.
What are you doing, Naomi?
At the very least...
What are you doing?
They got their hands on a real nuclear warhead.
Oh!
Isn't there some kind of safety device to prevent this type of terrorism?
Wait, no!
No, no!
Yes.
She's, like, massaging her calf.
Every missile and warhead in our arsenal is equipped with a POW, which uses a discreet detonation.
Girlie, what?
POW.
Why did...
This is...
Wait, or she's pulling up her stocking?
I can't tell!
A safety control system built into all nuclear weapon systems.
Ma'am!
What are you doing?
We can't rest easy.
We're right here!
Why not?
Oh my god.
Because the DARPA chief knows the detonation code.
Yeah, she's pulling up her...
Don't turn around, Snake.
Do not turn around.
It must have been removed from its missile.
All the missiles on these disposal sites are supposed to be dismantled.
It's not that easy to get your hands on an ICBM.
What if...
That used to be true.
I can't...
I can't pay attention.
I'm just looking at Naomi.
But since the end of the Cold War...
Press R1.
...you can pay the money.
Also, her...
Her shoes are on the bed!
That's so gross!
Don't do that!
Oh my god.
There's a fly in my room.
I think I'm gonna lose it.
Get out of here!
This is a clean mid-cafe.
Not a stinky mid-cafe where flies can fly around.
Oh my god.
Every scene delivers something new.
It's so...
It's like...
It's like a...
It's like a tree, you know?
Everything is new.
How well armed are these terrorists?
I know there was an exercise going on at the time they revolted.
They're heavily armed, I'm afraid.
Heavily armed...
What about their battle experience?
The six in charge are planning to...
Why is she just standing there?
I don't know.
They're standing man emojis.
After all, they're foxhound people.
Hey.
You're gonna make me blush.
The others are next generation special forces.
They're not your average grunts either.
What was that?
That was like the most dramatic kick ever.
I can't.
Oh my gosh.
You're gonna make me blush.
We're just...
I can't.
You're not kidding.
What is going on?
I cannot...
Can we watch it again?
Yeah.
That was really short, so let's watch it again.
That one was so funny.
Oh my goodness.
Hold on.
I kinda wanna watch it.
How well armed are these terrorists?
Wait.
Hold on.
I know there was an exercise going on at the time they revolted.
They're heavily armed, I'm afraid.
There we go.
What about their battle experience?
The six in charge are planning to thugth.
Oh my gosh.
I'm embarrassed.
Why am I looking at him?
Thank you!
Good luck have fun on your Metal Gear Observation Dunia!
Oh my gosh!
The kick is so crazy!
I love it!
I'm such a fan.
I should have done Cabaret.
So what exactly are they demanding?
A person's remains.
Remains?
That's right.
To be more accurate.
Cell specimens which contain the individual's genetic information.
Cell specimens.
Why would they want that?
What are you doing?
The terrorists need them.
Oh god!
I didn't expect to change the camera.
I've never seen that.
Genes?
Strengthened?
You've heard of the Human Genome Project.
Oh gosh.
They've been mapping the human genome and they're nearly finished.
What?
Following up on this research.
Thank you so much!
The military has been working towards identifying those genes.
Which are responsible for making effective soldiers.
There are genes that do that.
Naomi over here like...
That's so weird!
They're able to transplant those genes into regular soldiers.
That's so weird, right?
Gene therapy.
Yeah.
I'll explain this part.
Okay, here she comes.
Okay.
With gene therapy, it becomes easy to remove genes that cause sickness and disease.
Or, alternatively, to splice in additional genetic material.
Why are you so quiet?
You know what?
I knew that Naomi has...
She can overcome all sorts of genetic diseases.
And at the same time, add genetic characteristics as desired.
I knew she had no British accent in this one, but I completely forgot until just now.
And so you knew what genes were responsible for making the perfect soldier.
You could implant them in the same way, right?
No wonder they made him wear pants this time.
Can you imagine?
But it all depends on being able to isolate and identify those soldier genes.
The genes.
And in order to do that, it's helpful if you can study the genetic information...
The genetic information of one of the greatest soldiers ever.
They un-British-ed her?
They did, yeah.
She loses her British accent for some reason.
I think for the most part, um...
Well, Liquid still has his accent.
Genes...
Mei-Ling also no longer has her...
Oh yeah, she doesn't have her accent either.
Yeah...
Is that Jennifer Hale?
Yes, it is still Jennifer Hale.
It is still almost...
Almost all the original voice actors.
Just a...
A few changes, like um...
Uh...
What's his name?
Um...
Grey...
Grey Fox...
I'm trying to think of the voice actor's name.
Uh...
Jor...
Um...
I'm really sorry.
I've...
Uh...
I'm the ninja.
Um...
What's...
What's his voice actor's name again?
Greg!
Greg...
Greg Eagles.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
George Sears.
I know it started with a G.
It's so funny because I actually watched a video this morning about um...
About uh...
The voice actors of the Grimm Adventures of Billy and Mandy.
And Greg Eagles is also the voice of Grimm.
So it's really funny because it's just like...
Oh my gosh, you are...
You are...
Grey Fox?
And the DARPA chief?
And Grimm?
Like it's...
What?
Yeah!
Isn't that so awesome?
Isn't that so crazy?
Oh yeah, I totally forgot.
Yeah.
Grimm Fox.
It's so...
It's um...
It was cool seeing...
Watching the video and being like...
I...
I got to meet him.
I went to...
MGS Con.
Last year.
And I got to meet him.
And he was selling like some prints of...
The Grimm Adventures of Billy and Mandy.
So...
I was like...
Yo!
That was like one of my favorite shows as a kid.
So...
Because I loved Mandy.
Hater took a pay cut so all the OG VAs would come back.
Respect.
I love David Hater.
He's so...
Oh!
Big boss.
Big boss?
That's right.
We've been working feverishly to identify him.
He's so...
We had to identify the genes responsible for his incredible combat skill.
Oh!
So far, we've discovered about 60 of the so called soldier genes.
They have so much personality when they move around, you know?
I just love it so much.
So his body was recovered after all.
Yes.
And his cells have remained frozen in a cryo chamber.
I thought he was naked for a second.
Oh my gosh.
His genetic information is a priceless treasure to mankind.
Respectator.
He's so awesome.
He's so good to his fans, too.
They already have!
You!
It's your fault!
Oh, hello.
What are you doing?
I think he was getting the dust off of his jacket.
Checking the fly.
Your zipper's down, Colonel!
Okay.
The sons of Big Boss.
Dramatic stupid.
Nice.
Next Generation Special Forces Unit.
These guys... don't mess with them.
They have an IQ of 180, everybody.
I'm telling you.
Don't mess with them.
Tell me about these Next Generation Special Forces.
Why do you look like you're about to jump him?
They started out as an anti-terrorist special ops unit made up of former members of biochem units, technical escort units, and the Nuclear Emergency Search Team.
Their purpose was to respond to threats involving Next Generation weapons of mass destruction, including NBC weapons.
Until they were added, that is.
They.
Who's they?
Oh my god.
These guys didn't start out as regular army.
Looks like a pretty international group.
Mercenaries.
Look at them!
They're little portraits!
And it gets worse.
So cute!
Most of them were from a merc agency that I think you're familiar with.
They were part of Big Boss's private guard.
And after Big Boss went down, the military just bought out all their contracts.
What was one guy?
Oh, like this guy?
The speedy, fast man.
Outer Heaven.
Outer Heaven, baby!
After that, they were merged with our own VR unit, Force 21.
Running Man.
If you ask me, these so-called Next Generation Special Forces should be called Simulating Soldiers.
Why isn't he back?
Man.
They have no real battle experience.
Gosh, I really hope we get to see Decoy Octopus in this game.
Video game generation, huh?
Video game!
Don't forget, they've all been strengthened with gene therapy.
And they're smarter.
They carry genes which make them excellent soldiers.
Oh, yes.
Don't get careless just because they don't have much experience.
Okay.
I thought international law banned the military use of genetic therapy.
Yes, but those are just declarations, not actual treaties.
The interesting thing is that nearly every member of the unit conspired in this attack.
What I think I like most about this scene...
Well, until the static part.
Is the bitrate okay?
On it?
On YouTube?
And, like, watching it?
Like, it doesn't mess up, does it?
Why do they keep talking about pants therapy?
Yeah, looks fine?
Looks good?
Cool.
Looking clear?
Good, good, good.
Even though it's, like, all, like, kind of funky looking, you know?
What the hell is that gif?
Hahaha.
Thank you!
Greg Eagles!
Greg Eagles is still the DARPA chief.
Yes.
Oh, Rob Paulson.
Oh, Yakko!
Oh, okay.
It's gonna be interesting to hear it, then.
But if they were regular army, they must have been interviewed periodically by army counselors.
According to their files, they all got straight A's on their psychological tests.
They all seemed like fine, upstanding, patriotic soldiers.
They're so patriotic.
But they all took part in the uprising?
No.
Several people didn't show up.
They didn't show up on the day of the exercise.
That's why there was a resupply of troops.
They cheated on their tests?
Was there any sign recently that something might be wrong?
All I just realized?
For free?
There was a report a month ago that they were acting strangely.
Toes out?
Apparently, they consulted classified information about the soldier genes and performed their own gene therapy experiments.
They can do that?
Oh my god!
Ah!
Don't get closer!
Oh my god!
Stop!
Not the way he looks away again.
Oh my god!
Colonel, please!
Put an end to this!
Colonel, I'm uncomfortable!
I'm uncomfortable!
Yeah, get away.
Shy boy.
He's a bit of a shy boy.
Be a soldier, Mint.
Sorry.
All right.
Last one.
Maybe.
Unless...
I don't think they add another one.
They might.
They might add one about Liquid, right?
I don't remember.
We'll see.
Unit Foxhound.
This is just how it goes starting a Metal Gear Solid game.
The briefings are long.
Special Forces Unit Foxhound.
Your former unit.
And one that I was the commander of.
An elite group combining firepower and expertise.
They're every bit as good as when I was commanding them.
So they're still around.
Hmm.
There are six members of Foxhound involved in this terrorist activity.
He really does have terrible back posture.
Psycho Mantis.
With his powerful psychic abilities.
Wait.
Where's their pictures?
Sniper Wolf.
The beautiful and deadly sharpshooter.
He's like...
Wait.
He's going through them.
Decoy Octopus.
Master of disguise.
Wait.
I want to see them too.
Your oxygen.
Thank you.
Oh.
Is that it?
Hello?
Vulcan Raven.
Oh.
Giant and Shaman.
And Revolver Ocelot.
Specialist in interrogation and a formidable gunfighter.
Dramatic pause.
Sounds like a bunch of cartoon characters.
Maybe...
In charge of them.
Was he doing something that was off screen?
I don't know.
Liquid Snake.
Yes.
And you're the only person who can stand against him.
Where'd Naomi go?
Hello?
Naomi?
Wait.
Where is she?
Naomi?
Okay.
There was one for Liquid Snake.
I knew there would be.
She Liquid Snaked.
Oh.
She was behind Roy.
He's just that much of a unit.
Liquid Snake.
The man who shares your code name.
The Solid.
Versus the Liquid.
Tell me what you know.
I don't know.
He fought in the Gulf War as a teenager.
The youngest person in the SAS.
And the sass.
He is pretty sassy.
His job was to track down and destroy mobile scud missile launching platforms.
You were there too, I believe.
Didn't you infiltrate Western Iraq with a platoon of Green Berets?
I was just a kid myself back then.
Aww.
The details are classified.
But it seems that originally, he penetrated the Middle East as a sleeper for the SIS.
How do you feel about that?
He was a spy for the British Secret Intelligence Service.
But he never once showed his face in Century House.
He was taken prisoner in Iraq.
And after that, there was no trace of him for several years.
Yeah.
You like Castlevania, don't you?
After you retired, he was rescued and became a member of Foxhound.
I thought that by the time I left, they were no longer using code names.
I don't know his real name.
That interesting.
That information is so highly classified that even I can't look at it.
I know it.
Here's a photo of him.
Let me see.
Oh my gosh!
Wait!
You can actually see it!
You can actually tell that it's him!
Pretty shocking.
His skin tone is different.
Otherwise, you two are exact duplicates.
I have a twin?
I don't know the details, but it seems so.
That's why we really need you for this mission.
You're the only one who can beat him.
Big Boss was kind of freaky out there.
You've got something that he doesn't.
Why don't I find that thought more comforting?
Why is he standing like that?
Why was he standing like that?
Like the Hulk.
All right.
Guys, how are we feeling?
Are we getting a good vibe of the game so far?
Getting a good vibe of what we're in for?
Oh!
Wait!
No!
How do I get out?
Thank you!
Really digging the MGS telenovela.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, the haircut.
Wait.
Did I just accidentally...
Did I accidentally skip something?
Maybe that was the part where he cuts his hair.
Oh, no!
I thought it...
I thought I had accidentally...
I thought I had accidentally clicked on the file zero again.
Okay.
Hold on.
Maybe if I leave again, it will do it.
Right?
Let's see.
No!
I missed it!
I'm so sorry, you guys.
I'm sorry.
I haven't seen this title screen in so long.
If I wait on this screen, I don't think it shows the video, but that's okay.
I think we still see it when we do a new game anyway, so...
We press on.
You have to select exit.
That's what I did.
I pressed exit.
Watch the last brief...
Okay.
Let's try that one more time.
Sorry.
I do want to see it.
I'm sorry.
I thought I accidentally pressed zero again.
Oh!
Let's try it.
Liquid snakes wasn't that long.
Right?
It's just audio again, I think.
Don't worry.
Oh, is it?
Let's just try it, though.
It's okay.
It's okay, guys.
No worries.
No rush.
Liquid snake.
Ugh.
My controller cord is like everywhere.
The solid versus the liquid.
Tell me what you know.
I don't know.
He fought in the Gulf War as a teenager, the youngest person in the SAS.
His job was to track down and destroy mobile scud missile launching platforms.
Bum bum.
You were there too, I believe.
Oh my gosh, the almost convenient censoring of...
What if they censored...
Like, what if Snake really was...
I was just kidding myself back then.
...snakey.
And like they just censored him in crazy ways.
Kind of like how in MJS2 with Raiden, when he's on the Torch.
They censor him with a torture device.
They censor him with like the straw from the soda can.
I'm like an Austin Powers.
Yes, yes, yes!
I've never seen Austin Powers.
I thought that by the time I left, they were no longer using code names.
My mom never let me.
She said it was too inappropriate.
She was like, you're not allowed to... you're not allowed to...
Oh my gosh!
You can see him there!
You can see him!
But yeah...
Makes sense.
Yeah, she was like, you're not allowed to watch.
The gasp.
He doesn't look like he gets a haircut.
He looks... unless like...
He looks more like how he does in... in 2 maybe.
Maybe he's got like a little bit of a longer hair?
It doesn't look like he cuts that much.
The stance.
Okay.
Now... exit.
It's okay.
We missed out, but...
All he does is cut his hair.
Okay!
New game!
Normal.
Hard.
Very easy.
Easy.
I got... I'm gonna try on normal.
Because I feel like...
Rip.
Run.
But again, this is my first time using a GameCube controller.
So I'm gonna...
Do my bestest.
You're a pro?
Oh.
Absolutely.
I am...
A pro.
Absolutely.
Mint?
Boss?
Big... Big Moss?
Oh my god.
Thank you for the pink!
Thank you so much!
Let's go.
Radar for novices?
Standard.
There we go.
Game start?
Yes!
Here we go!
David Hayter!
Yeah!
Christopher Randolph!
Debbie Mae West!
Yeah!
Paul Eiding!
Jennifer Hale!
Yeah!
Kim Iguess!
Whoa!
Rob Wilson!
Yeah!
Patrick Zimmerman!
Doug Stone!
Yeah!
Patrick Zimmerman, the voice of Ocelot, is the husband of Chris Zimmerman.
Who... She is the one who, like, directed all the voices and everything.
Like, she's... she's so awesome.
Her dir... Whoa!
Her direction for the games is just so cool.
But they were like, who do we get to voice Ocelot?
And they... look at the rats.
They just kind of, like, chose him.
And he was so perfect.
Stay alert.
He'll beat you here.
Wow!
I'm going to swap down a couple of bothersome flies.
There he goes.
Liquid.
Bothersome flies.
Kim Clark!
Yes!
He's so him.
I know.
It's so great.
Ooh, the sounds are, like, kind of nice.
Look at us.
Wait, where'd our flippers go?
I guess we just dumped them.
Nobody sees me.
Sneaky sneaky!
Nobody, nobody sees.
It's good to have you back, boss.
Thank you!
Thanks for the super chat!
This is Snake.
Colonel, can you hear me?
Loud and clear.
What's the situation, Snake?
Looks like the elevator in the back is the only way up.
Just as I expected.
You'll have to take the elevator to the surface.
But make sure nobody sees you.
Yep.
If you need to, contact me by codec.
The frequency is one four zero point eight five.
One four zero point eight...
When you want to use the codec, push the pause button and then the A button.
What?
When we need to contact you, the codec will beep.
When you hear that noise, press the pause button and then the A button to receive the call.
What?
Oh.
It's two buttons?
The codec's receiver directly stimulates the small bones of your ear.
Oh my gosh.
No one but you will be able to hear it.
My small bones.
Got it.
Okay.
I'm ready to go.
I guess it makes sense because there is no select on the controller.
Okay.
Oh, wow.
Hello, Colonel.
Snake, you'll have to crawl to get through there.
Okay.
First, crouch down by pressing the crawl button.
What does that mean?
And then press the control stick in the direction you want to crawl.
Okay.
Just remember that you can't move very fast when you're crawling.
You can stand up by pressing the crawl button again.
Okay.
Thank you.
Start plus A button.
Is there still the ration down here or...
Oh, yes, there is.
I'll take that.
Stomp, stomp, stomp.
Stomp, stomp, stomp, stomp, stomp.
Nice.
Uh, get up there.
Get up.
Okay, nice.
Okay, so Y is basically triangle to action button.
Good to know.
And then crawl...
Okay.
That's B.
A is nothing.
Oh, X.
Okay.
Shoop, shoop, shoop, shoop, shoop, shoop, shoop, shoop.
Whoa.
And then up.
Look at the rat.
Look at him go.
He's so fat.
Okay.
My cigarettes, my skull.
Okay, my ration.
Okay.
Oh!
Okay, this is first person view.
Okay.
Oh shit.
No one.
Why is your vision so good already?
Hey, hold on though.
They're stupid.
They don't know.
They can't get over here.
I'm trying to figure out the controls.
Can you leave me alone for like two seconds?
The other ration is over there.
Then there should be another ration.
No!
Don't die in security!
180 IQ, by the way.
I mean, he saw me.
That was pretty good, the way he saw me.
It's not bad.
It's not bad, right?
Okay.
From... from... Okay, okay.
I have to get used to X as the crawl button.
That's so weird.
It's... it's... it's new.
It's... it's strange, but it's okay.
We're gonna... we're gonna... we're gonna fumble a little bit.
Oh my gosh, I just pressed the wrong button again.
This is fine.
We're gonna fumble...
Wait, I think he saw me at the same time.
No!
Oh my god!
I was in a cutscene!
This is so unfair!
They won't come over here.
They also won't see me.
From here.
Oh my gosh.
Oh wow, the water going down the thing is so cool.
Look, he's just gonna leave.
This is so messed up, you guys.
This is messed up.
Oh please, just go away so I can start the game!
Um, I think, um...
What was it?
Uh, there... okay, so this is crawl.
Okay.
Don't see me, you bastard.
Don't see me.
I need to go get the gun.
Where's the rest of the guys though?
Hold on.
Okay, this way.
Alright, go snake, go.
Okay.
We're not gonna let them see us.
I got distracted by the rat at first, okay.
But not this time.
We're gonna flip this guy.
We're gonna flip him over.
I think it's A.
Yeah, return your positions, everybody!
Nothing weird going on here.
Thank you!
Okay.
Turn around.
Oh.
Grab him!
Oh god, no!
No, why?
No, uh, okay, we're fine.
Yoink!
He didn't see anything.
He didn't see anything!
Oh my god, he's so short!
I would've never seen you, pipsqueak!
I would've never even noticed you were there!
It was not accidental!
For the M9.
Okay, I think I can go.
You know what?
Alright, let's go snake.
Ah!
It's the enemy.
I need help.
Uh...
Open the...
Start the...
Start the elevator.
Uh...
Uh, you guys?
This is not good.
Um, okay.
This is our first time...
How do I shoot?
Wait.
Okay, hold on.
How do I use the gun?
Uh oh.
Uh...
Ah!
Oh gosh, I'm fighting with my hands!
Wait!
Hold on!
I can't...
Stop it!
I don't know how to shoot!
This is unfair!
Wait.
Uh...
Press A button to aim!
A!
Oh, I...
I unequipped it.
We're fine, everybody.
Oh sh...
What the hell was that?
Um...
Oh my god.
I don't know how to use these controllers!
Caught in the dodge roll.
I know!
It was so...
Okay.
Alright.
This is...
This is fine.
This is so fine, you guys.
Do I still have my...
No.
Let's go.
Oh.
I don't want that.
Go away.
Okay.
This is fine, everybody.
Give me that.
Stop, stop, stop.
Yes, yes, yes!
It's just a little bit of a...
Um...
A little bit of a...
I don't know.
Performance anxiety, but we're fine.
I wish I had my gun.
Don't...
Don't see me here.
Turn around and walk away.
Don't get distracted by the rat.
I'm sorry.
Don't get distracted by the rat!
Where is he anyway?
I think that guy's gonna walk over here.
I do want to get the other ration in the other corner.
We can probably forego the one...
That was... what's the word?
The one in the lower corner.
He's gonna come back here.
He's gonna pass us, I think.
Actually, I don't know their route at all.
Oh, here he is.
Look at you.
Teeny tiny.
Little baby.
What's the... what is that sound?
It's like a scuttle...
Oh, there it is.
And then there's another guy on there.
Yup, yup, yup, yup.
So I... wait, do I need to press a button while I'm in there?
It must be Y then, right?
To press the button or...
I guess?
Snake made win.
Oh.
Doki doki.
Doki doki waku waku.
Maybe not waku waku.
I don't know where this guy goes.
Okay, I wanna be able to shoot him.
So once this guy comes back through here, I gotta...
Okay, so it's A... A and Z.
Right?
Okay.
Wait, how do I get out of here?
It must be Y, right?
It's triangle.
Oh.
Hey!
Get out of here!
Lazy bones!
Come on, get out of here.
I don't know what their pattern is.
Okay, it's Y to get out of here.
We don't wanna get out just yet.
Are they gonna see me?
Don't see me.
Okay.
Oh, wait.
This one.
No.
I was right.
Okay, A...
Oh, gosh.
Can you peek around the corner again?
Oh, my God.
No!
Oh, gosh!
Dang it!
Stop it!
Stop!
Stop shooting me!
I can't with this... Oh, I got him.
Oh, my God.
Stop shooting me.
I'm trying to learn the controls.
I've never played on this tank thing.
Wait, I'm holding the gun.
Oh, I unequipped.
Wait.
I didn't unequip it.
What happened?
I missed it.
Why are you just shooting?
Okay, he's gone.
Maybe I can get him from over here.
Oh, dang it.
You jerk.
Hey.
Hey, you.
Oh.
Can I... It's B, right?
There we go.
Okay.
All right.
Don't... Oh, my God.
Oh, please shoot.
Please shoot.
Can I loot these?
Oh.
It's fine.
Of course, getting out of the dang locker.
Okay.
It's fine, though.
We got this, you guys.
This game... I just got to get used to it a little bit.
Oh.
What is going on?
Oh, wow.
Oh.
Oh, oh.
There's the hindie.
Liquid.
Oh, my God.
Oh,
my God.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Yo, that was so crazy.
That was crazy.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
Also, for anyone curious, I'm not necessarily going for a full non-lethal route because I feel in this game it doesn't make much sense.
I will maybe for the guards.
There might be some times I kill guards.
But for the bosses, I'm going to kill them.
Because it only makes sense.
They end up dying anyway.
So, I gotta kill them.
Ultraviolets.
You enjoy all the killing.
Sorry.
Sorry, Colonel.
Age hasn't slowed you down one bit.
Not the call-out line.
Take it.
If it weren't for your suit and your shot, I would have turned into a popsicle out there.
Took you a long time.
All of the Genome soldiers in this exercise are using it.
I see.
I'm relieved to hear that.
Sorry, Colonel.
I had coffee and it's making me shake a little.
By the way, how's the diversionary operation going?
Two F-16s just took off from Galena and are headed your way.
The terrorist radar should have already picked them up.
Phew.
Hind D?
Colonel.
What's the Russian gunship doing here?
Oh no, I'm gonna have to fight that later.
But it looks like our little diversion got their attention.
Actually, I'm curious how the propelling part will be.
Who's that?
Oh!
I was looking at the guy behind him.
Look what is in there.
Behind me!
Whoa!
My controller's rumbly.
Now's your best chance to slip in unnoticed.
Unnoticed?
Snake?
Unnoticed, Snake?
There are only 18 hours left until their deadline.
You've got to hurry.
Oh well, whose fault is that for not getting me?
It must be crazy to fly Hind in this kind of weather.
Who's that?
Oh my god, she sounds so... different.
I haven't introduced you two yet.
This is Mei Ling.
Mei Ling!
She was assigned to us as our visual and data processing specialist.
I love you, Mei Ling.
She designed your codec, as well as your soliton radar system.
Contact her if you have any questions about either of them.
She sounds the same but different, you know?
Nice to meet you, Snake.
It's an honor to speak to a living legend like yourself.
Oh, it doesn't sound so bad.
Actually, it sounds...
Oh, what's wrong?
Nothing.
I just didn't expect a world-class designer of military.
Military technology to be so...
So cute.
Cute.
You're just flattering me.
No, I'm serious.
Well, I know I won't be bored for the next 18 hours.
What's this?
I'm being hit on by the famous Solid Snake?
But I'm surprised.
Cute.
I didn't think you'd be so frank.
Looks like we both have a lot to learn about each other.
No, my name is Snake.
It does, doesn't it?
Well, let's get to know each other better.
But first, can you explain about your soliton radar system?
Colonel looking away.
Can you explain about your soliton radar system?
Colonel's blushing.
Colonel, he's like...
The bright dot in the middle is you, Snake.
That's me.
The red dots are your enemies.
And the blue cone shape represents their field of vision.
Okay.
Get out of here.
Be careful, Snake.
The Genome Soldiers have highly developed senses of hearing and vision due to their gene therapy.
Make sure you don't let them see you.
Okay.
First, I want you to infiltrate the disposal site and look for the DARPA Chief.
DARPA Chief.
The diaper chief.
The same GPS transmitting nanomachines as you.
Highly developed.
He should appear on your radar system.
Okay.
Get whatever information you can from him about the terrorists.
If he's alive, that is.
Oh, he's fine.
He's okay.
He's fine.
Why did you guys say it like that?
But if you're discovered by an enemy, he won't be able to use it.
I think we need to upgrade our technology.
Yes, it gets jammed easily, I'm afraid.
Yes, it's all made from currently existing technology.
I think we need to upgrade that.
You won't be able to use it in an area with strong harmonic resonance.
So be careful.
Be careful.
We'll be monitoring your movement.
Nanomachines.
Mentor.
So contact us by codec anytime you want.
Got it.
I'll call if I'm feeling lonely.
Seriously, Snake.
We're here to back you up.
So call if you need some information or advice.
Okay.
I'm also in charge of your mission data.
Contact me if you want me to save your current status.
My frequency is 140.96.
140.96, everybody.
It's a dedicated frequency for saving data.
Don't forget it.
Remember, except for your binoculars, you can't use them.
You need to arm yourself with whatever weapons you can find.
I remember.
First, I'm strip searched by Dr. Naomi here.
Then all my weapons are taken away.
What weapons did you have?
Imagine yourself put in that position.
140.96.
Maybe I'll let you do a strip search on me.
Hold you to that, doctor.
By the way, sorry to disappoint you, but I did manage to smuggle out my smokes.
Oh, not in the...
How did you do that?
He ate them.
Thanks to the shot you gave me that suppressed my stomach.
Am I out of breath?
Cigarette.
How are those gonna help you?
You never know.
Hey!
This guy is so dumb!
Oh my God.
He's so dumb.
If you wanna get in, there's the front door.
It's the fastest way, but there's too much risk of being spotted by the enemy.
There's the door!
Which way should we go?
You can't just knock on the door and ask them to let me in.
I'm probably gonna go in the way that I...
What about the airdrill near the door?
That way.
Yeah, that one.
One sentry on the left.
And one on the right.
Sir?
But we already have our gun.
We can take these guys out, I think.
Also, since this is like MGS2, you can hold them up, right?
Oh, but I've been trying to practice how to hold up people, but I'm still not really good at it, so...
I'll do my best.
Pineapples.
Pineapple, pine...
There's nothing over here, right?
I don't remember there being anything over here.
Um...
Okay, let's see.
Uh, I'm assuming the zoom is the same...
Okay, yes.
And then it's X.
Okay, there's that guy over there.
Um...
There's a guy up there.
Yeah, there's, uh...
Obviously the spotlight's in the middle, but there's a guy over here.
That's our sleeping buddy!
Oh!
But there's also the camera here.
Yes, yes, yes.
Okay.
Okay, so A...
And then Z.
Okay.
We'll get this, we'll get this, you guys.
Can I run?
Oh my gosh, how am I supposed to run, though?
How am I supposed to...
Oh!
What?!
There's Auto-Abe?!
Yo, no way!
Oh, oh, oh, hold on.
Okay, wait.
My fingers are all messed up right now.
Okay.
I almost had him.
I could've gotten him.
But if he faints right now, they'll notice I'm here.
Do you think he's too far away?
Think he's too far?
Can't tell.
How am I supposed to walk when I have all the...
How am I supposed to do this?
Okay, hold on.
She's hacking.
Aimbot.
Let's get this guy.
Never mind.
Let's get him.
I can't tell if it's too far or not.
It looks way too far, right?
Okay, wait.
Oh, wait.
Hold on.
There we go.
Okay.
I'm just getting a feel for things, you guys.
I'm just getting a feel for things.
Okay.
So the quick...
Oh, okay.
The quick...
All this is...
Oh.
Oh, oh.
Oh, interesting.
Okay, so if I hold...
If I push down...
I didn't mean to do that.
If I push down, it brings up the menu.
But if I'm in first person, I can do that.
Okay.
Wow.
It's like not so...
Or it's...
Okay.
Sorry.
We're learning.
What is...
What is crawling?
Oh, my God.
Nope.
No, no, no.
Get up, Snake.
Run.
No, no, no, no.
There's nobody here.
Snake, we're still learning the controls.
We can't do this yet.
Oh.
Wait.
I can't move in first...
I can't walk in first person?
Why did I think I could?
Unless it's just holding my gun.
No.
Come back.
Please.
Okay.
Whose footprints are these?
No one's.
It's your imagination.
Do I have to equip it before I go into first person?
Okay.
Good to know.
Come here, mister.
I'm gonna get your butt.
Come on.
Oh, there you are.
Okay.
I don't think...
Oh.
I did get him.
I don't have very many bullets left.
And he's down.
And this is what makes the game a little bit easier because of the first person and stuff, you know?
Come here.
Do you think I can get him?
Oh.
I got him.
Go down.
Psst.
Come here.
Oh.
There he goes.
I will learn.
Oh, no.
I got the wrong one.
A surveillance camera.
What?
Oh, I can see their... what's it called?
Um, it's range.
Is that gun still in here?
Or...
Oh, yeah.
There we go.
Okay.
Nice.
A surveillance camera.
Okay.
That guy...
Go back to sleep.
Go to sleep, little baby.
Oh.
Uh.
We'll get him from this side.
Go to sleep.
Oh.
I need to equip the gun.
Go to sleep.
Go to sleep, little baby.
Um.
Now, how do I...
A crawl.
Oh.
Okay.
Crawl is...
This.
There we go.
Ikuzo.
I think...
Did I forget...
Did I forget anything?
I don't remember.
Did I forget...
It's fine if I forgot some items.
We got the SOCOM, though.
So we can perform violence.
But the M9 has the suppressor.
Gosh.
It makes it so easy.
Okay.
Hello.
Where's the rat?
Natsukasii.
Wait.
Where's the item?
No way.
It took away...
Wasn't there a ration down here?
Violence!
Thank you.
Thanks for the download.
Oh.
They took away my... no rats.
Follow the mice.
Where are they?
I only have three bullets left.
Maybe we need to be a... Oh, there they are!
Beep beep!
Oh, it did it by itself.
Thank you.
Wait!
Yes!
Master Miller!
Oh my god!
Just... he's in retirement.
What skills does Kaz have?
I'm actually legitimately... I actually don't know.
I've never seen Kaz on the floor.
He's always like... Burgers.
Hahaha!
Thanks master.
Oh yeah, let's call, uh, let's call Mei Ling.
The skill of arm regress.
What is it?
Start and... A?
A dark side.
Are you sure they're not dangerous?
To ensure the survival of the animals.
Follow the mice.
What is it?
Start plus A.
Okay.
Oh wait, it's already put in there.
Lucky ass.
Well, we should save anyway.
Never mind.
Oh wait.
Oh, wait, we're fine.
Just kidding.
New file.
Yes.
Okay, beep, beep.
Thanks, Mei Ling.
Wait, where's my... Um, excuse me.
Where is my... Where is my proverb?
Didn't realize you like this franchise.
Be cautious about the brain rot.
AP.
AP, it's over for me.
It's... It's... When did they tell us... Oh yeah.
When do we learn Nastasha's?
I don't remember hers actually.
What was it?
What was hers?
Mei Ling sounds different without an accent.
Yeah.
14152?
This is Nastasha Romanenko.
A pleasure to work with you, salad snake.
Nastasha!
You're the nuclear specialist that the colonel mentioned.
That's me.
You can ask me anything about nukes that you want.
I am also a military analyst.
So sad she never got like a 3D model.
So I have an extensive knowledge of weapon systems as well.
She's so hot.
They asked me to participate in this operation as a supervisor from the nuclear emergency search team.
I was happy to accept.
She still has her accent, but it's...
We must not allow terrorists to get their hands on nuclear weapons of any kind.
It's muted.
It's way less.
I hope I can help you to stop them.
It's...
You're a tough lady.
Those terrorists are serious about launching a nuclear weapon.
The world cannot stand by idly and allow that to happen.
And neither can I.
Yeah, it's much more subdued.
Unfortunately, all I can do from here is provide you with information.
Thank you, Nastasha.
Hopefully, that'll be enough.
Another soldier here wouldn't make a difference anyway.
It's good to work with you, Nastasha.
Same here, Snake.
Yeah, yeah, you can hear it there, right?
Okay, start a button.
So strange.
All right, little rats, let's go.
Let's go, little rats.
Oh.
Oh, yes, the water.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Why is it going down so fast?
Stop.
It's so messed up.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe I lost health.
This should be an exit right here.
Oh, no, it is not.
Interesting.
Okay.
Where do they want me to exit then from?
Hello?
Here?
Varian?
Aha!
I should have followed the rat.
Did that hit him?
Uh-oh, I only have one bullet left.
Good night.
How do I get up?
Shit.
Okay.
Start, start.
Use the elevator to change floors.
There should be a cargo elevator that you can take down somewhere around there.
How do I pick up the elevator?
Pick him up.
Try to find it.
How do I...
How do I pick him up for the loot?
Yeah.
Like, if I can check the bodies in two, right?
It's the same thing?
What do I...
Is it...
Maybe A?
A or B?
Let's try.
A.
Oh, there we go.
Give me all you got.
Okay.
He's got nothing.
Lame-ass.
Okay.
Oh, the music in here is so...
Nothing in here.
I should also have my ration equipment, right?
Yeah.
Let's have...
That was so close.
I don't know where he goes.
Oh.
Can I get out of here, please?
Thank you.
How do I want to take this guy out?
I don't know.
Okay.
How do I...
Hold on.
All right.
If I run up to him, behind him, and then do that...
Oh, no!
Oh.
I could still hold it up.
They don't know I have zero bullets.
Right.
Time to bluff.
Okay.
Is there anyone...
I think there's...
A guy upstairs, right?
So he'll hear me.
Oh, man.
Okay.
Let's see.
He comes around.
I'll wait for him.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna lose my brain.
Please.
No.
Go in there, Snake.
Oh, why?
Why?
Why do I just let go of the button?
Why do I...
Actually, this works, though.
Can you just lift up just a tiny bit, Snake?
They're gonna know.
They're never gonna stop leaving me alone.
They're never gonna leave me alone.
You can go.
Did he pull out his?
Now.
Did he pull out his...
He pulled out his shield.
The other guy is still asleep.
That's some strong 180 I.Q., everybody.
Are their legs okay now?
That guy's snoring up a storm over here.
Don't wake him up though, please.
Oh, dang it.
Oh.
Please, I have no more guns!
No more bullets!
Okay.
You guys, this is just all so familiar, isn't it?
Come on.
Leave me alone.
Hello?
No more gun.
Can I still use it though?
Even if it's empty?
Oh!
I could still bluff.
Perhaps.
I could make him lay down.
Maybe.
Yeah.
Get out of here, attack team!
Get out of here!
Okay.
That guy is the one that patrols over on that side.
Then we are going to have our other friend who walks around this tank, I think is what he does.
Oh, hello.
They are both on the other side.
They are both on the right side.
Where are you?
There's that...
Okay.
If I can...
Let's try this out.
You
jerk!
Oh.
Oh, dang.
Security!
Grab him!
Wait.
Oh
my god.
They are so loud.
You know what?
Let's just kill them.
Or let them kill me.
It's fine.
You guys can just kill me.
In fact, I'll help you.
Let's restart.
Okay.
It's okay because I didn't even have any bullets.
We are going to sneak up on him.
And we are going to get his butt.
We are going to get his butt.
The control.
It's okay.
One left!
Wait.
Only one?
I had two before.
Hey game!
You know?
It's not really fair.
I'm just saying.
If I had taken him down, the other guy would have seen him faint.
Maybe he'll come back.
Let's see.
Where are you?
Where did he go?
Where does he walk to?
Oh, there he is.
It's X to get up.
Is this about the elevator?
Thank you.
You guys...
There we go.
The other guy is going to come though!
Uh, shoot.
Um...
You're supposed to...
Why didn't you shake down?
Why didn't you shake your little booties?
Why didn't you shake your little booties and get on the ground?
Uh, wait.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, kill me again.
Actually, just take me out.
You have to be in front of him!
You
have to be in front of him!
I want him to get on the ground.
Okay, let's try...
Well, I was going to kill him.
But we won't kill him.
And I won't waste this bullet.
Maybe we just go upstairs.
You know what?
Maybe we don't even...
care about these guys.
Or...
Wait, the elevator...
We gotta go down to get to...
I need more bullets though.
We need to go upstairs and kind of loot the place a little bit.
I don't think you can make them lie down though.
Not in this one?
Maybe not.
Cause they're supposed to like...
chill there and be like...
Oh my...
I can't...
get used to the get up button.
I seriously cannot.
Because the A button...
is so big!
It's so big my fingers...
just instinctively click it.
It's so...
Just kill me.
Dang!
Oh, I almost had you.
Oh, hold on.
There he is!
Radar!
It's picking up the DARPA chief!
He's the green dot!
Hurry and rescue him!
Um...
Oh, this is first person.
There's no one over here though.
There's the guy in here, but we can't go in there.
Boop boop!
I know to press the action...
button, Colonel.
Pressing Y while...
holding the...
A will put down the gun without...
shooting.
I thought you had to...
unequip the... Whoa.
I can't see anything.
Oh, there we go.
I thought you had to unequip it so that it wouldn't...
It wouldn't shoot.
What's this?
It's a sparrow.
...
Sneaky sneaky...
Oh!
Oh, it's Johnny.
Oh god, why do I have to...
see this?
Ow!
Gross!
Ew, it's so steamy!
Boy oh boy!
I sound like Goofy.
That woman is built alright.
...
Honey my man!
Let's get our bullets.
Yay!
Uh, first person...
down?
Wait.
First person...
down?
Oh.
There's no one in here.
What is that?
Are you playing...
naughty games at work?
Oh, wrong way.
There we go.
Snake is such a...
voyeur.
Oh, gross!
We don't even know if he flushed!
We definitely know he didn't...
wash his hands.
Oh, there is a dirty magazine!
Nice.
La la la la la la la.
Meryl, I'm coming for you.
Are you still doing sit-ups?
Like you always do?
It's weird that it forces...
Oh, hello.
Forces you into the cutscene.
There she is.
Merl.
Oh, really?
Really?
Really, Snake?
Oh my gosh.
Don't look up, Merl.
Don't look up.
I'm just gonna completely...
forget about what the Colonel said.
About, uh...
About, um...
you know, his niece...
and all of that, you know.
How does she not see him?
I know.
He's just that sneaky.
Shh.
Hush.
Who's that?
I'm here to save you.
You're the DARPA chief.
Donald Anderson, right?
The diaper chief.
That's my favorite character, you guys!
You're here to save me, huh?
What's your outfit?
Uh... Louis Vuitton.
I'm the con they sent in here to save your worthless butt.
Really?
Greg Eagles.
It's true.
You don't look like one of them.
In that case...
Hurry up and get me out of here.
Slow down.
Don't worry.
First, I want some information about the terrorists.
The diaper chief in this very cell...
This guy standing before us...
Do they really have the ability to launch a nuke?
What are you talking about?
Just this diaper chief right here.
The terrorists are threatening the White House.
They say if they don't exceed to their demands, they'll launch a nuclear weapon.
Oh, LMAO.
Sweet Jesus.
Is it possible?
Well?
It's possible.
They could launch a nuke.
Oh my God.
Whoa!
I'm getting...
Oh my God.
I'm getting whiplash.
I'm getting motion sick.
You guys...
We were conducting exercises...
with a new type of experimental weapon.
A truly historical weapon.
Metal gear.
Ooh, whee!
With the ability to launch a nuclear attack...
from any place on the face of the Earth.
Miss Gurley.
Kicked up.
Do we get the real-life picture?
Metal Gear!
Ah, Rex!
Not with this little guy.
He's so cute!
Oh my god, little Rex.
Ow!
Oh my god, show the other side.
Show the laser...
Ow!
He's little...
He's so cute!
Guys, my mouth!
Oh my god!
Tiny arms...
Is this Grim from Grim Adventures of Billy and Mandy?
Yes!
It is!
You can hear it, right?
Revolution.
Revolution?
You can hear it a little bit.
It's so funny.
Rex has fallen into the hands of terrorists.
Rex?
Little baby.
Metal Gear Rex.
The codename for the new Metal Gear prototype.
They're probably already finished arming the warhead they plan to use with Rex.
Johnny's just like, shut the hell up, man.
These guys are bros.
They're all experienced in handling and equipping new weapons.
Maybe you shouldn't...
Shut up in there, will ya?
Maybe Snake shouldn't be standing in front of the door, you know?
Maybe, like...
Yeah, whatever.
Where could he be?
All
nuclear warheads were equipped with safety measures.
Some kind of detonation...
What are you doing up there?
Oh, you mean Pal.
Pal?
Yes, of course.
There is a Pal.
It's not a Pal, though.
It's set up so that you need to input two different passwords in order to launch the device.
There are two passwords?
Two?
Baker knows one.
And I know one.
Baker?
The president of Arms Tech?
That's right.
But did you talk?
Each of us needs to input our password or there can be no launch.
Pal Emmerich?
Icky.
Don't say that.
He's no Pal either.
Look at the membership!
Thank you so much.
Lithia, thank you.
They found out my password.
Oh, you're so weak.
You talk.
You're weak.
Psycho Mantis can read people's minds.
You can't resist.
No, you had the train.
Psycho Mantis.
One of the members of Foxhound.
Yeah, you know that.
He has psychic powers.
You just said that.
Password one, two, three.
This is bad.
No!
It's just a matter of time...
Oh, my God.
She's...
The sweat?
If they find out Baker's password...
Yes.
They'll be able to launch a nuke any time.
Any time.
But there is a way to stop the launch.
What?
The card keys.
Card keys?
Card keys.
They were designed by Arms Tech.
The system developers as an emergency override.
Even without the passwords, you can just insert the card keys and engage the safety system.
Okay.
Sounds easy enough.
Right, guys?
Yes.
You can stop the launch.
Look at her.
That card key.
So, where are the card keys?
Baker should have them.
Listen.
You need three card keys.
Three card keys.
There are three different slots to put them in.
Easy peasy.
You need to insert a card into each one of them.
Okay.
Three card keys.
Do you know where they are?
Do you know where they might be keeping Baker?
Somewhere in the second floor basement.
Second floor basement?
Second floor basement.
I heard the guards say they moved them into an area that has a lot of electronic jamming.
Meryl is pretty.
She's so pretty.
Any other clues?
Yes.
They cemented over the entrances, but didn't have enough time to paint them.
Why don't you look for the areas where the walls are a different color?
Got it.
Yippee!
Here.
Take this.
Oh, wow.
It's my ID card.
It'll open any level one door.
Why do you only have a level one security card?
It's called a PAN card.
That is insane.
It works together with your body's own electrical field.
Personal area network, huh?
Huh?
It transmits data using the salts in your body as a transmission medium.
Wow.
If you approach the door's security devices, they'll read the data stored in the card.
Girl, welcome to membership.
Thank you so much.
And the doors will open automatically.
Gotcha.
He's just the DARPA chief after all.
Yeah.
He's not even that big of a...
Okay.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
I'm gonna...
Oh, my God.
This persona is so flowy.
It's so great.
What is it?
You haven't heard any other way to disarm the pal, have you?
From your bosses or anyone?
No.
Are you sure you haven't heard anything?
I just said no.
So, does the White House plan to give in to the terrorist demands?
That's their problem.
Yeah.
That's not our problem.
It has nothing to do with my orders.
But what about the Pentagon?
Pentagon?
Hmm?
Uh-oh.
Oh!
Oh, his tummy!
Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
Oh, no!
I'm...
Ow!
Oh, my God.
It's so scary.
Look.
IBS.
He's got tummy issues.
The toilet's right there.
Ah!
Hey.
What happened?
Girlie, stop making a scene!
Stop making a scene!
Oh!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
Oh my god!
He's really dragging this now.
He's still going.
He's earning that Oscar.
Wait, his eyes turned black?
Yamcha.
Is he gonna grab him and go for a second round?
Huh.
Dead.
Oh, he just shut his eyes?
It looked like they went like...
Like he's wearing sclera lenses.
Great observation, Snake.
Huh.
Dead.
Really?
No!
Colonel, are you hiding something from me?
No.
No, Snake.
Absolutely not.
This counter-terrorist op is security level red.
You'll need the highest security clearance to learn the real story.
Then you just told me that you were hiding something and I have to play the game to unlock it.
I told you, the secretary of defense is in operational control.
I'm just here as your support.
Snake, we don't have time to do this.
Yeah.
What do you mean the real story?
What do you mean by that?
You mean it wasn't a heart attack.
Why would you say the real story?
The real story is you just had a heart attack, right?
That's all.
Oh, uh...
This way.
Thank you!
Oh, I hear her getting zipped up.
Oh, sorry.
How you doing down there?
Oh, there she goes!
Oh!
Pretty suspicious.
She's waiting for me.
Oh my gosh.
Sorry, I really...
Thank you!
Hope that you read this portable...
MGS portable ops quote.
You've given me a real reason to fight.
Thank you.
X is to crouch.
Y is to fight.
Y is action.
X is to crouch.
B is to fight.
And B is to fight.
X is to crouch.
And don't click the big A unless you mean it.
Okay.
Hmm...
Fight!
Actually, I was told to try something in this next part.
I want to kind of try it out.
Just move!
So you killed the chief, you bastard!
No, it wasn't me!
It was IBS.
It's really serious.
It's plaguing the nation.
No, you're not.
Don't move!
No, I'm solid.
Is this the first time you ever pointed a gun at a person?
Your hands are shaking.
Got your nose!
Where did that come from?
Can you shoot me, rookie?
I've got rookie's eyes.
I mean, she's got rookie's eyes.
Liar.
Your eyes wander.
There's no confidence in them.
The eyes of a rookie.
You're not a person, have you?
You talk too much.
You haven't even taken the safety off, rookie.
I told you, I'm no rookie.
Oh no!
You're not one of them, are you?
Open that door.
Oh, Johnny.
So we can get the hell out of here.
Looks like you'll be a little delayed.
Foxhound!
What are you doing?
Don't think!
Shoot!
Oh, you know what?
Never mind.
It didn't work at all.
What I was told to do?
Didn't work at all.
Well, maybe if I...
Anyway.
Shoot.
How do I shoot?
Why aren't you shooting at me?
Why aren't you shooting at all?
Shoot!
Don't talk to me like a rookie!
I'm telling you...
Shoot!
No!
Oh,
gosh.
Dang it.
They did it to me again.
Oh my god.
Hold on.
I need to...
Oh, gosh.
It's so...
Oh my god.
No!
Oh, I'm out!
No way.
What?
Uh...
Girlie, you need to handle this by yourself.
I'm sorry.
I'm out of bullets.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, there they are.
Never mind.
I got it.
I got them.
We're back.
We're back, everybody.
Oh.
Two.
Good job, girlie.
Oh.
Oh, shoot.
Where did the grenade go?
Oh.
It
doesn't help when the...
It kind of like... What's the word?
It kind of auto-aims.
So, even if I go for the head, it like...
aims down.
You see that?
So, it's... I don't know if there's a way to turn that off.
You did it, Merle.
Yeah, I saw it move.
Yeah, so like...
If I'm trying to aim, it tries to like move down a little.
It makes it more difficult.
Yes, girl!
Auto-miss.
Oh!
Please!
Oh, just kidding!
You fool!
You've killed him!
I'm sorry, sir.
His mental shielding was very strong.
I could not dive into his mind.
Oh my god, he sounds so awesome.
You fool!
Who did they kill?
Now we'll never get that detonation code.
Oh, wait.
What?
Boss, I have a good idea.
It was Baker.
Ah!
Whoa, what am I doing?
Oh my god, look at her go.
Yeah!
Oh!
Whoa!
Go stay!
Oh, yeah!
Whoa!
Dodged every single one.
Like a true champion.
Doesn't she pose there in the original?
Doesn't she like kind of...
Psycho Mantis!
Good girl.
Thank you.
Just like that.
Are you saying that to me or Snake?
I mean, wait.
Are you saying that to Meryl or Snake?
Not me, sorry.
Whew, got a little...
A little...
You know.
Naomi, I just had some kind of hallucination.
Naomi, I'm going kind of crazy.
No, Snake.
The nanomachines are functional properly.
So what was it?
Self-insert caught.
It must have been psychometric interference coming from Psycho Mantis.
Fox sounds psychic.
Think of it as a mental feedback loop.
So...
That was Mantis.
I would say that that scene...
It doesn't spoil, but it does...
Oh, I'm bleeding out.
Snake, there we go.
There you go.
Stop bleeding!
Stop!
You're getting...
You're messing up the floor!
We're good?
Okay.
Uh...
Oh, they're all gone even.
Well, almost.
Anything under here?
I can't remember.
Nope.
But there is stuff in here.
That we saw in the pot.
Wait, is there anything in here?
Ahaha!
Very good!
Hacking...
What is...
Is that the nuclear warheads building?
No.
Oh no, this is the first...
Okay, wait.
Because that looks like the tank.
And then...
Okay, no, this is just the building that we're in.
Oh, I see it.
VR missions?
No, I think that top one is the floor we were just at.
The floor you sneak into.
And then the second...
Right?
But there's no tank on this floor.
Huh, I don't know.
Actually, I don't think there is.
What's this one?
Six.
Wait, what is this?
Oh!
Come on, snake.
Here, let me...
Reangle.
Re...
Readjust.
Okay, there we go.
Ah!
Unequipped the gun!
Unequipped the gun, Mint!
X is for shooting!
I mean, no!
X is for crawling!
Oh my god...
P is for fight!
There's nothing under the desk, is there?
Actually, I didn't think about it.
X is for crawling!
A is to shoot!
X is to crawl!
And you shoot good!
Unequipped if you don't wanna waste your bullet!
I'm gonna check under the desk real quick.
Oh!
What the?
Oh, I was like, what is that spinning thing on the radar?
But it's this thingy.
That's so funny.
Nothing.
Okay.
Let's get out of here.
So now we...
Go fight.
Aww.
Now we go fight.
Well, first we go...
Explode.
Beep!
I remember some of the guard choke-out noises in this game being particularly over the top and silly if you want a good laugh.
Chris, thank you.
Not back-sitting at all.
I'm letting you know, I'm trying.
I'm so bad at getting the guy sometimes.
Not sometimes.
Like, almost all the time.
But, you know.
Which floors cave in?
Let's...
Start A.
Um...
What is it, Snake?
Hey!
I'm just saving for no big reason.
Not that I think I'm gonna...
Why can't I be like riding and do a little cart flip...
cartwheel over it, you know?
Thank you.
Shakespeare?
First they take your accent and now you're quoting a western guy?
That goes for items too.
Don't get too greedy or you might be sorry.
Be careful, Snake.
I hate that one.
I'm not gonna listen.
I should...
I feel like I should be calling Kodek more because I don't know how many things are different but also it's fun to talk to them, right?
Try!
He's telling me I'm dumb!
If things are getting too complicated try to simplify your thoughts.
You can also try calling Campbell for advice.
Thank you for the 50 gifted!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Nastasha, what do you have to say?
They were conducting exercises with this new Metal Gear prototype?
Is that what the DARPA chief said?
Yeah, it is.
What the hell?
I heard it was some kind of walking tank that can deliver an accurate nuclear strike from any terrain.
Mountains, deserts, swamps, wherever.
Wherever!
I'll be here and you'll be near!
But what about the PAL system that the DARPA chief mentioned?
It is a device attached to a nuclear weapon system to prevent the missile from being armed or launched.
Usually a secret detonation code or combination is necessary to launch the missile.
According to the chief, there are two codes and the terrorists already know one of them.
The other code.
If the terrorists find out that one too...
Do they though?
Because he's dead.
I gotta hurry and rescue President Baker.
Do they know?
Because one of them is dead.
Okay.
I don't remember.
Let's try down here.
Run!
Three...
Is this a trap?
Wow!
That actually makes your health go down way faster than it did before.
Is this the one I was looking for?
Well, no.
No, it's not because we need the C4.
Right?
You know what?
I'm just gonna crawl anyway.
Crawl, crawl, crawl.
Crawl, crawl, crawl, crawl.
Crawl, crawl.
Oh, don't get up, Snake.
Crawl, crawl, crawl.
Just in case.
I don't think it is though.
Oh, I think we're good.
Am I gonna regret this later?
More C4!
Nice.
Wait, there's so much C4.
I think we...
Oopsie.
Run!
I thought that was a hole.
One.
Grenades?
Is this one a trap?
Oh, doh, doh, doh, doh.
Oh.
Is this one a trap?
It says no smoking.
I can't...
Wait.
Why is she paranoid?
Because sometimes there's traps.
Wait, that's two.
Wait, did that say Famas?
Oh!
Guess we know where to get the Famas.
Wait, are they all labeled?
That's so cute.
Grenade.
Okay, does this one...
PSG?
Were they C4?
Were they labeled...
What is that one?
Nikita?
Were they labeled in the first game too?
I just never noticed.
Nikita.
Oh, cool.
How nice of them.
Now, I'm pretty sure this one...
Falls.
Ugh!
Ah!
Run, Snake, run!
Okay.
No.
Run!
Okay.
The place to blow it up is...
Step back a little bit.
Oh!
Wait, is there just the door?
Beep, beep.
What's this one?
Two.
Oh wait, I don't know where it is then.
In this one, right?
It doesn't...
Oh!
There!
It does look like a different color.
Just kidding.
Okay, C4.
How to use.
Press A button to set.
B button...
Detonate.
Easy.
How do I do the book?
Adult-oriented material.
Full of girly photos and interesting columns.
Interesting.
I'm running around with my book.
I like the music here.
Okay.
Whoa!
There we go.
Didn't have time to paint it, eh?
What were you going to paint it anyway?
Concrete color?
How do you...
How do you paint it?
Wait, hold on.
Let me make sure.
Set to A.
Okay, A to set.
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run.
Wait.
Concrete gray.
Um?
And then those two.
A to set.
This is Ocelot.
Oh my gosh!
Oh!
He looks...
He looks kind of naked in this...
in this position.
He looks a little...
Oh, there we go.
Oh!
Wait.
Why is his jacket, like, over top his body?
Were you cold, President Baker?
Were you cold?
Did they give you a...
a little jacket to help you...
to help you, um, stay warm?
Aww.
Actually, that's even...
His arm sleeves are like...
They're flapping everywhere.
Everywhere there, it's more of a liability.
Cause it's gonna, like...
What if those...
What if the breeze...
Oh my god.
They're gonna touch the wires!
It is Alaska.
You're right.
Okay.
Um...
I'm gonna call real quick.
We're gonna save.
Okay.
Ocelot time, baby.
Snake, you can't use your radar.
Yeah, I know.
Oh.
Don't worry about it.
New file.
Yes.
Ba-ding!
Okay.
Alright.
Be careful, Snake.
Thanks, Meiling.
Wait, I'm gonna go get those grenades.
I don't think I need them right now, but...
Um, you know what?
I will go get them.
Just a half.
Tum!
As Shakespeare said, you can't use the radar.
What if this is what...
That's what he meant, though.
As in like...
You can't get everything you want.
You can't always get...
What you want.
Okay.
I guess we're fine.
And it was...
This one too, right?
I'm so calm.
And, uh...
I think we're safe.
Right?
I'm so scared.
Lots of so calm bullets.
Very good.
Okay, cool.
Perfect.
The first person makes it easier...
compared to the original?
Oh, yeah.
It really does.
I think it's just...
For me, the controller is the more...
difficult thing.
Well, actually...
Um...
The easiest way that I've played the game...
Well, Metal Gear Solid 1...
I've done...
my best...
Like, my best performance...
Playing the Switch version.
Which is absolutely wild.
I think.
Um...
But, I don't know.
I don't know why it was so easy for me.
On a DDR mat.
You'll get used to it.
Yeah, yeah.
I will, uh...
I will practice with it...
some more and stuff.
I gotta get used to, like, the...
The first...
person being here, and then...
Okay.
We don't need to crouch in this.
And we don't need to kick-fight.
We just gotta...
We just gotta shoot.
Hopefully, we can actually shoot him in the head, though.
Oh my god.
Your sleeves!
Be careful!
Oh my god.
He's alive.
Yep.
Astute observation, Snake.
You're the arms tech president, Kenneth Baker, right?
President Baker.
Don't worry.
I'm here to save you.
No!
Don't touch it!
Well,
you're the one who was coughing like crazy, mister.
C4!
Your cough...
My
controller's going crazy.
Right.
Touch that wire and the C4 will blow up the log of the old man.
Oh my god!
So you're the one that the boss keeps talking about.
Look at the way he's standing.
He's so sassy.
And you.
Special Operations Foxhound.
Revolver.
Yes!
Keep going, kid!
Keep going!
Yes!
Dramatic pause!
Oh my god.
Okay.
Yes.
Don't stop.
Arcelor.
Yes!
Oh yes!
Keep it up!
Oh my god.
He's so awesome!
I've been waiting for you, Solid Snake.
Oh, I bet you have!
Now we'll see if the man can live up to the legend.
Shadashaska!
Don't...
This is the greatest handgun ever made.
The Colt Single Action Army.
Six bullets.
Six bullets?
More than enough to kill anything that moves.
Yeah!
He said the thing!
Stares at him.
Just kind of like, why are you putting your gun away, you idiot?
Don't let your guard down!
What do you mean?
Now I'll show you why they call me Revolver.
Revolver.
Yeah, Ocelot!
Draw!
Yeah!
Okay.
How to do this with first person?
Where is he?
Oh!
Hold on!
Let me draw!
Where are you?
Where are you anyway?
Oh!
Hello?
Oh, he's reloading?
I'm alive!
No!
No, Ocelot!
This is too easy!
No way!
Hmm...
You're pretty good.
Just what I'd expect from the man with the same code as the boss.
It's been a long time since I had such a good fight.
That was a good fight.
You're so right.
I'm just getting warmed up.
Ah!
This is... That is actually one of the bigger criticisms of this game.
Is that the boss fights tend to be too easy because of... Watch!
My hand!
Ah!
Poor President Baker is just like...
Oh, God!
Ah!
That's a cool shot.
Speedrunning the fight with Ocelot for real.
This one is really easy to cheese and um...
What's his name?
Uh... Vulcan Raven is very easy to cheese.
Allegedly.
You're that ninja!
After standing mostly still and getting shot seven times, you're pretty good.
You know what I just realized?
Snake's got those Kim Possible lips.
You see it?
I want to hear what he sounds like.
I want to
hear what he sounds like.
I like you.
I have no name.
Oh, he sounds so cool though.
I mean, it's... I get that...
I get that it's sad that it's not Grey Giggles but...
What's the voice...
What's it called?
The voice effect over top?
The voice effect...
Wait, what did it say?
What was it saying?
Whoa!
Sounds like Ryden?
Do you think so?
Oh no!
Oh my god he's going crazy!
Oh, the fight with him is probably gonna be so...
Wow!
Slow motion bullets!
What?
What was that implying?
Oh, he was cutting the top!
Oh, he cut the top of the building just to kick it at Snake!
No way!
The tension...
Bye!
It's a little messy, but okay.
It's like if I'm controlling him...
How do they make my man even more chuny?
Because the man describing these events is absolute otaku freak!
Can you talk?
Who are you?
I'm not one of them.
I like this part too.
The way Snake reacts in this part makes me laugh.
Oh, I get it.
Jim sent you.
Oh, Jim!
Jim!
Answer my question.
What about your code?
There's no time.
I... I talked.
Oh, yeah.
You're weak.
You...
Now the terrorists have both codes and can launch any time.
These cutscenes are crazy.
It's like the Matrix.
It's not like I didn't fight.
It is.
I managed to resist Psycho Mantis' mind probe.
He couldn't read you?
How'd you do it?
Surgical implants in my brain.
Surgical implants?
Kinda like psychic insulation.
Everyone who knows these top secret codes has it.
Wow.
Even the DARPA chief?
Of course.
Dun dun.
But the DARPA chief said Mantis got his code by reading his mind.
Oh.
Are you sure you heard him right?
Yeah.
Anyway, how did they get your code?
Why'd you talk, buddy?
I... I never had any training on how to resist torture.
It looks like he had some fun with you, all right.
It's just a little torture.
He's not human.
I tell you he loved every second of it.
He's such a freak.
He broke it.
Oh.
Looks like you're more than even now.
His was sliced off.
The effects.
You're a funny guy.
He is.
So, the DARPA chief, is he okay?
Nah.
Dead.
Dead?
Dun dun.
It can't be.
He's a little quirky, yeah.
No, that's not what you promised, Jim.
Now you want to shut me up?
Calm down.
Calm down?
What's wrong with you?
I just told you I was here to save you.
I didn't kill the DARPA chief.
He had a heart attack or something.
A heart attack?
Oh, don't be a fool.
Lucky Baker.
Anyway, the terrorists have both codes now.
Wow.
Oh, those boys are totally insane.
They wouldn't hesitate to launch.
I agree.
But what do they really want?
What do they really want?
Who knows?
Maybe they're like us in the arms industry.
Welcome to the bamboo ship.
Thank you so much.
Always looking forward to the next good war.
Well, I'm not going to let these maniacs start a war.
Not today.
Do you still have the card keys?
Card keys?
Give me a card key.
To override the detonation code.
I heard you had them.
No.
Definitely not a god bad woman.
Not anymore.
Who does then?
Not the terrorists?
No.
That woman.
Woman?
Who?
The one with the nice butt.
The soldier that was thrown in prison along with me.
Prison?
Prison.
That female soldier.
She said that she had just joined up as a new recruit.
This girl is a thorn in my side.
Because she refused to take part in the rebellion.
A new recruit?
Could that be the colonel's niece?
I gave her the key.
Looks like she managed to break out of here though.
I hope she's okay.
I gotta go to the bathroom after this part.
I'm sure she is.
She's green, but as tough as they come.
But how did you know she escaped?
I was in contact with her by Kodak.
Oh, this part.
This is the part that I like.
Because in the original, it's like the Goblet of Fire part.
Where in the book, Dumbledore reacts so calmly.
But in the movie, he's crazy.
If she still has it, you should be able to contact her.
In the original, he acts like...
I'm sure she has it.
This one, he acts so crazy.
What frequency was she at?
Oh, yeah.
Give her Kodak.
Let me tell you, it's...
Oh, sorry.
I forgot.
Oh, that's right.
It should be on the back of the package.
Try to contact her.
I'll contact her right away.
And in the original, he's just like damn, and he kind of hits his knee.
Is there some other way to prevent the missile from hitting his head?
In this one, he acts like an actual lunatic.
Hal Emmerich!
Little bit of an oddball, you guys.
Oh.
I'll say after this.
Where is this Emmerich?
Well, he's probably being held somewhere in the nuclear warhead storage building.
It's north from here.
That's where he worked.
Got it.
I understand, but why Metal Gear?
The nuclear age ended with the turn of the millennium.
Oh, you're wrong.
The nuclear threat hasn't disappeared.
The threat is more real than ever before.
It's so icky.
The amount of spent nuclear fuel and plutonium is increasing even today.
Real footage!
Have you ever seen a warehouse full of nuclear material?
You're pretty good.
Thank you.
Drums and drums of nuclear waste stack this high.
As far as you can see.
Because there's still no real way to use it or dispose of it.
So they just close the lid and try to pretend like it'll go away?
Essentially, yes.
Wow.
And they're not even doing a good job of storing it.
No.
Oh, there's just people right there.
Many of the drums are corroded with nuclear waste seeping out of them.
Unbelievable.
Un-be-lievable.
Not only that, several pounds of MUF are reported every year.
Not the MUF!
It stands for material unaccounted for.
It proves that there's a large and well-organized black market in nuclear materials.
Furthermore, since the end of the Cold War, Russian nuclear engineers in particular, are out of work with nowhere to turn.
Hey, I beat him that quickly because I'm good at the game.
In other words, there's plenty of available nuclear material and scientists for making a bomb.
We live in an age where any small country can have a nuclear weapons program.
What about the other superpowers?
The Russians and Chinese still pursue a policy of deterrence.
Deterrence.
Do you see?
Complete nuclear disarmament is an impossibility.
Oh, deterrence.
To maintain our own policy of deterrence, we need a weapon of overwhelming power.
Oh, it hurts.
The Peace Walker flashbacks.
You mean Metal Gear?
Yes.
Oh my god, Rex is so cute.
You know our industry suffered quite a blow as a result of the cuts in military budgets due to this so-called peace.
I remember hearing a lot about mergers and takeovers from the big weapons makers.
Oh, I missed the Ocelot boss fight.
Yes.
Sorry, it lasted like 15 seconds.
And after my company lost their bid to produce the UAV.
And now we have to deal with the US Air Force's next line of fighter jet.
The Metal Gear system was our last ace in the hole.
That's why we pushed to have Metal Gear developed as a black project.
Black project.
Secret projects paid for by the Pentagon's black budget.
Yeah, that's what the DARPA chief talked about earlier.
You can avoid a lot of red tape and get a great lead time on your weapons production.
You avoid the red tape because you use black instead.
Not even a bunch on the military oversight committee.
It's a common secret.
It's a well-known secret.
Bribes.
Just call it the military-industrial complex.
Anyway, Metal Gear was going to be formally adopted after the results of this exercise were analyzed.
I don't give a crap about you or your company.
Yeah.
Yes, that's about what I'd expect from a grunt like you.
Like Victoria's Secret?
Here.
This is what you came for, right?
Ah, thanks.
Finally.
Oh, thanks.
What's that?
An optical disc.
It's all here.
Don't give me your junk.
The main hard drive was destroyed by gunfire.
This is the only remaining copy of the data.
What kind of data?
Solid Snake vs.
Sam Fisher death battle episode.
I'm not seeing...
All the data collected from this exercise.
Don't play dumb.
I know you were sent to get this.
I hid it from that sadistic maniac while he was torturing me.
Where'd you hide it?
They don't know this disc exists.
Make sure that you don't get it.
I know that you report this to Jim.
Where'd you hide that?
To your boss.
Where did you hide that?
I'll give you my card, too.
It'll open up all security level two doors.
Between the cheeks.
I love how flowy his, uh, his bandana is.
So fun to look at.
No.
You go on without me.
Ugh.
My stomach's starting to hurt.
They got my password.
They don't want anything else from me.
Oof.
I have one more question.
Do you have IB?
What was that ninja thing?
It looked like you knew something.
Did it?
That ninja?
That was Foxhound's dark little secret.
Dark little secret?
I'll keep you my dark little secret.
An experimental genome soldier.
Don't tell anyone or you'll be...
You know him?
You should ask Dr. Naomi Hunter from Foxhound.
Oh.
She knows better than I.
Naomi.
You've got to stop them.
If it goes public, my, my company and I are, are finished.
Just another reason.
Who has to know?
What?
Doesn't Metal Gear use currently existing technology?
Metal Gear itself does, but...
Oh!
He's turning green!
What did you do to me?
Oh my god!
He ate the blueberry from...
Willy Wonka!
Oh!
He's turning into...
What's...
A grape!
Why is he so green?
He's hulking out.
Oh!
What are you talking about?
They...
They're just...
Using you...
Using me?
For...
That's it?
Oh!
That one was way less dramatic than, uh...
The DARPA chiefs.
The DARPA chief was crawling all over us!
Um...
Colonel, are you listening?
Now he's dead too!
Yeah, Colonel!
I have no idea.
I'm going to have to find you.
Don't lie to me!
I have no idea.
Some kind of poison?
Well, there are lots of drugs that can cause a heart attack in large doses.
I have no idea, Snake.
But we won't be able to tell without doing an autopsy.
Damn!
Snake, I want you and Meryl to work together.
Can I trust her?
More than you can trust me.
Get in contact with her.
Snake, there's a lot of electrical interference coming from there.
It should be okay if you do burst transmission like us.
But normal transmission is probably impossible.
Try moving away from that area.
Okay.
Snake, get a hold of yourself.
Naomi, what the hell was that ninja thing?
Move Long is the better All-American Rejects song.
You could tell because it was, like, in the Bionicle.
Is that the one that's...
Yes.
We have no one like that in our unit.
Is that the song?
Snake, I'm counting on you.
I'm counting on you.
Alright, we need to get her stuff from the back of the box.
Let's call some people real quick, such as Mei Ling.
Let's save.
I gotta go to the bathroom so bad.
Snake, you can't use your radar in that area.
There's...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Save.
Yes, exactly.
Yeah.
Memory card.
I'll just do new file.
Yes.
I've had too much coffee.
Be careful, Snake.
Come on, Mei Ling.
Tell me one of your stories.
Call Campbell, too.
This sucks.
Yeah.
And on top of that, they both died right in front of my eyes.
I have to pee.
Please.
The only way to stop a nuclear launch is to either use the detonation code release keys...
I guess I didn't have to start this up.
I guess I could have gone to the bathroom.
I gotta go to the bathroom.
Okay.
Or find the Metal Gear chief engineer that President Baker mentioned.
Hal Emmerich.
In any case, you should contact Meryl by codec.
Oh, okay.
Wasn't her frequency written on the back of the package?
Yes.
Oh, thank you.
Okay, I'll be right back.
I'll be right back.
I gotta go to the little ghosty's room.
BRB.
I'm back.
I am back.
Thank you.
For the...
Super chat.
Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
Oh my gosh.
You guys.
Welcome back.
I'm back.
Alright.
As one must do...
In this moment...
One must look at the back of the box.
Which I have...
Right next to me.
We must look at the back of the box, everybody.
So let's pull that up.
So we can get Meryl's codec.
It's written for ants.
I can't read it.
It's so small.
Okay, well...
I can't read it.
Well, we know what it says anyway.
Oh, but we can't even do it here.
Okay.
Oh, there's bullets and stuff there, too.
Hello, mister.
Do we have clearance, too, now?
I don't remember.
Oh, yes, we do.
Grab that.
Oh, never mind.
We didn't even use that many bullets.
Wait, what is this place?
What is this place?
Oh, the armory.
Oh, this is the...
Oh, now the people are here.
Okay.
Um...
But we gotta go...
Oh, well...
I guess...
Okay.
Was that door always there?
Not the size of the codec, but how you use it.
Right, of course, of course.
We... There's no reason for us to go in here.
We...
There's no reason for us to go in here.
Yeah, I don't think.
Okay, let's go...
I'm just gonna go this way, cause...
But...
Well, the guys are gonna, like, walk down the way.
Let's get our M... Hello?
M9?
Control... Controller?
There we go.
Okay.
We gotta go to the...
Um...
Nuclear Warheads building.
For...
Our little buddy.
Yes, even in the original?
That door wasn't available...
In the OG game with your card key at the time.
Okay, that's probably why.
It's originally like level 6.
That's so interesting.
Okay.
Alright, don't be a baby.
I'm a little scared though.
Cause what if they see me?
Where is the trap?
Oh, the trap is already activated.
Nice.
Okay.
Snake, turn around!
Press the button!
Drop him in the hole!
That's so rude!
I don't remember if there's any level 2s in here.
But we got it.
We'll come back anyway.
It doesn't really matter, I think.
Uh, whoop.
Press...
1.
Oh, that was close.
He was coming right up behind us.
Oh, the Famas!
It's okay, we'll come back.
Famas is level 2.
Why is it...
That was so close.
You little jerk.
I saw him back there.
Hmm...
Where are you?
Oh, oh!
Hello.
Hello, sir.
That's one down.
Next one...
Is...
Uh...
Actually, I don't know where he is.
Next one is...
Thank you, Soup!
Um...
This part is so lame.
Oh, dang it!
It's so not good as the original.
Get rid of the chorus and it's just so...
Oh, hello to you!
Hello, hello!
It's just not as nice.
Where the heck is this other guy?
Ah!
Not the status report!
You're killing me!
Oh, gosh!
No!
Please, no!
They don't...
We don't need the backup unit!
Oh, is there a...
No.
Yes!
Ah!
It feels so good.
Status report...
It's the bane of my existence, for real.
The status report will actually kill me.
I think.
Just imagining things.
Just imagining...
things.
They're not gonna come up here, are they?
Oh, shoot!
They're right here!
Ah!
Um, hold on.
Um...
Hmm...
I didn't realize they were on the second floor.
How do I want to handle this?
How do we want to...
I thought they were down below.
I didn't know they were up...
You didn't see them on your radar?
No!
They weren't on the radar!
Can I
get up, please?
Also, can we attach my rations?
Thank you.
And, uh...
Uh...
Oh, please, please, please, please!
Please!
You piece of shit!
Shut up!
Oh, oh...
And, uh...
I'm bleeding out.
But you will be too soon!
Can you, like, not run towards me?
It's stressing me out.
I underestimated.
Oh my god.
Ouch!
Can you calm down?
Clear!
No...
Don't keep going.
Get up, stank!
Oh, wait.
My cardboard box!
How could you?
Ah, la la la.
Do you think I can get him?
There we go.
I'm going to get him.
Stop!
Please, stop coming!
Why are you hooming?
At who?
At what?
Who are you hooming at?
Clear!
Get out of here.
I think I just...
Maybe ruined my chances of getting away with that.
All good!
Return to your positions, everybody.
Return to your positions.
If I knock this guy out, though, it's going to cause another status report issue thing, isn't it?
Stop move.
Actually, can you not make some noise?
Can you, like...
Are they
coming up?
Can't tell.
Are they going to come up?
Hmm.
I'm actually not sure.
I don't think so.
Lockers?
Oh, you're right.
Actually, that might be even better.
Oh.
I don't see...
I don't see anyone on the radar, so maybe it's okay.
B, B, B is to attack.
B, B.
B, B, B, B.
Oh.
Okay.
I think we're good, maybe.
The camera is so fast.
Did it go?
What?
No!
Please, no!
I did it!
I did it, me too!
Safe.
Oh, safe.
No!
It was so fast!
La, la, la.
Uh.
La.
This goes back outside, doesn't it?
Uh-oh.
I don't want to shoot the cams yet until we get the suppressor for the...
SOCOM.
Just imagining things.
So, so true.
So true.
Just imagining things.
Is there any way to get down from here, or...
Does this just go outside?
I don't want to go outside yet.
Or again.
It's so bright out.
Is there anything in here?
Hmm.
La, la, la.
Is there any items, though?
Nope.
Okay.
All the way back.
Maybe the...
Maybe they don't know where I am.
Maybe it got rid of the alert.
Right?
Yeah.
Yeah, it just got rid of it, probably.
Nothing here.
See?
Right.
But that guy who was asleep, he's going to be my biggest worry.
Because we're going to not know if he is staring at us or not.
Or not.
He's probably awake now.
Okay.
And the camera.
Um...
What's our best...
What's our best call to action here?
Oh.
I can hear him.
Oh, I can hear him.
Can I get him from here?
Nothing here.
Oh.
I missed my shot.
I wonder, though.
Maybe we... Hold on.
I'm going to...
Oh, wait.
If I press A, it doesn't come out.
Oh.
We can't get...
We can't get low enough.
That's a shame.
That is a darn shame.
Okay.
I'm going to wait for him to come all the way back.
We're going to have to be fast.
Actually...
I have another idea.
Wait a second.
To get to Huey, we go through...
We go to... Yes.
I know where to go.
Okay.
Yes, yes, yes.
Um...
Is he walking away?
I think we're good.
Can I go down?
Hello?
How do I go down?
Nothing here.
Please don't...
Please don't notice me.
Okay.
Good, good, good.
Here we go.
This is...
How do I drop?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
How do I drop down?
Drop down.
We got to go through...
How do I...
I said... I keep saying Huey.
Oh, no.
My brain is poisoned.
My brain is poisoned, you guys.
No.
Not Huey.
Shit.
Take him over here.
I'm getting a little bit more used to the controls now.
Yippee.
Thank you, sir.
Okay.
Where's our other friend at?
I'm not going to get that guy because he scares me.
What?
Just run.
Oh.
It's this guy.
I forgot about him.
Oh, shit.
Oh, gosh.
Never mind.
We're okay.
Everything's good.
How do I attach the suppressor?
Get out of here, Huey.
SMH.
Truth.
Respond.
Oh, here.
Equip.
With you.
Attach.
Yippee.
Now we can kill.
Without.
Without worry.
Thank you.
Um.
They're not going to come in here.
Oh, my God.
I think.
I think I'm getting a sense of deja vu.
In here.
I think I'm receiving...
Oh, a weird, strange...
What is this?
Sense of...
Oh, my brain.
Brain hurts.
It's like I've lived through this before.
Oh, my gosh.
Okay.
Attach the rations.
No.
Oh, okay.
You're just...
Where are you?
Acknowledge what?
Huh?
That I'm too strong for you?
Okay.
Hmm.
I know they're going to come in here.
And they're going to see my box.
And they're going to come after me.
They're going to see my box.
Why don't you go after your dead friends first?
Hmm.
Level a million IQ, everybody.
Um.
Excuse me.
I'm trying to call.
Thank you.
In any case, you should contact Meryl by codec.
Wasn't her frequency...
I forgot this whole time that we haven't called Meryl yet.
Oh, my gosh.
I forgot this.
I was just like, Meryl, when are you going to open the door for us to go?
We haven't even contacted her.
Oh, I'm...
Oh, no.
I forgot this whole time.
Who are you?
I was really impressed.
When are you going to open the door for us to go?
You're the Colonel's niece.
Meryl, right?
No, it's not him.
Just exactly who are you?
I'm the fool that your uncle sent to this hellhole.
You came alone?
You are so silly.
I don't need lectures.
You're just like your uncle, you know.
I didn't know my uncle.
We go way back.
What's your name?
My name is not important.
Could you be Snake?
Are you Solid Snake?
That's what some people called me.
The legendary Solid Snake?
You?
Yeah, I'm a little legendary.
Sorry about before.
I wasn't sure if you were one of the good guys.
But I knew you were.
How?
It's your eyes.
My eyes?
Not soldier's eyes.
They're rookie's eyes, right?
No.
They're beautiful, compassionate eyes.
Just what I'd expect from the legendary Solid Snake.
You trying to sweep me off my feet?
Wow.
Don't worry.
You'll land back on them once you meet me.
The reality is no match for the legend, I'm afraid.
I don't believe that.
Have more confidence, Snake.
Why did you look so surprised when you saw my face?
Because you look just like him.
You mean the terrorist leader, Liquid Snake?
Liquid Snake.
Yeah.
You know him?
You're not brothers, are you?
I have no family.
So what's the deal then?
I don't know.
I killed my dad.
Maybe I'll ask him personally.
But first, I want some information.
I miss womanizing, Snake.
You were involved in this exercise from the beginning.
What exactly happened here?
I just joined the training that same day.
That's okay.
But what is this place?
I don't think it's just a nuclear weapon disposal facility.
Yeah, it's a little weird.
It's just like them.
Nobody's told you anything, did they?
Nope.
Okay.
You see, this place isn't really for disposing nuclear weapons.
This base is owned and operated by a dummy corporation of arms tech.
This is a civilian base?
Right.
For the development of Metal Gear.
Guys, what should I have for dinner today?
Colonel.
I'm starting to get hungry.
Actually, I think I have a pizza in the fridge.
I was gonna have it yesterday, but I didn't.
Why pizza?
You read my mind.
They figured they could help keep it all hush-hush.
But they must have been test-firing dummy warheads for a while.
Why just this time?
The coffee is making me a little shaky.
I heard it was because this was supposed to be a final test before the formal adoption of the Metal Gear program.
So I'll have to go start the...
That's what I heard, anyway.
When I went to the bathroom, I should have started the oven.
Sounds kind of fishy.
It smells fishy in here.
So what do you think the terrorists want?
Sorry, I'm not sure.
I was captured with President Baker right after the revolt started.
Damn.
That's when he gave you the detonation code override keys, right?
That's right.
Reticulated Python.
Well, women have more hiding places than men.
Oh, and some more.
Anyway, you met Baker, huh?
Girlie?
He's dead.
Heart attack.
What do you mean?
The chief died from a heart attack, too?
Yeah.
Was either of them sick or anything?
No.
Not that I heard of.
You know, first time I get it, but second time, it's a little suspicious.
Something funny's going on.
Sounds like it.
But I have no idea what.
Me neither.
Dinner, diazepam, and cigarettes.
Do you know the person who designed Metal Gear?
You mean Dr. Emmerich?
How?
He should be in the research lab in the second floor basement of the nuclear warhead storage building to the north.
Not Huey.
I can't believe I kept saying Huey.
Second floor basement.
Yeah.
That's where his lab is.
I think they're forcing him to work on the nuclear launching program.
So they'll need him alive until that's done anyway.
Thank you.
Miller does say going to the bathroom is important since you never know when a long cutscene will begin.
In case we can't override the detonation code in time, I need to ask him how to destroy Metal Gear.
You plan to take that thing on by yourself, Snake?
Oh yeah.
It won't be the first time.
It's so cool.
How do we get to the nuclear warhead storage where the doctor's being held?
There's a cargo door on the first floor of this building that leads to the north.
What's the security level of the door there?
Five.
Five!
I've gotta go save the doctor.
You should go to the...
I'm going with you.
No, you're just gonna get in my way.
You're still too green.
I want you to hide somewhere.
I told you to be a good girl.
Oh yes you are.
You pause for just one second in front of your enemy and it's all over.
I know, I'm still green too.
Good luck doesn't last forever.
Five!
I don't know what happened.
I just couldn't pull the trigger right away.
Sad music?
I never had any problems in training.
It was frightening to think that with a pull of a trigger I could take someone's life.
It's not like shooting targets in training.
Wait.
What is this music?
I always dreamed of being a soldier.
Every day of my life.
My mind and body for the one day when I could finally see some real action.
And now...
So what now?
You wanna quit?
I can't quit.
I can't allow myself to quit now.
Listen.
You're not normal if you don't feel something the first time you kill.
I don't hate it, but...
Killing without guilt produces more carnage.
In a war...
You'll get used to it.
All of mankind's worst emotions, worst traits emerge.
It's easy to forget what a sin is in the middle of a battlefield.
I don't hate it, like I said, but it's not as iconic.
But this isn't a war.
It's a terrorist action.
You're just a little jumpy from the combat high.
The adrenaline in your bloodstream is starting to thin out.
Just take it easy.
But I learned all about combat high at the academy.
We'll talk about it later.
For now, just think about keeping yourself alive.
Can you open the door for me?
I think I'm in trouble.
If I get out of here alive, I'll think about that other stuff.
I need to get the hell.
Okay.
Let me try to say this another way.
Stay the hell out of my way.
You're a real bastard.
Just like my uncle said.
I told you.
The real me is no match for the legend.
What if I just hide under the...
the tank until...
Okay, Snake.
I'll be a good girl.
We'll link up after I grab the doctor.
Hang on to the key until then.
Got ya.
But listen, I know this area better than you.
Call me if you have any questions.
Be careful, okay?
I love the awkward laugh together.
After I open up the cargo door, I'll contact you.
Wait!
You're a...
Thank you!
Your influence made me buy the Metal Gear collection on Switch for my birthday!
Woohoo!
Have fun with it!
Um...
I have to leave first.
Get the FAMAS.
Yeah, we'll go back to the armory and go get it.
You know what?
Because we're right here by the...
I'm in caution anyway, so it's probably...
Come on, please!
Please, Snake!
No, God!
Please, please, please.
No one.
Just press the button.
Press the button!
Thank you.
Please, please, please, please!
Oh, God!
They're both coming!
Easy.
Which, uh...
Two.
Oh...
Who's there?
No one.
Who's that?
It's the enemy.
I need...
It is?
Oh...
Oh, come on!
Let me just get that gun!
Um...
I'll go in blasting.
I don't like the alert.
Oh my gosh!
Get out of my way!
Out of my way!
What the?
What?
No!
Is this a trap?
I think this one's a trap.
This one we need the cigarettes for.
Yeah.
Uh...
Are they gonna come in here?
That was so close!
They won't come in here because...
What are they gonna do?
Pass through the lasers?
They can't.
I don't...
What?
Who just died?
Um...
Huh?
Who just died?
He fell into the trap hole?
No way.
It's gonna run out and they're gonna leave.
Nice.
Okay.
He just does that.
I almost pressed the wrong button.
I almost pressed A when I had it equipped.
Press Y button for safety?
What do you mean?
Wait, I can turn the safety on?
Probably should save.
You are so...
right.
Can call it fake?
It's the theme they don't use anymore.
Save complete.
Come on, Mei-Ling.
Give me that.
Snake.
Oh, let's also call the colonel since we got Meryl.
I'm not wise.
Avoid the trap.
I got you, girl.
I know.
I was so smart before.
It looks like the place is protected by infrared sensors.
Copyright issues, right?
Yeah, it was very...
Very similar... wait.
No!
Colonel!
Your nephew!
Your nephew...
Niece!
Your niece!
Um...
Yeah, it was very similar to...
to...
Russian composed song.
So, unfortunately, it had to be...
Um...
Had to...
Could not use it anymore.
So sad.
Oh, there's the hole.
That is so...
I thought that was a hole again!
Oh my god!
Don't see me, but I am gonna...
Just gonna...
There we go.
Sleep tight.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Come on!
Please!
Wait a minute.
You reheat your pizza in the oven?
No, it's um...
Ah!
Perfect.
It's one of those, like, oven pizzas.
Where I can see ya.
No, it's...
Please smash the ball!
Thank you for the... super job!
What does that mean?
It's been nine years.
Wait, where is the...
Gas.
I thought you said you'd be a good girl.
I changed my mind.
Don't get careless.
That's when...
things always turn sour.
You said you'd be a good girl.
Sorry, but this is the only way I can figure whether or not I'm cut out to be a soldier.
Um...
I gotta get my hands dirty.
Actually, where... can I get the thermal goggles yet?
Cause the one room had...
the suppressor and the other...
had...
Wait.
Be careful, Snake.
That airlock is set with infrared sensors.
What is it?
You probably can't see them with your naked eyes, but there are infrared beams coming out of that wall.
Touch any one of them and the doors will seal off and the place will be flooded with poison gas.
Somehow you've got to get through without setting off those sensors.
I'm gonna die from the cigarettes!
Cigarettes are gonna kill me.
Uh...
Okay.
Okay, this one's slow.
Don't see me in here.
Oh, it's really...
Okay.
Nothing here.
Yep, nothing here.
Nice and easy.
I wonder if I should use one.
Um...
What is...
Mint alignment.
Good girl?
Bad girl?
Neutral girl?
I think I'm a...
I was a good girl, but I changed my mind.
I think I will use it just in case though.
We're about to go into another fight.
So we'll get some more rations.
Uh... okay.
Okay, that one is down.
It's really slow.
So now probably is...
Okay, it's going back up.
It's so slow.
This one's not so bad.
Nice.
Yippee!
I'm a bad girl.
I changed my mind.
I'm a bad girl now.
Good thing we got the grenades.
Who are you?
Who is this?
Deep Throat?
Never mind about that.
You're not using burst transmission.
Are you nearby?
There's a tank in front of your position.
Waiting to ambush you.
What?
Who are you anyway?
One of your fans.
Me?
You're one of my fans, huh?
I am going to save too.
Let's actually call Campbell too.
Because we didn't do that yet.
Colonel, I got a codec call from someone outside this operation.
We missed the one I guess about Meryl.
My bad.
I know.
We were monitoring the call.
Mei Ling knows everything about the communication system.
He's a wisp.
He's part of the fandom.
Have her explain it to you.
Thanks for the advice.
But the question is...
How did he learn it?
It's top secret information.
So you mean someone leaked the information.
And that's the only explanation I can think of.
Who's got my number?
Mei Ling, do you know where that transmission originated from?
Why are you so quiet all of a sudden?
I'm sorry.
The radio waves were too weak to locate their source.
But I'm sure he's near you.
Snake, you'll have to go through the minefield to advance.
One of my fans.
Okay.
Um...
Hey, Master Miller.
Master, does the name Deep Throat mean anything to you?
Yeah.
Deep Throat?
What?
You mean the guy from Watergate?
No.
But he uses the same name.
How do you know, Snake?
You don't know.
You don't know if it's the same guy from Watergate.
You can't say for sure.
You don't even know who he is.
He wasn't using burst transmission.
It seems he was transmitting from somewhere on this base.
Somewhere on this base?
Yes.
I have no idea who that could be.
Master Miller is very intrigued in this information.
He's like, who else is on the base?
Hey, Meryl, do you know a Deep Throat?
Sounds like...
Sounds like harassment if I ask her.
You'll be able to see the mines displayed on your radar.
Hey, Meryl, do you know Deep Throat?
Oh, we didn't even ask her.
Okay, we have some... a little bit of a...
We have, I guess, some...
Some clash.
After you locate the mines on your radar, crawl forward and retrieve them.
Oh, I'm gonna crawl forward and retrieve them.
...have killed over 20,000 non-combatants in the past 30 years...
Is that real?
...in countries like Cambodia and Nicaragua.
The killing and maiming of innocent victims...
Master Miller will be like...
...continues long after the wars have ended.
It is easy to plant the mines, you see.
But removing them is a different matter.
She's out.
She was like...
She didn't even let us ask.
By the way, bombs?
The superpowers need to donate more mine detectors...
...and other equipment to remove them.
It is the least we could do after laying them.
Yeah.
People still find grenades and stuff to this day.
Which is insane to me.
Pick up.
If you're one of my fans, isn't it an honor to have me call you?
Wouldn't you be like, wow!
A minefield, huh?
Don't forget to use your mine detector.
Oh, I got it.
When you find out where a mine is, crawl forward...
...and try to recover it.
In this game, does it matter which way I crawl towards it?
A minefield, huh?
Do I have to crawl from behind?
What can I do for you, Snake?
I'm just saving.
You know.
Don't forget to save.
Save!
Too shy to pick up.
Wow, the save is so fast.
How's it going, Snake?
Have you gotten used to the radar yet?
I'm getting there.
Imagine if Master Milla answered, Who told you that code name?
Pretty convenient, huh?
It also makes it easy for us to see everything.
You're watching everything?
Of course.
If you were my boyfriend, you'd never be able to cheat on me.
Being monitored 24 hours a day...
That'd be like hell.
Don't think of it like that.
At least you'd never get lost.
Snake does not like being watched.
I'll tell you, years ago when I was in another unit, my unit's morale was at an all-time low.
It was up to me to boost their morale somehow.
What do you mean by that?
What do you mean by that, Customer Johnson?
Is this a mine?
Oh.
Oh!
Holy cow, that was so close.
Nope,
turn around.
Just like that.
Be a good girl.
And then I can get up.
And we can go this way.
I'm too scared to know if I have to...
If I have to approach them from behind or not.
You know what I mean?
Spin.
But I guess maybe not.
Because I can get...
These ones?
Or...
Uh...
Just go?
Just get them?
I'm afraid of triggering the cutscene.
Ooh!
It doesn't matter in the first game.
So...
Maybe it's fine.
They will not go off?
Okay.
I'm trusting you guys.
That's so evil.
Okay.
That was scary.
That was so scary.
Alright.
No more mind detector.
I think we're good.
Clip our rations.
Um... Okay.
How to use the grenades.
Press A button to hold.
Release to throw.
How long button is pressed.
Varies the distance.
And we got...
A couple chaff grenades.
Not a lot.
Just a few.
But it should be enough to maybe get them stunned a couple times.
Oh!
When did we get magazines?
Mint Boss, I discovered you by Metal Gear.
When you were in heaven over a year ago and became a fan.
I discovered a long-term health issue and had a rough time.
Your positivity and Metal Gear brain rot helped save my life.
Oh my gosh, George!
I'm glad that...
Rather, I hope you're doing better now.
And I hope that...
Or I'm glad that...
I was able to help out even if just a little bit.
Okay.
I don't remember...
How to do this fight.
Like I remember and I don't remember at the same time.
Oh my gosh, we're gonna see Vulcan Raven for the first time though.
This is so exciting.
Come on out, buddy.
Like you use the chaff to...
Distract him and then you...
Throw the grenade...
Oh my ears.
You throw the grenade inside.
Alright.
Average VTuber enjoyer, thanks for the 10 gifted!
My D!
Wow!
Oh!
This is Raven's territory.
He's gonna say it!
Snakes don't belong in Alaska!
I will not let you pass.
He doesn't sound as cool.
Yeah!
Snakes don't belong in Alaska.
Whoa!
Snake, don't just stand there.
I have a message.
Go bird, go!
Snake, what is wrong with you?
Oh my god!
Snake, what's wrong with you?
That's right.
You belong on the ground.
Oh, I see.
I hear it now.
I hear it more now.
You belong on the ground.
I'm like a slithery snake.
A little snake.
You should crawl on the ground like the snake you are.
Come, let's fight!
Okay.
Don't forget to shut it!
Yeah, don't forget to shut it, buddy.
Okay.
Let me also...
Wait.
Chaff grenades, press A to aim, release, to throw.
Okay.
So we gotta get pretty close so we can...
We only have six, though.
Okay.
Remember to punch the tank.
Can I actually?
Oh my god.
Wait.
Why is there a...
He came out to laugh at me.
Oh my gosh.
I wish I could cartwheel right now.
No!
Oh my god.
Okay, I'm just gonna throw the chaff grenade.
Oh gosh, please!
I don't know if I... Okay, I threw it.
Nice.
I'm dying.
Ouch.
I don't know where I threw it.
To the...
You don't... Do not.
Do not.
Ow!
Oh my god.
Snake.
Where did he go?
Okay.
Oh god!
I'm stuck inside the hole!
What?
Oh no, he's gonna run me over.
He's gonna run me...
Why did you throw it that way?
Get that guy.
There we go.
Yeah, yeah.
And... Nice.
I think.
Actually, I'm not sure.
Actually,
I don't know if that worked.
Come here, gunner one.
Oh!
Nice.
Oh god!
Please, snake!
Please!
Oh my god.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Ohhhhhhh!
Laowie!
Oh my god.
Snake, please!
Oh, that did not work.
Oh, gunner two!
Oh, I pressed it but it didn't work.
Okay, that's fine.
I don't think it registered because he was loading.
Ha!
It lands right in his lap!
It's so funny.
Ha, ha, ha.
He's like holding on to it.
Oh, we have to wait for him to come back up.
Okay, there we go.
Alright, come back mister.
Oh, yeah.
Don't run me over.
Oh!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Oh gosh.
We only have one ration left.
Ha!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh my god.
Get up, snake.
Okay, I'm gonna chop grenade real quick.
So that we can, um...
Oh my gosh.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Where's some rations?
Please.
Please, rations.
Oh, no, no, no.
There's no rations.
Oh no, there's no rations.
Okay, that's not good.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Uh...
I know I might be wasting them but I don't want them to get me with the...
I'm about dead.
I'm gonna die.
I'm gonna die for real.
Where are the rations?
Um...
I'm gonna die!
If he gets me one more time, I'm dead.
Boo!
I can't... Oh.
Uh, yeah, that's fine actually.
So unfair.
This is so unfair!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Oh, that was a nice hit.
Ha!
Oh, dang it, he's not there yet.
There
are no rations.
I'm gonna die again.
Please.
So unfair.
This is so unfair!
Oh, la, la, la, la, la.
Don't get me.
Don't... Ah!
Oh my god, he just...
Oh, there he is, there he is.
Nice, nice, nice.
Ah!
Oh, we...
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la...
La, la, la, la, la, la...
We were so close.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Last time I did that fight...
I don't wanna brag, but I did it in one try.
Two!
That was too early.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Stop it!
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Oh, wait.
Oh!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
You wasted all the time laughing at me!
This is so unfair.
That's so unfair!
I can't believe!
That is so unfair!
No way!
Okay, well, I'm here now, I guess.
Oh my God!
That's right!
And then he goes inside for a second.
Come back out!
Oh, wait.
I'm gonna lose my health.
Oh my God!
Don't run me over!
You know what?
It's fine.
Wait, did he go back in?
You son of a jerk!
You...
You poopy hole!
Yeah, let it... I just ran right into that.
There we go.
Oh, no!
When
I got shot, it...
Oh my gosh, the way it lands in his lap is so funny.
When I got shot, it made me drop my grenade.
That's so messed up.
No, that's the wrong way.
That's the wrong way.
No, no, no.
I'm waiting for my...
Don't shoot me, please.
This is so...
Oh!
No!
Gotta fix my contact.
Thank you.
The voice is the same as Robin from Teen Titans.
No way!
Really?
Oh my God, he's gonna run!
Oh, no, no, no!
Get up!
Where did... Why did you turn around?
Haha!
This is...
I miss Ocelot fight.
The way it lands in his lap.
Okay.
He's down, but also so are we, basically.
We are so not looking good.
Why are there...
It does sound like Robin!
You're... It is Robin!
Um...
Still got two rations.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Oh, that's not what I meant to do.
It's okay, though.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I dropped it.
Shoot!
This way!
Don't run over me.
Why is this fight so stupid?
Please!
Snake, just throw it in there!
No!
There we go.
Yes, yes, yes.
Run, run, run, run, run, run.
Run, run, run.
Run, run.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There we go.
I'm gonna... I'm gonna die.
I'm gonna...
I dropped the grenade again.
Let's go get some more...
More grenades, please.
Thank you.
Where are you?
Where's...
You think it would be easier finding a tank?
Golly!
Whoa, Molly!
What?
And...
Shoot!
Oh my god!
This hurts so much.
No!
What?
That didn't get in him?
Someone said to crawl in here.
What happens if I do?
Is there another...
There's just ammo in here.
There's no...
There's no ration in here.
There's only ammo in here.
You're not supposed to get run over by the tank.
Aren't you supposed to run out of bullets at some point?
I pressed A.
Please.
Why didn't that work?
No, Snake, please.
Why?
What are these cutscenes?
What are these cutscenes that are killing me?
I don't understand.
I keep thinking that the cutscene means that it's hitting him, but it's not.
Oh my goodness.
I wish there was some more.
Does the stun grenade help so much?
I see that they're suggesting it.
Why don't they give any rations, though?
The game says, get good.
Truly.
The game just says, get good, loser.
I hate this.
I...
Why do you show me that?
Oh, there it is.
There it is.
In his little lap.
What?
But it showed it in his lap!
Or just get hit immediately again.
That's okay, too.
Shoot!
Right there.
No!
Oh!
Now it worked.
Yeah!
Why are you saying, Vince, die, die, die?
What do you mean?
The cutscene you keep seeing is when a grenade destroys a tank tread.
There's so many ways to do this, but she's stubborn.
Hey, this is the way that I've always done, you know?
And, yeah, I am stubborn.
What of it?
What?
Oh, he's doing sick wheelies.
Okay.
Get up.
Get out.
You know what?
That's how every Metal Gear game is, actually.
There's... Oh, my God.
No, please.
Oh!
But... Okay.
Okay.
I see it.
I get it now.
It kind of makes it so it... Oh, shit.
Oh, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It makes it so it's harder for it to move.
I get it.
What?
Where did that come from?
It just completely rolled.
Punch the tank.
Okay.
I'll punch the tank.
I did so well every time I fought this dang thing in the original.
I truly...
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm only gonna... I'm just gonna say...
I'm gonna... I'm gonna chalk it up to performance anxiety.
That's all I can say.
That's all I can... You know, I can believe in what really...
Oh, my God.
Maybe because I'm playing it the way that I have been in... What's it called?
In the original?
But, like, this is still so similar.
So, it's... You know.
Just CQC it.
Does that actually work?
I can't tell if you guys are trolling me.
Where'd you go?
Right in his lap.
Like Santa Claus.
We're only on gunner one.
Oh, gosh.
Round two.
Come on, gunner two.
See how you like this.
Thanks, Robin.
Wow.
That did big damage.
Can you move?
Stop capping me.
Why are you so obsessed with me?
Okay, we're going.
Up, up, up.
Go, go, go.
Run, run, run.
Oh, I only have four grenades left.
Please.
Nice.
I
need more grenades.
Don't follow me.
No, not trap grenades.
Regular grenades.
Oh, grenade, grenade.
I need more grenade, grenade.
There we go.
Santa Claus.
Wait.
Is it going to explode?
Did it already explode?
Oh.
Okay,
I'm going to go punch the tank.
I'll punch the tank.
You guys want me to punch the tank?
I'll go punch the tank.
CQC to flip the tank.
I wouldn't believe it in this game, truly.
He's so... Oh my god, he's aiming right at me.
This is so funny.
Okay.
Beat up the tank!
Ouch!
You guys, it didn't work.
It didn't...
Hold on, my chat froze.
Oh, my chat froze.
My tap just crashed.
No, I'll just do this.
Give me a second.
I almost died!
You guys, how could you lie to me?
How could you do that?
How could you lie to me?
You CQC'd the chat instead?
Okay, I think we're good.
Where is he?
Hold on, I'm going to go this way.
There it is.
No!
Hold on!
Don't cap me!
Let me get out of here first.
Okay.
We're so close.
We just got to do it.
We just got to beat him.
Up and away!
Sorry, Robin.
Why are you...
It's gonna explode.
It's gonna explode, Snake!
It's gonna explode!
No way, he's walking.
Oh my god, what a dummy.
Oh, nice.
Number three.
Wow.
Wait, Vulcan Raven...
How
are you still alive?
A buffoon.
From your what?
General Ivan, I hear that you lost your arm and ran away home.
Watch your tongue, Shaman.
Thank you!
In the language of the Sioux people, Sioux means snake.
Snake.
It is known as an animal to be feared.
Well, Snake is mine now.
When I meet him next, I'll take special care of him.
Oh yes, you will.
Not yet.
Oh, never mind.
Don't kill him yet.
He and I will meet again.
Yes, we will.
Sioux snake.
Yes, the raven on my head.
It thirsts for his blood.
Kaka!
Yeah!
I love Vulcan Raven.
He's so cool.
Thirst for his blood.
Wait, can I go back out?
I kinda wanna get some more stuff.
Wait, are the cameras gonna be here though?
Actually, I don't remember.
When did the camera show up?
Not quite yet.
Cool.
But, are there mines?
I don't think so.
Grenade.
Anything else?
That guy didn't even leave anything either.
Chaffs.
Which we will need lots and lots of later on.
Oh, this is all back too.
Nice.
Grenade.
Doesn't hurt to stock back up on some things.
Right!
Is there anything under the tank?
Can we even go under the tank?
Spin.
Nope.
Any goodies?
Things for me to collect?
Anything that I missed out on?
I don't think so.
Mei Ling would tell me that I am a fool right now.
Was that there the whole time?
But, I did so well on that last one.
We have 5 out of 5.
I didn't even use any.
So, take that.
Game.
Speaking of Mei Ling.
Let's save.
Save.
Thank you!
Just giving him the card like that.
Implying Robin flying out to the tank and landing in front of Snake was plaid.
I know.
Right!
We'll save complete.
There we go.
Okay.
Snake, have you ever heard the saying, friendly counsel cuts off many foes?
No.
It means that a little bit of advice from friends can save you a lot of trouble.
I know.
You should think about it.
If you're in trouble or if you need some information about something, please contact Colonel Campbell or someone else.
Okay?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Oh.
Okay.
That is so...
Oh my gosh.
That's so true.
Last night, I don't know.
Like recently?
Well, I don't know.
Ever since I came back, I've been feeling like kind of a little overwhelmed.
I feel like I'm kind of like a little...
There's just been a lot going on.
That I'm like, oh my gosh, I don't know.
I don't know.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Essentially, I've been kind of feeling like super not rusty.
It's just that, you know, when I was streaming before, I, you know, I was teeny tiny.
And then in heaven, I had a lot of stuff handled for me.
And then I came back.
Okay.
And there's like, you know, like things that I'm just like, I don't know how to handle some of this stuff.
And so last night, I like talked with Mataram for like maybe two hours.
I was just like, are you free?
Because I've just been feeling like it was like we talked until like 2 a.m.
or something.
I was like, I'm feeling I need I need your advice.
I'm so overwhelmed.
And I was like, I was like crying.
I'm just like.
So just like.
So I don't know what I'm doing.
But she gave me some good advice.
She's good to help.
Good stuff.
Good.
Good to help me.
And like, I've been talking with some other people, too.
Just about.
I don't know.
Sorry.
That, like, really resonated with me for some reason.
Thanks, Mei-Ling.
You're a real one.
You're a real one, Mei-Ling.
Wait.
There wasn't anything in here either, was there?
Unless it respawned.
Oh.
Oh, there is.
Nothing behind me?
Yeah.
Thanks, Mei-Ling.
Yeah, it's real advice.
Oh.
There we go.
Nice.
Okay, I think I got everything from this area for now.
Yeah.
But, yeah.
Yeah, it's just been... it hasn't been easy.
Because I'm... yeah, like I said...
But it's... you know, it's fine.
I'm just feeling all sorts of things.
Feeling all sorts of ways.
Let's get our ration.
Oh!
Never mind.
We don't need it.
I'm too good.
Wow!
This is so cool!
Look at them going!
Literally growing pains.
Yeah, a little maybe.
Let's see.
We don't need our mind detector anymore.
I'm gonna put our rations...
Oh wait!
We can't shoot in here.
Wait!
We can put them to...
No!
I was gonna say we can use our M9, but we can't!
Use that either!
Okay.
Never mind.
The game... before it lets you at least try, but now it's like...
Don't even think about it, missy.
Trying on a hearing aid play is good for the soul.
You're doing so well.
Keep it up.
Thanks, Conqueror.
I'm not doing that well, but it's okay.
I'm having fun.
It is interesting...
That's where they keep the nuclear warheads.
Can't you see them?
No, I'm...
Yeah.
There's lots of boxes piled up in here, but...
Why are there just warheads in boxes?
They're all dismantled warheads.
They just leave them here?
Yeah!
Just like President Baker said.
Totally careless.
They're working on a limited budget.
They try to put on a pretty face for the media, but this is the grim reality of it.
Where are my tax dollars going to?
Two.
All of the warheads in those boxes have had their detonation mechanisms removed, so there's no fear of them exploding.
Thank you for the five gifted.
Thank you.
If the warheads are broken, they might leak plutonium, and that would be a serious problem.
Oh.
Snake, never use your weapon on that floor.
Okay.
Well, it won't even let me anyway, so...
You can't catch me using my weapon on this floor.
Because I'm not allowed.
Because the game...
What?
What do you mean, no use?
It's a box!
Oh, because I'm crouched, I think.
I was about to say, you...
You can't do this to me.
Just a box.
He didn't even say anything to me, though.
I'm kind of surprised.
I like how she says, you see those boxes?
Actually, I don't.
Actually, I don't see.
I need that guy up there to move.
I need that guy up there to leave.
Okay, there we go.
Oh, lockers.
Okay,
um, thank you.
We're not safe.
Okay, thank you.
That's fine.
This is fine.
Yep, this is...okay.
Press the button.
Go, Snake, go.
Whoa!
B1.
Sheesh!
That was pretty close, wasn't it?
This is not the right floor.
B2.
This is the right floor.
Oh my gosh, you can see him!
Ow!
He's pacing.
He's a scientist.
You hear me?
Okay, this is where we discover the poison room.
Well, it doesn't look so gassy in there.
Actually, it looks fine.
Actually, it looks totally normal.
Oh, never mind.
Watch out, Snake.
The, like, the levels of security here.
First, you gotta make it gassy.
Whoa!
Yeah!
And then you also have to make it electrified.
It is overkill, absolutely.
Wait.
But, you know, um...
I guess, um, it's not overkill because I get past it.
Boing!
Hey!
It's filled with gas!
Also, the floor will kill you!
I'll destroy it.
I can't reach it.
Okay.
I'm gonna leave.
And go back.
Going all the way here, then to go all the way back.
I'll come back for you, Otacon.
I'll come back for you.
Oh, for anyone curious, I am going for the Otacon ending this time.
So, um, because I think it's funnier.
There's a particular scene that is, that is particularly comical.
So, uh, sorry, Meryl.
Um, but we are gonna get Otacon ending in this run.
Oh, we gotta go all the way back.
Actually, I'm going to try and do the heliport, um, thingy.
The heliport, uh...
What's the word?
Yes.
The thing.
I'm gonna do that thing.
Hahaha.
The truck ride.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, there's two guys down there, though.
Wait, is there two guys?
Oh, it's a...
Um...
I'm gonna hang over the rail and try and fall.
But I'm looking at their patterns real quick.
I don't...
Oh, no.
I think the camera will see me if I get out of the box, won't it?
I think it will.
So scary.
The time is, like, so well.
Okay.
Here we go.
Oh, shit.
Please.
There we go.
And drop.
No!
Okay, next time.
What's the button to drop?
Uh, maybe it's B.
I don't know it.
Hahaha.
Okay.
I should try number two.
Okay, we gotta wait for this guy to leave, too.
I think...
Yeah, he's coming over.
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, that...
Oh, okay.
We had it perfect.
If only I didn't mess it up.
What's the button?
Is it B?
I don't know if it's B or X.
It's X?
Thank you!
Okay.
X!
Nice.
Thank you, guys.
Otherwise, I would have totally pressed B.
Time to go!
Teleport.
How can you not see him?
It's the mask.
The mask is, you know, not helping them, you know?
I get it.
Okay.
To the heliport.
Huh?
It's not helping at all.
I get it.
He thinks it's full of junk or something.
Maybe.
Probably.
Okay.
Let's see.
We got a guy there.
We got the same guys.
No more.
No less.
Nice.
Does he look this way?
Okay.
Get off the heliport.
Oh, there you are.
Oh.
La, la, la, la.
Beep, beep, boop, bop.
M9 ammo.
Very good.
Which can I?
I don't think I can reach.
This guy's going to come back.
Oh, wait.
Oh.
Well, we want to get this guy over here first because otherwise he'll discover his sleeping friend.
Even though if he's sleeping right now, it's no biggie.
So calm to destroy the camera.
Yeah, oh actually that is a good point.
Once we... is he coming or does he not come this way actually?
I don't know.
Let's just put this guy to sleep.
Good night, little baby.
Go to sleep, little baby.
Oh, there he is.
It's fine.
Are you dead?
Oh!
Cool.
I
thought he was gone.
I thought he was gone.
He was in fact still there.
It doesn't matter anyway because...
Why would it... why did it go away?
It went down so quickly before.
That's weird.
Oh god.
Now... we... are these open?
Can I shoot from here?
That'd be pretty handy if I could.
If I back up a little.
Oh!
Oh ho ho!
Oh ho ho ho!
Can I get a little closer?
No.
Okay, right here.
Okay, right...
Here!
Alright.
Come over here.
Where I can see... see you.
Gotta get your legs.
Just a mosquito.
In Alaska.
It happens way more often than you'd imagine.
Those pesky Alaska mosquitoes, you guys, are so icky.
Did it work?
I think so.
Oh!
He technically did his report.
Oh, maybe he didn't.
Um...
Backup unit.
Unit.
Well, there they come.
We can get them, too.
Easy peasy.
One... hit them with the old one, too.
And they will never...
oh.
I think they woke him up.
I'm just imagining things.
There's a mosquito!
It's... it's really awful, powerful one.
It sucks all your...
Oh, they're searching?
I think.
Nothing here.
Where... I'm hearing so many footsteps.
Oh, I think I'm hearing them... above me, maybe?
They sound so close.
I can't believe there's the... they already... the... the one tanker's gone.
It's so fun... or the one tank is gone.
It's so funny.
Where am I going again?
Oh, the armory.
That's right.
Is that your leg?
Once he's down, we're gonna leave.
Actually, I think I can leave now, but...
We'll just be... be safe.
Go down.
Go to sleep.
Um...
Okay.
Hmm?
Is there somebody there?
No.
Nobody here.
Nobody.
Nothing here.
Oh, wait.
No, it's B-2.
It's okay.
Nowhere.
Actually...
It's five.
Nothing here.
We need... the Nikita missiles, right?
So stressful.
This guy's gonna come up and discover us.
I do know that.
So we need to act first.
We need to... box it up.
Oh, my God.
Is he gonna notice me or...
Am I in your way?
Oh, shoot.
Well, that just puts a little damper in our plans now.
Doesn't it?
Um...
What's that?
Oh, you kicked me before I could grab you.
Oh, come on.
It's okay, Snake.
All we gotta do is get the Nikita and go.
It doesn't matter.
But wait, actually...
This might be a good place to hide.
Right?
Because...
We can just...
...
They don't like coming in here.
They don't like coming in here, I've noticed.
So, uh, good stuff.
Okay, they are right where we need to go.
So you guys need to leave.
That's where the room is.
You're checking?
It's a spooky room.
It is.
I kind of wanted to hear the BDM one, though.
Kind of awesome.
You need to leave!
Actually, I think they do check in here, but we'll see if the radar goes down before they get it to this place.
Yep.
Nice.
Nice, nice, nice.
That guy...
what are you doing?
You're going that way.
Okay.
Get Nikita first.
Did he hear me in here?
Oh, shit.
Where's the... where's the box?
Okay.
I think the door's still open.
Okay, no, we're good.
Is there a...
No... no tricks.
No tricks.
Okay.
And what's in here?
What's this?
Eternal darkness?
Hello?
Oh, okay.
Alright, now we gotta go back all the way.
Let's wait for him to loop around again.
What if I leave a book?
Leave a sexy book for you to look at.
So you don't come back around.
Wait, how do I plan this?
Press A to set.
Over
there, you!
Thank you!
He's just hanging out.
You know what?
I gave him a little present, you know?
Now he won't come back.
Okay, let's go.
To what?
I gave him a little present.
Now we're... we're buds now.
We're buddies.
Do I...
I hear someone snoring.
I think.
I didn't.
Um...
They turned off the lasers right here.
This part.
Right?
Did they turn off the lasers here?
No, they didn't!
That's so evil.
Oh my god.
Um...
Dying!
Good to check.
When did they turn them off?
Colonel?
Can you do that for me?
Hmm...
It looks like the infrared sensors that were set up here had been switched off.
Wait!
What?
Am I willing to test it?
Am I... Am I willing to test it?
Huh?
Why don't I trust that?
I don't... I'm gonna try.
Because usually they are, right?
In my parents' homeland, they say, if there are more wolves, the people are eaten.
If there are more people, the wolves are eaten.
Who are... who is...
Do people eat wolves?
Try not to let them see you.
I know.
I know, Mei-Ling.
Gaslight 100.
Um...
Oh my god.
I'm gonna run.
Oh!
I've never seen this cutscene before, though.
Colonel?
Colonel!
Yo!
This is so messed up!
I...
Get me out of here!
Might as well give one last read before I die.
Call him?
Yeah, for real.
Colonel, this is your fault!
Snake, it's gas.
Hold your breath.
Your O2 gauge...
Until when?
If you don't breathe, the gauge will decrease.
When it reaches zero, your life gauge will begin to decrease.
What?
No way.
He just told me to hold my breath.
Merrill?
No!
That's not what I'm asking you.
I see.
Master Miller?
No idea.
A trap?
Could be.
But for the time being, I'll have to trust him.
Here's to almost two weeks of Mint's return of MGS Dream.
People who have been through war and survived develop a kind of sixth sense to warn them of danger.
Trust your instincts as a soldier.
As a gamer.
I love that line so much.
Um, well, I guess it's a good thing I saved.
I don't know.
What a joke.
What a joke!
The game told me the sensors were off!
The game told me the sensors were off.
That's so messed up.
Oh, thank goodness.
Okay.
I wonder though.
Okay, hold on.
Hold on.
I'm not even gonna look.
Let's try calling Colonel again.
Hmm.
It looks like the infrared sensors that were set up here have been switched off.
Yes!
Oh my god.
I'm so scared.
No, they have not been turned off.
Colonel is actually...
He is actively sabotaging me.
Oh my god.
Welcome back.
It's been a while, but I kept up.
Thank you so much!
Okay.
Oh, dang it.
I missed it.
I
think the game is a little bugged.
Respond!
This is messed up.
I think the game is a little bugged.
Is it because I took the...
The heliport way?
Would that affect it?
Hmm.
Interesting.
Just a game.
Do you want to love trolling?
Yeah, because there's also not the cameras set up here and stuff.
Interesting.
Um...
I think...
Actually, I am going to use this and we're going to grab the ration that's up here.
Colonel is misleading me more than chat does.
Colonel is...
really trying to make me throw.
Whoa...
Actually, this is a good opportunity.
Uh... box.
Oh, wait.
Get up.
And box.
And over here.
Over...
here.
My little safety net.
My little safety spot.
Can I see up there?
I kinda can.
Oh, there he is.
Okay.
Nice.
We do know that we can box in front of the...
We can box in front of the elevator though, so... hopefully.
As long as I align it right, I guess.
Does he stop there?
I guess he does, but I can go.
Thank you.
Okay, we gotta hurry.
We gotta go, go, go.
Oh my god, please.
Press the button.
Oh.
Let's go.
Holy cow!
That was close.
Me too.
Nothing I see here.
Nothing to see here.
All good.
It is the Nakina missiles that I need.
Wait...
Okay.
I was about to say, what if I don't even have them?
Okay Snake, we're gonna need you to hold your breath, buddy.
It's my first time trying this in this game, so...
It's gonna be interesting.
To say the least.
Might take a couple tries.
Okay, how do I use this?
A button to aim in first person view.
Release the fire and control.
Okay.
Wait, what are you saying?
Sorry, I'm missing some of your thingies.
Your donuts.
Oh wait.
Twin snakes is a ride in VR mission.
The colonel telling you sensors are off might be a glitch in the matrix.
Mysterious.
Welcome back, Mint.
Metal Gear brain rot is forever.
Forever!
You have 40 shots, so go for it.
True.
Okay, here we go.
And release!
Okay, turn.
Okay.
And nice and neat.
Go!
Zoom!
Don't shoot it down.
I think I'm a gamer.
Nice.
Now which one has the gas mask in it?
This one?
No.
This one.
That's a dirty magazine.
Wait.
A chaff grenade.
I'm just gonna chaff it.
I know I probably shouldn't, but...
Okay.
We gotta hurry.
Come on.
It's one of these.
Good.
Go!
Grab the book.
Grab the mask.
Put on the mask.
Can I get in this one while it's still jammed?
Oh, I ca- I could've.
I could've, but it's okay.
Shoo!
Okay.
Nice.
Hehehe.
Oh my gosh.
We got that Raiden vision real.
Is there a... Oh no.
There's nothing in here.
Oh wait.
There's actually nothing in here.
Okay.
There's a node.
I don't remember if there's anything over here that I can get.
But we'll try.
I don't have much oxygen left.
Come on.
Let's go.
Nope.
Not that one.
Yep.
This one.
Grenade.
Chaff.
Grenade full.
Oh shit.
Oh shoot.
Uh oh.
Uh... Chaff?
We're in trouble.
Ah!
Just run!
Shoo.
There's some more st- Oh, there's chaffs over there!
Oxygen runs out so fast.
And that's with the gas mask on.
That's with the gas mask on.
I mean, no one comes.
Maybe I could just...
...bolt through it.
...run really fast.
Maybe I could just...
Can you shoot the guns?
I don't think so because of the gas, right?
Or can I?
Can I?
Can I shoot them down?
Or will I die?
I'm scared.
You can?
Wait, no way.
Really?
Uh, where is it?
Oh.
Uh.
Oh!
I thought because of the gas, it was like gonna...
Pew!
I cannot see.
Could've run out of bullets at this rate.
Oh, I got him.
I cannot see with this mask on though.
Oh, there's one.
Ugh.
It's so hard to tell.
There we go.
Let's go back.
Okay.
And again.
It's that one right there that's gonna be tricky.
This one.
The one that's pointed straight in my direction.
And is not moving.
Could you move a little?
Could you...
Um.
Okay.
Uh.
Eltaline?
Oh, you are so smart.
Come on.
Where is it?
Where?
Oh, I got it.
Okay, nice.
So hard to say.
Oh, maybe I should've gotten closer.
Like here.
I can...
Uh.
Maybe not.
Wait.
Where is it?
Here?
That's it.
Yeah.
You.
Nice.
And...
Uh.
Oh, I can't see it.
Oh, there.
There.
Got him.
No, more Nakeda missiles.
Beep.
I think I can make it.
Grab it.
Run, Snake!
Run!
Nooo!
Oh no no no no.
For real.
No no no.
Oh my gosh.
I was right though.
I knew we'd make it.
Danger.
Okay.
Um... worse?
We wouldn't have died though.
We wouldn't have died.
It would have been fine.
Okay, let's go see our little buddy.
Our little piss-pal.
And one of my favorite scenes of the game.
One of my favorite parts of the game!
Oh, save?
Yeah, I'll save real quick.
Oh, he's saying the...
Are those the train stations?
Snake, you can't use the radar because something's jamming it.
And whatever's doing it is very close to you.
Be careful.
I'm careful, I'm careful.
Whoa, it's so... it's going back and forth between my headphones.
It's so crazy.
Whoa...
Be careful, Snake.
Thanks, Mei-Ling.
Um... Colonel?
I'm scared.
The less you maneuver a remote-controlled missile, the faster it will fly.
Thanks, Colonel.
Remember this if you want to fire the missile over a greater distance.
Awesome.
Thank you.
Also, what's going on?
Snake, look at your sea rations.
They're frozen.
You can't use frozen sea rats.
Until they defrost, you won't be able to replenish your energy.
Be very careful.
Wait, my... why are my rations frozen?
They'll defrost in a warm place.
Probably just your bare skin would be fine.
My sea rats?
Who says sea rats?
Master Miller, my sea rats are frozen.
People who've been through war and survived develop a kind of success to warn them of danger.
Gamer, gamer, gamer, gamer.
Trust your instincts as a soldier, as a gamer.
The sea rats.
Yo ho, yo ho, the rat life for me.
I'm on the sea, I am a rat, I have no business here.
Meryl, are you okay?
Meryl, what are these holes and walls for?
Uh, bullets?
I don't know.
For blowing tiny particles of dust off people's bodies before they enter the lab.
Oh!
I've never heard that dialogue before.
Nastasha, how you doing?
Good.
You found a SOCOM?
Yeah, I did.
That's a Special Operations Command Pistol.
It's a .45 caliber pistol with plenty of stopping power.
It's also equipped with a LAM for nighttime combat.
I love that artist's LAM.
You can equip that too.
That pistol was designed specifically for use by Special Forces.
So I think it will be useful.
Some people find it a little heavy and hard to use.
Her voice is so different.
Yeah.
But it shouldn't be a problem for you.
Okay, the voices are a little...
Oh, these holes!
They look like, they look like dominoes.
Alright, here we go.
I love this scene.
I hope it's good in this version too.
We'll see.
This scene is so awesome.
Oh my gosh.
There's not as much blood so far.
Wait.
Wait, why did he take off his stealth camo?
Oh my god though.
He sliced that guy in half.
No, no.
You're supposed to be invisible.
Okay, that's kind of cool though.
No, you're supposed to be invisible though.
Robin!
He's alive.
The music.
Caution, stand back.
Because the guy is supposed to be like, it's like he's a ghost.
I don't know.
I don't... I didn't really need to see the whole scene.
It was so much more mysterious when we didn't see it.
You know?
And then obviously, like, he's supposed to be invisible and then like...
The guy's like, it's like he's a ghost.
Hmm.
Oh!
He's a skewer!
Oh my gosh, the barbecue.
No, that doesn't make any sense.
No, that doesn't make any sense!
You can see it!
Wow, he looks so cool though.
Ghost?
Me?
The music is also killing me.
Okay.
This scene was definitely...
I'm...
I'm not a fan.
Actually, I'm...
I'm actually quite disappointed.
But that's okay.
That's fine.
I get it.
Not all the scenes are the same.
Can I loot their bodies?
You got any rations?
Oh my gosh, I completely forgot that I could get dog tags in this game.
Damn.
Okay, time to fight...
Gray Fox.
I don't know.
All my sea rats...
Wait, are they still frozen?
Uh-oh.
I'm gonna start calling them.
Stealth camouflage?
Who are you?
The nipples!
Ow!
Oh no!
Where is my friend?
It gets me every time.
What?
What are you talking about?
Right behind you.
Whoa!
Oh!
What next?
They made him pee twice!
Snake.
You're that ninja.
What?
You're that ninja!
I've been waiting for you, Snake.
No, no, I...
Who are you?
I already have more.
Neither enemy nor friend.
Yes!
I am back from a world where such words are meaningless.
Neither enemy nor friend.
I've removed all my shoes.
You're that maid.
Now you and I will battle to the death.
What do you want?
Oh, I've waited a long time for this day.
Now I want to enjoy this moment.
I think...
Grey Fox still sounds...
Like I said.
What's with these guys?
Hold on.
It's like one of my Japanese animes.
I've come from another world to battle with you.
What is it?
Revenge?
Because of the voice effects on his...
Like, with him, it doesn't sound so different, you know?
Maybe because...
A fight to the death with you?
Maybe side by side it does, but...
I think it sounds pretty good.
He said the thing.
I will kill you, or you will kill me.
A fight to the death with you?
B is to punch.
Get in there, Otacon!
B is to punch, you guys.
B is to punch.
Okay, that line, I remember how he said it before.
And it definitely was better before.
He's like, make me...
He's like, make me feel alive again.
Okay, how do I beat him again?
I have to just punch him, right?
Yeah.
And then he does like a...
Whoa!
Oh, I can only get one hit in?
Okay, I'm hearing the differences more now.
I'm hearing the differences in the voice acting more now.
Where are you?
Oh, come here.
Come here.
I can't kick him.
Why can't I kick you?
No!
I was in mid-attack!
Oh my gosh.
Oh, nice.
There we go.
I don't remember when I can...
When can I start using my gun?
I don't remember...
Oh, ouch.
It'd be so funny if you...
I just realized... wait, I need my...
They're still frozen!
Oh gosh.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hold on!
My sea rats!
Oh, ouch.
Oh,
keep...
please, Snake!
When he's like in mid-action...
Oh my god, the GameCube!
There we go.
Nice.
And then I have to remember that one last part where he like goes kind of in...
Oh, they're better.
They're better.
Nice.
Oh, hello?
Invincibility... Invincibility Frames!
Excuse me?
Oh my god.
That is unfair.
Excuse me, sir.
I kicked you.
And you...
Oh, I got stuck on the wall.
That's okay.
Okay.
This is...
Don't hurt the GameCube!
Don't hurt Mario!
Why can I only get one hit in?
Hey-do!
Whoa, yeah, well...
He's going... He's going crazy mode!
He's going... Insano style!
He's parkouring all over me!
Oh, there we go.
Can you stop doing Cirque du Soleil for two seconds?
Oh my god.
Please.
Nice!
There we go.
Oh!
Hurt me more, Snake!
Oh no, I'm so bad at this part.
Oh no, wait.
Oh!
Oh, never mind!
I know exactly where you are!
Hurry up and catch me.
Okay.
Oh, I saw where you went.
Nice.
Oh, uh...
Yeah?
Yup.
Uh...
Oh.
When can I use my gun?
Oh, shit.
Ah!
Uh-oh.
Okay.
Hey-do!
Is he gonna come get me?
Run?
Where are you?
Hello?
Hurt me more!
Hurt me more, Snake!
Hey!
Hurt me more!
He said the thing!
Nice.
I remember that one...
Yeah, we punched each other in Zanzibar!
Remember...
Oh!
Dang it!
I remember when I punched you and you punched me.
We were punching each other in Zanzibar.
I remember.
I remember that.
Good times.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my god.
No, no, no.
Snake, get up.
Get up, please.
Oh, Snake.
Oh, yeah.
It's okay.
He won't see me here.
Just kidding.
Be-do!
Can I, like...
Give me, like, two seconds, okay, Gravebox?
Never mind.
Like, two seconds to regain my composure.
Okay.
There we go.
All right.
Ah!
The feeling of battle.
So awesome.
Come on.
Do your little teleporty thing.
Come here.
There we go.
Come on.
Nice.
Go, baby.
We got two hits in.
Hurt me more.
Come on.
Oh, ouch.
All I've been doing is running away.
I still have a lot of rations, so I think we're mostly good, but at the same time, it's better to be safe than sorry, you know?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
That's good, Snake.
Can he, like...
Oh, my God.
Hadoop.
Why is it that every time he punches me, it
makes me, like, start losing blood?
Hurt me more.
Nice.
Come here.
Cause of the age.
You can't even punch well, Ninja.
Oh, I totally missed you.
I can't punch well.
Oh, his knife hands.
Got it.
I love if I just touch him.
It hurts me, though, even.
Hurt me more!
Oh, just a little bit.
Just a little bit more.
Ouch!
I'm trying!
Stand still!
I'll hurt you!
Ouch!
It's OK.
Yippee!
OK.
Don't touch him.
Wait.
Yeah, yeah.
Don't touch him.
Shoot.
Shoot him.
He's gonna go...
Oh, my God!
See,
this is what we could have been doing the whole time, but someone...
had to be like...
all over the place.
It's also mean.
I was running everywhere, too.
This guy was avoiding bullets!
And then...
Wait.
Where's the last part of the fight?
Is he dead?
No... No Electro Phase?
Say it!
Zanzibar!
Wait.
Is it here?
No.
This happens anyway.
Right?
And he goes...
I love how they kept this part, even though it was a...
dropped subplot.
Crazy!
Bang your head on the floor!
Oh!
Oh, my God!
Gray Fox, no!
Oh!
Oh, no!
Oh, he's crazy!
What's going on?
Gray Fox!
Oh!
Are you just gonna...
Are you...
Uh...
Is it over?
Are you just gonna run out?
Um...
The medicine...
Take your meds, everybody.
Snake, this might be a good time to move.
Snake, this might be a good...
Why is he always just standing there?
He stood there and got blasted by the tank.
Gray Fox.
Colonel, that ninja is Gray Fox.
No doubt about it.
Ridiculous.
He said it.
You, yourself, in Zanzibar land.
He said, I'm Gray Fox.
He should have been killed, but he's still alive.
What?
It happened before I joined Fox Health Medical Staff.
What do you know about that, Naomi, huh?
They were using a soldier for their gene therapy experiments.
What do you know about that, Naomi?
I never heard that.
Hm?
It happened right after you retired.
My predecessor, Dr. Clark, was in charge.
Dr. Clark?
Yes.
Dr. Clark.
He started the gene therapy project.
And where is he now?
Dead.
He was killed in an explosion in his lab two years ago.
So what about this soldier?
Apparently, for their test subject, they decided to use the body of a soldier who was recovered after the fall of Zanzibar land.
And that was Gray Fox.
But he was already dead.
Yes.
I miss English, Naomi.
Here, I'll redo the lines.
They fed him with a prototype exos while they experimented on him like a plaything.
Today's genome soldiers were born from those experiments.
That's the sickest thing I've ever heard.
I'm sorry, Colonel.
I didn't think my accent would offend you so much.
Because it's confidential information.
Is that the only reason?
Naomi, what happened to Gray Fox after that?
The records said he died in an accident.
I see.
I'm sorry.
But even if that ninja is Gray Fox...
He hated it.
From what I could tell...
That was Australian?
You're saying he's just living off his will to fight?
I'm not sure.
But he seems intent on fighting me to the death.
We'll meet again.
I know it.
Yeah.
Until you fight again?
Until you kill him?
Shut up, Naomi.
I'd rather not.
But maybe that's what he wants.
That's what he wants.
He said, hurt me more.
It was consensual.
Look at the little GameCube.
Oh my gosh.
It's so cute.
It looks just like...
Actually...
Sorry, my GameCube is black.
I was going to say it looks just like mine.
It is not.
Are you one of them?
An anime?
No, I'm not.
I always work alone.
Alone?
Are you an otaku too?
Come on.
Get out.
We can't stay here forever.
Snake in the Twin Snakes is so mean to Otacon.
He's so like...
In the original, he's kind of like...
He's like soft boy.
Your uniform is different from theirs.
But in this game, he's like...
Otacon.
Get up.
He's so mean to him.
You know me?
Aw, Hal.
I heard about you from Meryl.
Oh.
So you're here to rescue me?
Ugh.
My headphones are starting to hurt my ears.
Sorry.
There's something that I've got to do first.
Oh.
His beady eyes.
Well, at least you're not one of them.
Are you hurt?
I'm okay.
I just twisted my ankle a little trying to get away.
My boy.
It's okay.
My son is used to people being mean to him.
Stop, Yui.
I need information about Metal Gear.
Metal Gear.
Huh?
Metal Gear?
Yeah.
Oh, the posters aren't in this one.
That's...
What's Metal Gear really designed for?
Oh, wait.
It's a mobile TMD.
Wait.
What is that poster?
It's designed to shoot down nuclear missiles.
It's not a police mod.
Only for defensive purposes, of course.
Liar.
What?
I already know that Metal Gear is nothing but a nuclear equipped...
Stop shaking him.
...working death on you.
A nuclear?
What are you talking about?
Why are you acting like a bully?
He's like a high school bully to him.
The terrorists are planning to use Metal Gear to launch a nuclear missile.
You tell me you didn't know.
Oh, it's Zone of the Enders.
Oh my god.
Aren't they just trying to use the TMD missile module to launch a disabled nuclear warhead?
He's so unbothered by it, which is even funnier.
The purpose of this exercise was to test Metal Gear's nuclear launch capability using a dummy nuclear warhead.
The terrorists are just continuing the work you started.
No.
You're wrong.
I heard it directly from your boss, Baker.
No.
A nuclear missile on Rex?
So you really didn't know.
Oh, I'm sorry.
The president of Nauticon.
Little baby.
He's like, er...
No!
All the armament was built by a separate department...
The...
And the president personally supervised the final assembly with the main unit.
The picture on his badge looks like...
President Baker.
Yes.
Looks like his PS...
Metal Gear model.
I was never told what they armed Rex with.
I only know it's equipped with a Vulcan Cannon, a laser and a railgun.
Railgun!
Do you guys know what I mean?
Do you guys remember that old video?
Nail gun!
Every time they say rail gun it makes me want to say it.
Rail gun!
Good!
Rex is so cute.
But that's not all I think.
If Metal Gear fired only standard nuclear missiles, then they should already have all the practical data they need.
Thank you so much!
Metal Gear's co-developer, Rivermore National Labs, was working on a new type of nuclear weapon.
They were using NOVA and NIF laser nuclear fusion testing equipment and super computers.
So they developed a new type of nuclear weapon.
A nuclear weapon in a VR testing lab, huh?
Yes.
But you can't use virtual data on a battlefield.
They would need actual launch data.
These are some of the super computers.
If you link these, you can test everything in a virtual environment.
But it's all just theoretical.
So, this exercise was designed to test the real thing.
What did our president do?
He took a lot of time.
Did the terrorists launch that thing?
No.
Oh, and then your Nikes.
Damn!
Damn.
Holy...
I'm such a fool.
Snakes.
It's all my fault.
No, it's all...
The truth is...
My grandfather was part of the Manhattan Project.
Ah.
He suffered with a guilt for the rest of his life.
And my father?
He was born on August 6th, 1945.
The day of the Hiroshima bomb.
Huey is the devil.
God's got a sense of humor, all right.
He is the devil.
Three generations of Emmerich men.
Can't with that.
We must have the curse of nuclear weapons written into our DNA.
Oh, Huey.
I used to think that I could use science...
That guy sucks.
...to help mankind.
He's the literal devil.
I was the one being used.
No, Hal.
You didn't know.
Using science for peace.
That's only in anime.
Oh, no, Hal.
That's enough crying.
Pull yourself together.
You're so mean in this.
Where on this base are they keeping it?
Anime is real, Hal.
Yeah.
Rex is in the underground maintenance base.
Where's that?
North of the communications tower.
But it's a long way there.
Is it?
The emergency override system for the detonation code is there, too.
Yeah.
In the base's control room.
You'd better hurry.
If they were planning a launch from the start, then their ballistic program is probably finished.
And since they haven't called for me in a few hours, they must not need me.
In other words, they must be ready to launch.
We gotta go stop it.
Meryl's got the detonation code override keys.
Yeah, we gotta put in the override keys and stop it for sure.
If we can't override the power, we'll make up for it.
We'll have to destroy Rex.
Yeah!
Oh, no!
I need to use that guy in a later game.
Oh, you're hurt.
On that leg of yours, you'll just slow me down.
Oh.
You'll need me if you're gonna destroy Rex.
True.
I don't need you.
I just need your brain.
Hey, you said earlier I need that guy.
I created Rex.
It's my right.
My duty to destroy him.
If you get a chance...
Hey!
...try to escape.
Don't do that.
When the coast is gone...
...I'll contact you by codec.
Oh.
How am I supposed to escape from an island?
Hmm.
Okay.
Yeah.
Last luck on the membership.
Thank you.
Thank you guys for joining my membership.
I really appreciate it.
I want you to hide somewhere and keep me informed.
You know this place well, don't you?
Of course I do.
And don't worry.
I've got this.
Oh.
Whoa.
It's the same stealth technology as the ninja.
He looks so much like...
...Foxhound was gonna use them, but...
With the glasses.
...I'll be fine.
Bad leg and all.
And he looks so much like MGS1.
Good.
But I want Meryl to watch after you too.
Oh.
Autobot.
Thank you for the birthday.
Wait.
Did Sneak just smile?
That's my 7B32.
Thank you.
Meryl.
The engineer is okay.
That's a relief.
I want you to look after him.
That music.
Where are you now?
Very close.
There she is.
Over there.
Oh no.
Damn.
They spotted me.
Oh no.
Meryl.
What happened?
Mario.
Mario, did you hear something?
Wasn't that some kind of music?
Some kind of music.
Mario!
What did she look like?
She's got a nice butt.
We know that for sure.
She's kinda cute the way she walks.
She... she was wearing the same green uniform as the terrorists.
Oh.
And she...
If she's disguised as the enemy, Huh?
Wait!
You didn't talk about her butt!
Otacon!
Oh, the girl's bathroom.
Otacon is a gentleman now.
You guys, it was too raunchy for Nintendo, okay?
Nintendo said... No, no, no.
No talking about girl's butts, please.
You're not in pain, are you?
You feel okay?
Nothing bothering you?
What's wrong?
You're all friendly all of a sudden.
No, nothing.
I'm just glad you're okay.
You're strange.
I'm a little nervous.
Everyone else I've saved suddenly dies.
You're bad luck.
Forget it, doctor.
If I shoot those guys, do they make sounds like Kero-tan?
Call me Otacon.
Stands for Otaku Convention.
Oh, sorry.
Spoilers.
Sorry.
What does it stand for?
It stands for Otaku Convention.
And Otaku is a guy like me who likes Japanimation.
Yeah!
Oh!
Is this the one?
Is this the one of the Enders?
Oh, there it is!
Yeah, yeah!
The first country to successfully make bipedal robots.
They're still the best in the field of robotics.
And Japanese cartoons played some part in that?
They did.
They did?
I didn't get into science to make nuclear weapons, you know.
I just wanted to make robots.
Yeah, that's what all scientists do.
Why are we zooming in on them?
Stop!
The product placement is too obvious now.
Stop it!
Because I became a scientist because I wanted to make robots like the ones in the Japanese animes.
Really, it's true.
Sounds like an excuse to me.
We get it!
This is on the GameCube!
You're right.
We have to take responsibility.
Bad luck equals beat out equals boys?
Science has progressed because there is war.
And because of scientists' greed, weapons of mass destruction were born.
But you're not greedy, Otacon.
But that's all over.
You just want to make robots.
I won't take part in murder anymore.
Yeah.
You're a good boy.
You're a good guy, Otacon.
Whatever.
All I want from you is information.
Sure.
I know everything about this whole base.
Why you gotta touch him like that, though?
Ask me anything about Rex or about this place.
Also, with this stealth camouflage, I can sneak in and out of the armory and mess hall.
If you need ammo or rations, just tell me and I'll bring them to you.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, I know you will.
I'm on frequency 141.12.
141.12.
See you later.
Bye, Otacon.
See ya.
Bye-bye.
Otacon looks like my uncle?
You have a hot uncle, then.
Yippee!
Did he change his pants?
I don't think he did.
Why do they give you bullets in this if...
Like, can you actually shoot Gray Fox?
I've always just punched him to death.
It's clean.
He must drink a lot of water.
Oh my gosh!
That looks similar to the controller I'm using now.
Wowee!
It's a GameCube!
Wait, can I shoot this thing?
Ow!
Sorry.
Pencil.
Goodbye, Yoshi.
Yoshi!
Goodbye, Mario.
Why'd my life show up?
Yoshi!
So cute!
Does Mario heal you?
No way!
Is that why it says...
That one makes sense!
What's this?
Oh!
It's the...
That's so funny.
Wait, what's on this computer?
Actually, I think he destroyed this computer.
Oh!
No, he didn't.
Accessing...
Port...
Some of them.
Can't tell.
There's so much science in here.
So much science!
I want the box.
Let's go!
Um...
Let's save real quick.
Maybe?
Snake, there's an old Chinese saying.
A scholar who cherishes the love of comfort is not fit to be deemed a scholar.
Einstein said it another way.
He said that only a life lived for others is worth living.
That's why I entered MIT instead of CMU or Princeton like my friends.
Boo, Princeton!
I wanted to do applied physics, not just theoretical stuff.
Yeah!
I wanted to make things for people.
We wanted to do real stuff!
The Sol -Time -R system or the Codex system.
You're so awesome, Mei-Ling.
I just wanted to make something that would be useful for people.
Yeah!
I think that it was the same for Dr. Emmerich, too.
But he was used like a tool.
Used to make a horrible killing machine.
Just like Snake.
Used by everybody.
As a machine.
It would be better if engineers like us just stopped making things.
I don't know.
No!
No, you're wrong.
There's at least one person whose life has gotten better as a result of your inventions.
Me.
Me?
Without the Codex, I wouldn't be able to talk to you like this.
Yeah.
Thanks, Snake.
Aw.
Aw...
Why?
So sweet...
Actually, I forgot.
I want to see if she still does this.
Do not say.
Good luck, Snake.
Thanks, Mei-Ling.
What's up, Snake?
Good luck, Snake.
Thank you!
You're welcome.
Bye, Snake.
What can I do for you, Snake?
Come on, Snake.
Don't call me for no reason.
I just want to look at your pretty face.
She gets upset.
She's so cute.
She's upset at me.
Maybe one more time?
I love the squint.
She really said...
Cute.
But the real problem is your niece.
She's a problem.
She was supposed to be a good girl.
Why wasn't she a good girl?
Shut up, Naomi.
Exactly.
It's just that she's holding the detonation code over IDs.
Oh, I just thought you were human for a second.
For our last chance of stopping that nuclear launch.
No, you're a snake.
My mistake.
You're a cold man.
Your mission is more important than the life of your companions.
You're a cold man?
This is war.
Survival is the name of the game.
Sometimes you have to be cold to survive.
But that better mean...
Yes, but...
Snake, either way, I want you to find Meryl as soon as possible.
I understand.
It is kind of bad that he said that in front of Campbell.
I feel like in front of the colonel, it feels a little, you know...
Meryl?
No response.
Ah, let's try Master Meryl.
In war, a split second can mean the difference between victory and defeat.
Don't ever hesitate.
The slower you react, the greater the chance that you will be beaten.
Why does he sound out of breath?
Did you hear that?
He was like...
In war, every second counts.
Don't think that you will...
He's like, don't waste any second.
Why did... are you okay, Master Meryl?
Are you on the treadmill or something?
That inner voice that warns you when danger is nearby?
You can't learn that in training.
You've got to have survived a few firefights, seen a few friends blown away before you learned that trick.
He sounds so...
He's so, like, breathy.
I don't understand why.
Alright, guys.
Before we continue onwards, I'm going to go...
I'm going to set my oven.
I'm going to turn on my oven and I'm going to set an alarm for like five minutes or something.
I'll do like ten minutes and then...
And then...
Go put my pizza in the oven so I can have some food.
Bro is getting back shots.
Back shots?
While on the... Wait, what's a back shot?
Okay, clock.
What time is it?
Let's set it for not... No, that's not... Let's set it for 9.05.
Thank you!
Yeah.
No, not AM.
No, no, no.
PM, PM.
Okay, set for...
9 minutes from now.
Oh, wait.
Let me set it a little...
It should heat up in like 10 minutes, alright?
Okay, I'll be right back.
I'm going to go heat up...
Or I'm going to go set the oven for my pizza.
BRB.
Don't look it up.
Wait, what?
What am I looking up?
Hold on.
Hold on!
I'm on a timer!
Give me a second!
Oh, I just hit my knee.
Ah!
I don't know.
Okay, I'm back.
Okay.
So in 9 minutes, it should be heated up, maybe.
And then we can...
I'll go put my pizza in.
And then I'll set another timer.
Pizza!
BASAMIN!
OHAYO!
Back shots are when you throw your ball backwards towards the hoop.
No need to look it up now.
You're welcome.
Oh, so it's like a basketball... thing.
Makes...
Well, he's...
Oh, my God.
Master Miller is shooting the hoops on the job?
Master Miller...
Pay attention to me.
Okay, the way you guys are describing it is making me scared.
I'm just gonna believe whatever.
Whatever.
Let's listen to the...
Let's listen to Sasha instead.
What kind of pizza is this?
It's just cheese pizza.
Okay.
You're liking it?
Dart.
Fission and fusion.
Are you going to do a full run in one setting?
No, no.
I think maybe after...
Psycho Mantis, maybe.
Since he's coming up relatively soon.
Right?
Yeah, we go to Psycho Mantis, then we go through to...
We'll see.
Oh, I went the wrong way.
Maybe after Psycho Mantis.
And then I'll probably do a...
the rest of it next week.
I
don't know.
We'll see.
Oh, nice.
Everything's still broken.
Otacon gave me...
his stuff, right?
His card?
What card key do I have now?
Four.
Metal Gear Exercise Data.
Number four.
Was there four over here?
Did I go in here before?
Oh, grenade full.
Nakida bullet full.
I think I went in this one before already.
Night vision goggles!
What?
How did I miss that?
Wait, how did I actually miss that before?
That's kind of crazy.
Oh, uh oh.
How do I get out of here?
Run, Snake, run!
Go, go, go!
Oh, level four door.
Okay.
That makes way more sense.
I was gonna say, I thought there was a door that we could...
Okay.
B1, baby.
Where are cameras?
I shot them down.
Okay, I'm gonna try and hold up the guy going to the bathroom.
Freeze.
No.
Now pee without using your hands.
Oh.
I don't need any more rations right now.
Ew!
Why is that in the stall?
That's nasty.
Okay, come in.
Get in there.
Yup.
Goodnight.
Oh
my god.
I didn't realize that.
Freeze.
You're also going in the stall.
Pizza time?
What do you mean pizza time?
My alarm hasn't gone off yet.
You guys, I set an alarm.
Get in there.
This is where Psycho Mantis is.
Oh, I was like, what are those two dots?
But it's...
They're little guys.
We can't go into the girl's room.
Unfortunately.
Oh, wait.
Is that her?
Easy.
Wow, the bathroom got like such an upgrade.
Oh my gosh.
It's so nice.
There's a little place to do your makeup.
It's so cool.
It's so fancy in here now.
They have the toilet paper on the floor.
That's disgusting.
Ew.
Freeze.
You trickster.
I let my guard down because you're beautiful.
That's the second time I've been able to sneak up on the legendary Solid Snake.
What a peeper.
Ow!
You're Merrill.
You're hot.
No, wait, my alarm!
Oh, no.
No, no, hold on.
Oh, gosh.
What do you mean?
Hey, men aren't allowed in here.
Hold on.
I gotta get to the cutscene.
I had no idea you were so...
feminine.
This is no time to try and hit on me, Snake.
She has psychosis.
Besides, it's a waste of time.
Exactly.
When I joined up, they gave me psychotherapy to destroy my interest in men.
Psychotherapy.
Yeah.
Same smart mouth.
You're Merrill, all right.
Are you hurt?
Pizza time.
Not yet.
After all, I was disguised as a genome soldier.
So why'd you change?
You'd be a lot better off dressed like one of them.
I got tired of disguising myself.
Rip pizza?
No, it's just the oven.
I gotta go put the pizza inside.
Truth is, the uniform smelled like blood.
Ew.
What's that mark?
What is this music?
Oh, this?
It's a paint tattoo.
It's not real.
I'm a fan of Foxhound way back.
When guys like you and my uncle were in it.
This is a weird soundtrack.
None of that gene therapy like there is today.
You guys were real heroes.
There are no heroes in war.
It's funny you mention that.
All the heroes I know are either dead or in prison.
One or the other.
You're a hero, aren't you?
Her foundation does not match the rest of her body.
She looks like...
I'm just a guy who can only find meaning on the battlefield.
There's no winning or losing for a mercenary.
The only winners in war are the people.
That's right.
And you fight for the people.
She thinks she's way paler than she actually is.
I've never fought for anyone but myself.
I've got no purpose in life.
No ultimate goal.
I don't like the music yet.
Come on.
It's only when I'm cheating death on the battlefield.
The only time I feel truly alive.
Feel truly alive.
Seeing other people die makes you feel alive, huh?
I mean...
You can't stop loving war.
Is it the same for all soldiers throughout history?
No interest in men yet marries the toilet man?
Hey.
He was very convincing.
Why didn't you contact me?
Yeah, actually.
My Kodak was broken.
Your shoes.
Not in the bathroom.
Shouldn't you just be happy we met up like this?
Girlie, please.
That's so nasty.
Anyway.
How did you recognize me in disguise?
You got a nice...
I'd never forget a lady.
So there's something you like about me, huh?
Yeah.
You've got a great butt.
Butt?
Oh, I see.
First it's my eyes.
Now it's my butt.
What's next?
On the battlefield, you never think about what's next.
The tangle.
Love it.
Love that.
Love that for you, Snake.
I miss this guy.
So, Snake.
How are the negotiations going?
No progress.
Negotiations?
So it's all up to you, huh?
Stop them from launching a nuclear missile.
There are two ways.
Either we destroy Metal Gear, or...
We override the detonation code.
You got the card keys from Baker?
Ah, yeah.
You mean this?
Where are the others?
There should be three keys.
This is all I've got.
Where could the other two be?
I have no idea.
But they must be somewhere.
If we can't find them, we'll have no choice but to destroy Metal Gear.
There's like two ladies on this whole base.
I heard that Metal Gear is in an underground maintenance base to the north of here.
Did you hear the ladies' washroom floor is pretty clean?
Take me too.
I know this place better than you do.
You'll just slow me down.
You don't have enough battle experience.
I won't slow you down.
I promise.
She says that and then she gets shot and slows us down.
And what if you do?
Then you can shoot me.
I don't like to waste bullets.
None of that gene therapy nonsense.
You guys are real heroes.
Woman who goes all in on nanos a few years later.
Okay, to be fair, it's like ten years later.
Spoilers!
Sorry.
No spoilers.
Got it.
I'll be careful.
You know, I don't use makeup the way other women do.
No, you don't.
Because it looks very bad.
I hardly ever look at myself in the mirror.
Maybe you should look more.
I always despise that kind of woman.
Oh no, she's not like other girls.
I've always dreamed of becoming a soldier.
Your foundation.
But I was wrong.
It wasn't really my dream.
My father.
He was killed in action when I was younger.
You wanted to follow in your father's footsteps?
Not really.
I thought that if I became a soldier, I could understand him better.
It looks good here.
And so, you became a soldier.
It looks like she tries to blend it in with her neck at least.
I thought I was.
Until today.
Now I understand.
The truth is, I was just afraid of looking at myself.
Afraid of having to make my own decisions in life.
I'm so sad about the music change.
But I'm not gonna lie to myself anymore.
I'll do it myself.
It's time I took a long, hard look at myself.
...
I want to know who I am.
What I'm capable of.
I want to know why I've lived the way I've lived until now.
I want to know...
Take a good look.
You won't be seeing mirrors for a while.
There won't be any chances to wash your face, either.
I know your foundation.
Yeah.
This isn't a training exercise.
Our lives are riding on this.
There are no heroes or heroines.
No.
You lose, you die a dog's death.
A dog's death.
Yeah.
Is that FAMAS functional?
I have one, too.
Unfortunately, it's out of ammo.
Where'd you get that Desert Eagle?
I found it in the armory.
It's a .50 caliber Action Express.
There was a SOCOM pistol, too.
But I chose this.
Look, give us the leftovers.
So I got a leftover, huh?
Isn't that gun a little big for a girl?
Hey, Snake.
Now you treat me like a woman?
Come on.
Use my .45.
I want the...
She's like, give me that bigger gun.
Listen, I've used a gun like this since I was eight years old.
I'm more comfortable with it than I am with a bra.
Woo!
Yes, Snake.
If we're gonna go north, we'll have to go through the commander's room on this floor.
Okay.
The overland route is blocked by glaciers.
The door to the commander's room is security level five.
But you got the key.
This card will open it.
Ah, yeah.
Why does this like lighting on Snake's face?
Looks like he's got like a lightning bolt.
It was inside the pocket of the uniform I was wearing.
Nice.
It looks like he must have been guarding someplace important.
Could've used that earlier.
Okay, let's go.
I know this place better than you.
I'll be point man.
Follow me.
Oh.
She's going.
She's running.
What?
Why is he in Australia?
What happened to the music?
I'll keep a lookout.
Make sure you're ready, okay?
What happened to the music?
Okay.
Give me one second.
I'm gonna go into Kodak real quick.
Um.
I'm gonna go put my pizza in the oven.
So then we'll run around and then we'll wait a little bit until my pizza's cooked.
Because it shouldn't take too long.
It should take like 10 minutes and I don't want to be in the middle of Mantis' fight when it goes off.
So give me... Sorry, I know I keep leaving.
But give me like 2 minutes to put it into the oven.
And yeah, I'll be right back.
Okie dokie.
Alright, let me set a timer for Oh.
Yeah.
Let me set a timer for 10 minutes.
Thank you for all the super times.
Thank you.
10 minutes would be 25.
Ok.
Save.
Alright, let's grab some stuff.
Actually, let's We can call the Kodak first.
Colonel, your niece is fine.
Thank goodness.
No.
Snake.
She's quite a woman.
Don't say that about her.
I can't ask you to watch after Meryl, but duty first.
Maybe I was wrong.
Sending my own flesh and blood to war.
She understands about duty.
I know she does.
But what I want to know is What was the real purpose of this military exercise?
I don't know.
Like I said, I'm nothing more than a middleman.
Is this transmission being monitored by the military?
Of course.
I get it.
All the world's a stage and we're merely players, right?
Yes.
But even players can influence the play.
I just hope we can prevent it from having a bad ending.
Thanks for the beat.
What did I call Meryl?
Is she right there?
Oh, no response.
Come on, girlie.
Come on.
Time.
Uh, Master Miller?
You managed to link up with Meryl.
Yeah.
Good.
So now you must have the card keys that will override the detonation code.
Yes, we're gonna override that code.
You should hurry.
The time limit is running out.
Oh my gosh.
We only probably have like two hours.
Let's see Nastasha.
You found Meryl.
The Colonel will be so relieved.
Oh, okay.
It's a good thing you hooked up with Meryl.
You should have seen the Colonel.
He doesn't like to let it show because he's the boss.
But he was so happy.
He could barely contain himself.
Oh, that's right.
Her codec is broken.
I'm glad to hear that.
You're right.
Why did I keep saying hook up with her?
I don't really like the...
I don't really like that wording.
Talk to you later, Snake.
Bye.
Wait, does she turn red in this too?
I'm looking at you.
What?
What is it?
I almost punched her.
Why are you staring at my...
I'm not staring at...
your face.
Why are you staring at my face?
Come on, Snake.
Don't stare at me like that.
She doesn't look to be getting redder.
Does she?
Why are you staring at my face?
What are you doing?
We've got to get a move on.
She's so shy.
Your face.
What?
What is it?
She doesn't seem to be getting redder, does she?
Takes a while?
Why are you staring at my...
face?
It's the foundation.
It's covering her blush.
So true.
Come on, Snake.
It doesn't take that long in the original.
Don't stare at me like that.
What's wrong with your face?
Why are you staring at my face?
What are you doing?
We've got to get a move on.
She's so like...
If she could like...
index finger...
What?
What is it?
She's so like...
Oh my god.
Right now she's giving Bella from Twilight.
Why are you staring at my...
She's giving...
She's so Bella from Twilight.
Why are you...
Come on, Snake.
I don't think she's going to turn red.
That's a little sad, but...
Are these guys still in here?
Even they are gone?
Okay.
Everyone's gone.
So I'm taking advantage of the situation, baby.
Yeah.
Let's take that.
Bombas bullets are full.
What's this?
Wait.
That's the Pazaza meme.
Sorry.
Don't hit me.
Get out of my way, Meryl.
Wait.
Why is the name of the Pazaza meme different?
What's this?
Call Soup.
Sorry.
I'm hiding now.
What does this say?
Notice.
Oh.
Not yet.
Over here.
Stung grenade.
No more Nikita.
Why are there so many?
They're all just chilling there.
Everything is...
I think I'm good, honestly.
On everything.
I don't think I can get anything else.
Unless there's like a... Yeah.
I'm good on everything.
It's a well-stocked office.
Yes, it is.
Nice.
I don't think there's anything under these ones.
I don't think I can remember.
Sorry.
This is what I mean, Meryl.
Get out of my way, Meryl.
Okay.
Hold on.
Let me...
How much time?
Okay.
I have five minutes before my pizza is done.
Like I said, I don't want to get into Psycho Mantis and like have to stop mid-fight.
Let's just listen to this ASMR of their footsteps.
Oh my god.
The sound...
This is so like...
Snake, let's hurry up and go to the commander's room.
I'm sorry!
She is not having it.
She is leaving without me.
What kind of pizza?
It's just cheese pizza.
It's just a cheese pizza.
Can I go back into the girl's bathroom?
I'm not going to see mirrors for very long anymore.
I'm a handsome fellow, aren't I?
Working mirrors.
Yeah.
Technology.
Okay.
Wash your hands.
Maybe there's stuff in here too.
We haven't checked.
Oh.
Nice.
Okay.
Is this the one with the toilet on the ground?
Oh!
Oh.
Excuse me, Meryl.
I have to go to the little girl's room.
And let's...
Also...
Sniffle.
Sniffle, sniffle, sniffle, sniffle.
Okay.
We're just wasting time right now.
No way!
It works!
Okay.
Hold on.
We have to wash our hands.
Sniffle, sniffle, sniffle, sniffle.
Get under the fingernails.
All dry.
Did you hear about the marines in real life who fooled an AI security camera during training by sneaking around in a cardboard box?
I have heard about that!
I have.
Okay.
God.
This sound is just so...
It's like the Barbie movie.
Oh, it's so satisfying.
Look at her, like, slapping her thigh with her gun.
She looks so cool.
Freeze.
I probably shouldn't joke with that because I will make a mistake.
I will accidentally shoot her.
Or purposefully.
Okay.
Just one more minute, you guys.
Actually, I'm just gonna go.
I'm just gonna go get my pizza out of the fridge.
Out of the oven.
Okay.
I'll BRB one more time.
I'm so sorry.
BRB.
Pizza is served.
They're really hot though, so I gotta let them cool before...
I think I really need to eat before I fight him.
So maybe we'll take a little bit of a break.
Little bit of a break.
Well, they need to cool down.
Actually, you know what?
I'll eat once they're cool.
And in the middle of the battle, maybe.
I just realized something.
Also, I'm gone.
I'm missing...
No, no!
I put my thing on backwards.
Hold on.
I have to fix my headband.
Good enough.
Okay.
I realized something.
For Psycho Mantis, you know how you have to change the controller port and all that fun stuff?
What?
What do I do on the GameCube?
Colonel will tell me.
Colonel will tell me, right?
Oh, sorry.
Colonel will tell me.
Yes.
Oh my gosh.
What's wrong, Snake?
Don't you like girls?
Ouch!
It's okay.
It's hot.
She's so cute.
Oh, no thinking!
My head!
It hurts to think!
I'm just a woman!
Don't come here, Snake!
I'm getting motion sick for real.
Too many thighs!
I don't think she's okay, Snake.
I don't think she's okay.
What happened?
I'm fine.
Hi, Hana!
What is that?
Okay.
Let's go.
Come on, Mr. Foxhound.
The commander is waiting.
Wait, where's our extra, like...
That's the extra, like, zoomies and stuff?
That's what you take away?
But you'll add in everything else to this version?
I like that line, though.
The commander is waiting.
Also...
Oh!
There it is!
I was gonna say...
When you look at her, it's...
You looking at her, but...
It switches!
Oh my gosh, that's kinda cool.
But you can't move it.
You can't move around or anything.
Oh!
That is pretty cool.
And also, she's red on the thing now.
The commander is waiting.
Can you tranq her?
I wonder in this part, actually.
If we can tranq her instead.
Whoa!
She's getting handsy with us.
No, don't go any lower.
Do you like me?
That's for Hal.
Whoa.
Hold me, Snake.
What's wrong?
Your psychotherapy.
Hurry.
Please.
Make left me.
Snake...
I want you.
Who's that?
The fact that Psycho Mantis is saying all this...
That's one freaky guy.
Meryl's?
Hold on.
Do I need to do something now?
I'm eating pizza.
That wasn't me.
Meryl's not herself.
Don't use your weapon.
I was only starting the codec.
He's controlling Meryl.
That tune is his mind control music.
Don't use your weapon.
Try to knock her out.
Okay.
Oh, he shot me?
That's so messed up.
I was answering the codec.
Oh!
Whoa!
Wait.
I forgot how to shoot all of a sudden.
There we go.
She's out?
Useless woman!
Optic camouflage, huh?
Who are these guys?
I hope that's not your only trick.
Ah!
Him!
You doubt my power.
Psycho Mantis.
Now I will show you why I am the most powerful practitioner of psychokinesis and telepathy in the world.
No, there's no need for words, Snake.
I am...
Psycho Mantis.
Nyam!
That's right.
Doug Stone is so awesome.
This is no trick.
It's true power.
Who's the white guy?
That's useless.
I told you.
I can read your every thought.
Kojima!
In the middle.
Psycho Mantis.
Oh.
You're a careless man, aren't you?
Hey, what are you trying to say, huh?
However, you are a skilled warrior.
Yeah.
You like brute force.
Sure.
You are extremely cautious around traps.
Yeah, I am.
Still don't believe me?
Now I'll read more deeply into your soul.
She's just sleeping on the ground in front of us.
I see that you enjoy Nintendo games.
You like Silicon Knights games, don't you?
So you like adventure games?
Did you enjoy playing Eternal Darkness?
I'll be honest...
You seem to like The Legend of Zelda, don't you?
I had a friend help me set up the memory card.
You like action games?
You've been playing Super Mario Sunshine.
Just for this part.
No, I have not.
I'm a prudent person.
Don't believe me?
I will show you my psychokinetic power.
Put your controller on the floor.
Okay, I'm actually gonna put it close to the mic.
Put it down as flat as you can.
I'm not touching it though.
I mean, I'm holding it up.
Oh, he's looking at me?
Okay, I'm sorry.
That's good.
Okay.
It's flat on my hands.
Now, I will move your controller by the power of my will alone.
Not the fourth wall break.
Okay, here we go.
It's barely moving.
Oh my god.
It's barely shaking.
I don't even think you can hear it.
Thanks to your friend for saying that.
What do you think now?
Can you feel my power?
The demonstration is over.
Stop
drop and roll!
What is going on?
What?
Huh?
I don't remember.
The pictures.
Wait, they're back to normal.
Um...
That was weird.
Oh!
Um...
Colonel, what do I do?
No!
Not you, Naomi!
Help!
After the collapse of the Soviet Union, he came to America looking for a job.
He worked with the FBI on several cases as a psychic provider.
I'm sorry.
It's so funny.
He came to America because he was jobless.
He was unemployed.
He got too far into the killer's mind.
As a result, he became just like the killer.
So he was sort of infected by this serial murderer's thoughts?
In any case, after that he became sort of a psychic spy...
Wait, this music is not...
He traveled all around the world.
That's when he was recruited by Foxhound.
He can read people's minds.
This is not it.
He knows every move that you're going to make.
What should I do?
I've got no chance of beating him.
There must be some way.
He's a master at controlling people, Snake.
Don't let him manipulate you.
I don't know about the music.
I think we just got blasted.
Yep.
M9?
I don't need that.
Oh, I guess for Meryl.
Oh, nice.
Oh my god.
Okay, maybe I have to try shooting him.
Oh, shit!
Ouch!
Okay.
I have to remember his patterns again.
Oh, god.
Oh, that's...
Oh, no!
He's right there.
Oh, god.
Ouch.
Ouchie ouch.
No, not these guys, please.
Colonel, help me!
How do I shoot him?
I don't know what to do.
Not everything you see with your two eyes is real.
Destroying his spirit is more important than destroying his body.
Don't let him read you.
Okay.
Be a blank slate.
Clear your mind.
Um...
His...
Destroy his spirit.
Hey, Bozo.
Oh, god.
You look really dumb.
With that, uh...
Oh, my god.
You look really stupid with that mask on.
Uh...
You...
Your...
Your pants are ugly.
Oh, my god.
Oh, why don't you grow some hair, Baldi?
Ouch!
What port to put it in?
Put it in.
Somehow, you've got to get around him.
What port do I put it in?
Where do I put it in, Campbell?
Oh, my god.
He's using his psychic ability to read your controller's moves.
Campbell!
That's how he's evading your attack.
Okay.
I'm going to try port two.
You've got to do something so he can't read your controller's moves.
Think.
There must be some way.
Okay.
I'm on court...
I'm on port two right now.
There's four slots.
What?
How did that hit me?
I was on the ground.
Oh.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my god.
No, no, no, no.
Where are you?
Oh, where is he?
I
can't tell, actually, if I'm just bad or...
No.
Dang it.
Okay.
Actually, this remix is kind of awesome.
Ouch.
Okay.
Hold on.
It's not port two.
Turtle.
He's using his psychic ability to read your controller's moves.
That's how he's evading your attack.
Okay.
I'm going to try.
You've got to do something so he can't read your controller's moves.
Port three.
There must be some way.
Okay.
Oh.
Wait.
Where am I?
Oh.
I blend in with the floor.
Where are you?
There you are.
Come on.
Stop it.
Stop moving.
Oh.
Did I get you?
Nice.
Okay.
Port three.
Oh.
That's my arrow.
Ouch.
That didn't work.
Cut it out.
I can't...
Is it working?
Oh.
It doesn't seem to be working.
Oh, my God.
Not this thing again.
Not this guy, please.
Let's get here.
Oh, there's saw combos.
Where are you at?
There you are.
Oh, my God.
Shut up.
He's so slippery.
This guy is moving everywhere.
I don't think my shots are hitting him.
He's so slippery.
How is he?
I don't think...
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
Like, I know I'm bad, but like... Even
when he's still...
Oh no!
He dodged it still!
Wait, Colonel!
Colonel, wait!
Wait, Colonel, I think I...
Snake, is there any reason you can't use controller socket 4?
Oh.
Four?
Oh,
okay.
Four is a spooky number.
That's why.
Okay, we got this now.
Maybe.
Oh, if I can aim.
If I can aim for...
That's so funny.
What?
Oh, John.
These things suck.
Gosh, dang it, this guy again.
He's right there!
Actually, what if I use the fan mess instead?
Where are you?
Come here.
Where did you go?
And... shoot!
Whoa, whoa, where did you go?
Oh.
Dang.
This
is so scuffed.
This is so scuffed.
I was gonna say, it's way easier than the original, but it's just funny.
It's just funny how...
Hahahaha!
Ouch!
Oh!
And...
And, oh!
And, back to me.
Oh, not this guy again.
This is kinda the best spot.
Uh, this is so funny.
Oh.
Oh, not Meryl again.
Okay, this is fine though.
This is fine.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What's going on?
Uh...
I don't know.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, girly.
Ah, girly!
Hold on!
We'll get her.
We'll get her down.
Come on.
There we go.
Easy peasy.
That was close.
Meryl, stop!
Oh, oh, oh, oh my god.
I thought me punching her did enough.
Um... Okay, that should be good now.
Okay.
Okay, so fa- Oh, oh, I ran right into that.
Where are you?
Oh, there you are.
What?
I cannot read you!
Oh, where did you go?
Nobody?
Oh, no.
Where are you?
Oh.
Ouch!
He's so fast.
I shot him in the butt!
Oh, uh, oh, dang it.
I pressed X too slowly.
Oh, they're all coming out.
Oh, he's pulling out all the stops.
That's fine.
I can still hit you.
Colonel, your niece is going to be okay.
Is she?
I owe you one.
No way.
The boss fights in this are crazy.
But why did you go so far out of your way to save her?
For Campbell's sake?
Or maybe it's because you like her?
I don't want to see any woman die right in front of me.
Or a person, you know?
I don't want to see anyone die.
Since when did anybody's death bother you so much?
Naomi, it's true that Snake has killed a lot of people.
But that does not mean he doesn't have a heart.
It's okay, Colonel.
She's right.
Nah, just women.
Arigato, arigato.
Is it still possible to beat Psycho Mantis by dying twice and calling the Colonel afterwards to find out what's during the statue bust?
Oh, yeah!
Okay.
Should I switch back to port one?
Does it matter at this point?
Controller port?
Yeah, sorry.
I know.
I'm like trying port two, port three, and then Colonel's just like, hey, any reason you haven't switched to port four, dummy?
To get to Metal Gear's underground maintenance base, you have to go through the hidden door.
Open the door.
There's a hidden door behind the bookcase.
Yeah.
Called out.
I thought, well, I hit him that one time.
Go past the communication towers.
So I thought with the three port, it was fine.
And use the tower's walkway.
Hang time.
And then I'll tell you this.
I can read people's minds.
First time clear.
In my lifetime, I have read the past thousands and futures.
This game is way easier.
You don't need to thank, or you don't need to congratulate me.
Thousands upon thousands of men and women.
But thank you so much for that, Akadu.
Oh, disgust.
Oh, God.
Oh, gross.
Oh, you're so mean, Meryl.
And each mind that I peered into.
Was stuffed with the same single object of obsession.
That selfish and atrophistic desire to pass on one's seed.
It wasn't enough to make me sick.
Every living thing on this planet exists to mindlessly pass on their DNA.
We're designed that way.
And that is why there is war.
Is that?
But you...
Is that it?
...different.
I don't know about that.
You're the same as us.
We have no past.
No future.
Aw, no.
Snake has his dogs.
We live in the moment.
That's our only purpose.
He has his dogs.
Humans weren't designed to bring each other happiness.
I kind of like that they're not showing his face.
From the moment we're thrown into this world, we're fated to bring each other nothing but pain and...
Ah!
Oh, just kidding.
The first person whose mind I dove into was my father's.
Don't scare.
I saw nothing but disgust and hatred for me.
It is hard.
Because I was thinking in like...
My mother died in childbirth.
In the original, they show his face obviously, but it's more low poly, so you can't really tell how he looks exactly.
My father was going to kill me.
Oh.
That's when my future disappeared.
Voldemort confirmed.
And my past as well.
When I came to, the village was engulfed in flames.
Are you saying that you burned your village down to bury your past?
I see that you have suffered the same trauma.
We are truly the same.
You and I.
The world is a more interesting place with people like you in it.
I never agreed with the boss's revolution.
His dreams of world conquest do not interest me.
I just want an excuse to kill as many people as I could.
You monster.
Let him talk.
Yeah.
He doesn't have much time left.
I've seen true evil.
Snake, seeing you calms my soul.
Let him cook.
I'm like the boss.
No, worse.
That's so messed up.
Compared to you, I'm like a saint.
How could you even say that?
I read her mind as well.
Meryl's.
I saw you there.
You have a large place in her heart.
A large place.
And getting bigger.
But I do not know if your futures lie together.
Oh, they do not.
Getting bigger.
I have a last request.
What is it?
My mask.
Put it back on.
Okay.
The voices are too strong.
Like this, other people's thoughts force their way into my mind.
Before I die, I want to be by myself.
I want to be left alone in my own world.
No.
I really like Psycho Mantis.
I'll open the door for you.
If you want to find your future, go through that door.
The controller is rumbling more than when he was controlling it.
This is the first time I've ever used my power to help someone.
Awww.
Strange.
Such a nostalgic feeling.
Even in a goofy version of the series like this, it gets me all choked up.
Let's go, Meryl.
I'm sorry.
Meryl.
How could I let Mantis control my mind like that?
If you're going to doubt yourself, I'll leave you here.
You're right.
Don't regret your past.
Learn from it.
Regrets just make a person weaker.
So true, Snake.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
I won't do it again.
Snake, can I ask you something?
What's your name?
What's your birthday?
More complaints.
Your family.
About what Mantis said.
I was just wondering...
No regrets.
What?
What's the problem now?
No regrets.
Oh, no.
Nothing.
What's your issue?
What are you complaining about?
Are you cold?
What's your name?
Your real name.
I don't got one.
A name means nothing on the battlefield.
After a week, no one has a name.
How old are you?
Old enough.
Old enough to know what death looks like.
Any family?
No.
But I was raised by many people.
Is there anyone you like?
My dogs.
I've never been interested in anyone else's life.
My fifty huskies.
So you are all alone.
Just like Mantis said.
Other people just complicate my life.
I don't like to get involved.
You're a sad, lonely man.
Come on.
Let's go.
I like the original more because I think in the original it was more like kind of quick, like quick quips.
Like, how old are you?
Blah, blah, blah.
Where are you?
Like, how many people are in your family?
Blah, blah, blah.
Like it was, oh, oh, I used controller.
There we go.
Look out.
Yay!
Plugged it all back up.
Why is it so loud in my rumbly ears?
Who is this guy?
Who's that guy?
Actually, who's this guy too?
Oh, Silicon Knights guy!
Oh!
I see, I see, I see.
Wait, that's Yoji Shinkawa?
Is it actually?
He looks, no.
Is it?
He looks so young if that's him.
Is it actually Yoji Shinkawa?
Oh my gosh, I didn't recognize him because he looks so young.
No way!
Oh my gosh.
I mean, so does Hideo Kojima.
He looks so young.
Oops, sorry.
Ugh, I'm gonna miss this sound.
So crisp.
Yummy.
Good night.
Good night, sweet prince.
Alright, let's go, Merrill.
Oh, let's save.
Tongues!
No, I didn't use tongue.
Timelessly lie with their dying breaths.
I think he was telling the truth.
Maybe you should believe him.
Hmm.
Now you can eat your pizza in peace.
Actually, I already finished it.
I already finished my pizza.
Please Snake, don't give up.
Don't give up.
I think, actually, maybe we'll get to, right?
Like we'll get to...
Uh... Sniper Wolf.
Not finished Sniper Wolf.
We'll get to Meryl being down and then we can end it, because... I want to go keep going, just a little bit more.
You're welcome.
Oh.
You have something to say?
Can you please eat the mic?
You should be able to go north from the commander's room.
Master Mailer?
Psycho Mantis.
What a pathetic man.
He was born with all the right tools, but he never knew how to use them.
Never knew how to use them.
She's right behind me.
But if she's just like Snake, I'm right here.
The enormous costs for the development of military...
Are you eating your pizza while touching your controller with greasy hands?
Sacrilege.
No!
It's not... It wasn't that greasy of a pizza.
What did you say?
I missed what Nastasha said because of you.
Oh yeah, I forgot about Otacon.
Sorry, Otacon.
Wait, is he listed?
I don't remember what his codec is.
Is he in here?
Oh no.
What is Otacon's codec?
One for... Ah yes, 14112.
Sorry?
I guess fighting was all he ever knew.
What are you feeling sorry for him?
Sorry?
The Mantis had incredible power.
Mr. Hater.
Fantastic power.
Are you Canadian?
Maybe that power could have been used to make people happy.
Did you just say sorry?
It's a sad thing when you see all that power being used just for war.
What are you feeling sorry for him?
Snake.
Metal Gear is in an underground base to the north.
Hurry!
Snake.
Okay.
Let's go.
What's over here?
Nice.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry, girl.
Wow.
Okay.
You don't have to be so dramatic about it, Meryl.
Sheesh.
Left picture is Ryuhei Kitamura.
Japanese movie director who directed the Twin Snake cutscenes.
Oh!
I was gonna say.
Could there be wolves in here?
I was like...
Wolf dogs.
No wonder.
Okay.
So it wasn't Yoji Shikawa.
I feel... I don't feel as bad now.
How do you know so much?
Oh!
Five, six, seven, oh, nine.
I'm a musher.
Oh, my God.
I love it.
I'll take point.
Snake, you follow me.
Oh!
Oh, that's where we crawl through.
Huh?
Whose footsteps are these?
Where did you go?
Follow me.
To where, madam?
You just left me...
You left me to die.
No.
We can fit through there.
Okay.
I believed it maybe in...
In...
In the original, but there...
No, we can fit through that.
Please do a $40 reward.
Oh!
We can fit through that.
Snake, just go through.
Sounds kind of meaty.
We can fit through that.
Is this the way we came from?
Yeah.
Oh!
How do I get the dogs to pee on my box?
Oh, I hear them.
I hear them growling.
Oh!
Scary.
Oh, wait.
Actually, I can put them to sleep.
Oh!
Why is the music so scary?
Wait.
Oh!
I'm scared.
Why is it so scary?
Ah!
Good to know that there's some ammo there, though.
Oh!
Wait.
Where is he coming from?
Dog!
Wait.
Where did...
Where am I coming from?
I'm lost already.
Okay.
This...
Wait.
That's where we crawled out from, right?
Okay.
Can he pee on my box?
Pee on my box?
Pee on my box.
Oh!
Nice!
Pee on my box.
Wait.
It's never in the ground floor.
I need him to pee on my box so that we can get past the dogs easily.
Go!
Oh yeah, I have to punch her.
That's right.
We punch her and then hide.
And then... wait, which way is it?
I can't tell.
You know what, let's just go.
They're here.
Is this the correct spot?
Uh... maybe.
What's this?
Oh, this is Azimim.
Nice.
Wait, is this a hole?
It's so hard to tell.
Oh gosh, even in the original, I can never remember.
Oh no.
Okay, hold on.
Wait, this one, this one, this one.
Right?
A little...
Yeah.
There she is.
And the dog.
The baby dog.
Oh, he likes...
Why do they all like her?
It's cause she's so cute.
Okay, so we gotta hit her.
Hide!
I think I'm in trouble.
There's a whole cutscene.
Well, that didn't go as planned.
Too slow?
Oh yeah.
Okay.
One more try.
I had it.
What are you thinking?
You gotta get distant.
Oh.
What are you doing?
Stop.
Hold on, Meryl.
Ah!
Now they won't attack me.
Yay!
What are you doing?
Okay.
Come on, Meryl.
Let's get you...
Oh, sorry.
Let's get you in trouble.
You're so cute.
I wish I could pet the dog.
Look how cute it is.
Oh my god.
He's so cute.
Look at him.
He looks so happy.
Oh my gosh.
So cute.
All right.
Let's go.
Okay.
This place is mined.
I'll take point again.
Stay back, okay?
Okay.
But the radar isn't working.
And since we can't use the mine detector either...
No.
Psycho Mantis.
Leave it to me.
Okay.
So what do you think?
Pretty good, huh?
How did you know where the mines were?
It sounds weird, but when Mantis dove into my mind...
I was able to see where the mines were placed.
Are you impressed?
Well, a little bit.
Ew!
Only a little?
Are you impre...
It...
I...
You know what?
It was worth that.
I think.
Quite honestly.
Anyway...
Here I come.
I'm done.
Why are we once again standing in the middle of the way?
Why do we never learn our lesson?
Why?
Oh my god.
Why are you turning around?
No!
Oh my gosh.
Merrill.
Merrill?
Merrill!
Merrill, don't you know what that is?
Why are you guys just standing there?
Oh, she's actually...
She purposefully aimed for the leg.
Oh my god.
Like, I know she wasn't trying to kill her.
Sniper.
She's just getting every limb.
Dang.
Oh my gosh.
Sniper.
Why?
Oh my gosh.
Merrill.
Snake, leave me and run.
I guess I'm a rookie after all.
Oh, both of you are.
For standing in the middle of the way.
Her leg.
It's the oldest trick in the book.
You guys, this is actually the last time we will see Merrill.
Sniper's using me for bait to lure you out.
Oh my gosh.
This is the last time we will see Merrill.
Shoot me, Snake.
No.
My gun.
I can't reach it by myself.
Since we're going for the Otacon exit ending.
I promised I wouldn't slow you down.
I...
I can still help.
It's actually her...
I wanna help you.
This is actually her death.
It's so sad.
Why down?
Save your strength.
It's actually so sad.
Bye, Merrill.
I was a fool.
I wanted to be a soldier.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Merrill.
War is meaningless.
Nothing comes out of war.
Snake, please.
Ew.
Save your strength...
It's so like...
It's sad watching her trying to reach for her gun.
Don't give up on people.
So sad.
Please, help me.
She's being so dramatic despite dying.
Gosh, why are you gonna be so dramatic, Meryl?
I love that scene in the original.
Who just said Colonel?
Who just said that?
It must be Sniper Wolf, Foxhound's best shooter.
Sniper's usually work in pairs.
Who said Colonel?
I know her.
Naomi maybe.
She can wait for hours, days, or weeks.
It was a woman's voice.
She's just watching and waiting for you to expose yourself.
It's not Snake.
Maybe so, but Meryl can't hold out that long.
Snake, can you see Wolf from where you are?
There's nowhere to hide between here and the tower.
She must be on the second floor of the tower.
Tower.
Perfectly.
It's the classic sniper's position.
Classic.
At that distance, you won't be able to hit her with a standard weapon either.
You'll need a sniper rifle.
The penis gene.
Take it easy.
I'm going to save Meryl, no matter what it takes.
Okay.
Thanks.
What's wrong, Naomi?
Don't you know?
There's a tendency toward murder written in your very genes.
So saving someone else's skin is out of the question.
Why are you gotta bring that up again?
I don't know that far, but...
I don't know what the hell my genes look like, and I don't care.
I operate on instinct.
You hate me so much, Naomi.
Like an animal?
Like an animal.
I'm going to save Meryl.
I don't need an excuse.
Okay.
And I'm not doing it for someone else either.
I'm going to save Meryl for myself.
Colonel, don't worry.
Snake.
Thanks.
I understand.
Don't thank me yet.
I'm sorry.
Don't thank me yet, Colonel.
You have no reason to thank me.
I love that scene in the original where like the codec is just like going off over and over again.
And Snake is just sitting there like, oh my God, what do I do?
What do I do?
Like he's just...
He's not moving.
He's just like thinking.
Wait,
don't you like...
Oh.
Who...
Who caught me then?
Oh my gosh.
You are freaking me out, little pup.
Please.
Thank you.
Those dogs after getting a whiff of newly scented box on Snake.
Time to leave.
We're good now.
Everything's fine now.
Oh, Famas.
Very nice.
Can I always use more of that?
This is the PSG.
Okay.
Is that an exit?
Right there?
What is...
Nothing.
Oh, I guess there's nothing here.
Okay.
Go.
Crawl.
Stay.
Okay.
Nice.
See?
That's why the box was there.
That's why the box was important, everybody.
That's why the box was so important.
Dogs just running around in circles.
Okay.
We have to go all the way back to the...
Oh my goodness.
I can't find where the door is.
I have to go all the way back to the...
To the armory?
But we will do that next time.
Okay.
Even though I want to keep playing.
We will do that next time.
It's rumbling in my ears again.
What is this thing?
Is that a phone?
Ooh, it's freaky.
Wait.
Oh, the mirror's all broken, too.
He doesn't like to see himself.
What the heck is this thing?
I was wondering that before.
Is this in the...
Oh, that's the communications tower, isn't it?
We fight the hindie up there, right?
Oh, that's kind of funny.
Oh, fun!
Interesting, interesting.
Are those the giant staircases you climb?
Yes.
And I think we have...
Oh, wait.
We have 14 chaff grenades!
We're doing well.
We're doing alright.
Wait, are there any...
Are we still alone in here?
Oh.
No, we're not.
Okay.
Gonna go here.
Okay, yeah.
We're gonna go back inside.
I'm gonna save.
Save, save, save.
And yeah, we'll finish it off here.
You called, Snake?
Yep.
Nice.
Save complete.
The Chinese say it is the strong swimmer who most often drowns.
It's because the strong swimmer overestimates his abilities and underestimates the strength of the river.
You're probably quite used to the mission now, but don't get careless.
No, I'm not careless.
I'm very careful.
Do you remember what day tomorrow is?
You know, I thought about maybe if I finish this next week, maybe doing like playing Metal Gear Solid like Sunday, Monday, Tuesday.
Or, I don't know.
I don't know how long it would take me.
Maybe even like Saturday, Sunday, Monday, Tuesday.
Of like the 27th, 28th, 29th, 30th.
So, maybe.
Because I knew...
The other day I was just like, oh my gosh, it's A!
April!
I can do April 30th!
So...
The OG, of course.
I mean...
Well, actually it would probably be the Master Collection.
Or...
I already...
I've done the HD Collection.
Probably will be the Master Collection.
But...
Depends on how...
How...
I don't know.
I don't know if I would need four days.
I guess it depends on how much I play each day, right?
And how well I do.
But...
I think I'll...
I don't know.
We might do it.
Who knows?
The Master Collection kinda poopy.
No, they fixed it!
They have done a lot of patches.
I think it's...
Most...
I think it's like pretty much up to speed now.
From what I understand.
Like they've done a lot of patches on it.
So...
Um...
Updates are great.
Yeah.
They've done a bunch.
That was a good run, Mint.
Thank you!
Andregos, thanks for the tan gift!
And thank you!
I do wanna keep playing, but...
Um...
I...
I'm still not sure about a stream tomorrow.
Actually...
Um...
There's actually something I kinda wanna play.
There was a new...
Um...
Hollow Indie game that came out.
Like the...
Wow Wow Korone...
Korone...
Box?
Uh...
Hold on.
What is it called?
Ko...
Korone...
Yeah!
The Wow Wow Wow Korone Box!
I was thinking of playing that tomorrow.
So...
Um...
Since I didn't have a game planned or anything.
So...
Not sure what time yet.
Uh...
Might start actually around the same time as today's stream.
So...
Yeah!
And uh...
But it looks really fine and really cute.
So I wanted to try it out.
And I love Korone-san.
So...
Mm-hmm!
I haven't seen it yet.
So...
Uh...
That'd be good to see.
Yeah!
I wanna try it.
It looks so fine.
Um...
And uh...
Yeah!
Um...
Mythanar!
Thank you for the tan!
Gifted!
Thank you!
I saw that she got a new outfit.
It's so...
It's not what I expected.
Like...
It's so...
It's so cool!
The...
The Viking...
Viking style.
It's so...
I like her...
How messy and like...
Shaggy her hair is.
It's really cute.
So yeah...
It's so her too.
Yeah!
The Vinland Saga fit.
Her new song?
Oh wait!
I don't...
I don't know if I heard her new song.
I'm not going to listen to it here...
But...
Coll...
Collon...
Oh!
Trouble Wan...
Wan!
That's so cute!
I will listen to it.
Um!
But yeah...
Glad we get to watch you play Twinsnakes at last.
Me too!
Oh my gosh!
The cutscenes...
Are killing me.
Each time...
They are so crazy!
It's so much fun!
Okay.
They're so, so, so fun.
They're so outlandish.
I love them.
For real.
Thank you, Maryland!
Thank you for the stream.
You can never have enough MGS.
Those laughing pictures from the Mantis fight will give...
Those are really creepy!
I did not expect that.
I did not.
It was freaky.
It was freaky, freaky.
Still so surreal seeing this game in HD.
It's cool.
It is very different.
You can't replace the original, but I'm glad it exists.
Me too!
I agree.
Obviously, I don't say this is a remake remake.
That's why I'm very interested in what MGS3 Delta will be like.
I don't think it'll... I mean, I don't know.
I don't think it'll be like this.
But, it seems like they're remaining true to the original.
So, I'm very curious.
Like, if it's just gonna be the same game.
But, maybe, hopefully with, like, better gameplay.
And just, like, the cutscenes all the same.
Just HD graphics.
Thank you for the 50 gifted!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
I wouldn't...
I wouldn't really want it to be like this.
So...
But, we shall see.
I suppose.
We shall see.
This one...
It does...
The cutscenes do feel really weird.
Because...
Like, the tone is just completely different.
In the original, like, you can feel, like, this cold...
Holowness.
You know, like...
Because the audio is so...
Like, it's echoey.
And it's...
And...
It just feels, like, so different.
And, like...
So, each has a different energy.
Like, this one is so much more action.
And...
Crazy.
Outlandish.
But...
So, it's not...
I don't think I...
It's like...
I don't prefer this one.
But...
I also still love this one.
Because it's so funny.
Yeah, way di...
Different atmosphere.
Yeah!
And the music in the first one!
So...
It just hits so good.
Like, it just...
Even for me, when I was first playing it...
Like...
Obviously, I never played it as a kid.
I never even seen footage of it as a kid.
Like, I...
Never touched it until I first played it.
But...
Like, it still felt, like, nostalgic.
There's just something about it.
Then, I...
I did like, uh...
Psycho Mantis's...
Zzz...
Remix.
That was cool.
But...
Still hits different.
Yeah.
Humma humma.
Humma humma humma.
Twin Snakes seems pretty great so far.
It is a lot of fun.
It's...
Uh...
I'm...
Kind of like...
Oh!
If I play this...
And then play MGS2...
Next?
Maybe I won't...
Like, uh...
Well, the controls will be...
Uh...
A little different.
But...
Maybe...
It...
I'll...
It'll be, like, more...
I'll be able to...
Be a little bit more used to it.
Because I have not...
I have not touched MGS2.
I think since I last played it.
Twin Snakes seems like Otacon retelling the story to add its otaku weeb flair to the reality of what actually happened.
That's my favorite theory.
Yeah.
Mint doko?
Mint koko!
But yeah.
Thank you guys for, uh...
Hanging out with me.
With playing this.
And, um...
I think I'm...
I'm...
Going to go to bed.
Oh!
I was a little late...
For a stream today.
I had to delay it by about 45 minutes.
Which again...
Uh...
Actually, I don't think I apologized for that in the beginning.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry that I was late.
I had some errands.
And, um...
Hold on.
Uh...
Let me...
I did save, right?
I'm actually...
I...
I plan on talking just a little tiny bit more.
But I'm actually gonna turn off the gameplay.
And, um...
Uh...
I don't want it to, like...
Wear out or anything.
So, give me a second.
Let's transition here.
And I'm gonna just turn it off.
Okay.
Um...
Uh...
So, I was a little bit late.
But I cannot say why.
Hmm...
I...
Cannot say why I was a little bit late...
Hmm...
Mysterious...
Curious...
Yes!
I had some errands.
I went out...
Um...
Of my maid cafe.
I did a little bit of outside haunting.
Hmm...
Taco Bell?
I wish I had Taco Bell to go with.
Who said giving birth?
I don't think ghosts can give birth.
I don't...
I
don't think ghosts...
Nope.
I don't think ghosts can give birth.
But...
Congratulations.
Yeah, you'll be saying that.
You'll be saying that later.
You will be.
You will be saying that later.
Once I can tell you.
Maybe.
Yeah.
I think so.
But yeah, sorry I can't tell you yet.
But I also may have hinted about it in the next podcast episode on Monday.
So be sure to listen to episode...
3?
3.
Right?
3?
3.
Yes, 3.
Yeah.
So...
It feels so much longer.
When someone was just like...
Someone was just like...
Almost 2 weeks that you've been back.
I mean maybe if you count...
April 1st.
But...
I don't know.
Sorry.
Podcast episode 3.
Snake Eater.
Cheapreg.
No.
I'm gonna go sleep.
It was fun to be here.
I'm just getting sleepy.
Have a good night.
Thanks for hanging out till the end.
Congratulations in advance.
I hope it's a healthy big baby boss.
Boss baby.
Can't wait for April 30th.
April 30th.
I'm just like...
Yeah, I can wait.
Because I have so much that I need to plan and think of.
But I'm like...
Wait.
I want time to slow down a little bit.
I don't need it to go so quickly.
But...
Hopefully...
But the brain rot.
I missed you like I missed the raft.
You belong...
You belong on this boat.
Man.
Came back just to say thanks for the stream.
Thank you.
Time either goes too fast or too slow.
Yeah, I know.
Sometimes...
Though, if it's too slow, you gotta just...
Think and be like...
Okay, you know what?
It might be something that I'm doing that I don't like.
And it's going too slow.
And I just want it to pass.
But at the same time, you should appreciate the slow times too.
Because...
Um...
You know, then if you're just like...
When it gets too fast...
It's too...
It's...
It's hard to...
Notice...
It's hard to notice things in the moment.
When things are too fast.
Like a kidney stone.
If you have a kidney stone, go on a roller coaster.
Like... I think...
What is it?
Thunder Mountain...
Third seat from the last or something?
Is...
Huh?
What?
Yeah, if you have a kidney stone...
Some doctors actually...
I wanna say doctors.
I'm not a doctor, so don't listen to that.
Some things do...
I have read...
That it is also...
Said that you...
Should go on certain roller coasters...
That will help dislodge it.
I feel like...
2024 just came, but now it's already April.
I know!
I know, right?
Well, I mean, I spent two months in Japan and that flew by so quickly.
So...
To me, I can't even believe it's April.
Mid-April, I thought.
Disclaimer.
Mint is not a doctor.
No, I am a ghost maid.
I am not a doctor.
Yet.
Hmm...
With jumping out of a plane work...
No, I think you actually need like...
The bumpiness of a roller coaster to...
Dislodge it.
Like, look it up!
Look it up!
I wrote this before I saw Sakura.
Wow!
I didn't see it at all!
Too bad.
Well, it's okay.
Next year too.
Sakura.
Time flies when you're having fun.
And I've been having a lot of fun since you've been back, Mint.
Thank you!
Thanks, Nixxi!
Congratulations on being a doctor.
Stop spoiling!
Stop it!
I don't need excuses to go on a roller coaster.
All I'm saying is that...
It could help.
If you have a kidney stone.
Not 100%, but you know.
Yeah.
Hi, Asu!
Hot nurse Mint.
What?
Okay.
Tomorrow, like I said, I think I'll be streaming same time-ish.
Not as on the schedule, but as when I started the stream.
So, about 4pm EST.
I'll make a waiting room for it tonight.
But as usual, I probably won't be streaming on Monday.
So...
So you can watch the...
Watch the...
No.
Yes.
Listen to the podcast.
Listen to it.
You guys, I have a question.
Sorry, I just opened up Twitter.
When...
When did yapping become the word?
You know what I mean?
When did...
I feel like ever since I came back...
Like...
Everyone started saying like...
I'm doing a yapping stream.
When did that happen?
3 months ago?
So it's recent, huh?
I was like...
I've never seen it before.
When I come back and suddenly everyone's like...
I'm yapping.
I'm yapping here.
When the Twitch emote got popular.
Oh, it's a Twitch emote.
I heard it for the first time from Tuna.
Mint Phantom MD.
MD stands for maid doctor.
Yes.
I just ordered one of 5000 keycard set from MGS.
Oh, yes!
Nice!
I did want to get those too.
But it kind of feels weird.
It feels weird that they are 3 different cards.
Yappity yappy yapp.
Hmm.
Like I've heard of yapping before.
Like a word.
Like I didn't think it was a new word.
I'm surprised that so many Vtubers were using it.
For their streams.
Like if sometimes for like Zatsudan and stuff.
I would like call them chit chatting.
But...
But now they're all becoming yapping.
Yapping is from TikTok?
Oh wait, who?
Nobody...
Oh wait, the sources are getting crossed.
Okay, hi!
Welcome to membership.
Mr. Bones, welcome to membership.
Thank you!
Yeah, it just kind of picked up.
Hmm.
And like Matara says it all the time too.
So I'm just like...
Yappy yappy yapp.
Play Ace Combat.
Oh my gosh, what is this username?
You don't have to super chat me to play it.
Though I don't have any plans on playing it super soon.
But...
You can probably see it in the future.
Dr. Mint playing as Big Boss.
Can it be V?
I'm not Big Boss.
I'm Solid Mint.
It's popularized on TikTok.
Just looked it up.
There's actual research on roller coasters and kidney stones.
Thunder Mountain is recommended roller coaster...
That's what I said!
I don't know if you remember, but one time in Among Us, you said you have a very large pee-pee.
Is this still true?
Having a large pee-pee is...
Is a physical...
Not a physical.
It's a mindset.
Right?
I'd say...
I'd say sure.
Anyway.
It's a state of mind.
A mint set.
Yes.
The big pee-pee grind set.
Yeah.
Just...
Just think it and you got it.
April has been great so far.
My Kamiyoshi is back from hiatus.
I started a new job.
My best friend got engaged.
Here's to a fun summer.
Oh my gosh!
Congrats, Melanie!
Let's go!
Does Solid Mint imply the existence of liquid mint and gas mint?
Well, I mean, if I'm a ghost, I'm like kind of gaseous?
Maybe?
I don't want to say that.
I think...
I don't think I should say that.
I don't think I should say I'm gassy.
I don't think I should...
Okay.
Hold on.
If I say something stupid, I gotta do this.
Oh, wait.
Oh, no.
Hold on.
I messed up.
Thank you!
Soup?
If I say something dumb...
And I put this over my face...
There we go.
I should not say...
I should not say what I just said earlier.
Mistress, thank you!
Congratulations on threatening that accountant and getting your taxes done.
Oh, you can come back.
I mean, I didn't threaten anyone.
As mentioned, Ryuhei did a 1-2-1 cutscene remake of the OG Ps1 cutscenes before Kojima told him specifically Make it like one of his action films and then re-film them.
I did know about that.
Yes, yes.
Thank you for the really fun stream, Mint.
I'm so happy to get to see you play it and enjoy all the silly cutscenes.
I'm so happy seeing you react to snakes.
Sounds like a spy movie.
It's so goofy.
I really just feel like Otacon retelling.
It does!
GGG.
Ghastly, gassy ghost.
Ghastly, gas...
I have to have this on the ready.
Wee-woo!
Incoming... bad clip!
Avert,
avert, avert your eyes!
Don't... don't... don't watch!
Don't watch!
Do... do... do not watch.
Let's pick a better...
Oh no, I think...
Oh, a bunch of my fonts got...
Here we go.
This one's kind of cuter.
Beep-boop!
And then let's make it center.
Wait, why is it like off like that?
Oh, there we go.
Okay, outline a little bit more.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, that's as thick as it can get.
Oh wait, hold on.
If I make it this size...
And there...
Making this really official, aren't I?
Oh, it's so small.
And...
Oh!
Wait, wait.
Reset, reset.
There we go.
Oh, this one too.
Okay, okay, okay.
Now that's...
There we go.
Okay.
I'm going to head out.
Thank you guys so much as always for all the support.
All the gifted memberships.
All the super chats.
All the donations.
I appreciate you guys so much.
Even though it overwhelms me.
In a good way though.
In a good way.
You guys have been so crazy supportive and awesome.
And I appreciate it so much.
I will see you guys later.
Maybe tomorrow.
If you want to come watch.
Thank you super chat.
Thank you.
Wait, I saw it.
Where did it go?
Never mind.
Did I imagine that?
I don't know.
Can I use that incoming bad clip sound bite as my channel intro?
Yes, of course.
Of course.
Oh, there it is.
Wait, no it's not.
I'm so confused.
Anyway.
Oh.
Let's bust in our way out of here.
Bust in our way out of here.
Yeah.
Something strange.
Sleeping in your bed.
Let me tell you something.
There's something weird.
Sleeping in your bed.
Let me tell you something.
Busting makes me feel good.
Bustin' x4 B -b-bustin'!
You're seein' thi-in' Sleepin' in your bed.
Thanks for the stream!
Otsuomito!
Yeah!
Bustin' makes me feel good!
Thanks for the super chat!
Ow!
Let me tell you something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Bustin', bustin', bustin', bustin', bustin' Makes me feel good, feel good, feel good, feel good, feel good Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Bustin', bustin', bustin', bustin', yeah, yeah, yeah Bustin', bustin', bustin', bustin' Makes me feel good, feel good, feel good, feel good, feel good, feel good, feel good
Freaky ghost maid!
Freaky ghost man!
Freaky man, baby!
Thank you, Elaine!
Let me sleep in your bed.
Let me tell you something.
Sleepin' makes me feel good.
I ain't afraid of no sleep.
I ain't afraid of no bed.
An invisible bed.
Freaky ghost bed!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah Yeah!
Thank you guys again...
for hanging out with me today.
and...
uh... everything!
I hope you guys have a great weekend I hope you have a good... well, good rest of year weekend.
as long as I don't see you tomorrow.
Um... eat something yummy...
Well, it's kind of late for me, but if it's not so late for you, get something good tonight to eat.
Whatever you want.
It's the weekend, baby!
Yeah!
Makes me feel good, feel good, feel good, feel good, feel good, feel good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Have a good rest of your night!
You too!
Feel good, feel good.
Gonna go celebrate my birthday.
My birthday, my sister's birthday!
Happy birthday to your sister!
Otsumito!
Bye bye!