Why is it so quiet?
Why are you guys so crazy?
Why are you so crazy?
Why are you all so crazy?
Actually crazy.
I'm looking at you.
The guy above me is crazy.
Absolutely bonkers.
Thank you guys.
for all the the the the members and the donated members and
the donors the super chats thank you thanks
oh my goodness gracious but yes, thank you thank you very
much, oh my gosh, thank you for that great super thank you
Super Chat is mint colored, right?
I'm colorblind.
No!
Oh, yes, I really appreciate it.
I opened memberships yesterday.
I didn't even tell anyone and people found out somehow,
which is so crazy.
But welcome to membership.
If you join, thank you.
Or if you gifted.
If you were gifted.
If you gifted, thank you.
And if you were gifted, thank you for being here.
Anyway, of course, there's no...
No pressure to donate as usual and no pressure to join or
anything like that.
And for anyone who says that it's too cheap, screw you.
For anyone who says raise the price, no.
What's wrong with you?
You say what's wrong with me and I say what's wrong with
you?
I ask, what is wrong with you?
i i mentioned it kind of before briefly i said that um you
know for memberships i planned on uh making them a lower
tier or lower to a lower price because um because uh since i
have the podcast uh to be honest i won't be able to focus so
much on like membership content it kind of was like you know
you'll get you'll get some membership streams oh my gosh the
50.
thank you guys thank you some membership streams of course
but
it's like mostly for the emotes and then once I get the
Minecraft server set up that access to that yeah no pressure
of course you guys are making me feel like I need to do more
because you guys are joining so fast and then gifting so
many.
But yeah, oh my gosh, thank you for the pinks, thank you.
Also, I wanna say a little bit today, I don't know, I have
not been feeling so great lately.
Like just until up until this stream, my stomach was killing
me again.
I think I am I am possessing some people that are not eating
healthily so please think of your local ghost maid and eat
well so that if I possess you you don't hurt me in return
you know I think part of it is stress though just because
you know I kind of came back from Japan and didn't didn't
have any time to rest when came back home and uh and also i
don't know early okay have you guys ever heard okay so this
is for all you cat owners out there if you weren't aware if
you ever smell your cat and they smell a little bit sweet
then you're then like kind of like a maple syrup it's like
it could be like an actual medical condition and i smelled
my cat's head and i was just like why do you smell so sweet
what did you get into and then I was like oh and I
remembered so tomorrow I have to call the vet and schedule a
yeah it could be diabetes like a feline diabetes or it could
be like you know I looked it up because I wasn't aware of
the other things but it could be also a kidney thing or a
skin thing and he has been having like some issues with his
ear so I'm hoping it's the skin thing thing to take care of
but he's gonna be okay um because i'm gonna take him to the
vet and we're gonna get him all checked out and but it does
stress me out a little bit if he's good or not you know what
i mean so he's pregnant oh my gosh i've always wanted kids
grand kittens hoping for the best thank you yeah sorry i
don't mean to like start the stream with like such a heavy
topic but you know um just letting you guys letting you guys
know why i'm feeling a little a little in the brain you know
oh my tea okay i'm gonna no okay hold on no okay i tested
the game yesterday and it did this to me it is so bizarre or
clicking on this is it's showing up in obs right it's
showing up in obs right but on my actual screen it's not so
i have to look at it through obs it's very strange wait how
do i get out of this just click okay let me i'm actually
gonna pop out the screen maybe let me try that and have the
have it open three times okay wait oh wait that doesn't work
because i still have to have it on this this is so weird i
think it's because it's so old subtitles on maybe oh yes
yeah they will be on i just uh so weird very weird anyway
game must be haunted i know the cursor is so cursed i'm
gonna actually sorry i'm gonna make the notice a tiny bit
smaller since i think there's gonna be a lot of them but
thank you um okay for people that don't know this game it's
old game i also don't know so much about it i've always seen
oh thank you for the 50 thank you thank you so much i've
always seen like um like uh screenshots from it but I'll be
honest I've never I've never played it I've never tried this
game before so um it's kind of reminds me of like the
negotiator it's old though it's old and I've also never
watched anyone play it I just know that it's a little cursed
and it's like it's like one of those games where you input
your actions or input what you say before like AI was ever
like it has its own like in-game AI you know yeah og AI
chatbot this this is a classic it is a classic a classic
classic it's it's pretty cursed um so we're gonna do our
best to I don't know I don't know cause some mischief or
something I don't know I don't know I don't know probably
fuck sorry have you guys seen that video of Miranda Cosgrove
and they're like what's your favorite cuss word and she goes
probably fuck sorry bleep that bleep that bleep that bleep
that probably beep sorry sorry sorry sorry for saying such a
bad word I'm so sorry oh my clutch is pearls
anyway i'm so sorry anyway it was the way that i it was the
way that i said cause some mischief that made me think of it
okay anyway you guys you guys get me right you guys
understand me
right so do we name ourselves a melon oh wait i have to
choose a name oh they don't have mint tammy wait what would
the closest to mint be mark mary matt mel mel michael thank
you for that thank you oh my nat nat nick nicole oh my gosh
there's so many names but they don't have mint hmm oh hi
mark david let's see let's go to the very top
Adam, Al, Andrew.
Oh, my gosh.
I might say your name.
Isn't that kind of crazy?
Gonzalo.
Gonzolo.
Ashley.
Oh, Audrey.
Ben.
Am I, did I say your name?
Where is your hand if I said your name?
Gonzalo.
Is that an actual one in here?
Is that a real name?
Geneva.
I've never heard of that name before either.
Espin.
Any Espin's in the chat?
Aaron.
Eric.
Emily.
Ellen.
Elizabeth.
Ed.
Doug.
Diana.
Roll call.
Whisp roll call.
I'm Gonzalo.
Okay, since you're Gonzalo, we'll go with Gonzalo.
Wait, what did I say?
Pliskin?
That's so funny.
I thought when I tested this out, I just picked Adam, but I
thought oh, it does say please choose a name.
Type the first letter, scroll with the arrow keys, press
enter to begin.
It does say that entirely.
And I just I thought maybe I could type in my name and I was
like will they say it like is there like an in-game voice
thing kind of like you know and like certain some uh what's
the word some gotcha games you type in your name and it'll
be like mint hello how are you mint you know Godzilla oh my
god blue archive
So let's look at the instructions real quick.
Type to speak to the character at any time.
Move around with the arrow.
Look at this keyboard.
Sorry.
If I move off the screen, it's because I have the other
window open like to see.
Type to speak to the characters at any time.
Move around with arrow keys.
Pick up and use objects with the mouse.
Actually, I wonder if there's another way that I can capture
this.
I wonder if I do window capture instead if it will allow me
to see it.
Do you guys mind?
Sorry, I totally should have.
I didn't think it would be an issue.
I should have totally done it off stream.
I should have, I was like, oh, maybe it's because I messed
with something.
I was doing a couple of setting things.
Go ahead.
Okay, thank you guys.
It's not going to take long.
Let's see.
Window capture.
La la la la la.
la la la oh wait this is wait this is even hold on this is
the see this is what i'm seeing when i click instructions
nothing this is oh my gosh so it doesn't okay wait hold on
i'm gonna restart the game oh oh okay let's let's restart
let's restart
Um, okay.
It's okay because there's a little scene at the beginning
too we can watch.
And the cursor's fixed!
Look at that!
I think it was good.
I'm gonna move it down.
There.
May take up to 60 seconds.
We are so back, baby!
Yippee!
Well, they did say 60 seconds.
Hello?
Hey, it's Tripp.
Oh my god, Tripp.
Jeez, it's been a long time since we got together.
Blow out my eardrums.
Grace and I just thought it'd be really nice to see you
tonight.
Tonight?
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
How about...
eight o'clock or something yeah that'd be uh that'd be
really nice or seven um yeah we can make it oh yeah i will
i'll be there ah it is so suspicious sounding what is so
suspicious out there
facade look our little happy happy couple question mark
Maybe he's just shy.
I also struggle with talking on the phone.
Thank you guys for all the super chats.
Thank you.
And let's see.
It works!
Okay.
There is no problem that I can't solve.
I'm a genius!
Okay, let's see the hints.
Oh, wow.
This is a lot.
Okay.
Grace and Trip are in a desperate situation.
They need you.
You could influence them in several ways.
Exactly.
how is up to you.
One approach is to try to help them, to get them to work
through their problems.
Or you could try to provoke and upset them, even be cruel if
you want.
You can try to dig under the surface to expose the secrets
they're hiding.
Sometimes it's necessary to talk fast and interrupt grace
and trip to get a word in.
They tend to respond to agreement and disagreement.
Praise, criticism, flirtation.
References to relationship topics such as divorce and
questions about their life explanations and advice and so on
as the tension builds they may try to force you to take
sides eventually they may seek your advice to get you to
tell them what's wrong with them depending on what you say
or do will determine if they stay together or not facade
needs to be replayed several times to experience the
variation in the drama for more detailed hints blah blah the
mouse is oh wait it looks good for you guys it is cursed for
me you know what as long as it looks good for you guys a
okay all right let's turn the subtitles on and let's get
going baby let's go oh my gosh i'm nervous what was it i was
it was it wasta to walk around when are you going to get rid
of this what grace this i'm so small oh i know they're
trapping me Oh, never mind.
Wait, why am I moving back?
Give me a second.
Hello?
Fine?
Oh!
Gonzalo!
Hey!
I thought I heard someone out here.
Great to see you.
It's been a while.
How's it going?
Wait.
Hold on.
How do I move?
Oh, here we go.
Well, come on in.
Hello!
Don't worry.
Let me go get Grace.
Okay.
Oh, I'm going to come in.
No, no, here we are.
Oh, my God.
Gonzalo.
Hi.
How are you?
Oh, God.
It's been such a long time.
Hi.
Yeah.
How are you doing?
I just asked him that.
I'm great.
Oh, oh.
By the way, you look fabulous.
Oh, so come on in.
Make yourself a home.
Gonzalo.
That's such a...
That's an interesting...
way to say hello you're such a kidder Gonzalo let me get you
a drink oh no we have a guest we can let the answering
machine please what wait wait let's just wait for the
answering machine I'll pick up oh hmm Gonzalo no please
don't do that who is this grace is that you oh that's my dad
i can hear his voice oh dad excuse me i'm okay he's being
annoying as you just just hang it up are you alive i've i've
missed you dad grace's parents there's something else really
classy no they're impossible they're always expecting me to
act like the dutiful daughter it's so annoying this is so
beautiful oh i can't well it didn't take long for you two to
bond or whatever.
Aren't we friends?
Hey, wait, what's- Gonzalo?
Seeing you brings back good memories, you know?
We- why is there everyone talking over each other?
It's so chaos.
Whoa, I just realized something.
What?
Well, tonight is special.
Gonzalo, remember?
It was almost exactly 10 years ago tonight that you
introduced us.
Senior year of college.
Oh, geez.
Remember that?
I remember.
We really want to thank you for years and years of pain.
Agony.
Haunting.
Why do they look at each other like that?
It's great you to be here tonight.
What are you?
What is that?
Oh, that's just a little joke advice giver toy thing that I
like to consult every now and then.
What?
When I need a little guidance.
His mother gave that to him.
Stopping stuffer.
Aww.
I'm gonna fix us some drinks.
Well, we should drink.
We should have something fun.
Like Sangria?
Sangria.
Everybody tells me I fix the best drinks, so I'm sure you're
gonna love this.
Now, Tripp, don't get too worked up with the drinks tonight.
I'm gonna puke.
No.
Tripp, don't pressure our friend, okay?
Gonzalo.
Maybe you'd like some juice or mineral water.
Oh, come on.
no oh i'll take a hot one good okay all right fine fine this
reminds me of the time we had your book group friends over
grace i know what you want but i'll ask anyway what would
you like to drink i'm going to join our friend in what he is
having oh girl feeling spicy well i uh i know What's that?
Gonzalo.
Yes.
I'm hoping you can help me understand where I went wrong
with my new decorating.
Your decorating is beautiful.
All right, Grace, yours is ready.
Thanks.
See, I told you you would like it.
Yeah.
There's nothing wrong with it.
Yeah, that's what I said.
So, about my decorating.
That's what I...
You know, when I look at this wedding picture hanging here
in this room.
Do you have anime figures?
Yeah.
Oh, God.
It's impressive.
Even after a full day's work, it's only magazine ads, great.
somehow finds the time to decorate haha I guess it's just
the artist in me dying to get out this is yours oh it tastes
good so about this wedding picture here it obviously just
does not go anymore what do you mean with my new decorating
at all oh grace whoa it's like distorting whoa whoa I think
it's melting ah yes I've been waiting for someone oh but I I
liked what you said about my decorating.
Besides, I'm redoing it all this week.
What do you mean?
You've been waiting for someone to say that.
Well, you and I are getting along better tonight than I
first thought.
Aren't we friends?
Like, I'm confused.
Oh, God.
Oh, thanks.
Oh, that's nice, Grace.
Our friend seems happy to see you again after so long.
What?
Uh-oh.
Music's getting kind of great.
Have you noticed we're fighting in front of our friend?
Grace.
on that kind of statement is not helpful.
I'm going to check there's nothing wrong with disagreeing in
front of our friend.
We're not disagreeing.
Shut up.
That's...
Whoa.
Are you sick?
Why are you coughing?
Why are they so offended?
What did you...
He's...
Mellon.
You're being...
Okay.
Gonzalo, I think this evening is over.
You've got to leave.
Oh!
Oh, no!
You'll be fine.
You should just go.
No!
I'm sorry, Tripp.
I didn't mean it.
For some reason, Mellon just makes them, like, kick you out.
generated stage play.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, cancel, cancel, cancel.
It like opened up this own document.
That's so funny.
Wow, guys, how we get a good feel about that one?
I don't know what.
Melon.
Gonzalo, get out of here.
Get out of here.
How do we feel about that?
How are we feeling?
I think, um, I don't... That's... You need to leave.
Okay, replay.
Back to main menu.
To replay, please exit and...
No way.
What?
I have to exit every...
I have to relaunch it every time.
No way!
Aw.
Oh, an electronic tip jar.
That's so cute.
Okay.
Let's try...
Oh my gosh.
we have 20 60 seconds every time for it to load it has to 60
second generate a new scenario i guess that makes sense
right okay this next time this next time i think i'm going
to genuinely try okay you should say ectoplasm to them are
they not enough kept you waiting huh
we're gonna we're gonna also i am seeing that there are
stream labs don't knows i think they're totally backlogged
by the members but i am seeing you guys thank you get melind
bozo
hey it's trip hey trip uh i i guess it's been quite some
time since we last saw you uh but uh grace and i thought
it'd be uh great if you came over tonight Speak to them in
Metal Gear Solid Quotes.
Really?
It'd be great.
We could try that too.
We have every scenario we'd ever want to do.
So good.
You could just combine around eight or something.
Can I skip this?
Okay.
I think I can.
I think I just did.
Or I broke the game.
Never mind.
Look at our happy couple.
Yeah, Grace, yeah, Trip.
I thought that was like her boyfriend or something that I
called.
I was really scared for them.
I was scared.
Like, what if she's been seeing another man?
Oh, my gosh.
No, how do I get to Gonzalo again?
I like when they say Gonzalo!
Melon.
All right, here we go.
Round two.
I wonder if you can talk to the phone.
I tried.
I tried saying hello to my dad.
Chip, when are you going to get rid of this?
Oh.
What sorry if for some reason think that you I know I know
I'll do it right now.
All right.
Oh, he's here.
I'm here
Hello open up.
Oh Gonzalo Trim, I'm so happy you could make it.
Oh me too.
We haven't seen you in so long Well, come on in okay I'll
I'll go get grace grace please no no here we are what's in
here Gonzalo yes hi how are you I am so happy to see you
after so long yeah how are you sorry I went to Europe well
that's why I learned how to kiss I learned how to kiss well
come in make yourself at home Out, close the door.
Yeah, you should do that.
That's a new photo from our trip to Italy a couple of weeks
ago.
Oh.
Italy.
Oh, sorry.
Well, um, come look at this Italy photo.
Gonzalo.
Oh, you'll never guess where I took that picture.
Is this really something you want to brag about, Trip?
Why not?
I'll tell you about it in a sec.
No, hold on.
Now.
Yeah, yeah, I've got to tell you about Italy.
Yes.
Trip, we don't want to depress our guests.
Damn it, Grace, would it kill you to be positive for once?
Shut up, Grace.
Italy!
That's...
Um...
Gonzalo.
Tell me about Italy.
You had me going there for a sec.
Tell me.
We're afraid to push your luck.
Mess with us.
You're crazy, you know that?
This is going well.
Anyway, what were we talking about?
Italy.
I think I've said Italy five times now.
Please.
So, about my decorating?
What?
We were not talking about that!
I've been collecting these little glass sculptures for a
long time now.
Everybody always comments on Grace's sculptures.
But now when I look at them, they give me such a headache.
I prefer anime.
Ah, yes.
I've been waiting.
for someone to say that what are you talking about trip he
is just being honest about my decorating which I appreciate
I am being honest but I still think this looks fine well you
two are all chummy already that's hmm Gonzalo seeing you
brings back wonderful what does that sound really yeah oh he
grabbed his little magic eight ball huh I just realized
something what yeah well Actually, tonight's a special
night.
We should celebrate, in fact.
What do you mean?
Gonzalo.
Yes.
Remember, it was almost exactly 10 years ago tonight that
you introduced us?
Oh, I can hug him.
You're hugging me.
That's kind of you.
I'm sure Tripp's happy to get...
Oh, you're hugging me.
Oh.
That's nice, Grace.
Our friend seems to be...
Oh.
Oh, wow.
Nade, Nade.
You seem to remember how much Tripp left getting attention.
I can't kiss him!
I'm not going to let go.
Keep going.
All right.
Gonzalo, that's it.
No!
I thought you were down to clown, Tripp.
Don't look at me like that while you kick me out.
No, I have to restart the game again.
Please!
No, Tripp!
He felt something, you know, and so he felt that maybe if he
didn't kick me out something new would start after this he
has like a little musical theater moment he's just like I
never knew that you saw me like that but from this moment I
can't stop thinking about the touch of your lips upon mine
the kiss button was too strong I had no idea was there the
comfort or the hug i kept cutting them off okay we're gonna
be serious we're serious i don't even know how these guys
like hate each other how are we supposed i'm i'm not
supposed to be in the middle of this
hey it's trip trip uh hey it's trip uh hey it's been a while
uh yeah you sure are tripping tonight mister uh grace and i
just i'm just gonna skip it
Be the bigger threat.
Absolutely.
Also, let me know if I have to turn up the game volume so
you can hear them while I'm playing.
Because I turn it down for his little voicemail.
It's so loud.
You know what?
I'm just going to go with Adam.
Let's just get into it.
I'm literally crying for laughing so hard.
where are the new wine glasses oh that should be obvious i
keep doing this oh god trip don't turn this into a big
production please oh he's here i'm here you told me to be an
hour hello now he's right on time open the door it's mint hi
i'm adam hey god it's been so long since we've seen you oh i
don't like him calling me i'm good i'm great great yeah Wow,
it's really really great to see you.
Oh, come on in.
He likes me Oh
What can I do
Just make me go and try to enjoy myself
Adam hi how are you I am so happy to see you after so long
hi grace grace and I've got to say you look really good well
come on in make yourself um what's I'm gonna fix us some
drinks what did I say wrong you need to help me break in my
expensive new set of cocktail making fun like sangria
everybody tells me I fixed the best drink so I'm sure you're
gonna love sangria now trip don't get too worked up with the
drinks perfect no no Adam maybe you'd like some juice or
mineral water thank you I'll take a hot spicy drink okay
look I'm just gonna open up a bottle of Merlot and make
everybody happy yeah Adam trust me it's good stuff Yes, you
don't need to push the fancy drinks tonight.
Oh, I took it first.
Grace, I assume you want your usual- You can't use it now.
I took it now.
I took it.
The Merlot sounds fine.
Oh.
Sure thing.
Okay.
I took it first.
I doubt it.
Who?
Sure thing.
Why not?
Who knows?
Yes.
Alright, guys.
Ask me a question about...
your future and I will ask the magic eight ball for its
grand wise advice not advice it's true this true this is
what will happen pizza tomorrow I doubt it oh but it's
Friday oh is trip a murderer later.
It depends on how well we do here.
Will I finally find love?
Perhaps soon!
Oh my gosh, oh my gosh, oh my gosh, oh my gosh, oh my gosh.
The stakes are high.
Is Grace evil?
No.
Okay, okay.
Trip or Grace?
It can't be that.
It has to be yes or no question.
the conch has spoken can love bloom on the battlefield who
knows
I love this thing
you're a little close to me Grace
how's the weather
I'll ask the eight ball Is the weather good?
Perhaps soon.
Um, how do I put this down?
Oh, dang it.
I can sit it again.
Uh, what's he doing?
Oh, well.
Thanks.
Adam, you're always so sweet.
Grace, I'm giving you the first glass.
Why'd you cut her off like that?
Thanks.
Nope, that glass is mine.
Adam, I was going.
Oh, I'll get it.
No, no, no, no.
Sippy, sippy.
We can let the answering machine get it.
You know what, I'm just gonna put this in the bathroom.
How did you walk in front of us?
Sippy, sippy.
I'm drunk.
Oh yeah, you know, I think I'll fix you a real drink in not
too long.
Anyhow, Chip's parents.
So sweet people, we're really down to earth.
Oh my god, everyone is talking, please!
Travis, are you there?
It's your mother.
Oh.
I haven't heard from you in grace in a while.
Take a look at this photo I just put up for you.
from our trip to Italy.
I'm just calling to find out if you're settled in and your
new apartment.
That's all.
Adam, come over here and sit on my couch with me.
No, I know you're traveling a lot these days.
Everybody's talking!
Who is Travis?
Oh, Trip, don't put our friend on the spot like that.
Well, actually, this trip to Italy was meant to be our
second honeymoon.
Trip, don't exaggerate.
It was simply a weekend getaway.
So, in a word, this says...
It says...
Love.
says love oh or not he doesn't believe I don't know Travis's
trip's full name oh romance it says romance romance of
course yeah oh never mind what that's what you said could be
could be good one yeah yeah why why am I the awkward one
here Adam maybe you didn't come here to hear this what oh
trip there's nothing wrong with disagreeing in front of
disagreeing we're not disagreeing oh oh oh we're not no
everything everything is good what what you know ever since
we got married trip is forever trying to get me to buy new
And it's true.
I kind of enjoy it, but...
Yeah, it's great.
Everybody loves it when they come in and see our latest
decoration scheme.
But, Adam, you have to look at this room and admit it looks
terrible.
Grace, I mean, look around.
This room is... It's hideous.
Ah, yeah.
It looks great.
Adam, I knew you'd like it.
Yeah.
See, Grace, you don't realize how good all this looks.
I mean, it's a little empty.
Could use some more wall scrolls or something.
So, about my decorating.
You know, at work I waste all day designing ads for
apartments like this.
Uh-huh.
And it makes me think, I want this style for my apartment.
Yeah?
This style makes me feel like I'm inside one of your ads.
It's great.
Oh, I'm sitting.
Damn it, I'm wrong.
It's just not coming together at all.
That's okay.
Not coming together?
What?
What's going on?
Why is she so angry?
Oh, you're hugging me.
Ah, it's good to see you two bonding again.
I'm coming.
Well, you're really affectionate tonight, aren't you?
I'm drunk.
She's a villain.
I bet I can return most of this and start over again on this
room.
Are you okay?
I love this.
No, I can't say love or I'll still say I'm...
They think I'm loving.
The room looks great.
What?
Aha.
I knew it.
I was right, Grace.
You're the only one unhappy with your decorating.
No, decorating is not.
It's not.
Grace, come on.
You're so good at it.
You're so good.
Just like you're good at your job.
You design great magazines.
Oh my god, we're helping you guys.
I think we're actually helping.
You are impossible.
Or not.
I'm never happy.
Trip our whole marriage.
I don't think we're helping.
What?
He's not doing anything.
What's wrong, Grace?
What's wrong?
Adam.
I...
And you.
I can predict what you'll say.
Me?
I'm so positive tonight.
It's driving me crazy.
Um, uh, what should I say, you guys?
More real.
I like my fancy drinks, okay?
Oh, my God.
What should I say?
I like the good things in life.
Does that make me a bad person?
They're just drinks.
Goddamn second honeymoon.
You never call me when you're on business trips.
You never call me.
You know that?
Um, um, what do I say?
Something positive?
Okay, you know what?
I'll take another drink.
I need to ask you something.
Grace.
Trip, let me ask our guest a question.
Never mind, they ignored me.
Adam.
Yes.
Yes or no?
Oh.
In a marriage, shouldn't you try to help the other person
get what they want?
What?
I mean, marriage is supposed to be about what the other
person wants, not what you want, right?
Yes or no?
Um, uh, yes.
agree with her why are you upset should oh yeah that's
that's fine that's fine you should both try so hard to reach
out to you grace and you reject me you're cold you're
distant i can't keep going this way turn up the healing me
oh my god you're tearing me apart lisa go away hey hey i
don't want to look at you hey oh my god um are we still
doing barbecue what are you saying what grace what the hell
are you saying about me in there wait i'm in here i'm sorry
this is a disaster no no i'm having fun i'm having fun
please adam from what you said before about saying yes i
think we've already learned something about grace oh we're
talking about me again are we she's getting the gun race we
don't know god we don't have to do this no stand the
pretending anymore i can't take it stay get get away from
the window grace okay ah sorry i think this evening is over
what you gotta leave no i was helping just go no
what did i do oh
man there's they are so we were helping what's wrong with
being a little positive
Is there actually a good ending?
I have no idea.
The fact that each scenario is different too is crazy.
My drink, hey at least we finished our drink, right?
I think I should be like a hostage negotiator.
I think actually maybe this game will train you for hostage
negotiation situations because only the bad outcomes happen.
and so it trains you to not say those things
what if i say oh my god i'm gonna okay i'm gonna go in with
this approach i'm gonna say i just got a new job as a
marriage counselor then they feel safe trauma dumping on me
and then i say i charge 150 an hour uh hey it's been a while
uh but uh And I also get paid for it.
Why don't you come over tonight?
Grace and I?
Stonks.
We'd love to see you.
Mint as a hostage negotiator.
Stop by tonight.
Around eight or so.
It'll be great.
Oh, sorry.
I forgot.
I can skip this part.
A guy got the good ending and completed the game by being
rude and not giving a crap the entire time for a stride.
No way.
Okay.
I can be a jerk.
I can't, well, you have to be, like, the right level of
jerk.
Because if you're just, like, shut up, Grace.
What if I don't say anything the entire time?
What if I, like...
What if I just...
What if I just stand there?
What if I don't say anything?
Let's try it.
Sorry that the subtitles seem a little bit, like,
inconsistent.
But...
That's the best we can do.
Trip, when are you going to get rid of this?
Oh, gosh, I did it again.
Wah, wah!
I know, I know, I'll do it right now, all right?
You know, I've had to ask you about this separate.
I'll get rid of it in just a minute.
I'm here!
Fine, Trip, fine.
Open the door.
Gonzalo!
Hey!
I thought I heard someone out here.
Great to see.
Oh.
Uh...
Well, come on in.
Wait, what happened?
Uh...
It'll be just a sec while I go get Grace.
Trip, I'm stuck in the door!
Trip, trip I- oh okay, never mind.
I was gonna say trip, I can't come in.
I'm gonna sit down.
Put on a happy face.
I don't understand why you're always doing this to me.
Grace, we do this later.
Can I make a little phone call real quick?
No new messages.
Oh, I didn't do anything.
Gonzalo.
hi how are you oh it's so nice to see you it feels like it's
been forever yeah it has been a long time hide the ball so
true oh I'm and I well come on in make your oh that that's
just a little joke advice giver toy thing that I like to
consult every now let's put it in the kitchen when I need a
little guidance his mother gave that to him stocking stuffer
stocking stuffer oh well if I So, make yourself at home.
I am.
I'm taking your stuff.
Close the door.
Oh, good, good.
Gonzalo.
Take a look at this photo I just put up from our trip to
Italy.
Wow, we're already getting into it.
Gonzalo.
Come here.
I want you to look.
Gonzalo.
Come over here and sit on the couch with me.
Oh, they're making me choose.
Actually, I'm going to go sit on the couch with them.
Trip, darling, your obsession with that photo is making our
friend uncomfortable.
I'm very uncomfortable.
Romance.
It says romance.
I'm going to fix us some drinks.
Oh, and I've got these fancy new cocktail shakers.
No!
What are you going to try out?
He got it.
It's a martini sound.
I'm a real expert at fixing these.
At least that's what everyone tells me.
Uh-huh.
Trip, let's not go crazy with the drinks, okay?
Yeah.
It says italy.
Italy.
It's really.
I'm just going to make you a martini.
No, no, Gonzalo.
Maybe you'd like some juice or...
mineral water you
know I'm just gonna open up a bottle of Merlot or something
I just want us to not saying anything you guys yes sometimes
a simple glass of wine is better than those fancy drinks you
always insist on making this one looks like a Yu-Gi-Oh
character right I know it's not true this one right here oh
do you like those sculptures oh I used to be so into
collecting them into them you love your sculptures so much
i'm not even allowed to touch them trip your poker buddies
used them as ash trays what anyhow gonzalo what do you mean
anyhow trip he says no i'm not yeah it does look like that
yeah the harpy um i'll have a glass of merlot too oh good
good okay good big sigh god why are we big so gonzalo yeah i
hope you didn't come here tonight to be entertained I poured
you the first glass Okay, thanks anyway.
Oh, she's just walked through her that kind of statement is
not helpful trip there's nothing wrong with disagreeing in
front of our friend They're talking over each other again
Well, two are all chummy already that's that's good.
You know ever since we got married I can't help it.
I'm forever buying new furniture and redecorating.
They're just going off on their own I don't need to do
anything.
It's in your blood you grow up with this stuff.
Sheesh.
Here you are.
So I normally like redecorating, Gonzalo.
Now be honest with me.
Agree that this room just does not work.
He's going to kick you out.
Come on.
I'm not saying anything.
Well, I'll just put this on the bar for you.
Thank you.
About my decorating.
All day at work, I design ads for decorative objects, like
these sculptures.
Right.
And then I think I want to design them into my apartment.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Everybody always says how much they love grace's sculptures
but oh but you've not said a single word for a while now are
you all right they noticed they noticed just oh just watch
oh good oh oh i'm sure i can return most of this and try to
start over again on this room
grace everything's fine no one is complaining about your He
is just being courteous this room is not grace.
Come on people like you don't you're the only one to go into
Advertising I could have painted that painting on the wall
instead of buying it.
Oh my god.
This is so fierce never happy.
Oh, you're driving me insane You're god, you're decorating
both insufferable
Gonzalo can you believe this I cannot I cannot believe this
Gonzalo can you can you can you just god damn manipulation
manipulation station just want to be together and be happy
I'm still grace can you that can you move can't we just do
that I'm stuck here I'm gonna also not face you know what
Gonzalo I need to ask you something okay yeah grace let me
ask our guests a question okay ask away Gonzalo yes or no oh
if one person in a marriage gives the other advice and and
that advice is taken years later can you be blamed for that
oh my god what is it okay to get blamed for giving advice
that was taken like ten years ago yes or no um yeah let's
check the eight ball could be look don't bother answering I
don't need I was too late.
I keep trying to help you, Grace, but you reject me.
You cut me off.
You cut me out of your life.
God damn it.
Oh, my God.
He's so loud.
Oh, yeah, good.
Get away from me.
I don't want to look at you.
I'm going to comfort her.
Damn it, Trey.
Oh, never mind.
Come here.
Come back.
I don't want to kiss you on accident.
No, wait.
Please.
What?
Are you talking about me now?
I'm not talking to you.
Gonzalo.
I can't believe you have to see this.
Um, me neither.
Gonzalo.
In what you said before about marriage.
I think that tells us something about Tripp.
So true.
We're talking about me, are we?
Oh, he's back!
Grace, we don't have to do this.
Things are okay.
I can't stand the pretending anymore.
I can't take it.
Me neither.
Me, neither.
No.
Grace, we can...
I mean, come on.
Don't make it out to be so bad.
She's so angry!
Ugh!
I'm on Grace's side right now.
What is it?
Is there something about me?
Um.
Look, why don't we talk about us, our relationship?
It's so annoying.
Grace, why is it that anytime I want to do something nice
for you, you resist it?
Trip.
Like I always have to convince you.
Gonzalo.
Oh, no.
I can't drink it.
Oh, I can.
I can drink all his wine.
Yeah?
Well, you were in the middle of a sentence.
money makes us so happy we're so happy aren't we trip jesus
what do you want now you're unhappy because we're oh that
brass bull it's just so infuriating what's wrong with the
bull how you put that goddamn gift on display in our own
living room who who gifted this god gonzalo i'm getting
really tired of talking about trip stuff oh sorry um let's
talk about anime Huh.
Gonzalo, you're saying I don't communicate?
Wait, that's all.
Comisan doesn't communicate?
This is your favorite enemy?
I really do.
I try to be open and honest.
You know, Gonzalo.
Stop.
What if...
Communication sucks.
No, communication.
See, Grace, I feel like it's you that's not reaching out.
Ugh.
Um, you, you both are bad at talking.
Ah-ha!
Gonzalo.
You're saying I'm communicative?
You know, Tripp, whenever I really try to talk honestly
about things...
No, I said you're both bad about it.
You don't want to hear it.
What?
Gonzalo.
I think I'm the only one who is trying to be the most honest
here.
Duh.
Um, be honest about your feelings.
feeling yes look you're doing it again you're putting this
all on me I can't I'm just trying to help you man Gonzalo
yes there's something about me just tell me what it is um
let's see let's keep talking about grace Gonzalo look around
this apartment it's got everything anyone would ever want
but grace oh no she's never satisfied trip oh I'm so sick of
this you complain too much I don't think well, I mean We've
got everything Trip, you just don't You don't have love Ah,
what the hell are you talking about?
That makes no sense Okay Gonzalo If there's something about
me, just tell me what it is You're annoying Uh-huh Gonzalo,
you're saying I'm angry?
No, I said I'm It makes me so angry Did I ever tell you how
she humiliated me at a gallery in front of her artist
friends?
What?
What did you do?
What did she do?
What?
Whatever I really said, I'm sure you deserved it.
Oh.
What?
Hold on.
Let's keep our focus on Trip.
No.
It's your fault.
Ten years ago, freshly married and just out of college,
convinced me to go into advertising instead of art.
What?
If it weren't for you, I could be.
be a real artist by now she's blaming him that was your
decision that that was your decision grace that's bullshit
oh no i'm on your side no we need we need to talk about us
both not just one what makes me the most angry trip is what
you took away from me what i wasted 10 years in this You can
still be an artist.
What's wrong with advertising?
Gonzalo.
All this time, I just can't stop thinking that I should have
been painting.
Why don't you just do it?
That's what I'm saying.
Just...
Be a goddamn artist already.
Just do it!
Yes.
Ah, yes.
Just you saying that should really help her.
Well, if I could be a painter, I...
I would.
Look, let's not focus on just me or you.
Oh my god, I think we're actually getting somewhere here,
you guys.
You just pretend to like all this stuff.
Fancy cigars and fine wine.
You think I'm not good enough.
I never said that.
I'm saying there's more to you than all this.
Oh.
What else is there?
What?
Then cigar.
Thank you.
That helps us.
It does.
Trip, I know that you like to hang out at that little sports
bar on the corner.
What?
Wouldn't not...
No.
Why did he...
Trip, it's all right.
Oh, he moved closer.
The sports bar.
Oh, God.
This is so frigging insane.
I love sports.
Oh, you...
Does anyone...
Um...
Okay, that's it.
No more of this bullshit.
Gonzalo, I know what you're hinting at.
About us.
Oh, no.
What about our lifestyle?
What?
Do you two want the truth?
Give us the truth.
Gonzalo, do you want to hear it?
Yes.
Grace?
See, Gonzalo, I've been paying attention to what you've been
saying tonight.
Okay.
You've been really pushing me tonight.
I'm a pusher.
It makes me wonder if you're really my friend or not.
Trip?
Gonzalo, quit interrupting me.
Let me finish.
Gonzalo, come on.
on yes or no do you really think that saying that grace is
communicative telling me i'm not communicative telling grace
to make art that will somehow realize something about our
marriage is all of that arguing intended to mean something
yes right yes realize you realize your power see i'm ashamed
of my parents where is this coming from what Your parents
are great.
I love seeing them.
I know, I know.
But compared to yours, they're so ignorant.
But they're real.
I hate how my parents are pretending to be something.
I've tried hard to be like your family.
What?
I don't...
But I feel like a phony.
I feel like I can never get rid of my past.
What's your past?
What happened?
It's kind of like I don't know who I am anymore.
What are you talking about?
this guy needs therapy oh let's go drop a melon I'm going to
give you the truth to trip oh they're see they're being
honest with each other oh oh oh oh oh I painted this yes
bullshit I am an artist trip fuck you whoa it's beautiful
secretly painting what's wrong with you go on a goddamn
business trip I paint what's wrong with me anymore if you're
you could never be an artist crap what's wrong with art oh
why it's MSP it's it's so love oh I'm sitting again I'm up
again Jesus okay Gonzalo grace I have one more thing to say
again again
what what grace i know you want to be an artist yes but i
could never be married to you if you were what why not i
can't i i just can't but trip when i married you see i was
sure i could convince you to give it up to to go into
advertising what's so special about advertising it worked
but now i don't know grace What is wrong with Tripp?
I don't know.
Why do you hate art?
Tripp, what is wrong with you?
Oh, my God.
That's how I feel.
This changes everything.
Yeah.
Are you?
You really have to be an artist.
Oh, my God.
You finally admitted it.
You just don't want me to be an artist.
artist why are you so what you you think i'm a phony for
despising my upbringing what is your upbringing but at least
you had a real upbringing it's me who had a fake one oh my
gosh i'm gonna comfort gonzalo oh oh my god yes yes yes yes
look yes i need to talk yeah i'm here for you thanks for
coming over you i think you helped us And no, Gonzalo.
You don't need to say anything more.
Say anything more.
Are they leaving?
This is your house.
Gonzalo.
Please.
It's okay.
Can I get another drink?
I didn't eat today, please.
I thought we were having dinner.
I'm taking the magic eight ball.
Will I starve tonight?
Bye.
No!
Oh, thank God.
Wait, what'd you say?
Oh!
What just happened?
Did I win?
You moved in with them.
She said, bye, thanks.
Yippee!
What?
It's my house now.
Oh my god, this is actually like what happens to me for
real.
I go and hunt someone and then sometimes they leave and it
becomes my house.
That's really exciting.
I didn't know that that could happen in the game as well.
Hold on.
Let's try another one.
I think someone said, like, speak only.
That one, we barely talked and it actually ended up working
out.
How is that possible?
Maybe they really just needed to talk things out and we were
just a good friend to listen, you know?
You can...
I want to actually...
I do want to kind of romance someone.
You know?
let's kind of let's kind of who should we romance trip or
grace trip is kind of crazy trip is i don't understand what
his deal is why does he hate art so much why does he not
want her to be a painter why can't she just do that but like
as a hobby even grace okay we're gonna we're gonna romance
grace
okay all right here we go
She has to advertise.
Why is so like...
Oh my god, I'm going to ask her if she painted that.
Only MGS quotes, right?
Okay, let's do that one, and then we'll romance Grace.
Okay.
She's going to really fall hard for Gonzalo.
Some titles on.
Okay.
All right, first we'll do the Metal Gear.
And then?
Where are the new wine glasses?
Oh my gosh, I do that.
That should be obvious.
Oh god, Tripp, don't turn this into a big production,
please.
Oh, he's here.
I'm here.
You said he's coming an hour from now.
He's supposed to be here now.
I'm here.
Mm-hmm.
Gonzalo.
Hey.
God, it's been so long.
Kept you in.
How you doing, man?
Wait, what?
Waiting, huh?
well come on in what else should I say it'll be just a sec
while I go get grace okay oh wait no
no here we are Gonzalo yes hi how are you I am so happy to
see you after so long yeah how are you well come in make
yourself at home
oh Gonzalo that's so nice of you to say oh by the way you
look fabulous oh hey Gonzalo seeing oh oh I'll go no no we
have a guess we can let the answering machine pick it up
it's probably just the cleaning service cancelling on us
again no please don't do that who is this grace oh it's my
dad I can hear his voice oh oh excuse me okay he's being
annoying as usual just just hang it up she didn't care oh
good you hung up I can call him back later or you know she
didn't notice she didn't notice wait oh you wait I think
they just noticed sorry sorry you maniac you sex maniac
never afraid to mess with us you're a beautiful crazy you
know that I'm crazy anyway what were we talking about hey
Gonzalo seeing you again makes me remember the good time so
we all used to oh yeah those crazy parties those crazy
parties yeah yeah i've um i've missed you hey i've just
realized you too what oh yeah gonzalez yeah careful too many
compliments can go to trip's head i i i'll i'll compliment
you too grace uh well remember how sorry i gave up the metal
your quote thing i couldn't think of anything to say wait
what do you say what did he ask um well without you we
wouldn't even have this celebration huh you two really are
getting along well tonight so yeah Gonzalo you can help me
understand where i went wrong with my new decorating oh oh
grace i'm gonna ask her okay we don't need to do that oh i'm
back on the couch you know i've been Yeah, the...
Well, it's funny how after a full day's work designing
magazine ads, Grace finds the time to decorate and
redecorate.
I guess it's just the artist in me dying to get out.
Oh, wait.
So, yeah, I just bought this painting.
But, God, you know, it looks like an amateur painted it.
You painted it.
Oh, well, it looks so amateurish, doesn't it?
No, it's awesome.
Oh, how nice.
I've been waiting so long for someone to say that.
I'm going to hug her.
What?
been refreshingly on oh uh you're hugging me no i'm
comforting you oh that's oh that's nice grace i think a hug
was just what you needed can you give us us a second trip
all right good maybe you're on my side tonight after all can
you can you give us a moment trip why does he always look
like not enjoying this are you why do they always look like
they're notice we're fighting in front of our friend heads
are backwards you know that kind of statement is not helpful
trip there's nothing wrong with i'm having so much fun what
what do you mean yeah i want you to look at this photo from
our recent trip to no oh no no go look at trip's italy photo
so come on i'd rather be with you grace yeah yes go take a
look Gonzalo no no just take a look this picture this is
your idea stop pressuring me stop pressuring no no come take
a look no trip you see your fetish for all things european
is making our friend very uncomfortable i'm uncomfortable
grace this was supposed to be our second honeymoon what
gonzalo trip is absolutely on the ground wait see I just
wanted us to spend some time together.
All those business trips of yours to Europe must have done
something to you.
Ugh, you're driving me insane.
You're driving me crazy.
You're tearing me apart.
I try to reach out to you.
I try to be romantic with you, but you're cold and distant.
I do.
I really try.
Stop yelling at me.
Why?
Gonzalo.
Yes.
Yeah.
Gonzalo.
I know what you're about to say.
With your damn kissing.
and flirting Christ.
Grace.
Trip, our whole marriage, you're so...
Huh?
What was that?
I didn't do anything.
I just want to be together and be happy.
I'm comforting.
Can you just see that?
Can't we just do that?
I'm comforting.
All right.
You know what?
Gonzalo.
Yeah.
I'm going to ask you something.
Trip.
in love with your wife let me ask our guests to question
comforting i'm solo yes or no it's okay for a married person
to talk and be friendly with someone of the opposite sex
right oh what um i mean come on if you're married a little
bit of harmless flirting and joking around is allowed am i
right yes sir what oh okay fine the real truth is trip you
flirt with everybody the clients at work our friends
everybody you can't help yourself you're always looking
around our entire marriage god damn it oh yeah go on go away
are you freaking take this are you okay grace god damn it
are you okay grace comfort comfort Gonzalo I what I can't
hear you I was not talking Gonzalo.
Gonzalo.
Yeah, yeah.
In what you said before.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Where'd you go?
We're talking about me, are we?
Damn it, Trip.
You and my parents are always planning these stupid trips I
have to go on.
They're vacations.
Expensive ones at that.
What's wrong with vacations?
Of course, nobody thinks to ask me what I want.
What do you want, Grace?
Oh, she looked at me.
She wants me to ask.
You want to know more?
Thank you.
That helps.
Grace, you never want to go on vacation with me.
me and your parents so i have to plan everything she doesn't
want to go on vacation let's talk some more about grace yeah
comfort gonzalo yes thanks but what we need right now is to
just get all this out in the open i'm hugging jesus i'm
hugging jesus gonzalo yes with that stuff oh
look why don't we talk about us our relationship jesus
gonzalo quit it with that stuff i'm doing what you won't
let's talk some more about grace you're the reason we live
like pretentious like your parents you mean oh i don't need
any of this stuff it's all you oh oh um uh uh bad let's keep
talking about grace we gonzalo all this time I just can't
stop thinking that I should have been painting.
Why don't you just do it then?
Oh, we're back at this one.
You goddamn artist already.
What are you afraid of, Grace?
Well, this painting, well, see, all I really wanted was
something personal and beautiful and special.
Okay, and so...
But I just...
No, I just get so depressed and angry when I look at it.
Your triangles are so personal.
I it's it's wonderful triangles.
Yes.
No, look there's nothing wrong with the stupid painting.
It makes me feel like shit.
It's not stupid.
You feel like that for no reason.
Even though now you're a creative director at work and even
though you redecorate so triangular.
The truth is you're not an artist.
I'm sorry.
You're not.
Gonzalo.
Why do you say my name?
You're an artist.
Gonzalo.
You know, we already talked about that.
Okay.
Paint.
Gonzalo.
Can we possibly talk any more about Grace's stuff tonight?
Comfort.
Gonzalo.
Stop it with that stuff.
No!
Gonzalo.
Jesus.
Quit it with that stuff.
What?
I'm gonna... Can I kiss her?
I can kiss her.
kiss her you think if i try to she'll get mad no let's
switch to talking about trip gonzalo you blame me for all of
this don't you what no why do you mean i've been right all
along gonzalo do you agree with that lie no wait no what oh
thank god you disagree that might help him understand you
only say that because you so badly don't want me to be the
game is the game is what the game is the focus to grace
gonzalo you think this is all my fault don't you see you
lied to me when you said i'd be yes gonzalo you think i'm
lying yes oh yes yes yeah thank you look how sad he looks oh
he's crying
we should we should talk about trip see grace you're the one
turning is such a big issue i still say advertising is the
best thing for you best for me or for you what gonzalo yes
um i think you should paint okay i'm sick of this bullshit
what is this over here i know what you're hinting at okay
what about me yeah about art do you two want the truth huh
yeah Gonzalo do you want to hear it no I don't care what you
have to say grace yes see Gonzalo I've been paying attention
to what you've been saying tonight yeah you've been pushing
me tonight oh I'm pushing you on I wonder are you really my
friend or not Gonzalo.
Let me finish.
Gonzalo, I ask you this.
Yes or no?
Oh.
Do you really think that praising me, asking if we're okay,
kissing grace?
But especially what you said about harmless flirting.
And you don't even say yes when I ask you if you want the
truth.
That I'm supposed to realize something about myself from all
that.
Is what you've said tonight supposed to add up somehow to
something?
Maybe.
Is it?
I just want a yes or no.
Oh, it's okay.
Yes.
Okay.
okay grace I know you want to be an artist but I could never
be married to you if you were I'm gonna kiss her what I
can't I just can't but trip when I married you see I was
sure I could convince you to give it up I don't think she
cares advertising oh and I did it and it worked European
kiss no I don't know No, Grace.
European.
I don't know.
Oh, my God.
Gonzalo.
I.
This changes everything.
Gonzalo.
Ooh.
I .E.
Yes.
It does change everything.
No.
Gonzalo.
Hold on.
Yes.
Where's he going?
He's stomping over there.
I think it's over.
Okay.
Trip, what?
No.
It's over, Grace.
Don't you see that?
She doesn't see anything.
She's only looking at me.
You just told me.
I just told you something about me.
I should have said a long time ago.
What's that?
I can't be married to an artist.
This guy sucks so much.
What do you have against art?
Please, it's okay.
Trip, no.
I...
No, Grace.
This is about me.
I see now.
It's not about you or about our marriage.
Me?
Our marriage?
Where'd he go?
Hey, no, wait.
Gonzalo.
I'm sorry.
Thank you, though.
You really helped me.
He's actually leaving.
Oh, get out of your trip.
It's our house.
It's our house now.
Oh, my God.
I should have told him that I wanted to be an artist.
Oh my gosh, free wife with the house!
Let's go!
This might actually be a better ending for them.
We're free wife with the house!
Yippee!
What?
The what?
I really want an ending where she kind of falls for me
though.
Hmm.
I wonder if that even exists.
It's our wife now.
this game is crazy need more Riz alright this time you you
guys are telling me what to type okay and I'll type it at
any moment it might be hard because some of this stuff is
kind of quickly timed okay but you guys have to tell me what
to type okay
thank you miss miss don't tell me what I can't do thank you
so much thank you all right all right just say yes to
everything melon speed run hey there it's trip see you trip
all right we could come out of this with the new wife.
I'm just saying.
If you play your cards right.
Answer everything with Bazinga.
Stop.
I already said melon.
Subtitles.
Ah, ah, ah.
There we go.
All right.
First of all, do we knock on the door or do we just stand
out here?
and what do we say when he greets us
lemon okay i'm seeing mostly just stand so we're just gonna
stand can
i leave actually gonzalo
gonzalo ding
oh no he had to sit through the i'm so sorry sorry we have
to sit through it again okay I think I will make this the
last run though actually I will make this probably the last
one um what I just I just I knew what was coming I heard
them arguing and I was like I'm not dealing with your I'm
not dealing with your with this tonight I cannot deal I
cannot deal with it I do not have the the patience the
mental capacity
failed marriage what if I never go in there what do you
think happens I wonder
oh welcome the membership thank you
not dealing with your BS so true
Okay.
Final Gonzalo.
Here we go.
I'm gonna stand here.
Standing here.
I realize this is a waste of time.
Oh, I see.
Oh, I know.
I'll do it right now, all right?
You know, I've had to ask you about this.
Step up.
I'll get rid of it in just a minute.
Okay.
Fine trip, fine.
Wait, what is she not like?
Um, I'm here.
Gonzalo!
Hey!
I thought I heard someone out here.
Great to see you.
It's been a while.
How's it going?
What should I say?
Oh, hi, Mark.
Hi!
Wow, it's really, really great to see you.
Come on in!
Your name's Mark now.
Got it?
Uh, it'll be just a sec while I go get Grace.
what is this no no here we are oh hello Gonzalo hi how are
you oh god it's been such a long time Merry Christmas I said
the same thing skibby skibby skibby by the way you look
wonderful well come in make yourself at home out close the
door Gonzalo seeing you again makes me remember the
wonderful I'll get it.
No, no, we have a guest.
We can let the answering machine pick it up.
Grace, no, I won't.
Don't be rude.
I'll get it.
It's probably just the execs at work.
Grace, Grace, hello.
Please don't do that.
I did it.
Who is this, Grace?
Is that you?
Oh, it's my dad.
I can hear his voice.
Oh.
I threw it.
Oh, good.
You hung up.
I can call him back later or in a few days.
I missed you, Grace.
I wanted to say hello.
Oh, well.
Oh, that's nice of you to say.
Grace, aren't you?
glad we invited him over yeah hmm hmm well grace's parents
is it really her dad really classy no they're impossible
they expect me to drive up to the house in Connecticut to
attend all their stupid socialite charity benefits and
parties it's so tires I well it didn't take long for you two
to bond or whatever we bonded so Gonzalo you can help me
understand your eyes wrong with my new decorating.
Grace, oh.
Gonzalo.
I think you're flirting with me to get on my good side.
Oh!
Grace, no, no, no.
He's just joking.
Oh!
What?
That worked!
The Riz!
Do you like country life?
When I saw this armoire in the store, it seemed to have such
a clean, simple look to it.
Yeah, it looks great.
How did that work?
But looking at it here in the apartment it just looks like a
go what else come on guys come on guys grace your dad sounds
hot your dad sounds hot no no you've you've done quite
enough with my parents tonight let's not talk about them
anymore okay sorry grace it seems no one elris elris elris
that's what you always say grab the rainbow sculpture needs
to be redone oh let's not talk about that anymore i'm
redoing the whole place what is this what anyway hey grace
Gonzalo seeing you brings back good memories you know yes
grace what is this whoa I just realized something what oh
tonight's a special night a celebration in fact it is
celebration remember it was almost exactly ten years ago
tonight that you introduced us senior year of college oh
geez remember that sussie um well without you we wouldn't
even have this celebration
um i'm just reading i'm just putting in what you guys write
you probably didn't come here to hear this wait wait what's
wrong trip trip it's okay if we disagree in front of our
friend we're not disagreeing we're not disagreeing oh who is
this oh who's i thought you might like this photo i just put
up from our recent trip to It's a beautiful picture of the
Italian countryside.
Of course he'll like it.
Of course.
I don't know you don't like it, but our friend might
Gonzalo.
I'm looking by the way anybody join me on the couch if you
like Okay, Gonzalo.
Yeah, one word What does this picture say to you?
Don't care.
Elewell.
Well, actually this trip to Italy was meant to be our second
honeymoon.
Wow Oh, was that what it was?
Huh.
I'm always the last to know.
Why is it like?
Also, we have music this time and everything.
Time together.
It's interesting.
In a word, this says...
Grace stayed behind in the hotel room when I was out taking
this picture.
Romance.
Right.
Love.
Romance.
Oh, but the last time I said love, you kicked me out.
In our marriage, that's just a code word for manipulation.
Grace, it's been such a long time since we had a chance to
plan that trip without even asking me if I wanted to go.
I was curious what he'd say.
that's not the first time he's done that and you knew i
planned to attend my friend's art show that weekend what a
very good friend from college had a gallery show of his new
paintings that weekend and i missed it thank you for the
gift this is bullshit uh no you're full of god damn i need
to what i what are you saying to me well you just said you
know you said that you're full and I'm oh and you I know
what you're going to say you've been critical of me all
evening I have I said I compliment I flirted with you your
goddamn parents I think you're better than me I'm sure what
what are you saying to me oh baby core thanks for the gift
in all right you know what Gonzalo I'm going to ask you
something grace okay trip let me ask our guest a question so
Stop sabotaging us.
Gonzalo.
Yes or no?
Do you think it's wrong for one person in a marriage to
listen too much to the other?
What?
To trust your husband or wife too much, to rely on them too
much.
Is that wrong?
Yes or no?
Okay.
You guys are saying yes.
Yes.
What?
You guys said yes.
Oh.
All right.
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, I keep trying to help you.
Grace, could you reject me?
You cut me off.
You cut me out of your life.
God damn it.
His cake.
When it was, when he was walking away.
Did you guys see him?
I can't stand you.
God damn it.
What should I say?
What should I do to, I'll comfort her?
No, wait, please.
What?
Are you talking about me now?
I wasn't talking about you.
Gonzalo.
I can't believe you have.
have to see this oh comfort i comforted i comfort kiss her
oh no don't do that god oh grace are you talking about what
do you care you guys i think i don't think she liked it
gonzalo oh shit grace is just so we're talking about me are
we what grace even though now you're a creative director at
work and even though you redecorate the apartment all the
time the truth is you're not an artist i'm sorry Wait,
where'd she go?!
Uh-oh.
Oh, oh my god.
Oh my god.
Um...
Gonzalo.
You see, this is what I've had to put up with for ten
goddamn years.
I thought this was a celebration.
Let's not focus on just me or you.
Let's talk about us both.
Trip, can't you see?
It's the way you speak.
The way you talk to me.
What?
I'm not allowed to be angry.
Teleports behind you.
You tell me what to do.
You don't listen.
I love you, Grace.
Okay.
I'm not telling her what to do.
to tell her I love you grace look quit the flirting already
I'm not gonna put up with that at this point oh let's keep
talking about grace okay Gonzalo it's time that trip finally
just admits that our marriage don't need to admits that our
marriage is not stop it stop interrupting her wait how do
you spell interrupting I'll dig her no oh god let's keep our
focus on Grace you know trip whenever I really try to talk
honestly you know what Gonzalo that's it you need to leave
I'm sorry but I don't know what the grace he's kicking grace
he's stopping our love grace we'll be fine grace no grace oh
someone said in the chat say I love you how you I tried.
I tried.
Grace.
Oh, grace.
Bye, Shamin!
Should have kissed Trip.
It's a very broken relationship here.
But yeah.
Should have went for the dad.
This is terrifying.
Oh, Gonzalo.
can't stop our love trip
welcome to bamboo ship thank you guys so much break thank
you for the 50 thank you for the 50 gifted
it's interesting how varied the dialogue can even be in this
that well we've gotten the one where um uh they stay
together and talk things out we've gotten the ending where
obviously we were kicked out we've gotten the ending where
trip walks out we haven't oh sorry oh yeah we haven't seen
um grace walk out they're incredibly awful but interesting
the game was way out of its time yeah like you can walk
around you can pick stuff up they interact you can type
whatever like it's kind of insane it's and then there's so
much that's already been like recorded like
so i need to probably okay let's do one more i know i said
that was the last one but we're gonna try and do one more
where we side with trip unfortunately to uh to um then see
if we can get to leave why more why more why more why more
bromance route time we're gonna do a really cool handshake
together oh i oh yes i could be a girl named this time i
guess you're right oh i guess you're right i guess you're
right i guess you're right does anyone like i mean like can
grace like get like a knife from the kitchen or something
like or or trip can either of them like kind of like i want
to see them actually go insane wait so if we're not gonzalo
gonzalina sadly no dang dang let's see what hello there we
go amy let's just go with amy
actually is uh is janevra is that a girl's name i want to
see how i want to know how that's spelled lisa you're
tearing me apart lisa
i know i don't know why i'm so eppy today
let's just try it okay or there is lisa Oh, where'd it go?
Lisa, okay.
Let's start.
Oh, hi, Mark.
All right.
We're on trips.
We're on trip side.
Oh, she's here.
Oh, you told me to be an hour from now.
Oh, she's supposed to be here now.
everything so it's tree wow lisa i'm so happy you can make
it oh yeah hi wow it's so great to see you after so long
hello hi well come in yeah it'll be just a sec while i go
get grace oh i hate grace kiss him i don't want to get
kicked wait should i kiss him while grace is not here I
should have kissed him.
No, no, here we are.
You're mine.
Hi.
How are you?
I am...
Mm-hmm.
And I've got to say, you look really good.
Make yourself at home.
Come on in.
Oh, I think we're going to need to have some drinks first if
we're going to talk about sex.
Oh, Tripp.
Come on.
That's not funny.
Lisa.
I should warn you.
I never know how much.
of what i say is true hey lisa let's talk sexy you you think
i'm communicative ha ha oh you're you're quite the kidder
tonight yeah never afraid to say anything that pops into
your mind oh yeah boobies hey Wait, did you...
Yeah.
Take out the garbage like I asked you to?
Oh, good question.
Yes, did you take out the garbage under the kitchen sink?
Yeah.
Oh, all right, good.
I just wanted to make sure you hadn't forgotten that.
Whoa, I just realized something.
When's the last time you were...
Oh, tonight's a special night.
Oh.
Yeah, tonight is special.
Intimate?
Remember?
Uh, well, remember how you introduced us almost exactly 10
years ago?
Don't ignore me!
Yes.
We really want to thank you for years and years of pain.
Sexy time.
Lisa, flirting with me will only make it harder to let you
leave tonight.
Don't get carried away, Tripp.
She's just telling you what you want to hear.
What does that mean?
sexy time if i just keep saying sexy time you think it's a
oh lisa i thought you might like this photo i just put up
from our recent trip to italy italy might like it it's a
beautiful picture of the italian countryside of course
she'll like it lisa come take a look at this yes go take a
look by the way anybody join me trip i want you no lisa what
does this picture make you think of romance thinker right
love romance oh everything in italy was so romantic a scene
i want to go with you trip the well um but it was the art
that was so amazing the art you hate that oh my god he said
A word!
Um.
I want you, Tripp.
Wait, wait.
What's wrong, Tripp?
Tripp, it's okay if we disagree in front of our friend.
We're not disagreeing.
No, no.
Comfort.
Oh, uh, you're hugging me.
Lisa, careful.
Too much affection can go to Tripp's head.
Right.
It's okay, it's okay.
Oh.
Well, you're really affectionate tonight, aren't you?
time we're risen we're risen we're risen lisa how funny
you're flirting with me i am okay okay that's enough let's
not go there how far can we go you know ever since we got
married trip is forever trying to get me to buy new
furniture and redecorate really aggressive all the sudden i
kind of enjoy it but yeah i'm scared everybody look i'm
scared well i want to ask you You are very, you're very
aggressive.
You have to look at this room and admit it looks terrible.
Terrible.
I mean, look, or...
No, no, no, no.
See, Grace loves expensive furniture.
She grew up in this really nice house with really nice
couches and fancy dishes.
And she can't live without this stuff.
She's not like other girls.
She doesn't want to wear pearls.
You know, at work I waste all day designing ads for
apartments with perfect views like this.
And then it makes me think I want to design it into my
apartment.
This view makes me feel like a million.
Oh my gosh, you know, she wants to wear paper clips.
Damn it, I'm wrong.
I simply want a view of trees and green.
Trees?
What?
Trees are disgusting.
Ah, what a nice surprise and honest answer.
Lisa.
Wait, Grace, I don't know where you're getting this.
Wait, that's what you said.
You, you, you, you, you.
I could have painted that painting on the wall instead of
buying it.
yeah we've seen how your artist friends live as if you could
survive that kind of lifestyle give me a break give me give
me a break no no no you're being honest i'm being honest
okay well i i was worried there for a bit that you were on
tripside tonight i am um oh no no no hold on i gotta get
back on tripside lisa stop that it's embarrassing already
god oh That's the last one I'll do.
That's the last one I'll do.
Or else they'll kick me out.
So, drinks.
Drinks!
Chip's favorite pastime is to get the blood alcohol content
of his guests higher than his golf score.
Why don't I make us one of my new drink inventions?
I call it Grace's Inner Soul.
It's a mixture of chardonnay, bitters, and lots of ice.
I'd love that.
Ah.
Lisa, you have deliciously wicked taste.
Oh, yes.
It's a secret.
Chip doesn't even like the taste of alcohol.
What?
So, Lisa.
how does that sound lisa chris getting i love a drink maybe
you just want some juice no or a mineral water no yeah no
i'm gonna make the whole bottle our friend is here we're
gonna enjoy ourselves that's all there is to it yeah
everybody loves my drinks everybody loves his drinks
everybody loves his drinks well of course trip after all you
got enough practice when you were a real bartender can i
actually drink this in college you were a bartender how do
you know about that oh i know you were trying to keep it a
big secret but one time my friends and I went slumming off
campus to some crappy bar in the sticks and we saw you
there.
Oh, that's great.
Oh, I love bartenders.
What's wrong with being a bartender?
What is wrong with that?
What are you saying?
I love bartenders.
What's wrong with being a bartender?
Oh, and you I can predict what you'll say the way you keep
trying to explain everything um sexy dad look just quit the
flirting right now i'm warning you what is everybody hinting
at that i'm a bad person that i don't love my wife what ah
all right you know what lisa i'm going to ask you something
okay grace trip let me ask our guest a question okay lisa
yes or no Should a married person be allowed to flirt with
other people for fun?
Oh, yes.
What?
Why?
See?
Oh, yes.
That's fine.
What?
What's that look on your face for, huh?
The real truth is, Tripp, you flirt with everybody.
The clients at work, our friends, everybody.
You can't help yourself.
You're always looking around our entire marriage.
God damn it.
She's gone.
Yeah, go on.
Get out of my face.
I'm coming here.
freaking look at you oh hey come here come here come here
come here come here oh no no no no hold on before she comes
back oh where'd you go oh no no don't don't do that what's
it to you i've tried to kiss him lee lisa trip can just be
so oh we're talking about me are we what what trip it's your
These guys are so dramatic.
I need like...
To listen to some relaxing ASMR after this or something.
If it weren't for you, I could be a real artist by now.
Your art sucks.
This painting, well...
See, all I really wanted was something personal.
It's bad.
Look, there's nothing wrong with the stupid painting.
I guess there is.
It makes me feel like shit.
It's bad.
focus on just me or you let's talk no art lisa you blame me
for all of this don't you yes grace you're the one yes yes
oh my god you think i'm to blame i'm to blame for all of
this yes yes
art bad art this is too much i can't go away no just leave
me alone for a second i don't want to
Okay, Lisa.
You know what?
I think you should leave.
You'll be fine.
You should just go.
Why?
What happened?
What?
I was too freaky.
Did you ever see the AR room this game was made for?
It's just a guy with prototype VR goggles and a giant
backpack on.
I've never seen it.
Trip rejected me.
But I didn't...
But I didn't do anything!
Another one.
What do you mean another one?
Thank you.
Thank you for the gift that you guys thank you.
More smooch.
Dang.
I didn't know he was a bartender.
M-M-M.
Manless Mane-M.
What do you mean?
Sticking out your wisp for the Riz made.
They're so do-do-do.
They're so mata-tax.
I just wanna be your phantomy.
Wait, no!
There's literally phantom tax!
Or are you taking?
you for that fam to get up to thank you it wasn't me someone
sent that k barn blame k barn k barn made me read that can
love bloom between a bartender and an artist I've learned so
much about these two that trip has some really deep rooted
problems with his with his upbringing he doesn't he wants to
be like one of the He wants to be one of the Joneses and and
Grace hates that how she grew up and and doesn't want to
live like this fancy lifestyle.
He has an inferiority complex.
Yes!
Why does he hate art?
Thank you for the gifts and resting glitch face.
Thank you!
He hates occupations in general.
I don't know why right now YouTube chat is kind of glitching
for me so I'm gonna go I'm gonna refresh I'm gonna refresh
Wait Wait hold on YouTube?
Uh oh.
YouTube?
I think everything's crashing I think Maybe I'm in trouble
Oh wait, wait, there we go
And Okay Hold Quick, while she can't see I can see, I can
see, I can see
That was fun That was interesting That was something for
sure what why why first of all why i guess we got the
quote-unquote good end right where they talk it out that was
a game that was a game
gonzalo and lisa got married gonzalo the fact that the way
they say the name so in it's just really funny what's the
good ending were they you got two good endings isn't bad is
him leaving a good ending I guess oh my gosh and Jory goes
thank you for the 50 thank you you guys are insane you guys
are so crazy thank you so much oh elevator ending that's
true that was maybe the best ending just avoid it all leave
it leave it to them i don't know why we became a marriage
counselor um what a mysterious game truly truly mysterious
if i remember correctly she is cheating on him what oh my
gosh mr alvacy thank you for that fancy thank you thank you
so much oh my gosh you guys are crazy please i don't that
the memberships are not as expensive as usually but like
please please um wait so is that really not her dad he's
cheating on her too well she said
she said that he flirts with everybody the bingo thanks for
the gift in Why is that thanks for the 10 gift?
Oh my gosh, welcome, welcome, welcome, welcome, thanks for
the 10 gift, thank you.
Hmm.
I think they have a lot of issues.
I think we can all agree that they have issues.
And maybe, you know, if you're in a relationship and you're
just like, is this going well?
Plug it better, thank you for that birthday!
That's one, thank you for the 20!
Jay, thank you for the 20!
Oh my gosh, if you are in a, if you are in a relationship
and you're like, man, I have issues.
Or if you're not in a relationship, this is something that
you are missing out on.
Isn't that so sad?
Alessandro, thank you for the 10.
Yeah, thank you for the 15.
Casey Raptor, thank you.
Thank you for the 5, Sophia, thank you for the 10.
Come on, welcome.
Why is everybody giving 50 memberships?
My notifications are never going to end.
Oh my god, Shady Noctis, thank you for the 50.
Thank you guys so much.
Thank you.
I have, I don't even know how many emotes I can commission
at this point.
Here, let me see.
I don't even know.
Um, memberships.
Holy cow.
Sorry.
Oh, oh, wow.
let me see okay emoji 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16
17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25 26 27 28 29 30 this is this is
not including the ones that I already have 31 32 33 34 35 36
37 wait that might fill it up because it's not letting me
add another one but it's not telling me that I need to get
more members I
think I have to commission a lot of emotes oh my gosh you
guys are still gifted please
Oh, we have all the slots already?
I guess so.
I have to commission so many emotes.
Suffering from success.
37.
We need some glow sticks.
There's one with me holding glow sticks.
It's this one.
It's kind of...
smaller but i'm holding the glow sticks oh my god emo but
thank you thank you for the uncle silver thank you oh my
gosh you guys please you're gifting too many and everybody
gives it a lot last time wow
thank you guys it's a sea of green for real
I'm curious what the generated stage play is, but it like
opens up a, uh, it opens up like a, um, um, what's it
called?
A, a, a, is it a text file?
What is this?
Oh, cannot find the program files, facade, stage plays,
facade, stage play, text file.
Do you want to a new file yes there's nothing here it's
empty it's empty can we have a wisp emo yes i will i i have
many things i must must uh oh my gosh lucy thank you i have
many things i must i must uh i must of of decide on how
what's emotes now oh my gosh hey boss youtube charged my
account wrong for membership so here's the rest of it with
interests oh wake up block thank you but yeah hey many
people have been asking have you seen akiba made war if not
love a live react to the op oh you could probably do that
right i'll be honest haven't i still haven't seen it i'm so
bad i know it's like literally made for me get it made for
me crunchy baby and jay just like free you know emotes are
free so fake needs stop i why i have i can i can be i am
fine with the emotes i just have to find an artist i've got
to have to find an artist who is who i could be like can you
make 30 emotes
okay um what was i looking up oh akiba mid-war opening do
you think i can just watch it i made nice mince finger guns
in my door thank you for that question far thank you gonna
i'm gonna give me a second no no no no we're gonna watch it
together you think it's fine though if maybe i won't get
copy if i talk enough maybe i won't get copyright struck and
i don't i won't make it so loud um let me do this well i'm
just gonna do the same window capture uh made die kaiten
I crop it.
Oh, wait, how do I...
Oh, here.
This one.
I crop it and crop it.
Crop it, crop it, crop it.
Crop it, crop it.
Crop it.
Transition?
Transition.
How do I transition?
Hello?
Why won't you...
Why won't you let me?
What's going on?
Oh, oh, I'm in...
Oh!
For some reason, I wouldn't let me...
That's weird.
Time to watch the Akiva Maid Wars opening.
For the first time.
I've never watched it before.
Wow.
This is from a year ago.
It was uploaded.
I guess it was from last year, wasn't it?
Joseph, thanks for that, Katsuba.
Thank you.
Finally, and leave.
Oh, wait.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Hold on.
Velen books!
No, I'm sorry.
Suika books!
Wait, so if this is...
If this is...
If this is this area, then that means like there's arcade
and then there's like super potato and then this would be...
It said Tsukimo, but maybe it's supposed to be the
Kotobukiya.
If it's this area.
Wow!
Hey, that's me.
Oh, why is she blocked out?
Do the characters get introduced?
Oh my gosh, the Momo-i- the Momo-i doke!
Oh, wait, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, it's so fast.
So this is, this is, this clock is like, like, um, it's
really, uh, it's like one of those, how do I say, oh my
gosh, sorry.
It's, um, it's, uh, yeah, it's very famous.
So that's the word.
It's a legendary clock in Akiba.
It's right outside the station towards the Radio Kaikan, the
Radio Kaikan building side.
Legendary clock.
So it's really cool that they included it.
This is such a jam.
Wait, hold on.
I know I keep stopping and going through, but I want to see
what they include.
Of course, there's a train.
Which one is this supposed to be?
I guess it's just supposed to be one of the...
Wait, hmm?
Hmm.
I guess it's maybe...
What building is this supposed to be?
Actual electronic shop.
Yeah, they still exist.
They still exist in Akiva.
Oh no, Den is huge.
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na.
They're so cute, I love their outfits so much.
Wow.
Are they actually fighting so many people?
Oh, cute!
The confetti, I'm surprised the confetti doesn't ruin the
bit right.
Why is this a bob, though?
But no, this area, this almost looks like, this actually
looks like Yodobashi.
It looks like, I don't know if it is or not though, like
Yodobashi camera.
Oh, so cute.
Such a bob.
I could be getting this area wrong, right?
Because it's, if it's, it's chemo, I don't know.
If it's the melon books...
Hmm, but it depends on if this is Chuo Dori or not, but
because it...
Because if it's the...
Sorry, I'm getting all confused now.
I'm getting all confused now.
It's a Kumo.
Yeah, it's a Kumo, but the area I'm thinking of... See,
there's Akibao right there.
Oh, sorry, Okibao.
Akibao.
Quick, take us to Google Street View.
You're so right.
Okibao.
It's so funny.
Akibao?
There's several in Akiba though.
Those are also like popular electronic stores in Akiba.
Geogesser Mint.
I'm no, I'm no, what's that guy's name?
It's funny because besides the Suika books, the opening
shows like mostly, it doesn't show like any of the anime
like stuff.
It mostly focuses on like, you know, you can see like the
DVD like stores that you can buy and sell stuff.
And then there's the computer Semmon store.
It doesn't focus on all the anime stuff there is around in
the area too.
Thanks for the fun stream, Mint, I need to sleep now, good
night, things are hanging out, thank you, I think this might
be an alley parallel to the main road, I think so too, but
that's why I'm, that's why my brain is like, where are we,
because, okay, this looks like the building that has, well,
maybe not, it looks like the building that has, has the main
dream in it which would make sense if this were if this were
the Kinokunia sorry Kotobukiya and then if this were the
melon books because the melon but the melon books you have
to go you you have to you either go through the what's the
word the the the the arcade or you go around to the front
but this looks like Chua Dori over here so I don't know I
don't know oh my gosh I'm a fake akiba fan this anime takes
place in the 90s oh
90s the night oh there was the windows yeah that's right
where'd it go they did have the windows oh windmill windmill
95 are there even maid cafes back then
Mmm, mysterious, old-timey Akiba.
Sometimes I, there's like, sometimes I'll go through, like,
sites that have, like, old shops and stuff that were in
Akiba.
I just like to read about them.
During the Maid Wars.
That's why there's no Maids, because they're still at war.
I get it.
now.
I understand now.
That was fun.
That was silly.
I'm going to move over here.
Hello.
And I'm gonna I'm gonna one second.
I'm gonna put on some BGM.
And I'm, oh, let me exit out of the facade game too.
Exit.
Okay.
And BGM, BGM, BGM, BGM, BGM, BGM, BGM, BGM, BGM, BGM, BGM,
BGM, BGM.
Where was my music?
Why can't I ever find it?
There we go.
Bada-dada-dada-dada-dum-dum-dum.
Thank you for the 10 gifted.
Smash boo!
I want melon bread now.
No, the song is called Lemon Cake.
You're so close.
I still haven't even...
I'm still using all the same BGM I used to use in the past.
When did I even save this?
July...
Wait, this doesn't make any sense.
It says created...
August 13th, 2020.
But then it says modified July 18th, 2020.
How does that make any sense?
What?
How was it created in August?
Small brain Thank you for the 50 Thank you
Time travel Time travel real Time travel real What Is it
okay if I can recommend you a video called Eurasian waifu
Air Force Recruitment video Yes Just posted in my tag Man
Emory
Stop!
Oh my gosh.
You guys next week Emory and...
Can I say that?
Can I say that we're gonna collab next week?
Well, I said it.
Gonna collab with Emory next week.
When I was in Japan, Emory and I hung out a couple times.
Yippee!
We went shopping and um, we got our hair done together and
it was so fun.
Spoilers.
I don't know what I'm at all doing next week, though.
What are we streaming?
I think we're doing a collab with a lethal company.
And I'm doing mods for the first time ever.
The one mod that I've always wanted to do was the Skid
Walker mod.
Where it copies your voices?
Oh my gosh.
I'm kind of scared.
Fukuoka, thanks for the vibe, Kim did!
Thank you guys, everybody joining, everybody gifting.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Yeah, there's like a skinwalker mod that will like copy your
voice and then like so you'll be, you know, walking through
the mines, swinging your pickaxe side to side, side to side.
And then you'll hear your friend and you'll be like, oh hi!
But it wasn't your friend, it was...
It's actually a monster.
It's genuinely so confusing.
The Goku mod!
What's that?
What's the Goku mod?
Is it just the two of you playing Lethal?
No, we have some other people.
Yes.
We have some other people.
but I've never collabed with them before so I'm a little
nervous
yeah yeah
who is he?
I'm not gonna say what about Mataro?
I do want to play games with Mataro I don't know maybe
because I talk to her so much thank you so much maybe
because I talk with her so much because of the podcast like
you know maybe we're okay no i'm just kidding i still do
want to play games with her but i'm trying to um ease myself
in to collapse and stuff like that so i don't know just
because you know i don't want to come in swinging when um i
just got back Yeah, yeah.
Take your time.
Thank you.
Maybe after the pod season.
I also, you know, I don't want people to get sick of us.
Like, if we're always on the pod and we're always talking.
And, um, we're, like, you know, I don't want it to be like,
oh, you guys are collabing too.
Oh my gosh, I've seen way too much of a Minta Matara.
Please.
Well, obviously we will be streaming, though, when I go and
visit her and she plays Metal Gear.
So, hmm.
So, there's that to look forward to.
Matara overdose.
Hakuna Matara.
Metal Gear.
Nah.
So, I don't know exactly how that's gonna work, though.
Are we gonna watch BBC Wildlife videos?
stop mine my trauma I can't believe these people are friends
I hate that notorious BSJ thank you for that happy gift
thank you also looking at the some of these are probably
older stream labs but Akiba maid war watch along the show
felt like watching a yakuza show but with maids instead is
there like is there like any mystery to it or is it like
just kind of It's not violent, but I don't know how to say.
Spy animals.
No spy animals.
A little mystery.
Plenty of violence.
It's quite surreal.
Meep!
Thank you for the 50 gift.
Thank you.
Oh yeah, the blurred face mystery girl.
Well, I wasn't, you know how like in some shows, um they'll
blur people out or they'll like scratch people out until
they're introduced in the show i wasn't sure if that was the
case um i like shows like that though where they change the
opening they'll reveal more things in the opening as more
stuff is revealed in the show is so cool
naigif low-key emotion wrecking
Huh?
Azura!
Thank you for the 50 gift and thank you!
Gakogurashi was great for that.
Oh my gosh, I think of Gakogurashi.
Every time when I think of like that concept.
Gift shower.
I know.
Why are you guys so nice to me?
Whoa.
What's going on?
Did you get Rem on Nike?
You know what?
I'm not a huge Nike player.
I'm haunted.
I'm glitching.
I'm not a big Nike player.
uh i played a little bit um how's fujisan doing today let's
check fujisan update
you cannot see fujisan it's cloudy that's typically how it
is that's one of the reasons or one of one of the few
reasons i don't like summer it's because it's always cloudy
maria why are you
Thank you!
Thank you so much, I hope you've been enjoying Metal Gear.
V2ers from Japan play a lot of old Ace Combat lately.
War need to play in EM.
Yeah.
Nike is solid, but once we get far enough, it gets so
tedious.
I don't know, I...
I really love, I don't, I'm the type that can, that focuses
mostly on one gotcha game at a time.
So me, me and Blue Archive, we are tight.
We are, we are so tight.
I don't see myself giving up Blue Archive and hopefully I
don't see it disappearing from the English side anytime
soon.
A lot of YouTubers have been playing Metal Gear so all
lately.
I know.
So awesome.
I wonder why.
More people should play Metal Gear though.
More people should play Metal Gear and know why it's so
great.
I like Asana and Karin.
Unlike Pre-Kanay.
I mean, I mean, I mean, the master collection I think helps
a ton with people being able to play before obviously you
had to jump through a little bit of hoops to either like you
know you could play the GOG metal gear solid but with all
the issues it has and then and then if you wanted to play it
you'd have to like get like a PS3 and all this stuff and
then also you have to all there was was the HD collection
and yeah so I get it I get why more people are playing it
now well the techniques are the vibe captain thank you ducky
uh-oh but yeah so do you have any ways on how to get into
Metal Gear Solid for people who want to play play play play
it blue archive has many cute and funny yeah they're so cute
they're so cute and they're so goofy i love them riko thanks
for the podcast and thank you
hoping for and peace walker come to peace soon me too me too
yeah but there is there is master collection too happens in
it metal gear acid playthrough win i i do plan on playing it
i probably will regret it but i do there will be a time when
i will play it she don't come i thank you for the busy thank
you for the time thank you mgs lore stream when maybe well i
mean we'll have the lore podcast or not lore podcast we
don't want to spoil stuff for her right um thank you guys
for the stream labs as well if you're still looking for
mystery rex i would suggest summertime rendering i saw that
um when i was watching heavenly delusion is that what it's
called heavenly delusion um uh when i always finish an
episode it would recommend summertime rendering halaji thank
you for the time thank you thank you thank you thank you
it was good I love time travel I love time travel so much so
so awesome I don't know why I love time travel I think I
think I must blame girl who left through time you've seen
heavenly delusion manga is so good I haven't read the manga
the anime was really and then also beach did the open so why
are we yelling why are we yelling
hmm have you checked apothecary diaries what is the genre of
apothecary diaries because because I've seen a lot about it
but I don't know anything about it but From what I saw, I
thought it was like a Shojo or something.
It's a mystery!
Romance.
It's like a mystery.
Kyler, thanks for the 10 Gifts.
Thank you.
It's so...
It's anime breaking bad?
What?
Historical mystery.
Romance, mystery, and romance.
I mean...
It's like a mystery.
Is it a mystery or like a mystery?
This looks like MTS 5 is my first game, though.
Let's me be really confused.
Yeah, I can believe that.
Hey, I'm Dragon.
Thank you for the toy, honey.
Thank you.
Oh my gosh, you guys are...
No wonder... No wonder we hit the...
No wonder we hit the amount...
The max amount of...
Of, uh...
Oh my god.
Wait...
You guys, I think we have enough members, for real.
I'm concerned about the Minecraft server.
I don't think I can make a server this big.
I don't...
I've actually never made a server before, so I'm going to...
Do my best.
Pokerawa thinks you're the vibe gifted.
Wait, I said stop.
You probably can't.
Oh my god, you guys stop playing.
What does...
Like...
Don't people do Minecraft servers for, like, their
Patreon...
things and stuff poopy thank you but how do they how do they
do it though oh my gosh thank you for that katsuba thank you
oh close the first of all it does thank you for the 50s nick
thank you for the five fion thank you for the 10 thank you
guys did you thank you for the five fox play thank you for
the five billy joe thank you for the 10.
But how to...
Those are usually not $2 subs, though.
Am I...
Did I make a mistake?
Oh, Lepanto fan, thank you for the fan thing!
An epic stuff, really suck it in my face.
What do I do then?
What do I do?
Oh, if I...
I can't change the price because...
because okay this is the issue if I change the price it
kicks everyone out and if I if I make a higher tier I think
if you if people gift members it will default to that tier
so like I don't want it to be more expensive like I know
that people you know vtuber fans probably have so many
like the last person you think about you know like
especially if the like especially if there's some people who
are like oh i'm also a patreon member then you do definitely
don't need to be spending so much on so much on a youtube
membership too oh my god i guess we got the party how many
members are we at i don't want to say i'm scared this is
This is definitely the most I've ever had though Ever Ever
Ever
Congrats Thank you I think So like seven Yeah about Give or
take You know Yeah.
Oh my gosh, thank you guys for joining.
Thank you guys so much.
This is why I didn't want to open on stream because I knew
it would just be a free for all.
I knew it would be chaos.
I didn't want to just be sitting here being like, thank you.
Thank you.
oh wow the floodgates are open oh my gosh thank you guys
thank you thank you so much she hates that game no I just
want to talk I want us to you know hang out not just me
being like thank you thank you thank you thank you
Like, Kamiyoshi could never be the last VTuber I think
about.
Stop.
I will be sad if your server is not called Outer Heaven.
Especially since you yourself are out of heaven,
technically.
I will take that consideration, that naming consideration,
to heart.
Yes.
I'm excited though.
Actually, I have next week, if I can get the everything kind
of set up, I have a stream planned for starting the server
at least and like kind of building a little bit of stuff so
that we can...
I'm scared though.
I'm really scared.
I don't know.
Maybe I need to rethink this though.
Because I can't just be like...
like alright first come first serve gets into the Minecraft
server you know I don't know well well also people can have
access but that doesn't mean everybody will be on at the
same time right so maybe it's actually okay there can be a
max limit but everyone has access not everyone not the limit
won't be the limit the limit does not exist I recently on
the plane They had Did you guys know that they made A Mean
Girls movie Well they had a Mean Girls musical And then they
made Made the Mean Girls movie musical
I don't know I don't think I liked it very much I don't
think I liked it very much The server will lag The server
will lag So bad Ooh I also missed an opportunity not calling
Heaven Zanzibar.
Yes, let me travel back in time to before I played Metal
Gear and say that I'm going to Zanzibar instead.
And everyone will be like, what?
That makes no sense.
Regina George is so pretty.
She is very pretty.
I don't know, I just didn't like the...
I felt the songs were, like, kind of lacking.
I'd never seen the musical before, by the way, so.
But I felt like the songs were lacking in, like, power,
except for Regina, usually.
But I don't, it was also, it felt, like, uncomfortable
sometimes with some of the changes that they made.
I was like, huh?
I don't get it.
Create a time paradox.
Ghost Babel.
I'm still trying to find a copy of Ghost Babel.
Have you ever played the Ace Combat 7 special mission DLC?
I have not played it yet.
Not yet, not yet.
Epy mint.
I'm Epy.
Slepy, slepy.
You'll probably never see more than 50% members logged into
the Minecraft server at once.
Yeah, but like, I worry if I stream it.
Like, what if people...
I wonder if there's a way that I can make it so people can't
log in while I'm streaming.
But like, I'll obviously log in off stream.
But I wonder if there's a way that I could be like, hey,
don't...
You're not allowed in while I'm streaming.
But I'm also scared of what I'll see.
Oh my goodness, thank you for the birthday gift, thank you!
I have a lot to...
I have a lot to learn and experiment with.
Please be patient with me.
Maybe you have multiple servers?
Maybe.
But what if I show one server more?
love than the other that's not so good right I don't know I
don't know the servers are going to compete oh my gosh some
people will be like I'm server I'm server Zanzibar I'm
server outer heaven and then they'll be like oh my gosh okay
that we're gonna organize we're gonna organize a takedown of
outer heaven and we're gonna storm in there and we're gonna
burn everybody's houses what if that happens there will be
war server Rex and Ray server server shagohan not the
factions made wars
I can't stop yawning I don't know I'll get some advice from
people and see what I do Luckily Luckily I didn't write
Minecraft server access In the perks of joining membership
So So You know It We could just...
We could just...
We could just pretend it never happened.
Give more a chance!
No!
You could do a lottery.
Maybe, but I would feel bad about it too.
I think.
I think I would feel bad about it too.
Please don't rush, take your time.
I will, thank you.
I will, I will.
especially because some people keep gifting so many
memberships my god your luck is abysmal
but also if it's a lottery i don't even know how i would
distribute it like how would i be like okay i would have to
i don't know i don't want to think about it you know what
let's just Oh, I'm saving that for Future Mint.
I don't need to worry about it.
Thank you guys for the gift.
Thank you.
Thank you guys.
But anyway.
Almost.
Wait.
As of today.
It has been one week.
Of me back.
Yippee.
Oh my gosh.
Happy one week anniversary.
Everybody!
Happy one week to me.
Please stop the gifting of memberships.
Oh, I can't do high notes.
anymore.
My throat.
I wonder if it will ever recover.
Maybe I need to drink more honey stuff.
I have in here.
Well, this is ginger and yuzu.
I guess that doesn't really help.
Before in the past, I used to still sick girl.
I don't think I'm still sick.
I think it's just that my voice is...
Since my voice was so damaged before, it's taking a long
time to recover or you know it like uh that was also another
reason i um took some time sorry i'm trying to get a this
voice this voice mint out um another reason i took so long
or not so sorry not took so long another reason i took some
time off the two months in japan was because i wanted to
rest my voice Because even prior to that, I'd been having
some issues with my...
Not my voice giving out, but like...
I could feel it getting a little weaker.
So...
But I think I just need to take better care of it too.
And you totally did that, right?
You'd be surprised!
go to idol shows and I wouldn't scream so loud like I would
do like if I did calls I would do them like in my normal
voice now I wouldn't go so like loud and crazy so didn't you
go to karaoke's yeah sometimes I only went like like four or
five times I didn't go that often what do you mean extadow
What do you mean?
I was being good.
I was,
I promise.
But yeah.
That's a lot of times.
In two months?
Five times is not that much.
I think.
Let's go.
Do you remember the first time I went?
And then...
You know, thinking about it now...
I think I went...
By myself to karaoke every time.
I really wanted to go to Pasella.
Pasella is like one of my favorite...
Uh...
Karioki places because they have this yummy honey toast...
That I like to get.
Thank you for the five gift that thank you.
Your voice needs roughly a week to heal between heavy, heavy
overuse-ish.
Yeah, but what about, how about sickness?
Pasella is awesome.
But, and then they have, they have like the big honey toast
and then they have the small honey toast.
But the small honey toast, I don't like it so much because,
because it's like,
it's it's it's it's it's more it's too hard in my opinion
thank you for the vibe gift of roger coke and um but you
need to get the big honey toast you need to go with friends
or else you'll not be able to finish it all so um so many
memberships you're telling me oh my gosh thank you for I
meant I hope your spiritual reawakening reawakening go as
well take care sweetie I'm sure you will do great thank you
thank you so much nah I'd win they're big though hold on let
me get a picture let me get a picture for you guys they're
so yummy pasela honey toast
I can find one.
Okay.
This one has, like, a person in the background.
So, you can kind of get, like, the scale.
Oh, my gosh.
It's so cool.
If I talk about something, I can just show you guys.
Wowie.
Whoa!
Okay.
I just Googled this.
So, I don't know who that person is.
But look how big!
Oh, my gosh.
It looks so delicious.
And it's like that nice thick toast too and it's like oh I
love oh it's so good it's so yummy and they have different
kinds like this one holy canola look at this one look at
this one look at this one oh it's so small look at that it
looks so gosh and each of those little parts are like some
of the the toast the bread oh my gosh i really wanted to go
and get one oh oh oh oh here here here here here here here
here here here they show this the this they show the small
size too why is it so tiny but it's like not the same
because i like the softness of the toast you know
But yeah, this is at Pase-la karaoke places in Japan.
Mmm, yummy.
So small.
So tiny.
And that is toast?
Yeah.
It's toast.
Cubic food.
That's big.
What, the honey toast?
Are you kidding me?
It's huge!
It's also filled, you guys!
It's like, it's so big.
Hold on, let me see if I can find.
Uh, I mean...
Uh...
It's so big!
Honey toast, caffeine, Akihabara is delicious!
Yes!
That's what we're talking about!
Bye, Shamin!
I've had this one before.
Hold on.
Oh, it's a PNG.
This one.
I've had this one before.
Yummy, yummy, yummy.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm thrilled.
First tacos, who went down the 50?
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
I love cinnamon roll.
I love, love, love cinnamon roll.
Recently, I've been pretty into Kogi Mune.
I think she's really cute.
But also, there was a new...
There was a new...
Well, I say new.
Maybe like...
I think he was released last year.
But he's like...
He's like...
What's the word?
He's a ghost that draws...
Hold on, Sanrio ghost.
Hanamaru Obake He's so cute Hanamaru Obake I'm like, you're
just like me You're a ghost Hold on Save image Save image
Show you guys Look Look how cute Oh, he's so cute Hanamaru
Obake Hanamaru is like You know, I'm Those swirly, when
like, teachers, like, draw, like, 100% on your homework.
It's the big swirly.
That's what...
Oh, wait.
Hold on.
There's a picture.
This, this, this, this, this, this, this.
You see the Hanamaru on the ground?
Yeah.
So Hanamaru Obake.
you it's literally you it's me oh you guys are getting 100
in school man did i talk about my okay i'm gonna talk a
little bit about the japan school i went to because uh the
japan school the japanese school i went to a little bit um i
think i mentioned before how i was just like oh yeah like i
don't regret going at all um i had so much fun and i learned
a lot um i don't remember if i talked about this on stream
before you didn't really mention much i'm not gonna say the
name or anything obviously but uh the reason i would i would
choose not to go back what kind of school was it it was a
japanese school like japanese learning school so um the
reason First of all, they were very flexible.
I originally wanted six months, but they were like, we can't
kind of get you for that.
So, but we have two months we can give you.
And I was like, okay, that works fine.
But when I entered the class, there were people there that,
there were people there that had been there for like months
and months and months before me.
And so,
wasn't the housing situation an issue too no not really they
helped me get a place which was the only issue was it was 20
minutes away from the train station and you guys I scammed
myself I scammed myself I still I'm still so angry about it
um it sounds like quite a walk i love walking so i actually
don't mind i like it was only an issue when i was when i was
uh late in the mornings jr pass no not the jr pass i got the
takiken i got the commuter pass which is like if you're
staying in japan for a long time highly recommend it if
you're like either going to uh to like you know like for me
i'm going to the same place every day So, when you get the
pass, you choose two different stations, and every station
in between that is also included in the pass.
So, it's super duper duper, super handy.
I got one once, too, when I actually worked in Akihabara for
a little bit, and I got it from my school to, this was years
ago, but I got it from my school to Akihabara, so I could go
to Akihabara as well.
often as I want, I mean, I would say free, but I paid for
it.
So, but yeah, the take can, um, uh, and so I got it.
Oh, how do I say, okay.
My station's name was kind of weird.
I don't know how to describe it without saying it exactly.
Um, But when I was putting in the stations, I got the
station that I was like my the station that I went to by my
apartment to and I thought I put in my station that I got
off for school.
But no, I put in I put in I didn't realize that I missed a
part on it.
and so I paid like $150 for it because I had it last two
months and no I'm sorry just a month it was just a month
because I got it kind of late because I was trying to find
right now there's like a Seika pass shortage so I was trying
to find a place that would print it I could not find a place
that would even like allow me to get it so it discounted it
discounted my my um the amount that i spent but ultimately i
ended up like paying double for for my for my tickets and
only and then because because the the the train was also
weird the trains in between or the stations in between it
only counted some of them I know I'm sorry I'm being very
vague because I don't want to like just give away where I
went and everything but it was it was so I was so angry at
myself when I realized I was so mad I was like and you know
it was my fault I should have double checked salty commute
handling mishap yeah I feel this frustration scamming
yourself sucks it does it does it does so you know if you
get the if you get the commuter pass definitely double
triple check and yeah don't be like me luckily you know for
me I could afford it but if you know what if I was you know
in a worse position I would have been like I would have been
really suffering so that's okay we're no strangers to scam I
honestly don't know if I could have gotten a refund but I
felt bad about wasting the past if that were the case you
know what I mean and I don't know I didn't I didn't want to
but yeah that's okay we live and learn or die and learn in
my case but yeah about the school I I went in where some of
the students were there like many many months before me and
so you know in the textbook we were learning from it was
like lessons I don't remember 20 let's just say 25 to 50
okay so they learned from lesson 25 the people that were in
the class i learned well yes then we had this one big test
that was the entirety of the book so we took that test which
was lessons 25 through 50.
i came in at lesson 40.
like no way this sucks oh it sucked so much and because you
know um like i when i like properly learned japanese i you
know that was so long ago i forgot so much of it and like
especially like tiny tiny things too like the correct way to
use this this form or whatever whatever so i was like you
know i'm obviously um it was just hard trying to catch up
but i'm glad because now i'm back into like the mindset of
studying um and i did learn a lot of like kegel um and uh
yeah so it was good i i do wish also there was like more
talking in the class I don't know.
I feel like that's so important.
It's so funny though.
On my first day, on my first day, it was a pretty small
class.
someone, someone asked me, like, first of my teacher was
like, oh, Minto, your voice is so cute.
I was like, no, no, no, no, no.
And someone in the class, this guy, he was just like, are
you a V-Tuber?
Oh, no.
First he asked, are you, are you a are you a voice actor and
i was like no and then he goes and then and then i was like
no they were like you've never done any voice acting work
like your voice is kind of unique i was like no no i'm i
just uh i don't know then and then like while i was leaving
because it was at the end of class they were like the guy he
was just like she's probably a vtuber
and uh it was so funny because um uh there was a there was a
i ended up like him and this other girl we would go and get
lunch together after class and like they would he kept what
he would keep asking me he'd be like are you a vtuber are
you a vtuber are you a vtuber And I'm like, no, no, no, no,
no, no.
And I think at one point I was like, you know what?
Maybe I'll mess with him a little bit.
Because he would ask me, he would be like, are you part of
this company?
And I was like, no, no, no, no, no.
Like he asked if I was part of Hollow Live.
And I was like, no.
He didn't know VTubers at all.
He was just like, that's the only thing I know.
and so I was like I was like no but at one point I was like
you know what I am gonna mess with him I was like you know
what sorry I I was I was like I was like I I am a vtuber and
and he had a bet going with another guy in our class that I
was a that I was that I was a vtuber and he was like yes I'm
gonna tell him I was like no no no no don't tell him just
like you know kind of keep him like on his toes or whatever
and then they would like he would try to ask me stuff and
the girl too she was just like i can't tell if you're lying
or not and i was like what what do you mean
and like and um he would be like if you're really a vtuber
tell me a story and i was just like
I was like, I can't, you know, like, that's too private.
I don't wanna be found out.
And then, okay, so this whole, the whole like two months, I
was keeping this up.
And on the very last day, we went and like, the three of us
went and got coffee.
And he looked at me and he's just like, you know what?
You really had me going.
I really thought that you were a VTuber.
And I was like, gotcha.
It was so, it was so silly.
I was like, no way.
They just didn't believe me at all.
Like, she, she was so, they were both very nice.
But, um, like, when I say I'm an introvert, like, I am a
true introvert.
introverted than me so I'm the one like trying to start all
the conversations and I'm just like the weather it's so hot
today like it was crazy it was crazy how much I was like how
much I was like oh my god I'm having to pretend I'm an
extrovert here it would be a little awkward it would be
because we would just be eating in silence for a long time
but it was good mmm it was it was still a fun time I got to
do a lot and quiet classmates it would be so funny because
we would be like sitting in silence in our classroom there
was only ever six of us at the most in a class at a time.
Yeah, and we would be sitting there in silence and we would
hear like the class next door like...
What do you mean?
Slap my own joke.
Shut up!
But we would hear the class next to us laugh and like be
really loud and energetic and we're all just sitting there
like, how did we all...
How did... How did we all get in...
How did all the...
this class be only introverts.
I don't understand.
But yeah.
Cast lighting is fun.
Oh, wait.
But yeah.
It was, so.
I, I, I, did enjoy my time i don't think like you know i'm
not like i never thought like oh this was such a waste of
money i think i had a good experience and i always wanted to
why are you guys spamming stop it
thank you for the 10 gift thank you are you planning to take
the jlpt no i don't think so i don't studied specifically
for them but that it wasn't that kind of class either it
wasn't like okay you are taking n2 class it wasn't anything
like that or whatever so just to get functional yeah yeah i
i would much rather like feel confident and feel good in my
abilities than like i mean obviously like studying would
enhance that too of course like you know setting for the
jlpt i mean um but but i would rather just be like oh yeah i
can i can talk and hang out and i don't need a piece of
paper to to say that or not i took the exam just to see if
i'm already on that level that's okay too like if you want
to take it go for it but yeah yeah still i'm still not so
nihongo-jaro but you know I'm Gumbari Masuing my way through
life did you get all bees no I got good grades I got good
grades sitting in kanji is so difficult it can be I I've
honestly so I have found the most help with wani-kani for
kanji but if you're wanting to know how to write it it's
impossible like i can i can't i can't write anything i can
see so many kanji and recognize them and read them and
everything but i cannot write it at all but wani kanji is
really is has been the most um helpful for me at least just
use my keyboard exactly exactly I mean, there's already,
isn't that an issue in Japan too?
There's people who don't know how to write so much anymore?
Um, but, uh, yeah.
I wonder, is that like an issue in like, you know, like in
China?
Is that also an issue or so many people type that they can't
be Hong Kong?
That they can't write so much anymore?
yeah it is what is this what is this it's an issue in the
USA too to be honest okay so kind of true yeah my dad can
barely write anymore from living in the States
yep yeah I had to write everything though I have I have
callus on my on my hands from holding pencils I don't I hold
a pencil my handwriting is so awful it's so oh my gosh you
guys I realize with the with like some of the patreon stuff
I have to come up with a signature I don't I don't have a
signature what do I do what do I thank
you for the read yeah I don't have a I need like I don't
even know how to I don't know what to come up with at all
like do I I'm gonna copy Hanamaru Obake I'm just gonna make
it like a it's like that I cut episode it's exactly like
that I cut episode but like my handwriting isn't so fancy so
I need like something kind of simple I don't I don't know,
like, okay, I'm gonna look up.
Idol sign.
Idol sign?
Wait, I need one that like starts with an M though.
I don't know what... Wait!
A heart could be an M, right?
Maybe.
I don't know.
Gliss, thanks for the vibe you did!
If it's upside down?
No.
Hold on, I'm gonna, let me open up paint.
Let's, let's workshop.
Oh, wait.
Let's workshop this a little bit.
We workshop, we workshop.
Um, okay.
Even though this is on a mouse.
So it might, it's already gonna be ugly, but don't worry
about it.
Crop, crop, crop, crop, crop, crop.
crop crop crop crop okay there we go okay see okay i'm
looking up idle signatures right now i'm not gonna copy
anyone wait this one that also this one that has an m and
it's cute
like uh
why i is so difficult
signed in ectoplasm but i want the i want okay hold on maybe
if we do like that i and t and then we and then we turn it
into a wisp uh with the hi-ti-kakshi and Oh,
the cat ears, hold on.
Perfection.
No, you guys have to give me feedback.
Looks like a whale.
I thought it was a whale.
Oh, man.
Okay.
See, this is why we're workshopping.
This is why we're workshopping.
Catfish No Like I'm looking up this one This one has like Um
I I hate cursive N So we're not gonna do it Mint And then Oh
Oh I feel like this would look better if it was like in a
cute collar and like oh oh ah he's back hmm i like mine like
really big and curly you know the whale is about an onion
what i have to do what to do what to do what to do oh wait
what if i do okay i've seen ones like this too where it's
like a big you know like that that's the M.
It doesn't have to make perfect sense.
Like, it can be like, you know, and then we could like, I
and T.
And like, then here
It's me.
And then here.
And, um, Is that an Among Us?
No!
You're not seeing the vision.
Hold on.
Let's change this one.
I'm going to make it a little bit more exciting.
Like, um.
Like that.
Um.
It's a diglet.
Oh, now it's just Wabafet.
Would it be better if he did it in Kana?
So, hi, Mint.
First time seeing you.
Hi, Coke's Metal.
Thank you.
I could try and do it.
My name is spelled in katakana, not hiragana.
So, I think in katakana, I would look ugly.
Like, hold on.
Like, because katakana is this.
Mi-toto.
I can't even write it well.
There's no way to make this look cute, I think.
As a signature.
Must be hiragana.
Yeah, hiragana is so much cuter.
I'm such a fool.
Why didn't I write my name in hiragana?
I'm going to change it today.
Minto.
Toe.
Stop.
Not mean.
Toe.
Hmm.
Give us your best.
Wow, Buffett.
Ah.
Yeah.
Look at this one.
This is what.
Hold on.
I'm going to save it.
This is what we're aiming for, you guys.
This level of... This level.
this why is it so big I do kind of like the direction like
this direction if I don't make it a wabba fit I think it
could be kind of cute like uh hold on there's some that are
like this um maybe oh oh maybe like uh maybe like a Miffy
face.
Miffy.
I love Miffy.
Give it sleeves, arms.
I don't think that'll work.
I think it makes it look so ugly.
I think it makes it look ugly.
That's okay, though.
Hmm.
Every time you say minto, it sounds like mentos.
Let's see this one.
Hmm.
Make the sleeve into an M.
What?
How does that happen?
How does, how, how, how, how?
Hmm.
Or, um, let's see.
Uh, uh, uh.
Wait, that's actually not so bad.
With the little tongue out.
Like it, like me, like me.
Tap out.
We're on to something.
And then I could add like some...
Little...
Mmm.
Tehepero.
What can I add?
I would put like little sparklies maybe.
I think I would look better if it's like you know how like
in idol master when they show their signatures they're like
all sparkly they're like They're glowing and they're all
sparkly in the eyes make it look like Gengar Maybe it would
look maybe I mean also it's drawn on my with my mouse so
We're workshopping it we're workshopping it.
It's my signature.
You don't have to like it except people who are getting it
on a postcard and have to look at it every time You'll see
it.
You're going to look at this guy's little face and you're
going to be like, oh, no.
Oh, no.
Hmm.
Idol master signatures are nice.
Yeah, that's what I'm looking at.
Well, I'm looking at just like idol signatures in general.
For inspiration.
But most of them are like so complex because they do, they
do like, a lot they have like the cut like yeah the kanji
incorporated and things like that it's and then it's easier
i feel like with hiragana because it's so it's so loopy hmm
like uh like if i did like if i did the minto in like oh
wrong way like something like that and then you have like
this and and like this and like you know or here and then
like that for the toe like it's they're always so crazy you
know and then and then when you do it like that and then it
has like a face in here it's like a kind of like that like
they always go so crazy with them The face is essential for
my branding.
Can't you try to write mint normally as your signature?
No!
No.
Must be perfect from the beginning.
And to can't just be my ugly handwriting.
That has to be special.
Can, can, can, can't.
Look at the membership, thank you!
Can we make custom mint signatures in your art tag?
You can, but I prefer to make my own.
So, if you do, I will not use it.
I can tell you that now, but I appreciate it.
I just can't, I won't use it.
Because I prefer to come up with that on my own.
Gotta add a doodle for pizzazz.
is fuller but yeah no i think i'll go with i'll i'll start
with this it kind of looks like funashi
minto with papyrus it's like when you when you have some of
those doc have you ever like filled out the document like
the doc you signed things and instead of like actually
drawing a signature it's like you can type your signature
and it counts as your signature It's me with the...
Me with the...
With the, with the, with the, with the, comic sans, with the
papyrus.
If I were to write mint, I would have to be, like, done
so...
Okay, like, here's an example.
I mean, these are...
It's so hard, like, with these ones, because a lot of them
are their kanji, but just to give you an idea, Here's some
Idol Master ones.
Riyamu's is so cute.
Ooh, it's so cute.
Oh my, she's also got that little eyes in it.
That's so funny.
Yeah.
Then, here.
Mine fits right in, you guys.
It's like, it's like, we're, it's, it just fits perfectly
right in there.
Oh my gosh.
Huey!
Oh my gosh, Huey, thank you for the 50s.
I like the really, like...
The really...
Maybe if I...
Oh, I don't know.
I don't know.
I'll figure it out.
You should be on this boat!
Mitsumi no Yuika signature is the best.
Wait, which one is that one?
Oh.
Oh wait, there it is.
Wait, is it?
It's so cute.
Oh wait!
It has the high!
Oh my gosh, that's so cute.
That's so cute.
I'll show you guys too.
Like, look at that.
They're so crazy.
But, and then, of course, the kanji always, like, makes it
so much more.
See, that's why I was like, oh, you know, I can do, like,
stars or whatever in it, little circles.
Make, just dress it up a little bit.
I love, I love circular autographs.
Maybe because they look so...
um maybe because they look so nice on shikishi like you know
this this the the busyness like just shows up so well circ
yeah like a stamp yeah yeah it is very aesthetically
pleasing but with my name i don't really have any circles
which is why i would have to make the mint or the m like the
biggest circular part maybe unless i like circled my name
and wrote wrote it on the inside but
is there a kanji for mint maybe but but you could do minto
and have the o go all around oh you're cooking you're
cooking so like oh i do like having it like a butt m too
wait oh No.
Min-to.
Um, I-I-Round.
Thank you for the time, gift, and thank you.
Um, um.
Min-to.
Why can't I?
Why can't?
Min-to.
Just looks like I circled my name.
this is hard
well whatever i come up with you guys will see on the uh on
the postcards i suppose you guys will see on the postcards i
think oh my gosh it's already 10 30 I'm gonna head to bed.
I think I'm going to head out.
Tomorrow I have a Tomodachi life.
Tomodachi life, yeah, will create some crazy situations.
Last time I played, none of my people got married, so that's
the goal.
I wonder what's the most cursed pairing we can get.
I wonder.
Yes, yes, yes.
So Jamesman, thank you!
Thank you guys for enjoying this.
Well, maybe enjoying.
For hanging out with me and participating in this cursed
game.
Facade was so silly.
It's free, by the way.
If you ever want to try it out yourself, just like Google
it.
You can download it for free.
So it is free.
You can do it.
however you can be like oh I'm going to get the most cursed
combination ever
from divorced trying to get married oh my gosh we should
make them in in in Tomodachi life
hey mint it's me Piccolo did you know your initials are MF
MF signature hype thanks Piccolo what'd you just call me
Gonzalo Yeah Thank you guys for Hanging out with me until
the very end Really really appreciate it And Yeah I guess
I'll see you guys Later I'll see you guys tomorrow And Um
What's the meantime Oh.
Play, play, play me out.
Play me out.
Play me, play me out.
Play me out, play me out.
Play me out.
Thanks for the pink.
Since we have the Bustin Emo now, we can, you can use it.
You can use the Bustin Ozu Bustin.
What do you mean?
If there's something strange, sleeping in your bed.
Let me tell you something.
You can hear it, right?
Okay, yeah.
Ow!
Let me tell you something.
Busting makes me feel good.
Busting, busting, busting.
Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin
Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin Bustin
Bustin Bustin Bustin Yeah!
Bustum!
Makes me feel good!
Feel good!
Yeah!
Mm-mm!
Bustum!
Oh yeah yeah!
Oh!
Ha!
He who!
La la da da!
Yeah!
Feel good!
Freaky ghost made Freaky mess man Freaking McMahon baby Why
can't I remember Ow Ow ow ow Let me sleep in your bed Freaky
divorce baby
I ain't afraid of no art.
I ain't afraid of no painting.
An invisible bartender.
Freaky ghost bartender.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm afraid of no melon.
Mustin.
Drink water, everybody.
The super for the freaky ghost mermaid.
Thank you!
Thank you guys for all the donations!
Thank you for all the stream labs.
Thank you for all the thank you for all the donated, gifted.
Thank you for all the super chats.
Thank you for all the support.
You guys have been absolutely insane.
I'm a little overwhelmed.
Now I'm reevaluating.
Oh my god, stupid shark!
Thank you for the 10 gift and thank you.
Bustin, Bustin, Bustin, Bustin, Bustin, Bustin makes me feel
good, feel good, feel good, feel good.
Bustin makes me feel good.
Ah, Sumita!
Oh, we just happened.
It just went to the next song, sorry.
Bye-bye.
Thank you for watching.