I thought I was in stream or no, the brought studio mode.
That wouldn't make sense.
Oh my gosh.
I was just checking the sound.
I was making sure you could hear the...
I was making sure...
like the game was the game volume was on hi everybody
welcome to the for the do that's how i check the audio
um hello i am not in yet with everybody oh i need to set up
probably fugi too don't i oh wow wow wow wow my oh she's a
pervert you guys i saw what she was doing i saw i saw the
pictures that henya was taking she's playing bunny garden
she she just posted in the group thing she was like she's
like is she was like could you guys give me five minutes i'm
so sorry uh 8 15 that's so long i'm ready whenever
Takes one to no one.
Happy Friday.
Woo!
Yippee!
What was it?
Oh, sorry.
I'm a little unprepared, I think.
Log in with Discord.
Authorize.
Wait, how do I do this?
Oh, group.
And then don't look.
Don't look.
Said don't look.
Okay.
That should be good whenever I join.
Whenever I join the voice chat.
Hey, happy Friday.
What was that?
It's nothing.
I told you don't look.
I told you.
Let's see what the mods look like.
Not yet.
You must be patient.
Ducky, thank you for the gifted.
Also Spank, thank you earlier for the Dono and Drigos.
Thank you for the 10 gifted.
Wandering Taco, thank you for the 10 gifted.
Suk-sukku dragon, thank you for the 10 gifted.
Shino, thank you for the 20 gifted.
Hope I got everybody from earlier.
Hope I got everybody.
archive mods oh my gosh there were so many blue archive mods
so many um but unfortunately i do not have any this time um
maybe another time i think i picked some good ones though
this time i think how are you guys how how you good how how
was your week been did you um yo man let me get that burg
please it looks so good right you get the shrek tank at
least no i have it but i don't have it enabled because i
used the shrek tank last time you know what i gotta i gotta
do stuff that you guys aren't gonna expect okay um prepping
the ladies to destroy bricky who what destroy what is that a
character in this game carrie welcome the member Hello,
hello, hello, hello, happy Friday, hello, hello, hello,
hello, hello, anyone else watched The Amazing Digital
Circus?
Oh my gosh, I was like in the middle of the episode, and
then I was like, oh, I'm going to take a shower, and then I
took a shower, and then I was like, oh, I haven't watched
this week's, I'm so late, I didn't watch this week's Blue
Archive yet, so I watched that instead i watched that
instead but yeah the the digital circus came out uh like oh
my gosh when i saw it when i saw it it was insane i was like
it said it had come out 49 minutes ago and then it was
already at one million views so i don't even know what is it
at right now so i'm gonna let you know i've started to get
more mgs brain rot because of you and started streaming
metal gear recently Thank you!
Yippee!
1.5 and 2 hours.
That's crazy.
All the children are probably like, oh, digital circus!
You know?
Probably like, oh.
Thank you for waiting, Daio.
Wait, Hanya, who is your favorite girl?
Who is your favorite girl, Hanya?
a wonder yeah today i'm playing with henya matara and haruka
again we played last week we played hell divers 2 um which
oof man i'm so oof but um we are playing left for dead too
today yippee and i've got some silly mods all set up for you
guys you guys you guys so to download the solid snake mod I
I did but um I do not have it enabled hmm I know shocking
shocking I thought you said no mods yet when did I ever say
that when I ever say that?
Could I get an early happy birthday from Sultry Voice Minto?
Happy birthday, Mick Mac.
This is Sultry.
trying to think of something like something else to say but
um oh happy birthday mr president
don't look haruka it's
good don't look she was surprised about bunny garden Lin
Chan my Oshino waifu da yo Lin Chan so cute We have the same
We have the same bunny girl Yes sir No sir So if I minto
manchini moment What do you mean by that?
What do you mean by that?
Oh do the MGS 5 birthday song Congratulations!
Happy birthday, salutations!
Happy birthday, may your skies be blue!
Happy birthday to you!
Why are you clapping?
Because it's a song!
You clapping it, don't you?
don't you i love that i love that birthday song so much i
wonder but tara's not even looking at the chat is it safe to
stream this yeah i streamed on here streamed on youtube and
they didn't hate me i don't even think my stream got
demonetized which is so i mean well to be honest i didn't
get that bad that bad that far you know sometimes in bunny
girl the bunny garden game it gets like kind of you know
whoo but i think we i think we were good typical akiba
arcade clapper you shut up you shut the hell up uh shut how
dare you how that was the most offensive that was huh meat
mom you good in two minutes henya we're all good it's you
matara it's you we i i think we're all good matara
yeah oh my gosh it's already been almost 15 minutes whoa
whoa it's already been almost 15 minutes that's crazy oh she
said i have been ready and Matara started the call.
Okay, I'm going into the call, you guys.
I'll see you guys later, okay?
I'm going in.
I'm going in!
Ray, thank you for coming.
Hello?
Hiya!
Hello!
Oh my god, Mint, that is so embarrassing.
What?
That's so embarrassing.
I can't believe you did.
what did i do oh sorry am i am i the cringe oh gosh oh henya
did not like that no it's okay i was thinking about dean
chan me too honestly yeah have you all been playing that
bunny game that haruka bought yes i saw it okay sell the
game to me wait what okay you go into debt you give all your
money to bunny girls and then you can give them gifts you
give them like kuchi you give them you with a cue.
I gave them panties.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Oh yeah.
You can give lingerie.
Yeah.
You can take their picture.
It's like a dating sim.
But they take your money.
Yeah.
And you think you drink alcohol?
Yeah you drink alcohol.
And you can take a picture with them.
No, not with them, but you take a picture of girl.
Of, yeah.
And you can pick a post, what post you want her to do it.
Wait.
And stuff?
You can go on vacation with them.
Oh, that's what I'm trying to do.
Are we just going to glaze over the fact about giving
underwear to these women who are working?
It's a gift.
They like it.
The gift of lingerie.
Yeah, I like it.
So my favorite game in Yakuza Zero was the hostess game.
Oh, you'll love this then.
You'll love this.
You'll love it.
But people are going to know that I'm a pervert.
I don't want them to know that.
That's okay.
I don't want them to know that I'm a pervert.
it's a secret did you just said you were just now no no no
it's a secret nobody's gonna really know i'm like haha i'm
joking on how would they know how would they know how would
they know they're never gonna know they're never gonna know
how would they know they won't know what did i just buy a
game where i can give underwear to women yeah but they like
it you're a little firmer they love They love it.
Hentai.
No, no, Hentai.
It's called socializing.
I think I'm very good at getting good at socializing now.
It's so true.
Before this, I would be too scared to go to a bunny girl
bar.
But now I think I feel very confident.
I live there.
Oh my god.
So this is the socializing in 2024?
Yes.
Okay.
I think I'm learning a lot now.
Yeah.
Hanya and Min, since you played the game, who do you think
would be my favorite girl in the game?
I don't know, I haven't talked to anyone except Nianchan.
Nianchan bunny.
Nianchan is best girl.
Yes, Nianchan is my wife.
Yeah, wait, she's my wife, Hanya.
No, she's my wife, Hanya.
Hanya, I think you need to find...
Come on, Hanya.
She looked at me first, Hanya.
Hanya, come on.
Min, I thought we got married, and now you say your wife is
Hanya.
Wait, what did we get married?
He didn't know.
Wait, when did you guys get married?
What?
Why wasn't I there to help with the marriage?
I know we're married.
It's the husband and I are the best marriage.
I mean, it'd be white to him.
Yeah.
I now pronounce this.
I now pronounce this marriage.
Hikimori and death.
Hikimori.
Yeah.
You may now.
played the game because kissing is illegal you may now gift
lingerie to your girlfriend okay henna let's go and see
ninchan together yay yes everyone thanks for coming to this
collab uh it was very short sweet but everyone i'm gonna
play in this bunny game now so at the beginning that's the
three girls that you get in the game yeah yeah yeah i think
the little blue-haired one seems really cute she is very
cute but she's like everybody's cute yeah they're all cute
she's like the cool type she's like a oh i love cool women
oh maybe you're enjoying them yeah yeah yeah okay you have
her we'll have vince okay what about you how to of the three
girls on the picture is there one that like speaks to you
the most um i think the alcohol is speaking to me the one in
the middle do they all have breasts that big oh yeah yeah
everybody has a big boob yeah I didn't even realize about
the breasts I was staring at the ears when I had my panties
too don't worry yeah they'll show you panties yeah she
didn't see any of the women's I'd be like wow her butt is
jiggling while she's shooting the gun and Haruka was like
what I didn't even notice that look at her butt isn't it
huge I literally was just staring at the alcohol in their
hand as well as like That's an amazing alcoholic drink.
Yeah, there's a lot of alcohol in there.
I just got an alcohol, actually, my first alcohol of the
week.
Whoa!
They have a wine in the game.
Yeah.
Oh, I love wine.
No, I'm having a little bit of cognac.
I'm going to set up a game.
I like the fact that the short hair girl has like a gradient
black to blue in the tips of her hair.
Oh, yeah.
That's what I like.
I think that's so cute.
I like her hair a lot.
It's like my hair.
You like my hair?
It is actually kind of like your hair is white to blue so
it's sort of there.
Yeah.
Yeah, sort of.
But Nijan is the best.
Yeah.
Nijan is so cute.
You just got married and she's already replacing with a
virtual wife.
That's so sad.
That's kind of the reality of things, isn't it?
Yeah.
Nothing can beat too deep.
It's my life now.
Can you girls join off me?
Because I'm trying to invite you on my screen right now.
Oh, it keeps your name keeps like popping up.
I think it's like the games try to remind you I exist.
It keeps just saying it's like scrolling.
I'm like clicking Henya invite and mint.
Is it sending you the invite?
Oh, I just got one.
Nice.
Wait a minute.
I'm trying to play a game.
Is normal difficulty okay?
Harder?
I only played this game once for two hours.
Yeah, normal is good.
Normal good.
Yeah.
Good, good, good, good.
Wait, how do I?
I click my name.
I'm going.
Hold on.
I'm getting rid of steam.
You guys did get my invite, right?
Because I know meat is in here.
Yeah, I'm in.
Okay, awesome.
I'm excited.
Wait, is that a makeup?
I was burping, sorry.
Oh, it was actually very cute.
It's not.
Shut the fuck.
It was so cute.
I will literally strangle you with Rinchan's bunny ears.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, you're turning me on.
Wait, what?
I don't think you realize that.
Don't look, everybody!
I'm going to be Nick.
What people like that?
Hold on.
Yeah.
I think you crashed.
Oh, no.
Did the game really crash?
Yeah, hold on.
I'm reloading again.
Man, your laugh.
When I was in the loading screen, I thought that was part of
the game and I was severely freaked out.
Yeah, I was a little scared.
It's like a little girl laugh.
God, I hate...
I hate it so much.
Oh, come on.
You guys pick characters.
Oh, my God.
I still have the mods on.
So this is going to be fun.
I have my mods on too.
I'm so excited.
That's why I'm laughing.
For me, Fit, you pick Coco Kiru from Hololive on my end.
Oh!
Yeah.
I'm Woody.
Wait, like from the toy stories?
Nice!
That's so funny.
no we basically I'm participating in like this little
tournament for this game that a friend's organizing so I
figure I need to actually play the game before the
tournament oh yeah yeah I hope you have fun so Hennia is
going to be coach who should I be should I be Nick then yeah
whoever you want I'm just doing random if that's okay
whoever it gives me I'm gonna be Hennia wants you to be
coach please be coach Okay, I'm going to be coached then.
If there's four characters, I can be the other one.
I'll be Rochelle then.
Coachy, coachy.
You're the puffer fish lady from SpongeBob for me.
Hell yeah.
Oh, the driving school lady?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, my gosh, I'm so excited.
Let's go.
Prices aren't the only things getting slashed.
Oh.
Anything I need to know about the game?
My wallet's getting slashed.
Wait, is this your phone?
first time playing Matara.
I played like one time a few years ago, but I don't know if
it was this Left 4 Dead or Left 4 Dead 1, because I didn't
own this game.
So I don't know if I played this game or if I played the
pre- I own Left 4 Dead 1.
Okay.
Um, maybe it's a 1.
Just shoot.
Yeah, I figured.
Is there like melee?
Is there anything like special that I need to know?
I think this, the first level will kind of teach you the
controls.
Yeah.
I played this one.
We're in the hotel.
Yes, yes.
Right?
And then we go to the shopping mall oh you remember nice i
played this is the i played this exact like just one time a
one-time nice day is this loud enough because the game's
kind of loud for me is it chat how's the audio is it i think
i turned my down i turned my down like so much i think those
things are down there it's audio how do i switch how do i
switch from gun to axe or can I only pick one uh you can
pick a second you can pick a second weapon like oh wait oh I
guess you can only have the gun or the yeah it's only like
gun or yeah I'll pick the gun oh oh I'll pick the gun then
yeah it's not letting me have both the gun and the I guess
that's the you can pick a better like you can pick up
another gun later so if you want to get an axe for now or
yeah I think so axe or crowbar is better what do you all
think i got the axe crumble what was that line it's like
here comes johnny
oh my god it's so loud we just moved together yeah this game
is so loud i have to turn it down so much yeah
there's no killing teletubbies on my screen
is it normal that i keep thinking the blood on the screen is
mine but it's the zombies it makes it really hard to see
there's blood you might be able to turn it down a little bit
maybe i don't yeah i think i see so much blood oh oh wait oh
i'm so sorry oh it's not you it's the zombie
Sorry.
I'm just slashing.
It might be anyone to be honest.
It could be anyone.
All right.
I need...
You guys wait just a minute.
I need to turn off the blood.
Turn off the blood.
Okay.
How do I turn off this blood?
Oh, make sure you don't.
Oh, thank you for the magnum.
Me?
Here.
I didn't give that.
Oh, my God.
What's wrong with me?
Uh-oh.
It's on fire.
You should have saved that for like...
Yeah, right like this.
I'm coming.
I should have really saved this for this.
A bunch of people on fire.
Oh shit, I forgot about this one.
Is it our girls?
Are they on fire?
These girls are on fire.
Hunt!
Ha!
Yeah!
No!
Hunter has come.
How did you know we're coming?
I'm coming!
Hold on, I got you behind.
Behind, behind, behind.
Oh, sorry.
I keep forgetting if you get puked on it, we'll start a
horde.
It'll come towards you.
Oh no.
Oh my god.
Mint protected Matara Khan.
That's my girl.
Get out of my way.
I'm not trying to protect you at all.
Wait, I can't hold a katana and gun at the same time?
No, you can only have, like, one thing.
No way!
Uh-oh, it's all fiery down there.
So if I didn't use the axe, did I have less blood?
Because I cannot see anything.
I hate it.
Oh, sorry.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my health.
Sorry.
Sorry, I just saw Waluigi.
Waluigi.
Oh, my God.
Girls, if you see another weapon on the floor that is in a
gun, can you let me know?
Yeah.
How do I get down there?
Get adrenaline.
Should have grabbed the gun.
Should have could have would have.
What's this?
Got it.
Am I?
I got you, girl.
There you go.
Oh, who's getting Kenya?
I'm Kenya!
Oh my god, Kenya.
Anya, do you have a house with her, baby?
No!
Oh!
Haruka behind you!
I don't think you're doing so good, Henya.
Oh, Henya, I'm trying.
Henya, I'm gonna scoot close to you.
Oh, wait.
It's okay, Haruka me.
Haruka, thank you.
Oh, shit.
There's a big guy coming.
It's okay, he's on fire.
I need a bigger, I need a gun.
Oh, I'm on fire now too.
It's the thing season.
i need a big boy give me a big boy what are you talking
about oh you oh it's a song can you pick up uh henya there's
a there's a health pack here where are you and he's dead oh
yeah okay can i give you this health pack oh oh face rerun
away sorry i almost jumped out the window hold on i'm gonna
come over that way why i'm gonna heal you in a second i
don't know if you can we can we heal henya right no we have
to get her we have to get her at the safe house.
Haru, come to me, and I'm going to heal you.
Come, come, come here.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
But it's okay.
My team happy, Hanya happy.
Why is this fire still going?
Hanya, I'm so sorry.
Because it hates us.
You know, oh my god, oh my god.
Oh, we can rescue her, I see her.
Why are they only?
Oh my god.
Oh, she's always, she always gets hit.
Oh, my God.
I'm reloading.
No.
This is starting off good.
I think this is starting off real nice.
Shove them back.
All right.
Let's stick together.
Maybe.
And also, you know, I lost a lot of health from like, I
don't know, it was like PvP, you know, like, from team.
Like, you know, like.
Henya kept attacking you.
Why did you do that, Henya?
Wait, what?
Why were you attacking Mint?
No, no, no.
You gotta get good.
Not blaming on me, Nygote.
Alright, let's try this again.
Let's try to...
Just get good.
Stick together.
I am good.
I am great, actually.
Greatest of all time, as they say.
They say the same thing about me and Mango, actually.
Mango?
Yeah, he's a...
smash player and drinker he's a competitive smash player and
drinker he does both she's good to go get melee weapon also
girls there's drugs on the bed if you guys want some
otherwise i'm gonna do all of them oh yeah yeah yeah oh
before it's gonna start oh oh oh i'm coming i'm coming i'm
like exploded on me i I can't see anything...
Freaking boomers!
Oh, I'm icky, I'm icky.
I'm blind and icky.
Guys, I think the horde is coming.
Are they?
No, we're fine.
I don't know how to tell you all this.
I think the horde is coming.
We'll be fine.
All right.
When in doubt, more drugs.
You better watch out, you better watch out.
You better watch out.
Watch out!
Is there anything down here?
There's a lot
going on.
Wait, can I not hit him?
Oh, the bat is a little bit weaker.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, I got a defibrillator in case one of you you girlies
guys oh you dropped your health kit though so yeah i'm gonna
use it now and then i'm gonna grab the disabler oh there's a
pipe bomb harry if you want to take it okay it's okay i just
picked up the defibrillator for this exact issue i got you i
got you you better watch out you better watch out teamwork
tanya is gonna steal your wife who minecraft blocked me get
the fuck
Don't shoot teammates.
I'm not trying to.
Get on my way.
Oh shit.
You better watch out.
What's this?
Pills?
Uh oh.
For me, that's the Torah.
Help me!
Thank you, Henya.
My angel.
I shot him too!
Henya, my love, my angel.
My favorite small woman.
I don't know how other small woman I love than you.
That's what I saw.
Reloading.
spreading watch out oh yeah smoker smoker i'm here i'm here
oh thank you you better watch out oh come on where where's
the oh i can't see anything i'm sorry if i shoot you is this
a regular gameplay experience of this game yeah pretty i
can't see anything people are puking everywhere pretty
average if i say so myself oh what's the magnum pistol
scared the heck out of me it's a stronger is it good i got a
banana for me it's a banana yeah banana
better watch out toxic acid oh we gotta keep going yeah okay
from here yeah i think outside oh Sorry, I'm burning.
Ah!
Thank you, thank you!
Thank you!
I provide.
A room.
Nothing in it.
I'm saving your kamioshi?
Embarrassing.
Um, I am slow to press.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, um...
You're thinking about other women since you played that
bunny garden game.
That's true.
Rin-chan is, you know...
It's not easy.
Oh, shit.
Oh, shi-dari-dari!
Oh my god.
It takes so many.
He's on top of me.
Oh, you got him?
Oh.
Oh, nice exploding.
The boomer.
Good job.
Oh.
Nice.
Good job.
Over here, guys.
Which way?
This way?
Oh my god.
Okay.
I played like the one round of this game.
That's some sort of nightmare.
God damn zombie apocalypse.
Is melee or um.
Zombie apocalypse.
Weapons better.
Shit, shit.
Shit.
Depends on, I think, your play style, right?
Hmm.
But I think that axe is kind of...
My name's Alice.
Uh-oh, guys, I can't see well.
Amelia is saying that she's coach on my...
Guys, I think we're gonna die.
Oh, oh, oh.
What's happening?
I don't know.
Probably the door's open.
Just hoarding a little bit.
Oh, no.
Uh-oh.
Horse coming, guys.
Watch out.
Oh, my God.
Where are they?
Behind you!
Get out of here!
Charge!
Oh my god!
We won't die!
We won't!
Oh no!
Oh my gosh!
Who is who?
I don't know!
Just shoot!
Keep shooting!
Uh oh.
You got it.
There you go.
Over here.
Over this way?
Yeah.
I feel like voices are not loud and then the game is so
loud.
Hold on, hold on.
I can hear you.
I can hear you, Mata.
Oh, thank you.
Hold on.
Oh my god, they're all on fire!
Oh.
Oh my god, Mick, your kamioshi is healing me.
Thank you, Henya.
A sweet kiss from a maiden has awoken my spirits.
this bomb at you i feel so awake after a sweet kiss from my
love huh oh over here guys thank you thank you over here
over here of course thank you thank you oh my goodness meant
it was the best kiss ever yeah i bet a kiss oh my god
with your big it was the worst time for me to reload oh my
god i can't see anything i cannot see anything either that's
okay over here oh hey get off of me oh oh my god this way
wait this way oh my god how do we play this this is so
stressful over here yeah it's over here hello oh hello there
you go now we're here oh my god okay well fight finally
start a pipe bomb pipe bomb Pipe bomb!
Alright guys, I'm gonna throw a big bomb, be careful!
Oh, you already did.
Never mind, you beat me to it.
Never mind.
She said, oh my gosh.
She said I'm throwing a pipe bomb.
The safe room.
Wait, what is the bile?
Safe room!
Come here!
Yay!
Safe room time!
Here they come!
What do you mean here they come?
Let's go!
Good job girls!
Yippee!
oh my gosh look at you melee queen 74 oh my lord i do what i
do when i do what i do i do i'm the only one that kills
people with a melee weapon yeah get better weapons soon
hopefully yeah i think i'm gonna switch the melee back again
switch the melee again good also let's heal right what is
this no we can heal here yeah yeah i'll get the shot yeah
i'm gonna i'm gonna I'm gonna carry a defibrillator just in
case one of us dies.
Oh, I already have...
Sorry.
You guys are healing.
It does the California girls dance for me.
Yeah.
Wait, are you for real?
Is it?
Yeah.
Is there no melee weapons here, by the way?
No, there is.
Do you guys see a melee weapon, by the way?
So this gun is a cat for me.
Cat?
Oh, you have the cat mod.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a cat.
So when have I shoot it?
Oh, thank you everybody.
There's a heart.
I've popped out of the car.
What?
That's cute.
What about this one?
Wait, I don't see it.
A shotgun.
Just a regular shotgun.
Oh, okay.
I see from my side.
That's cool.
I should do the mods next time.
I don't know if I should bring the shotgun or the can.
They're really easy to use too.
Oh, really?
Yeah, it's really easy too.
I'm gonna bring the shotty.
Yeah, I got a shotgun too.
Ready?
Oh, here's one guy's cop.
Oh my god, hello?
Oh shit, try to close it.
I'm ready bitch!
Oh, sorry!
What you up?
Oh my god, please.
I'm like missing, I'm always missing like an inch or two.
I feel like I keep thinking that I'm just like an inch or
two longer than I really am.
Jeez.
Get off of me.
I hate that.
Does that ever happen to anybody else?
What is it?
Now you're your primary.
I'm a little longer than I am.
But your pistol won't happen.
You're pretty long on my stream.
Oh, I don't want my little longer.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, please.
I'm reloading.
I'm sorry.
Oh shit, I need help.
I need help.
Thank you, Haruka.
My queen.
Alright, so your primary gun will have ammo, but your
secondary gun, like your pistol will have infinite ammo.
want to do i don't want to go oh my gosh oh my god this is
so jarring this gameplay why so it's like shaking my whole
screen is something over here no am i going crazy thank you
for playing this with me i am having the time of my life
it's a little crazy it is it's a little sorry yeah but it's
fun oh there's a grenade launcher here if anyone wants it
little grenade They didn't get it.
Not me.
Alright, I can't wait to bring up this Pepsi gun.
The craziest thing is, like, how much the game shakes when
you're trying to do anything is just so fast.
It is very, it's a super fast, fast pace game.
So fast.
Yeah.
Which way do we go?
It's like, I heard a crying player.
Oh, no.
It's a witch.
Uh-oh.
Start up.
Ah!
Oh!
Oh, I'm trying to kill her.
Oh, my God.
Oh, you got her.
I got her.
Oh, sorry.
I didn't realize that.
So the witch, if you wake her up, she'll scream and alert
every single zombie round.
Yeah, it's kind of not great.
Oh, it's a zombie around too.
Apologize, but I've also never played those before.
Oh, gosh.
Wait, did you kill him?
Here, hold on.
Matara, let me heal you.
Let me heal you.
Yeah, I'm here to let you know what every zombie does.
My maid.
Can I get a moa and my...
Oh my gosh, it's so funny.
My thing is...
Wow.
Yeah, don't worry, Mug.
I'm here to tell you how...
Wait, is it this way?
I think.
Let go.
Oh, God, this is better.
It's nice.
Didn't even Moe Moe Q and me while she healed me.
But!
Ow!
It's out for the owl!
Unbelievable.
Okay, Hanya.
Oh, no, we need more health.
We have to...
I think we have to go down here.
It's okay.
We'll get more health soon.
Down here?
The hat is so tall.
Haruka, you're Doug Dimmodome with a really huge hat.
Doug Dimmodome, Dimmodome, Dimmodome, Dimmodome.
Oh my gosh.
Yeah, you got a really tall hat on.
Oh my god, I'm not hitting anyone!
Oh, I gotta heal myself.
Oh, hunter, hunter.
Oh, sorry.
You guys got this.
Thank you.
What is this?
Oh, I got it.
I got it.
I got pills here.
Pills here.
No, that's a grenade.
So the bile will damage the enemies, right?
If I throw it.
Hold on.
I want to.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I think they know they gather to it.
So they all like.
Oh, perfect.
So it's easier to.
Oh, nice.
How do you got?
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah, they really.
So it's like a.
It really, really loud.
It came from above.
Get chainsaw.
Oh, my God.
Where?
Oh, do you want it?
Right here, right here.
Do you want it?
It can have it.
It has gas though, I'm pretty sure.
Gas, gas, gas.
I'm gonna step on the gas.
Turned I fly.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna step on the gas.
Oh, this is.
Oh.
That's what I have.
Do you like my car?
My car.
behind behind behind you got it you got it you're good
you're good i'm hearing a toad nearby oh what's that noises
oh there's one there's a guy here mother they come from
everywhere where do we go oh up here listen mothers need
love too sometimes oh my goodness
No worries.
Oh my goodness.
Meanwhile, getting eaten by a zombie?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Okay.
Oh, don't blow that up.
Okay, wait, wait.
What if I open it and then I throw that in?
Oh, I hear something.
Hear something icky.
Careful, careful.
Oh, I can't see anything!
Oh my gosh.
Oh, oopsies.
Yay!
Oh, I can't see!
Oh no!
Up these stairs.
Up the stairs?
Oh my.
Okay.
Oh, pipe bomb, pipe bomb, pipe bomb.
Watch out.
Good job.
Oh, it's all on fire though.
Here, you go.
It'll pass.
You go.
Matara, you go.
The fire.
Yeah, you go.
Actually, I'm gonna use this.
Give me fire!
What is this?
Pills here.
Oh, pills for health.
What's this one?
Is this a shotgun?
Oh, sniper!
Oh!
Sniper!
Sniper.
My beloved.
I have some ammo on my hand as well if we need.
Uh oh.
Watch out.
The spitter is a...
Ah!
Gross.
I need help.
Peace.
Oh, my aim.
Oh, my God.
Yikes.
Thank you.
God, I love a little gun.
The little gun that could, you know?
Do we go down or do we go up?
Oh, I think we go down.
Do you go down?
Okay.
The little gun that could, you know?
Wait, wait.
There's fall damage, by the way.
Do not do what I just did.
Oh, there's fall damage?
No way.
Yep.
Oh, I did not.
There's a fall damage.
Yep.
Oh, there's a little blower?
Over here, you guys.
A little blower.
Well, he like blows bile, you know?
Bio-hazado.
Whoa!
Look at you guys.
I'm hearing Peter Griffin.
I think the boomer's nearby.
Peter Griffin?
Wait, well, you gotta go up, I think, right?
Stop saying the boomer, okay?
I'm old, I know, but I'm really offended.
I Can't see you stop saying the boomer I can't see it Oh,
sorry Wow,
wow, wow, wow Wow, wow Don't shoot teammates, where was that
teammate?
Oh, fuck, sorry.
I just shot a teammate.
Go in there Go in there, go in there Oh, I'm stuck Oh, oh My
goodness rag doll maybe the sniper's not so even so fast
maybe the sniper's not so great i gotta be far away though
girls how come there's like no med kits every anywhere oh
you say there's a town nearby a who i'm hearing a guy who
like hugs your face oh i got you Jockey!
Yes, they're called Jockey.
I like them with your face.
I thought you said toad from Mario.
Mario.
Yeah, the Jockey is toad for me.
Oh!
Hold on, girls.
I got a little Molotov cocktail for our enemies.
There's another one in the room if you girls want to throw
another one too.
Oh, good.
Oh.
Oh, well, that was a little.
Hold on.
Let me get the other- That was anticlimactic.
Oh, shut up.
Let me get another Molotov.
Hold on.
Oh!
Oh my god!
You killed it with the fire!
So, whoever was saying I was anti-climatic, huh?
I was fully climatic.
It was actually pretty good.
I actually hit the climax.
Oh my god.
Oh my god!
Oh my god, Chota, Chota, Chota!
Chota, Chota, Chota!
You have to pick me up your seat.
No!
You guys are okay!
Chona's behind us.
Oh, I did it!
I did it!
Back up, back up!
Why did you set us on fire?
Oh my god.
Why did this...
Fire!
Why did you set us on fire, my dad?
Okay, I'm coming.
Did I get you adrenaline?
Into the ring of fire.
I hate you so much.
Down, down, down.
I'm gonna... Wait!
I lost my Molotov because of you!
No way!
You actually hit it on the enemy.
You like hit it on this I didn't use it.
Oh, I need a health pack.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'll heal you.
I need the... I need you.
Mint also has one.
There's a bunch.
I'll give you mine.
Hania, you also need one.
I want to heal.
Okay.
I'll hold on to it.
Alright, everybody.
I need your help.
Oh, I got you.
Come here.
Now come here.
Hold on.
I need Chad's help for a good gun.
Is this the AK-47?
What?
What's a good gun?
What's this one?
Laser sight.
Okay, perfect.
So apparently this gun at the end here, oh, AK rifle with
the laser sight is really good.
I don't know what this one, but I would take it.
This is good.
Which one's the AK?
This one, this one at the end, at the end.
Thank you, everybody.
This one at the end here?
Okay, I'm going to get a combat shotgun.
Also, is the golf club good?
Or...
Should I switch to the...
I like my grenade launcher so far.
I'll keep it.
Yeah, I like shotgun.
Oh, yeah.
I want this.
Jeez, I made you with the shotgun timing till the war's
done.
I won't let you through the barricade until I get it.
What does he want?
I can't... Oh, the snacks.
We need a code.
I want the snacks too.
You better not try to whiz a lot of this.
We gotta go to the store and get some snacks for this guy.
Yay, corn!
I love snacks.
I love corn.
Wow, she really is your Kamioshi.
Let's get corn!
Mid, you don't understand, Hanyar.
How much Mith loves.
Okay, wait, where are they coming from?
From the store?
Everywhere.
They're coming from everywhere.
Uh-oh.
Oh.
Grenade, where?
I got it!
Okay, we gotta escort the cart.
Let's go follow me, Hanyar.
Oh my god.
Ah!
Thanks I guess.
We have to bring the cola back to the gun owner.
Oh!
Ah!
I got you.
I got you!
Ah!
Got the cola!
You got the Coca Cola!
Protect the princess!
Oh my gosh.
Oh, Haruka, are you okay?
I should be fine here.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, sorry, Haruka, I almost shot you.
I have no idea what's going on by the way.
Sorry, I'm being quiet.
Oh my gosh!
I'm dying!
I'm gonna help you up in just one minute.
I got you, I got you!
Oh wait!
Matara!
Matara, kill the guy that's...
Okay, thank you.
Hey, watch out!
Better watch out!
Watch out!
You better watch out!
I was like...
I'm gonna throw him on!
I think I drank him!
Oh my god.
Where did I go?
Ah!
Did you drink the cola?
I drank her!
Oh no!
We have to help Hania, we have to save Hania.
Hania!
Oh, what are you being dragged by?
I don't see him!
Wait, where is the smoker?
Oh, he's up here!
He's on the roof!
I'm gonna die!
I got him!
Someone got him!
What the hell was that?
Thank you!
I'm going into the store to see if there's anything to find,
okay?
Just because, uh...
No, we have to deliver the cola.
Yeah, we gotta deliver the coke.
Was there nothing in the store else?
No, I'm delivering the coke already.
Oh, you can shoot the tongue too?
Oh, okay.
Thank you, thank you.
Oh!
I like what people are saying, shoot the tongue.
I've never played the game before, y'all.
I have no idea what to do.
My base.
I'm coming.
I'm throwing my darn base.
Oh god.
I got the I got the cola Going going I
throw the bomb.
I throw the bomb the cola.
Careful girls.
Oh my god.
I'm still here.
But no, what the fuck?
But I saved you didn't I?
No, I mean you did but now but I saved you didn't I But I
helped didn't I?
What happened?
You're alive, aren't you?
Whoa, what just happened?
I've played this so many times now.
I can't even remember what's going on.
I thought you'd be a little bit better.
Oh my god.
Oh, why did I jump into it?
Help me!
My point's sad.
I wanted to feel alive, okay?
I wanted to feel this.
I said what I said.
We're all done.
Okay, I haven't played this in like three years, so you have
to give me like a little bit of a actually no it's been less
than that just kidding
oh there we go there is not enough health packs in this game
we need more health packs i'm dying that's the that's the
that's the left for dead feeling i i am like shocked by this
game always feeling like you're dying oh watch out there's a
did it get the spitter i got the spitter it's her i think we
have to go back no i can't remember sorry i shot you oh you
shoot me girl i'm gonna die we're all being so close to
death actually it's it's so quite oh we're going backwards
oh we're going backwards oh okay it's actually concerning
how close we are to death all four of us honestly me every
day Uh-oh, I hear you.
Me every day.
I hear you.
I can't even run.
It's me.
It's my tummy.
It's grumbling.
Can we go in?
Let us in.
Oh, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys.
Help me, help me back, back, back.
Okay, never mind.
You got them.
I'm good.
Didn't even need y'all's help.
Oh, go back to the market?
The market?
What do I hear?
Zombie shooter, your boy.
Oh, ouch.
And my boy.
Am I missing these, like, point one?
blank shots what's going on what's wrong with our is your
your age is slowing you down I think so yeah oh my gosh I
can't even I can't even run I'm so slow golf club I only
have one HP let me too yeah we're all like right about to
die yeah grabbing a shot
oh wait i have a health kit who needs no i don't i don't i
don't i thought i did my bad jocky jocky is dead it's gone
sorry it's because i saw the yeah i don't have a health kit
my bad you're bad yeah you're bad wait where do we go you
guys are you okay how do we're coming we're on normal
difficulty if anyone's not wondering any if anyone's normal
if anyone's normal i'm going to die i got you i got you i'm
right here no i got rid of come here princess get up one
kiss from your true love
you have like four hp this way oh okay okay are we gonna
make it oh of course we're gonna die another day as madonna
once said i'm gonna die another day i'm gonna die i died
what edya how i need a dog okay am i the one growling oh is
it you are you i don't know there's like somebody growling
it's kind of sexy I don't know if it's you growling it's
definitely not hold on hold on hey shut up Thanos here
Thanos oh fuck where I think the boss is Thanos for me it's
Metal Gear Ray it's Metal Gear Ray for you I'm just
constricted I'm dying right now I'm dying I'm dying I'm
dying I'm dying I'm Wait, how am I not able to save you?
Hold on.
I am down.
I saved you.
You're fine.
No, I'm not.
I'm dead.
I'm shooting like some mini boss guy.
Hanya, are you okay?
I'm dead.
Yeah, me too.
Where, where, where?
I have a defibrillator.
No, they're promoted.
Yeah, we're permanent.
Go to the safe house and we'll be revived.
Okay, perfect.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You can make it.
Hold on.
Let's see if there's health with here, Haru.
You're close.
We're close.
Might as well just go.
Yeah, just go.
Just go.
Go, just go.
It's almost there.
Okay.
Look at that.
I'm hearing toad.
You're pulling the pile?
Oh, there's a spitter right there.
Nice.
Oh.
Saw someone jump over.
Nice.
Is this the safe room?
This is the safe room.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Oh, good job.
what is this game left for dead yeah this is left for dead i
don't understand anything yeah i think i'm too old my brain
i'm like i don't understand what's going on it's it's a lot
it's a lot like it's fun it is so fun though but it's really
fun i definitely could play this again wait what's this one
i'm gonna keep my here somewhere is this gonna be around
here somewhere this isn't what i have before tactical
somebody said i'm pointing and clicking on heads i'm not i'm
just pointing towards where the zombie is sort of i don't
think i'm clicking on any heads out of these three what's
the best one what's this one i'll get that i'll get this one
oh no i lost my laser pointer very cute oh my god is that a
scratch mark on your chest yeah yeah it is Yummy, yummy,
yummy.
Yum, yum, yum.
I got it from, um, when I was a kid, I was playing, I was
playing Teletubbies and now I'm here to kill Teletubbies.
Hey, Mrs. Puff, get out of my way.
What?
I Teletubbies scratched me when I was a kid.
Oh my god!
Ah, hold on to the door!
Oh my god.
Oh wait, I can use my pipe bomb.
Wait, where did I pipe bomb go?
Oh no, I don't think we need to.
There's, like, not that many.
Oh, okay.
Oh, maybe there is a lot.
You can use your...
No, we're not.
right here though
the scary thing about using a scope in this game is you
can't see anything like yeah you can't really you can't aim
it's hard to use a scope in this yeah because it's too fast
oh you're fine you're fine oh i'm sorry i'm being kind of
quiet i really just have to focus i can't Yeah, me too.
I'm playing with you.
It's okay.
Did you hit me?
I did it by accident, but you also deserved it, you bitch.
What the?
I'm gonna get you for that with this golf club.
I challenge you.
He hit me.
Punch me in the throat.
Punch me like you mean it.
I think he's nearby.
Toad.
Who is a jocky?
A jocky.
Toad is the jocky for me.
Oh, yeah, jocky, jocky, jocky.
Oh, that's a mannequin.
Get the mannequin.
There it is.
Oh, you got him.
Good job.
Can I go back in the safe room and reload or is that
cheesing?
You can go, I'm thinking.
You can.
Oh, spitter, spitter, spitter.
I'll go with Thanos!
I'm hearing Thanos music!
He's spitter!
Oh, I see him!
I see him!
Cute girls yelling, Tascaru.
Oh my God, he's throwing.
Oh, I just made that shot.
None!
Why am I taking so long for reload?
Hello?
Might be the gun you have.
Oh, boy.
Oh, my God.
He's down?
Whee!
i think i killed him is someone on me no is someone shooting
me i'm so glad i have that as the fanos because like when
that boss comes in i'm hearing the fanos theme oh and he's
just running around throwing it's so epic what is the fanos
theme revered to reload whoa i was like i think it's also
because i switched weapons so it like restarted the reload
animation i have metal gear ray as the tank oh you really
that's so funny it's the tank nice i'm the vanilla one
You're Ray, my beloved!
I know, me too.
Get the Molotov.
For me, the spitter is Waluigi, which I thought was funny.
And then the fucking...
How do I get that?
The Waluigi cart song plays when he arrives every time
it's...
That is funny.
I have a pipe bomb.
We can, um...
We can coordinate our pipe bombs and stuff, I think.
Oh, another one, another one!
Fuck, I need help, I need help!
I'm joined!
Uh, you're just reloading.
I always reloaded the worst time.
Oh!
Big guy, big boy Nice, nice, nice The Charger is Shrek for
me which is funny That is funny Oh, they're coming, they're
coming Oh, I should get a mod I should get a mod Yeah, all
you do is like you just like Subscribe like it's It's soyyy
Yeah Isn't it like workshop Yeah, yeah, yeah Yes, yeah Oh,
wait, I'm just trying I'm so easy Reloading Reloading Linlla
So you're just murdering teletubbies?
I killed him.
Oh, I hear a voice?
I hear a sound?
I hear a voice.
Take your meds.
What's happening?
Oh, my, my, my.
Sorry, sorry.
I'm hearing voices in my head.
Is it this way?
I don't know, actually.
Oh, replace your low ammo.
Here?
Okay.
Oh, this fully low key.
Low load.
It's here.
Oh, crying girls around.
Yeah, I just, they just said.
So there's a witch.
There's a witch somewhere.
So how does the witch work?
I think you have to kill her.
Oh, fine.
She gets alerted, right?
Can you, can you ignore it?
Can you get her out of her?
I think you have to kill her before she gets alerted, or you
have to sneak by.
I can't.
Yeah, you can sneak by.
I don't hear her.
I hear her.
Yeah, I can hear her.
I would say, but aren't the bullets going to alert her?
Just sneak around the witch because she'll...
Oh, oh, I ain't being fine.
I got him.
Oh, ow, John.
Oh, guys, I'm going to throw a pipe bomb.
Dude, dude, dude, dude.
Uh-oh.
I got him.
Nice, nice.
Oh, you saved me.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
Reloading.
I have 11 bullets left.
If anybody sees ammo, let me know.
Let's look around.
Oh, vile, vile.
Vile, spitter, spitter, spitter, spitter, spitty.
Wait, where is he?
Did they switch to your pistol matta because that's has I
don't have a pistol.
I have a katana.
Do you want me to sit or heal you?
Yes, please.
I am dying.
There's bathrooms and stuff.
I'm gonna check in them.
Oh, guys, there's ammo here.
There's ammo in the men's bathroom.
Thank you, Meant.
You're better than Rin, Sean.
Any day.
Whoever she is.
Ammo in the men's bathroom, girls, if you want.
Men's bathroom?
Well, I want it.
Yeah, men's bathroom.
The other one.
The other men's bathroom.
Oh, well, is there no one in the ladies' restrooms?
This one?
I can't see in here.
Amma!
Oh my god.
I just looked.
Wait, what?
Are you okay?
I heard something.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, big boy.
Oh, big boy.
Oh, sorry if I shot you.
Ah, P.C.'s done.
Oh, my god.
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
The smoker is Ronald McDonald for me.
Oh, it's me.
Hold on, hold on.
Can we take, like, one second before we advance because my
eyes in the dark with the light.
Oh my god.
Are you okay?
Are you okay, Mrs. Puff?
I'm old.
Oh, are you okay?
I'm so old.
Stop calling me Mrs. Puff.
It's like taking me out, please.
You have to stop.
That's what you are.
You're Mrs. Puff with the skinny legs.
What about me?
What am I?
You're Garfield.
Oh, Garfield.
The cat.
Yeah.
Alright.
Oh.
I still hear.
I'm actually... Here, come out of the dark.
Come out of the darkness.
We gotta go upstairs anyway, so...
Out of the darkness!
Into the dark cloud!
Oh, there's the witch!
There's the witch!
Oh, shit!
Oh!
I'm sorry!
No!
I can't find...
It's so much right here at the elevator!
Even at the elevator!
Ah!
Yeah!
I'm pinned!
Help me!
Oh, fuck, I also am pinned.
I'm also impinned!
I also impinned!
Help!
I'm gonna die!
I'm dead!
What?
I'm dead.
No, no!
How is this game on normal?
It's so hard on normal.
We saved me, Daew!
We gotta go.
I can barely walk.
Is there no health kit?
Oh, health kit.
Yeah, I think Mint or Haru should take it.
You guys have less HP than me.
I think Haru carries better than I do.
Let me die.
But you're limping, though.
It's okay.
Whatever you want.
Haru, I'm not against you taking it, because I think
you're...
She's healing.
I can tell.
Sorry.
Do you like my dance moves, man?
Oh!
You good?
Oh, oh!
Oh, my God.
You okay?
Oh, he was right behind me.
Oh,
I'm down again.
I'm down, I'm down, I'm down.
Oh, I'm down, down, down, down, down, down,
down, down, down, down, down, down.
I love you.
We sing.
Hania, this was actually amazing.
Could you please keep singing?
You're welcome.
Such a big buff to me.
I have first aid needed.
Next knockdown means death.
Oh, flesh.
I'm dead, dead, dead.
Hold on, there's like healing, there might be healing kids
here, girls.
Can you come with me real quick?
Oh, there might be healing kids here.
I'm headshotting some zombos, which were teletopies in my
vision.
I can't see anything.
Everything's black and white.
I also can't see anything.
I'm like a dog.
Oh, boomer has vomited.
Boomer, boomer.
Uh oh, he's, oh, there's a charger coming.
I'll hide it behind you.
Nice.
Oh, good job, good job.
Oh, sorry.
Oh my God, did I do that?
It's okay.
I need two help, so don't worry.
Oh, don't I do that.
Hold on.
Hold on, I got you.
I got you.
What?
How are we a zombie zombie?
How do you have like full health?
How does that happen?
It really comes out.
Uh oh.
I have a... I have...
Oh my god.
Finally I'm held.
I'm in the loving embrace of a man.
Thank you.
I'm gonna throw a...
I'm dead.
I got killed by Haruka!
I'm so sorry!
I am so so sorry.
I love you.
This is the worst game I've ever played.
I'm struggling so much.
You've just been laying here this whole time.
I'm going to check my music real quick.
Yay, I'm back.
Guys, this was rough.
This was rough.
Oh, I tried.
That was hard.
I'm going to try.
oh man that was crazy you know what else is crazy dumb rats
in the room amen
i was crazy once he locked me in the room the rats the rats
made me crazy rats rats rats rats we are the rats rats we
are the rats let's clear some stuff out a little bit before
we open the door this time.
You guys are...
Guys, there's a little help kit I'm missing, by the way,
here.
There's one more help kit if one of you wants to...
Oh, I didn't grab it.
I didn't grab it.
That's mine.
Grab it so we can, like, not...
Let me reload my ammo.
Where do we...
Which way do we go, actually?
Where do we go now?
Are we just going from one song to the next?
Did I hit you, Hanja?
I don't think I...
I don't know.
I'm getting hit a lot, so you should be fine.
Okay.
It might be me.
It might not be me.
It might be anybody.
It's a zombie.
Fuck you, Lala!
It's up the stairs.
Up the stairs.
That's where we had to go.
I'm going around people.
I remember back in the old days.
They're the one who scratched my chest when I was a kid.
You're dead.
Lala.
I'm on the Henya Protection Squad.
Oh, Henya, was there Teletubbies in Japan?
No.
I think I never really watched I don't know, but I think But
it wasn't that popular I guess Really?
I don't know Maybe my chat in JP Bros.
knows about Teletabees I'm not sure The JP Bros.
I love that The JP what?
JP Bros.
Like brothers?
Yeah.
I call them JP Bros.
We go downstairs, don't we?
Hold on, I'm gonna throw a Molotov there.
Huggy.
JP Oni-chan.
That's so funny.
Maybe Yonita!
Or do you guys.
How do you guys?
Ah!
Help me!
Oh, there's a snake on my boot!
Oh my god.
I have had it with these wonderful breasts.
On her motherfucking breasts!
That's my snake in my boot.
Oh, you said boots.
I thought you said breasts.
I'm so sorry.
Why would I say breasts?
I genuinely was like, that is so weird that she said.
dress but why would i do that i think i'm a yes ad person
i'm an improv child if that is what mint decides to be that
is what mint decides to be i know it's a little late you
guys but how's the how is the audio
it might be a little late is it audio is it audio is it okay
behind no no i get him I hear it!
I hear him!
You hear Ray?
Ow!
Oh my gosh.
Get off of me.
Stop!
The shooting!
My dog's out too!
Nice gun!
Nice one!
I'm out of ammo on like all my guns so I'm gonna, um, I'm
just gonna die I guess.
Uh oh.
I guess I'll just die!
Where's more ammo?
Oh where's the- in the bathrooms nearby remember yeah we're
about to hit the ammo was it here i think it was this way i
think it was down here oh my god i guess i'll just die i
guess i'll just die is it this one oh there's a pipe bomber
in here if anybody wants it guys they're about to all come
in through this side um there's no ammo in here there's just
a knife there was ammo in the bathroom in the men's bathroom
remember maybe we were just there maybe it's in the girl's
bathroom this time maybe it's the girls guys I need I need
help there's a charger I guess I'll get the knife since I
have nothing I'll die yeah I got a poopy knife stinky poopy
I can't just reload the banana every time I'm like a new
banana in it and the peel what was that song that like all
the ba ba ba ba ba banana oh oh oh
well we go upstairs don't we go upstairs here yeah i think
so upstairs here oh who's coughing like that are you okay me
sorry oh i had a cigar okay i'm also out of ammo let's go
let's look around and see if we can find out There is a gun
here mint if you need it's a chrome shotgun.
Oh, I'll get the shotgun Thank you behind behind fucking
charger charger Fucking trick
Through here.
Oh, we're doing better than previously.
That's good.
Okay.
Okay There might be a really What is it?
Oh, I got a defibrillator.
Oh another head.
I think Ken you should have it because she's dying Boomer.
Boomer?
We got him.
Oh.
Sorry, Peter, Gryphon, but you have to die.
Oh, one.
Oh, go!
Thank you.
Hello.
Oh, let me one hit these guys.
Actually, I'm going to use this one.
Let me one shot.
Guys, there's a little bomb there.
There's like a little bomb there if you have an empty item.
I got it.
I'll use it.
Guys, a lot of zombies.
A lot of zombies.
Sorry if I shot you.
Wow.
A zombie, zombie.
In here?
Can you button me?
Do we have anything inside here?
Oh, ammo!
There's an ammo here!
Oh my god, girly.
Where are they?
Oh, um.
Uh, I'm reloading, sorry.
I didn't notice.
Are you guys with health, by the way?
Because I have one extra health pack in my inventory.
I have pills, so I'm going to take them.
Okay.
Take your medication.
I'm taking my medication, and I got the defibrillator.
Is that a katana?
yeah no that's a good oh there's a first aid place as well
here oh it's just for pills oh no the pills are good oh I
need pills for now there's a guy behind the door there's a
lot there's a lot I'm gonna throw a bomb
okay it kind of worked though they all came inside yeah kind
of worked out so all right guys so we There's another bomb
in here We have what?
We have to disarm the We have to go to Thirdborn though It's
gonna be just so endless Or just You have to go to the
Endless No We should just run Yeah just run Alright I'm
pulling I'm backing you up Haruka I'm behind you I'm
shooting the guys Behind you It'll come behind you I'm
shooting the guys behind you Depp Oh
I'm behind
Oh I'm backing you from behind Haru.
Don't worry.
Watch out for the smoker.
Okay, KK.
How are you guys already on the third floor?
Did you kill it?
Wait, how the heck you guys already on the third floor?
Haruka, I got you.
I got you.
I'm behind you.
Keep going.
Oh, there's fire.
There's fire.
Don't worry.
Just keep running.
I'm covering you from behind.
You did it.
I went the wrong way.
No, no, no.
I'm doing my best.
I'm gonna die!
We're coming!
Haruka, I need a second and I can revive you.
I don't think, I don't know if I can revive you.
You have like a heart on you.
Hold on, we're coming, we're coming, we're coming!
Girls, I need to revive, Haruka, while I'm shooting, please.
Oh my, there's vial, watch out, watch out, watch out, watch
out!
Oh gosh.
Fuck.
Oh God, are you both down?
Wait, what?
There's one of you out there, the deflator?
Oh!
I have it!
I have the defibrillator!
Saber, Saber, Mint, I'm healing you while this is happening.
Wait, how do I use it?
I'm gonna do it!
Oh, I'm using it!
I'm using it!
Yeah, get it, get it, get it!
Mint, mint, mint, stop, stop, stop, mint!
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop moving.
Oh, thank you.
I need your help!
No, Matara!
Matara, you need more help than I do!
It's okay, it's okay, go, go, go, go!
No!
Matara!
Wait, where am I?
Is my gun gone?
Yeah, go pick it up, maybe.
There's a med kit here!
I mean, so much just my gun, but that's fine.
I'll take this cap.
Oh, I don't.
Oh, maybe I took your gun by accident.
Shit.
Wait, actually, how do...
I think I accidentally took your gun.
That's okay.
Do you want the cap?
No, no, I want...
Can we switch?
Uh, how do I drop the gun?
Charger around.
Get ready.
Where's the charger?
How do we drop the gun?
Oh, watch out!
Sorry if I shot you.
I'm assuming you had this gun in my hand, I'm assuming.
Hold on.
Let me accidentally pick up another gun.
Let's see if that works.
Did I steal your...
I didn't pick up a gun yet.
Oh, I think I accidentally took your gun because I was
pressing E.
Wait, how do I...
Hold on, hold on.
How do I drop it?
Okay.
There's a gun.
Take the other one.
Where's my gun?
There we go.
Wait, she's behind me!
Guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys.
Oh.
Uh?
Okay, wait.
Did somebody drop my gun?
Is this...
This wasn't my gun.
I had like a laser scope...
There you go.
That's the laser scope one.
Oh, heyna, heyna.
Guys!
Thank you, little child.
everybody's guys apparently it's okay well i picked up the
one that was on the floor and it was yours i think you
dropped it because you thought it was uh maybe maybe yeah
who helped oh my god everything hurts this game is crazy
nice shot you want to stop playing then or do you want to
keep going yeah you're gonna be aren't you in a tournament
for this yeah i am are you gonna be okay the teams are super
unbalanced like the the flesh team is so strong they have
people who have been content creators for this game but it's
also not a real tournament it's like a friend tournament oh
okay oh oh she's alive oh she's dead i got you oh i'm good
i'm good reviving nice and nice i did it i did it if you
find ammo let me know sorry i hit you okay oh that was my
feelings okay yeah you heard my feelings i i literally
revived you i think i can get one hidden okay you know i
brought you back sorry for being kind of loud you guys took
you into this world i can take you out again actually i
think it's the opposite don't do it mom
oh i love there's a there's a molotov here girls molotov oh
i have a bomb in case we ever You threw a bomb there.
Mata!
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Here you go.
Hold on.
I think they're gonna explode.
Yeah!
I think I shot to myself.
It's okay.
I try to heal you.
God dang it.
I'm the one who took it.
It's okay, Hanya.
That is who.
At least you tried.
And that is very cute.
Thank you.
Are we going back downstairs?
I think so.
What is this music I'm hearing?
We're going the right way.
If you guys see ammo on the floor, Oh, sorry.
I think I need a gun so that you guys don't accidentally
shoot me.
Yeah, you keep running in front of our shot.
Oh, Jackie!
Yeah, I think I need a pistol.
Oh, my mom.
You can always get a pistol because it's infantry.
Yeah, I think so.
Over this katana.
Yeah, the melee is really strong, but it's hard to use
sometimes.
Yeah.
What is this music I'm hearing?
It's like an accordion.
It's me.
A music?
I think it's one of the mods that I have, but I don't know
what it means.
Oh, my gosh.
Thank you.
I protected my- Ah, she, I protected my O-Shee.
And you keep going down.
You keep going down.
Come on, Mrs. Pop.
Oh, no.
Take it easy, Mrs. Pop.
If I die, it's forever.
Oh, no.
Yeah, I think Millie is like, tough.
Nice, sir.
Where is the safe room?
Oh, is it?
Oh, no, not this one.
Oh, what?
Maybe, like, we have to go up?
Do you remember, Haruka?
I'm hearing the smoker.
I'm hearing Ronald McDonald.
Oh, here he is.
I see him.
Watch out.
Oh, I got hit.
You got him?
Oh, that was close to my head.
What are you, son of a bitch?
Where do we go from you?
You have a med kit?
Oh, upstairs?
Oh, people are saying third floor.
Third floor?
Oh, the third floor?
I forgot I had a med kit on me.
I'm such an idiot.
Oh, you have one?
Nice.
Oh, spitter, spitter, spitter, spitter!
Ouch!
Oh, it's easy.
Oh, it's easy!
Mrs. Puff!
It's okay.
We'll get you.
Oh, thanks, Haruka.
This is it.
Yeah, did it.
Safe room.
Safe room!
Nice!
Nice.
Come on.
Get in, get in!
Come on!
Get in, Haru!
Get in!
Nice!
Yeah!
Good job!
Yay!
Yata!
I have no idea what I'm doing.
You got this.
Yeah, look at you, you're the tank slayer.
I'm the tank slayer.
I hit the big man with my gun.
This map is confusing.
Nicely done.
I love this game.
Me too, it's fun.
It's actually really fun.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I like it though.
How can you read which one it is, is what?
Oh, you can see it says, like, sniper rifle AK-47 combat
shotgun.
No, it doesn't say for me.
If you right-click, you could shove your enemies away.
Hold on, hold on.
Can I pee super quickly before you open the door?
Yeah, of course.
I'm just going to go, like, two seconds.
One, two, two.
If you wanted to shove the zombies away, you could just
right-click.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, right-click.
It's helpful.
Boom.
Change the knife or a gun?
Oh, but there's no, like, pistols or anything.
Can we get a pistol in the future, or is that the only thing
we get at the bigger game?
Or some smaller gun.
I think there's a pistol in the future, I think.
Oh, okay, okay.
It's this one, right?
I don't see any zombies.
Let's go with AKs.
I'm with you.
Oh, yeah, the cricket bat.
Yeah, that's true.
No more knife.
No more knif-y, is what I like to say.
No more kidney.
Kidney?
Kidney-y.
You're looking really dashing, Haruka.
Thanks, what do I look like?
Can I get a yee-ha?
Yee-ha!
Yay!
Yeah!
Was that good?
Oh yeah, that was so good.
Thanks, thanks.
Uh.
what is dashing you running it's like it's like very
handsome oh it can also mean running but it can mean
handsome too oh i see what do i look like on your screen
mint you're doug dimmadome owner of the dimsdale dimmadome
but with a really tall hat oh fuck yeah that's what i'm
talking about let's go lady wait i accidentally switched my
gun oh i don't know what gun i don't know which I think I
lost my good AK with the sniper scope because I died.
Oh, no.
You'll get another sniper scope.
You'll need another.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm not too worried.
All right, are we ready?
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
Ricky is talking shit to me.
Which one is that?
He's telling me that Haruka is doing all the objectives and
I'm useless.
Oh, thanks, Ricky.
Don't believe the signs.
Washing your hands won't help when they attack you.
Who is Seda?
the shotgun jimmy gibbs jr thanks bricky i haven't played
this game in years it's been forever yeah he's telling me
i'm bad and saying that you're good oh damn i don't know
about that bricky got a sniper with a oh my god is this the
same gun i was using it like barely aims what the heck is as
well as my previous gun feels harder to aim this one hey i
was here hey i was here i don't Is it because my previous
gun had like the little laser scope so it was easier to aim?
Okay.
I remember that this is like as far as I played.
We beat this level.
And it was really tough.
This one is tough.
Give us a few tries.
Oh.
In the elevator, gang.
Okay.
On here, gang.
So the laser made it easier.
Damn it.
Need to fill the car with gas.
Oh, my God.
Jimmy.
Okay.
do you girls think do we think what hear me out strategy
maybe one of us carries the gas while the other ones shoot
around that or two and two what is a better strategy i think
we hope for the best we don't want to go in no we absolutely
need a strategy baby we don't need no strategy i think
certainly absolutely I got one I'm protecting you okay Hena
I'm protecting you oh never mind okay I got I'm protecting
you I'm not protecting someone help please I'm coming I'm
coming I'm coming oh God what
happened to you like you were I got caught by a smoker and
then a jockey, okay?
Guys, there's health kits in the middle of the store.
I'm gonna die.
Okay, I'm shooting.
I was shooting.
Oh, thank you.
Min, there's health kits in the middle, she was saying.
I got a health kit too.
Oh my gosh, get off of me.
Hold on.
I think we need to be two and two.
I think two and two is the strategy here, you.
Genuinely.
No one's watching, right?
Kenya, I'll see you by the car, okay?
I'm protecting you or actually I can go with mint if you
want okay okay I'll go down there okay I'm behind you get
the gas let's go get the gas I got the gas I'm getting the
gas I'm getting the gas we can do two and two okay that way
if anything happens we can wait where the hell oh oh my oh
my oh oh whoa I got him I got him.
Yeah, you sure did, girl.
Hey, I took the front.
You got the finishing shot, but I...
Guys, guys!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Where's your partner?
Haruka's right here.
I thought you guys were my partner.
No, Haruka was your partner.
Wait, what?
She was up there.
Haruka, we gotta be two and two.
What?
I think we gotta be.
We gotta be three.
Yeah, by my own.
What are y'all doing?
What the world?
We're supposed to be two and two, Haru, just again.
I'm dropping yeah.
Yeah, yeah, that's good.
That's good.
Oh, there's more gas up there.
Wait, no, no, no, let's go get the other one.
That was really smart.
Oh, no, it's too much in!
Wait, uh, Mink, Mink, I'm gonna go save her.
Yeah, go save her.
Go save her.
Okay, wait, Mink, you have to save me now.
Oh, wait, what?
What do you mean?
Wait, what's the music?
I mean, mine was like, I was dropping the gas from the top
floor to the ground, so...
I'm coming!
Oh my god.
Wait.
What happened to you?
Oh, there's Metal Gear!
I think we have to be two and two together.
because if we get attacked by the special enemy we're fucked
we have to be two and two uh where is what i was doing i was
going to the top stairs and i was standing on the leg and i
was dropping it down so it's easier instead of going down
the stairs that's what i was doing oh my god well can can
one of us stay with you then how to oh gosh oh gosh please
please oh i got a jackie i'm coming i'm coming oh good job
good job okay
Okay, I'm going upstairs.
Oh, there's one up here.
There's one up here.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Mint, mint, mint.
Wait one second.
I'm behind.
Okay, yeah.
All right.
I scream!
Mint, mint, do you want to get the ones in the back over
there?
Which one?
Okay.
In front of me.
In front of where I am.
Where are?
What do you mean in front of you?
What are we talking about?
Oh, shoot.
I don't know.
Oh, I'm pinned.
Oh, thank you.
I got you.
Yep.
Thank you, Haruka.
Come with me.
There's two more over here.
Okay.
Oh, over this way.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, they're like over that way.
See?
Let's go over there.
Yeah.
I saw them.
If you guys drop it, we can put it in.
Oh, sorry.
What the heck?
I don't...
I couldn't figure out how to...
Oh, there's some over here.
Yeah, throw them around.
Ice cream.
Yeah.
Good girl.
Oh, there's more.
Yeah, throw them over.
I'll shoot some of these guys while...
Oh, there's some over here.
Over here.
Oh, my God.
I can't see.
I left click Good job, girlie Okay, I'm getting the ones
over here Oh, I need help, I need help Mint, Mint, I need
help I see you Wait, I don't see you Oh my gosh I need help
I'm on the stairs I'm on the stairs I'm trying to get the
smoker Good girl Good girl Henry, do you have Haruka?
Yeah Let's wait until we have all the gas together I'm
getting I'm getting one The last two maybe I'm falling human
I'm falling human Because I think If we Every time we fill
up the gas Oh my gosh So let's wait till all the gas are
together.
Wait a minute, I'm here, I'm here.
Hold on.
Hold on, Min.
Wait, wait, wait.
Ice cream!
Every time we fill up the car, the whore comes in.
So let's wait till we have all the gas together.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's wait it.
Reloading here.
Okay, Min, I'm behind you.
Are you?
I'm far behind you, but I'm behind you.
Okay, I'm coming down.
Are we going down to the girls?
Yeah, because there's ice cream.
There's some gasoline.
Are they actually all ice cream for you?
Is that what it is?
No, I have a, whenever there's a horde, a SpongeBob yelling
free ice cream.
There you go.
Okay, how many are we missing?
Oh, sorry, I had a gun.
What's seven plus four?
11, we need two more.
Was there one over here?
I guess it's gone.
Oh, big guy, big guy, where?
Ah!
All the two are very far over here.
I don't know how to ping, but it's there.
Oh, I will make it over here.
Oh, gosh.
Oh my God, I can't.
I can't hit!
Oh fuck, I'm stunned, I'm stunned, I'm stunned!
I'm down, I'm down!
I'm down too, I'm down too, I'm down too!
Thank you, Haru.
Help me, please!
I'm coming in, I'm coming in.
I'm killing my teams more than the fucking zombies.
Oh, he's down, he's down!
Is nobody raising?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm raising you.
I need us all!
Reloading.
girls there's two health kits right here mint and henya in
the back thank you i i just i think where wait where what's
seven plus one two three four where behind the do you see
where i'm looking at they're over there oh gosh i'm coming
over here let's go let's go okay wait mint i can't heal
myself oh because of the horde how do we get there okay okay
uh we're gonna
I can't see, I can't see, I can't see.
Oh.
I got you, I got you, I got you, I got you, I got you.
I got you, I got you.
Hold on, I'm taking care of these guys first.
Then I'll get you, I'll get you.
It looks like it's not even true.
Oh, there's fire.
Oh my god, I can't, I can't get you.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Oh my.
I got you.
I'm good.
I got you, I got you.
Yeah, you.
Okay, so the gas cans get blown up, you guys.
No way.
I swear that's what just happened.
And the gas cans got it.
Wait, but where's...
There's no more gas.
Nope.
No, they all spawn back.
They do?
Oh, I see.
I see.
They're back up there.
Oh, my God.
So the thing is, I'm pretty sure if you shoot the gas tanks,
they'll spawn fire, so don't shoot them.
Oh, my God.
let's put how about this let's put like two more and then
we'll put the rest of like oh thank you no but i think it's
every time we fill a car a horde comes in yeah yeah so let's
do two and then let's do four the ice cream never ends oh my
god that way we don't have a chance to like shoot it and
kill it i think uh the one right here like three and three
oh wait okay we gotta keep going never mind uh i went up the
wrong stairs i went up the wrong three and three or like two
and four three uh we have to like split up the amount of
them that we're doing oh i'm getting gas right now so um oh
wait oh my god are you really yeah i got you i got you i got
you i got you henry there's also kills here mint if you want
since you might need the extra i think i do 100 health yeah
yeah grab them here nice oh you killed peter oh yay i killed
peter there oh i think we got
Oh my god, oh my god.
No!
Oh my god, please.
How do you throw the gas, by the way?
Just left click, left click.
It's not letting me.
Really?
It's fine, it's fine, it's fine.
Oh my god.
Oh, yeah, we paddle time?
Stop.
What is this?
Oh, I got some, there's a lot of bombs over here.
here oh bio bomb okay i grabbed that for something i killed
them oh nice oh gosh okay
oh where are you where are you i'm on the stairs thank you
good job mint i'm not next to you i'm downstairs i'm coming
upstairs i don't know how to get to the other oh my god the
ice cream Here we go.
This is where we need to go.
I need.
Where do I go?
There we go.
Over here.
Oh, fuck.
I just blew up the other.
I even knew I fucking had to.
I'm so silly.
Oh, there we go.
It's okay.
Ow.
How do we get the...
Oh, man.
Let's get that one on the floor there that they just
dropped.
Okay.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh my god.
Charger!
Thank you, Henry.
Yeah, fine, fine, fine.
Okay.
This is the most frustrating one I saw.
I swear.
Let's get both of these and fill them in at the same time.
Oh my God.
I'm so sorry.
I just blew it up.
I did the same thing.
Don't even sweat it.
Nice.
I'll fill both of these pretty much at the same time.
I think we have to go this way.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think so too.
Oh, there we go.
There you go.
Oh, my God.
Kyle, Kyle, Kyle.
Oh, I'm down.
Oh.
I'm coming.
I'm kind of far though.
It's okay if I die No, I'm coming up.
Mitch shut up.
I'll die.
You're supposed to haunt me forever you bitch I'm coming
your ass fuck.
Oh fuck mint.
No, no, hold on.
Maybe I can't.
I might be able to save you I don't think I can't get the
tongue.
I can't get the tongue.
I fell down.
I'm coming back.
I couldn't get the tongue hug but wait a minute let me save
muta me okay i'm gonna go get muta yeah you free ice cream
did i oh no oh my god no way no way no way no way no way i
just i just got up man i just oh my god have you gotten
countercreated no
I'm reloading, I'm reloading.
Oh my god, oh my gosh.
Just go.
But Dara, you're down!
Oh.
I am down.
Oh no.
Free life.
Okay, I think...
Strategy time.
Fuck my ball!
Yay!
I think we should...
So does it actually, can I ask our chat, does it actually
get harder the more gas you fill in?
Yeah, every time you put the gas in, it makes it work.
So that's why we got to gather all the gas and then put it
in at once.
But if we, if even one of us shoots the gas, it's all going
to blow up.
So I don't think it's a good idea.
Here's an idea.
What if we gather two and two and two and two everywhere,
like not at the car, but we drop all the gas on the bottom
floor?
So that way, even if we blow up a gas, we're only blowing up
two gases.
We're not blowing up, like, a million gases.
Do you know what I mean?
Oh, like, leave them where you drop them.
Like, it's going to be two, two, two, two, two, two, two,
instead of, like, seven gases at the, you know?
Yeah.
You can just place them behind somewhere else if we don't
accidentally shoot them.
Yeah, because the problem is if we shoot one gas by
accident, it's going to blow up all the gases that are.
And people are saying the spitter can trigger it.
And I also think we should be in teams of two, because if
one of us gets like attacked by a spitter or something the
teammate can help.
Okay.
Are we good with like keeping me and Mint, Henya, Haruka, or
do you guys want to change?
I'm good.
Okay.
I just want to kill things.
I do.
Okay.
So if you kill things, then Henya, you grab the gas and
Haruka, you kill stuff to protect her.
Okay.
Someone said in my chat, like every fourth tank or so is a
tank.
Or sorry, every fourth.
Every fourth.
So that means we should do five for four.
544 because it's 13 total okay instead of getting 441 it's
gonna be harder we should do 544 hey hi is that okay i'm
confused i yeah we're killing yeah we're killing we're
killing here are we going the right way yeah wasn't it the
other way no no that's the right way okay it's down here i
hear music again hold on all right girls okay it's fucking
time Thank you, mom.
Anya?
Anya, are you okay, Tiger Boo?
Sorry, I was fixing my mom.
Your mom!
Oh, wait, I got you the wrong gun.
Oh, you're at the safe house?
Sorry, mom, I can't have dinner.
I'm currently trying to save the world.
Hold on.
Oh, yeah, I got it.
Saving the what's left of humanity.
Yeah, sorry, mom.
I got to save what's left of humanity.
You can have fun in your resort.
Hold on.
Can you wait one second before getting into the elevator?
I want to switch guns.
Hurry up.
I want to get the AK.
You can't go in the elevator.
You just can't press the button.
They're all coming, though.
No lunch for today.
I'm good.
Thank you.
There they go.
Thanks, Mom.
I'm coming.
Thank you, Mom.
Here they come.
Maybe I need it.
Can you ask Mama Nia if there's any delicious Reese's that
she wants?
I'll bring them for her.
Oh, they're climbing.
She likes ranch sauce.
Ranch?
All right.
I can bring some ranch.
Do you know her favorite brand?
I like ranch, too.
I'll ask her.
Thank you.
Yeah, ask her.
Really?
Thank you.
Could you ask your mom what is your favorite Japanese food
too so I can give it to you?
My mom likes those little like bird shaped ones.
They're in the shape of a little bird.
It's like a little marshmallow kind of like a bird.
Oh, look up to it.
I'll show you.
Oh my gosh.
Don't you know birds are drones for the government?
They aren't quite you.
Actually, my Okasan likes Pan.
She likes bread.
Yeah, did she like Japanese bread?
All right, Amata, I'm following you!
Yeah, no, Mint.
Let's go get the...
Oh!
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Oh, whoa!
Oh, yeah!
We can put it...
Yeah!
Let's put it behind the car.
Oh, Mint, Mint, behind me.
Oh!
Thank you, girl.
Sorry if I shot you a little bit while that happened.
It's okay.
Spitter?
Oh!
Amata, I need you to come over!
I have a better shot!
I'm here one second.
I was getting attacked.
All right.
Should I shot you, man?
You can't go.
Can I shot you many times today?
Bring this health kit with you.
Bring an XP with you.
Okay, I'm bringing some gas.
I think I already have one.
I'm following you in.
Okay, then let's just go.
It's going ice cream!
Here we go.
Oh my gosh.
I never thought I want ice cream this much until now.
I'm helping.
One second.
I'm also...
There's a horn on me too, girlie.
Oh my god.
Don't shoot over here.
Don't shoot over here!
They're fine.
Oh, I found it!
I found it!
Okay.
There's two.
I think if we have five, we should load it.
Do we have five?
Uh, we have three.
We have three.
Okay.
Hold on, Mint.
Okay, this one.
Oh, one more.
Let me grab it.
Uh, my time!
One second, Mint.
I'm behind you.
I got it!
I'm far behind you.
Oh, you're far behind me.
I think you took my pistol.
Had you.
Wait, I did?
I'm far behind you, Mint.
I think so.
I'm upstairs.
I see it.
Yeah, throw these two down.
That's perfect.
Good job, girl.
I don't have it.
I got the other one.
No, I just throw it down.
Throw it down.
Wait, what did I just say?
Perfect.
Good girl.
Let's bring these closer.
I got my banana.
Don't worry.
We can grab these two as well.
You got your banana?
Nice.
I don't know.
We can't grab them without setting it on fire.
We're done.
I'm far up.
I'm far from you, Mint.
All right, let's go.
I'm down still.
I'm sorry.
Why are you upstairs?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Should I start loading them in?
Should I?
I mean, there's already a horde.
I think you could.
I think you...
Just be careful that we don't blow them up by accident.
I'm gonna load...
Oh!
Hey!
Back off, buddy!
Buh-Buh-Buh!
I gotta be careful not to wait.
How do I load it?
Oh shit!
I need help!
I'm coming!
Oh my god.
Oh, we're in trouble.
We're in trouble!
Girls, girls, we need your help.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, my God.
Oh, there's a tank.
We need your help.
I'm down.
Okay, okay.
Okay, we're coming.
We're done.
Be careful.
Don't blow up the gas canisters.
We got a ton.
We're so.
It's my Jover.
It's fine.
It's up to you, Hanja.
No!
Oh, you're doing so good.
I don't know about that.
I don't know.
Can you pick me up quickly if you can?
Okay.
We'll come in.
Mrs. Pop!
I need some help!
Hmm.
Oh, for third fault damage!
Jump!
Oh!
I didn't want to throw the bomb.
I was scared about.
I thought we were doing so good this time around, though.
I think it doesn't matter if you load them or not.
The horde just comes.
I think if you pick them, if you touch them, the horde
comes, right?
Really?
I don't know.
That's crazy.
So if you guys won, what Hedy and I have been doing, we've
been putting the gas behind the car.
Yeah, that's what we did.
That's what we were doing.
But then I tried loading it, and then the tank came out.
Well, shit.
Let's try it again.
I think we had a good vibe over here.
I think we had a good vibe.
I think maybe what we should do, when we're closer to
loading a bunch of them in, let's all stick together at the
end.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
For real, for real.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know if they actually heard me.
Sorry guys, I have a cold.
Do you think they heard me or do you think they're just...
I guess we find out.
Sorry, Hanyu, let me wipe my nose.
Alright, I'm good.
What's going on?
What is happening?
Nice one, nice one.
Nice one.
I was wiping my nose because I clearly sneezed.
Yeah, I think they were freezing it.
Let's go.
How do we start this?
Well, if you're looking for ideas.
So, my gosh, I have a joke for you.
Room stairs.
I have a joke.
Why did the chicken cross the road?
Oh, why?
To get to the other side.
Oh, that's a good one.
Oh, sorry.
My feelings.
There she is.
Just pour it in.
Wait, that's not mint.
That's Hania.
Mint, mint, mint.
Let's go together.
Oh, I guess let's protect Hania for like two seconds because
she's alone.
Yeah.
Oh, thank you, thank you.
I got the bullet.
Good job, Billy.
Another gas.
I'm pouring in a gas.
Right behind it.
Alright, Henry.
I'm ready.
I got you.
Don't get it.
There we go.
Oh, guys.
I need help.
I think I got...
Oh, my God.
Leave me alone.
Where is it?
you oh my god it was like taking you away it really was it
likes me oh sorry if i hit you i'm ready okay i'm ready okay
let's go back upstairs where we belong
where we belong i've got you there's some ass will chase me
oh whoa wow wow the harunya is strong And Ardenial is
stronger than anything.
Watch out the horse gonna appear from that back room.
Be prepared.
I'm going upstairs, Matara.
Okay, I'm following you.
Okay, there's a key over here.
I'm gonna put away.
Shit, nice, nice, nice, nice.
Actually, he said it.
Me into the left, mid, mid, mid, right.
Oh, no, never mind.
I'm so stupid.
Never mind, never mind, never mind.
Left here.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Yeah, other left.
All right, then.
Let's go down.
Should we go down?
Should we go down in the middle stair?
Uh, are they coming through here?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
I got one.
I'm sorry!
Was it you?
I thought it was me.
It was me.
I'm sorry.
Oh, um, it was all you.
It was all you.
It was just a dream.
I think we can go up for you.
It was all you.
I'm just putting the gas tank behind the carpet.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Maybe we should do that.
Oh, well, well, well, panel.
It's just you and me, buddy.
What?
Well, it's caught on fire!
Okay, okay.
I remember the day.
Oh, wait, how do we get over there?
It took my life from me.
Oh, it's time to end it, panel.
What is he?
Wait, you can go, go, go, shoot, shoot, shoot.
Okay.
Let's go.
And your girls, there are the narwhal.
There you go.
Oh, no.
Oh, help me, please!
Someone!
Oh gosh, over.
Could you please go up?
I fell off the stairs.
Go up, go up the stairs.
Oh, I see you, I see you, I see you.
I didn't realize that was a big...
What happened to you?
What did you do?
Don't ask, don't ask, don't ask, don't ask, don't ask.
You don't need to know.
Okay.
I think we should load the current gas into the car.
I think we should load the current gas into the car, y'all.
I think...
Wait, wait, there's a tank!
There's a tank!
After the tank is dead, I think we should load the current
gas.
There's a bunch of ammo downstairs.
Yeah, I know.
I gotta go get there.
I ain't going down without a fucking piece of shit.
Come at me!
Good job.
Can I reload, please?
Good job, girls.
Oh, my gosh.
All right, I'm going to start loading the gas in the car.
Okay.
Be careful.
If you can protect me, Mint.
I'm just a single ghost, you know?
single go oh it's a single you know what hang it let's go
get more gas yeah you better you better hurry up mata you
better i'm only gonna do i'm only gonna do five gotta reload
gotta reload gotta reload you gotta reload you gotta reload
you gotta reload you keep doing it i think they're following
i think they're going after um uh haruka all right i'm gonna
stop at five yeah yeah keep going Uh-oh, what was that?
It's fine, it's fine, I killed him.
I got you.
All right, Min.
This is kind of peaceful, actually.
Min, do you want to get pills for the health?
There's pills here if you want.
Oh, no, I'm good.
Let's bring these.
Haruka, Haruka, Haruka, I see you.
I see you.
I got you.
Help, help, me.
No, don't worry.
I got you.
Thank you.
Min, do you need drugs?
No, I think I'm good.
You sure?
I'm going to pick up a med kit anyway, though.
Okay, okay, do it.
Oh, you need to use this bile head at some point.
Oh, yeah.
I'm gonna grab this gas over here.
Okay.
Yep.
I'm protecting you.
Wait, wait, wait.
Mint behind.
Yeah I'm gonna put it behind the car.
Wait, how do we get the gas?
We have four more gases.
I think we need them.
We're gonna, we're gonna, we're gonna blow up these gases.
I know we are.
No, no, no, we won't.
We won't, we won't.
We won't.
Don't worry.
Okay, I'm gonna put it in the car.
Oh, get out of my way.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think you can start putting it in the car.
Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Mint, you're fine.
You're fine.
Don't even sweat it.
Okay.
What was that?
Oh shit guys, guys, I need your help.
I need your help, I need your help, I need your help.
What the fuck just happened?
I got you.
I saw you flying away!
Yeah, I got crawled by the guy.
Oh, did the gas tank up top up here?
Oh, I'm loading.
How do we get that?
Oh no, her- oh god, Woody, hello?
How the fuck do we- It's okay.
We only got, after this, we only need four more guys.
We're like, pretty much almost done.
Let's stick together.
Let's stick together, gamer girls.
Do not blow up the gas tank.
What gas tank?
Where is...
Oh, I see it.
I'm going to get it.
I'm going to load it.
Good job, honey.
Good job, Haru.
Oh, I'm the smoke.
I got
a...
Vile, vile, vile.
All right, I'm going to stay up here.
I think I have...
Yeah, I'm going to have to get caught too.
Where's all the gas?
It's on the switch.
Okay, mint.
Yeah.
I think it gets exploded.
Uh oh.
Here comes Metal Gear Ray.
I see two of them.
Right here.
Mate, let's follow Hania.
Okay.
Right here.
Okay, I'm coming.
Oh wait, I gotta heal.
I'm gonna heal.
If you'll cover for me, Mata, I'm gonna heal real quick.
You'll heal.
Oh, wait, wait.
Hania, you're alone.
Be careful.
Okay.
Okay, I'm coming.
We're coming.
Well, for Haruka, are you doing the tag?
This way, this way, this way, this way.
Which way?
Oh, let's help Haru.
I'm gonna kill this tag.
Let's help Haru.
I'm gonna kill him.
Solo the tag!
Let me solo the tag!
Oh, um...
Oh my godubs!
OUCHI!
OUCHI, OCHI, OCHI.
OUCHI, OCHI.
OUCHI.
Oh fuck, I didn't realize he was a big guy.
I thought he was dead.
Is he dead?
He's dead!
HEe he!
Oh my gosh.
You got her?
Oh, I got you.
I got her, I got her, I got you.
I got you?
Tanya, take the drugs for help.
Wait, she's not up yet!
I'm not up yet!
Oh, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go.
Guys, we only need three more.
Oh, sorry.
How about we all go together?
We can try.
Let's go all together.
Where is it?
There's two over there in the back.
Oh, how do we get up there?
I think over here, no?
Wait, wait, somebody's alone.
There's Haru, Haru.
Yeah, where Haru is.
Where Haru is?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, sorry, sorry.
From how do we can go there?
Okay, perfect.
I think now if we stayed together and used drugs for health,
I think we might get it.
I think it's this way, this way, this way.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think we have to go...
Oh, this way?
This way, this way.
Yeah, yeah, this way.
Follow where Henye is?
They're coming from the stairs behind.
Oh, goodness Christ.
Spooked me.
I'm kind of slow, so I'll guard from the back.
I'm sticking back with Mint.
I'm a little slow.
It's okay, baby.
Guys, there were two packs over.
Not two packs.
Yeah, yeah, we're coming.
coming.
Okay, okay.
I'll grab, I'll grab one of them.
Yeah, since Mint is slow.
Or, I got it, I got it.
Guys, there's pills here if anybody needs.
There's a gas.
I got you.
Henya, I'm gonna give you pills.
Thank you.
No, no, no.
Oh my god, Henya, wait, stop for a second.
Okay.
I'm gonna die, but that's okay.
Oh, I need help.
Henya, behind you.
Behind you.
Thank you.
How do you Oh my god, I was so close to...
Did I finish?
I don't even know.
No!
I was so close!
Mint, if you need to ask, then you didn't finish.
That's true.
There's a smoker, by the way!
Be careful!
Guys, I'm running down to get mint.
I'm trying my best, but I am alone.
Oh, sorry, that's you.
Oh, fuck, I got some!
I got some!
Ice cream!
Ice cream coming in!
Oh, watch out, watch out, watch out!
I can't get them from behind you!
Be careful.
Don't shoot the barrel.
I know.
I'm putting it in.
I don't care if I die.
I got it.
Mint, mint.
You can give you pills.
You can give you drugs.
I'm stuck.
I'm down again.
It's okay though.
Oh my gosh.
What a freak.
I was getting tea bagged for real.
Stop it.
It's okay.
We're so close.
There's one more.
Just get it.
Don't even worry about me.
Just put it in.
We need your extra firepower, you bitch.
I'm behind you.
Let's get the last one.
There's one more.
Yeah.
Let's get one more.
Come on, girls.
Oh my god.
We're about to win.
We're about to win the game.
Oh, big guy.
The guy.
The big guy.
Oh, my god.
He's going upstairs.
Fuck.
I thought that would avoid the shot.
We're going the wrong way.
Wow.
Is there one more?
Oh, no.
Jockey!
Where's the... where's the...
Where's Ray?
I have a... I have a bomb!
I'm not afraid to use it!
Hanyu!
Hanyu, I'm coming!
I'm a little slow though.
Thank you, thank you!
Hanyu!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh my gosh.
No, it's okay, it's okay.
Hanyu, I... I... I don't think I can...
Hanyu, I'm down to you.
Oh, it's fine.
It's fine.
I'll get you guys give me oh never mind How do you use our
only hope how do one can only you you're the only hope how
do you kill the enemies so how do is easier for her I'm dead
dead it's only you it's only you mata it's no it's hard.
No and if she can get you if she can get you out Oh, how do
I can't see behind you?
Oh, but I can't get behind you.
Okay, let's see where's it going.
Ah, Haru is shooting me.
I had a bomb!
I had a bomb if you need it.
You could grab it from my dead body.
Peel it from my hands.
I don't know where Haru is.
Okay, she's behind me.
Okay, Haru, how are we doing this?
We gotta get up there.
Oh, watch out.
I don't think you can go from there.
Fuck shit.
Oh my god.
She's cornered.
She's not cornered.
You have to go first floor and get the other stairs.
I think it is on her.
Is that a jockey?
Oh no.
Oh.
Haru.
Good luck.
She's so strong.
I think you're about to do it.
I genuinely think next round is the round, girl.
Wait, what do you mean next round?
We're still...
We still have here.
Oh gosh.
We just got...
Uh-oh.
The ice cream.
Haru with the pistol my queen I genuinely think like we're
about to get we can take like a two minute break re-center P
Oh my goodness Oh my goodness Whoa why are they purple Nice
nice Good job Haru My queen She is so Imagine she clutches
it She's so good No No she got caught oh my god matara why'd
you have to say that why'd you have to say that imagine if
she clutches gets immediately caught by the soma okay no i'm
doing so well too i mean it really did really well that time
here's an idea can we take like a two minute break and just
like recenter our chakras because i think we're gonna get
the next one are you okay Are you okay?
Are you okay, Matara?
I need just like a two minute breather, and then I think
we're gonna do it.
Okay, two minute breather for you.
Yeah, I'm fine, I'm fine.
I just need like two minutes, because that was really
overwhelming.
This stage is so stinky.
But it was fun.
I think we're just about to get it.
Genuinely.
I think we have a really good thing going with like throwing
everything down in like two big waves, having teammates,
like, I think that's really good.
I like putting in the gas.
my ass for a bit but then the fucking smoker got me i know
you can blame matara it's okay you can say matara why would
you jinx it like that martara this is your fault why would
you do that i'm here i'm gonna spank you with this yowie
paddle turn around turn around okay okay spanking this is
like reminiscent of anime cons and like are you gonna glomp
me i'm turning around i'm turning
can't believe it let me lower my sensitivity i feel like my
sensitivity is so high okay okay jimmy gibbs jr is the man
the man i mean i don't know anybody like that man but there
was man man man man overtracks the man the legend the legend
i do but not now okay okay but oh yeah can we please add the
classic emote in my channel oh what's that hang banging to
the music it's like the little the little duck smoking wait
how do you do the emotes in this.
How do you do the emotes?
In Twitch, you just type in and then it shows up.
No, in this game.
In this game.
No, I have classics.
Dancing, do you?
How do you do them, guys?
Chat?
I did it wrong.
You suck.
There's still a med pack here if anyone wants it.
I think somebody with low health should use it and then
grab... Oh, wait.
I didn't have an extra med pack.
Not bad.
I'm stupid.
Oh, I have an extra.
No, we all have one med pack, right?
Oh, okay.
Z?
Well, no, how did I don't have it.
Oh, this is it.
I didn't have it.
Does that feel good?
I don't have one.
Oh, it's not emo.
Grab the one downstairs, though.
We're fine.
Ooh.
Make.
All right, girls.
Girls, I need you all together.
Envision the win.
Be like professional athletes.
Imagine putting in the 13th Gascat and cheering.
Hoorah.
Sorry.
Woo, we did it.
13th Gascat.
Whoopie.
We won.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Are you manifesting?
I'm manifesting.
You have to be happy as if we just won.
Tanya, please.
Not the Garfield scratch.
Listen, the clutch that I made and then you have to jinx it
for me.
Sorry, I was sneezing.
Tanya, can you just pretend to be so happy that we won?
Just imagine we win.
Yay!
No, go!
You gotta go!
Let's go!
Yay!
All right, let's go.
Don't you have to be like...
If we lose, it's because Henya's power of imagination.
You do not blame Henya for your own skill issue?
Come on!
No, I blame Henya if we lose.
Skill issue, do you.
Skill issue, do you?
Okay.
Henya.
I saw you on the kills board.
Every time Don't you skill issue dao me baby girl.
It's a ping.
I live in Japan Wait, hang yeah, did you just say ping?
It's a ping dao.
Real gamers don't blame the ping Oh, I said real issue dao.
It's a ping It's a ping issue dao.
It's a real issue to ping dao.
I sigh on the scoreboard Hanyo.
I know what you do in your spare time.
before you move to Japan so we can play with the same thing.
Okay.
Yeah, Henya.
She was talking to me.
She was talking to me!
I mean, she was talking to me, Ben.
I'm already married, so I technically, you guys are from
Hawaii.
Oh, don't fill it up now.
We're filling them up after, right?
I'll go get the other two over there.
All right, Henya.
Yeah.
Let's go.
I got overzealous.
I got overzealous a little bit.
We go this way.
Yeah, let's go this way.
Yeah, mint, mint, mint, mint.
The other way.
There's two counts at the end.
Which way?
Oh, down here?
Let's keep the two counts on the floor for the end,
actually.
Keep the two on the floor at the end.
Yeah, yeah, they're the easiest to get.
Charger!
I'm out of!
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here,
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I can't get it from
here, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, oh,
what am I hearing?
Oh my gosh!
Okay, I got him.
We're okay.
Oh, sorry.
You scared me.
I got him.
Hold on, let me get the pills.
There's always pills upstairs, Mint, if you want some for
the extra help.
Did you grab both of them?
No, there's another pill there if you want to grab it.
Nice.
An adrenaline.
Oh, I'll try.
Oh, get off of me.
Grab the pill too.
Yeah, yeah.
Wait, wait, how did... There's two of them.
There's two of them here.
used to going downstairs.
Wait, are there any over here, or?
Are there any over here?
Let's go check.
Oh, I think this is how we get the ones over here.
Okay, okay, okay, okay!
Oh, let's throw them.
Oh, good girl.
You did find them.
Oh, you're freaking good girl.
Would you like the 360 roll throw?
True, now you're probably just rolling!
There's also bombs over here.
There's bombs over here.
How'd you beat a 360?
there's bombs over there where oh down where the gas cans
were oh i see i see i see hold on i just dropped my pistol
okay oh why would okay i'm here watch out watch out oh okay
let's go back down okay there's a lot on the floor yeah i'm
gonna start loading them up so we don't accidentally blow
them up there's a tank nearby oops there's a tank okay let's
kill the tank and then careful of the tank if you can leave
it's here because ferno starts blasting his
away oh my god get him red kid while you can i was reloading
get a med kid while you can me my god haru no no not you
haru haru i'm coming in a second to kill the hunter first?
I think we're not gonna do so well this time.
We're fine, we're fine, we're fine.
Stop jinxing it.
Don't jinx it, don't jinx it.
Oh my god!
You harlot!
Get hango, I'll get Haru.
We're fine.
I think we need to load a few of these in the thingy.
Hold on, I got you, I got you Haru.
Come here, come in, come in.
Oh no, I could just get this health kit over here.
Oh, yeah, get the health kit and there's also meds and
stuff.
Oh, I actually need one now that I look at it.
Yeah, here you go.
Take that.
I'll take this one.
And I'm just gonna heal real quick while I wait.
Okay, watch not to blow them up now.
Don't blow up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Watch out for that one over there.
Reload in here.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
I need help with the jumper.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
I need to be careful.
Oh, no!
Good job.
Oh, no, no!
Oh, I'm fire.
them fuck fine I got you oh there's still two over here
there's still two over here keep the two on the floor for
the end because they're the easiest keep those two for the
end cuz they're gonna be easiest to get them okay I wonder
oh no the ones on the oh shoot I didn't even notice I should
have reloaded earlier wait who's alone Haruka you're alone
oh we always try to go with a buddy just in case in case you
get like um you're such a mom you're such a mom i can't hear
you had her sorry because i was shooting uh-oh i can't
reload gotta get some more i can't reload it's timon the
police force we're saving those henya we're gonna save them
yeah keep those until the end henya because they're the
easiest she already grabbed them they're the easiest to get
so we should keep game i think that one is the one from over
here right so okay i'm gonna try and get this one over here
you can start bringing those two henya actually because
we're pretty much at the end we just need two more no we
need four more yeah and we're getting these four more so
don't worry those two plus these two good job there's only
one here yeah that's what i'm saying that's what i was
saying wait there's over here though over here yeah let's
get the other one yay bring both of there's two just in
case.
Tanks here, I hear his music, he's blasting it again, look
at them.
Was there just one there, Mint or two?
Yeah, just one, just one.
Oh, fuck.
Mint, I just dropped.
You're alone.
I accidentally fell through the floor.
It's okay.
I'm far.
I'm trying to kill a jockey.
Oh, gosh.
Okay, there's a guy.
There's a guy.
I'm gonna die, I think.
Mint, I'm so sorry.
I fell through the floor.
How do I...
Does it move this way?
Or does it move Oh gosh!
Oh, he downed me.
He downed me.
Oh.
Sorry, Mint.
It's okay.
I fell.
I'm just down, you know.
Oh, you're also down.
Cool.
Mrs. Puff.
Don't worry, I got you.
I got you.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
What do you think I am?
I'm not a feet man.
I'm gonna go get mint.
I'm so slow.
Hurry.
I'm gonna get ice cream.
I'm back there again.
I'm here mint.
Oh, the, what's it called?
Are you sure you're here?
Because I'm like literally blacking out.
Can you, can you shoot them?
Yeah, that's what I'm doing.
Okay, good girl, good girl.
I think it got blown up so let's grab the, oh.
Yeah, yeah, let's grab the other one.
Oh, oh, I hear, I hear him again.
Oh, hold on.
Oh, we just blew them up.
Sorry, I think I just blew them up.
Behind you, behind you.
I was taking pills.
My girl.
Min Min, there's one back there.
Oh, thank you, Hunter.
Thank you so much.
Girls, how many?
Min, Min, there's...
Oh, shit.
You're alone.
How many do we have downstairs?
It's these two that need to go.
Zero down here.
Zero.
All right, hold on.
They're going to come out from here.
Yep.
Oh, and from here?
Oh, shoot.
Watch out, though.
Okay, I'm going to throw it overboard.
I'm going to throw it overboard.
Yeah, get it, get it, get it.
Throwing gasoline.
Guys, we're about to throw you the last one.
We're going to get the last one.
No, there's...
We're going to get the last one, and we're done.
We need two more.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Get the one we just threw on the floor, and we're done.
We beat the game.
Throw the last one, and then let's go help them.
Okay, let's go help.
We're coming, we're coming.
Oh gosh, they're right behind us.
They're right behind us, yeah.
They're behind us, they're behind us.
Oh my goodness.
Come on, get in the car.
I'm coming to the car.
How do I get in?
I don't know.
Let me in.
Let me in!
Come on, Matara.
You're so slow.
Shut the fuck up!
There we go.
Yippee!
Oh my gosh, Matara, we beat the whole game how do you feel
let's go isn't this only like round one of the whole game
yeah actually i'm so sorry for swearing so much but that was
amazing oh my god let's go we did it oh i used the least
amount of first aid kit no wonder i died the most
oh my god dang matara you're Can you like use I was using
Millie until like the end the beginning of the game.
Yeah, yeah I killed all them tanks all them tanks.
Oh, no, don't look at we got it baby girl
Let's go Let's go friendly fire Revive the most teammates
though hello
19% zombies were harmed in the making of this.
Oh, I got the most headshots though.
I don't aim for the head ever.
I just aim.
We kill three thousand.
I know it's hard to in the moment, right?
Yeah.
Oh.
That was amazing, but exhausting.
That's just a taste of how your tournament will be.
Yeah.
How do you feel?
I'm not ready.
Not ready.
I feel like I was not prepared.
Like, end of May?
Oh, yeah.
Good luck.
No, no, no, no, no.
The people again.
Oh, the end of May?
Yeah.
Arigato.
Do we keep going or do we stop here?
Up to you guys.
It's up to you.
What's in your...
I feel like I can keep going.
So, yeah, up to you guys.
Yeah, I could stop or I could go.
I think it's, you know, if anybody's too tired.
Is the first mission the hardest?
No.
Does it get easier?
We could also choose like anyone.
We don't have to do like the second one.
We can choose any.
The second one says streets.
Like the carnival one.
Well, the carnival one's kind of annoying too.
Oh, it's because I have the campaign.
Death sender passing.
One is to do dark carnival.
How about blood harvest?
Blood harvest?
Blood.
passing hard rain dead air no mercy the sacrifice whoa
there's also the concert what sounds interesting dark
carnival my beloved oh is that actually i think they don't i
think it might be smart i don't know okay i'll read out a
few names and you girls say what you prefer okay the passing
dark carnival swamp fever hard rain the parish the sacrifice
no mercy crash course death Dead air, blood harvest, cold
stream, the last sand.
Dark carnival!
Alright.
Oh, people are saying the carnival's hardest.
Why are people saying the carnival's hardest?
Maybe I just saw one person.
Carnival, carnival.
Well, people are saying no mercy is quick for Alaska him.
Oh, is it?
Yeah, we can do anything.
Oh, there's no mercy then.
I'm fine with anything.
I'm just reading chat.
Don't most hear a dark carnival.
Oh, oh.
I don't think no mercy in the carnival is a good one.
Yeah, that's what I'm seeing too.
I've never, I don't think I've done no mercy.
I don't know though.
All right, no mercy.
Try it.
Haruka, are you good?
I see you, poor.
Wait, what's she doing?
She's calling me stinky.
Oh no, I didn't download anymore.
What do you mean?
Do you need to download this app?
No.
are you okay yeah oh there's a chat uh-huh yeah there is
there is yeah don't say mean things say nice things it says
say jp what does it mean by that don't say mean things in
the chat say jp jp is it a cheat code oh oh it's gonna like
unlock secret weapons oh oh oh it's just jp to me too Oh.
JP.
All right, I'm starting.
I'm going to need a drink after this game, I think.
I didn't think we'd be playing as the Left 4 Dead 1 people,
so I didn't download any of their mod.
The Left 4 Dead 1 guy, I thought he was from Dead by
Daylight.
I didn't realize he was from this game.
Which one?
The one with the hat?
The old one.
Yeah.
Wait, he's in a...
He's in Dead by Daylight.
Dead by Daylight?
I think his name is Bill.
Yeah.
I think so.
Really?
That's cool.
Look at Billy.
Dude.
What?
Sorry, we're all humans and then Henya is like silver the
hedgehog.
I am.
Yeah, you.
For me, Mitt, my brain is fucking up.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
Bye, Joel.
Wake up.
Grab a brush and put a little makeup!
I don't think you trust in your marine, your marine is what
my friend wanted to say, your marine oh
I didn't bring a health pack with me oh you know what, I'm a
gamer, I don't need it Go get it.
Go get it.
I don't need one.
What?
Gamer.
God, gamer.
Where the fuck are we?
Do we go down?
How do we go behind you?
I think we go down, sir.
This kind of reminds me half-life.
Oh.
There's a half-life VR.
I don't know if you saw him yet.
Oh, yeah, but I get motion sickness.
That's hard.
I wish I could.
What happens over here?
What happens?
Uh-oh.
Can't see anything.
What's the best gun?
Is it still the easy?
AK here, or is it another gun, y'all?
Neighbor.
Oh, my God.
Oh, I thought those were my friends.
Hey, guys.
My house.
Welcome.
This is a gigantic house.
Right.
What is it?
Oh, my goodness.
Those people are alive.
I mean, they're dead.
Nope, not anymore.
You good?
Thank you.
I just don't stop coming.
And they don't stop coming and they don't stop coming.
Should we go downstairs?
Sure.
Well, I went downstairs.
Oh, they don't stop coming and they don't stop coming.
Oh, oh, no.
Oh my God.
Ow.
Did we get him?
How the heck am I already yellow?
Oh no, Hanya.
Oh no.
Use your health pack.
Hey!
They don't stop coming and they don't stop coming and they
don't stop coming.
I have a Molotov in case there's a big gang.
Ow!
Sorry, I was shooting the other guy!
I'm so...
Ow!
The guy jumpy, jumpy, jumpy!
Pecota!
Yeah!
I hate when Pecota swamps me like that and that's crazy.
Who?
Pecota!
Dakota in her jail outfit.
Wait, who's Dakota?
Who's Dakota?
Dakota?
Oh, Pecora!
I also heard Dakota.
Yeah, I thought you were saying Dakota.
I thought you were saying Dakota also.
Dakota!
Haru, Haru.
She's all the way in the back.
She's about to die.
Oh, no!
Oh, it was a smoker.
Should I have done the impression?
Yeah, do it.
Do it.
I want to hear it.
Oh, that's good.
Guys, Haru, there's a...
Do you need a health kit, Haru?
Yes, I am bleeding.
Okay, come here, come here, and I will...
I'm going to die.
Hold on.
Stop, stop, stop, Haru?
All my spleens.
Spleens?
My spleens.
Oh, her spleens.
Where am I?
I'm bad.
I can't see anything.
I guess this is this way.
Yeah.
This way?
He's already?
Nice?
Oh.
Some cars set up alarms.
Uh oh.
Can you alert to the cord?
Nice.
I'm launching now.
I can't move!
Dang, yeah, what the fuck?
Woo!
Good girl.
Good job.
Good girls.
Good girl.
You know what I mean is you're dying and I'm a men kid.
I'm gonna hesitate giving you my men kids.
Why do you think I'm your wife, da yo?
You know, I think you fucking alerted the time!
The girls are fighting!
Oopsie da-do.
Oopsie-do-do-do.
Okay, you're all forgiving.
Oh, guys, guys, I'm getting drunk!
Talk!
Oh, shit, sorry, honey.
Why are you gonna brag about it, huh?
I'm sorry!
Oh my god, listen, listen.
I'm shooting in the fucking jaw.
is there any oh boy is there any ammo anywhere if anyone saw
yeah i also would need yeah i have a pistol nice i guess
we're going into the subway oh what's this oh a chainsaw if
anybody wants it me a chainsaw
let's go down here i think not here not here okay There's a
fight spot just to hate.
Give me a second break.
Oh, I found some peace.
Safe room!
We've caught it.
Wait, that was it?
Good job.
Yeah, I mean, it was the first mission of the...
Oh!
Oh, yeah.
Uh-oh.
Did we...
Oh.
I was like, why did we disconnect?
All right, mid with the killin.
That's my girl.
Hang out with the special kill.
Whoa, five.
Oh, my gosh.
Yata!
Wow.
Killing it.
I'm doing it.
Rip and tear.
Rip and tear, everybody.
All right, let me see if there's a better.
I'm gonna heal and then I'm gonna grab.
What gun is this?
Nope.
Man, man, man.
Yeah, does everybody have an extra med pack?
I'm grabbing one.
What's a med pack?
Haru, did you grab your med pack?
I don't need one.
Haru is living on the end.
Haru, grab one.
Yeah, Haru.
Come on.
Haru.
No!
Oh!
How dare you ruin my edginess, Moth?
That's so fucked.
Yeah, it is.
You don't have to say about my...
You don't want to mess with me with a train, so...
I'm still here, almost.
Oh, I forgot in my mod I gave him a card for me on shirts as
well, some of the monsters.
That's so fun.
No!
What do you mean?
I don't know what are you talking about?
Why you open the door, Hanya!
Hanyor.
We're gonna go kill him.
Time to kill.
Wait, where are you guys?
What city is this canonically?
Are we in like the United States?
Probably, right?
Take them.
Beautiful.
Rip and tear until everything is dead.
Rip and tear.
This way?
Kill.
I like train.
I'm gonna tell him it's Jigsaw.
Nice.
Oh, Haru's got it.
I do it.
Haru, are you okay?
Let me catch you up.
Oh my gosh, are you okay?
Don't you, but I don't need a bed kit.
No!
Take your meds, Grandpa!
Take your meds!
Take your meds, Haruka!
I'm taking my rage!
Oh, really?
Take your meds, Haruka.
Never!
Oh, what's this one?
Oh, I think I want to go with this one.
Take your meds, Grandma.
Oh, there's my beautiful goon.
I'm ready to die.
Oh, sorry.
Can we not shoot me?
That would be great.
Sorry.
I don't need my meds, I just don't want any of you.
I'm so sorry.
My echo, Steve!
Oh, go Steve!
You don't want to face with my...
Oh, Steve!
Oh, John, leave me alone!
Steve!
Oh, here they come!
Oh, my goodness.
I can't see anything.
Right?
My vision is just blinded by...
My beauty?
Blinded by my sexiness.
Just say it.
I don't need no fucking medicine to be able to kick some
fucking zombies ass into the next Tuesday There's some
Molotov over here Molotov No breakfast Three words eight
letters Hell yeah What's the letter?
Hell yeah Do you know how to smell?
Apparently not Guys there's ammo here upstairs and a big gun
Oh yeah there's ammo there's ammo And there's stairs I think
this is where we need to go in the in the future Oh what's
his oh big gun Big gun.
Big gun.
The boy ammo packs on the ground to share ammo with the
team.
Okay, I'm going to have an extra ammo for us for like a big
fight if we all run out.
We go up these stairs, I believe.
Okay.
Here we go up the stairs.
Oh, a little girly.
Oh, I accidentally took the wrong gun.
We'll see.
We got to flick them door switch.
However, there's going to be a hard if we do so.
Be careful.
Okay.
Yeah, make sure you grab the little molotov.
Because, uh, yep.
I'm just going to be talking.
like this for the rest of the mission are you are you gonna
be talking like this haruka
oh this is oh my god there's like a big turret oh haruka
alerted the horde does anybody want to get crazy with the
big turret yeah you got it girly come on uh i can't it's
very limited oh gosh do your best do your best um yep
Son of a bitch.
Oh, nice.
Big guy, big boy, big boy.
Big boy.
Oh, you know what?
I better kick you.
Okay.
Charger.
Oh, my God.
Me, behind you.
Behind me?
How do I get off this thing?
I'm really struggling with this gun.
Why can't I shoot?
Why wouldn't it shoot?
You're dead.
Oh, where am I?
Calm down!
Ah!
Oh, are you good?
She's alive.
Ready?
Yeah, I'm not loving the shotgun.
I think it's not my type of gun.
It's hard.
You have to shoot fast, you know?
Yeah.
I need one of those.
I need one of them fast American guns.
You know what I mean?
None of these Russian flashing scopes for me.
For me.
Yeah.
All right, Queen.
None of them.
So be a deal.
Where do we go?
Oh, shit, I'm getting tugged.
Help me.
Thank you.
What?
You got it?
Nice.
Yeah.
Fuck you.
Nice.
I still remember the time you gave me a raw burger, that son
of a bitch.
That's not very American of him.
I'm going.
I'm going to eat a burger.
I tell you what.
I tell you what, Bobby.
Real good American burger made on you.
the propane gas my chainsaw chainsaw i hear crying me too i
hear crying every day of my life that's the weakness leaving
my body oh i hear what the oh help us help us i can use each
other i want to help us guys why don't you help us what did
they just left us this It's a doggy dog world out there.
Danger Lord, it filmed a yo.
I used to think that it was doggy dog.
Oh yeah, yeah, I know what you mean.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Doggy dog world.
I'll tell you.
I'll tell you what.
Is it down here?
I believe so.
Oh, Haru, what happened to not needing medkits, huh?
Sia pick up and need that medkit.
It's the nature from the Lord of Sailors.
Oh, sorry, Haru.
Sorry.
Sorry, Haru.
Ah!
Oh, jeez.
Oh, God.
Oh, guys, guys.
I need your help.
Ah!
I'm getting jocky.
Oh, no!
Stop.
Why can't I get out?
Oh, my gosh.
There we go.
Oh, God.
Oh, you win.
I'm allergic to women.
Get off of my body.
Sick, buddy.
I got you.
Yeah.
Not you.
I don't need no medicine.
I could just meditate.
My health will come back from normal quickly.
Manifest a healthy lifestyle and it will come to you.
Honestly, I need nothing but American burgers.
Then my health will come.
Well, okay, come here, Mitara Kong.
Come here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ooh, I sure do love medicine.
Chow down on that.
I love my prescription medication.
I'll tell you what.
Oh, sorry.
I was just testing it.
Careful, I'm gonna put a fire.
Move, move, move, move, move, move.
Could you warn me?
Oh my god.
I'm setting another fire!
give me fire oh my god turning up baby no color in your
future no color in my future no color in your future except
we handle that we say we handle that free ice cream quick
there's a safe Roman hair.
Oh, nice.
Get in, get in!
Nice!
But what if I don't want to get in?
What if I like it?
Shoot you down, you son of a bitch!
Ah!
Okay.
How unpatriotic does he come to?
Almost about Nice!
Absolutely unpatriotic.
It was about to die.
Yee-haw!
That's the patriotic experience yay i love the fourth of
july there's a there's a use your health kit i'm using my
health watch this guys you're giving me anxiety i'm gonna
meditate real quick do it i am meditating i have gotten i
now my ankle has magically fixed itself that's crazy crazy
let's go girl you know what i'm saying Is there any gas on
my chain muscle?
I don't think there's any gas here.
Don't talk to me, but the rats.
About the rats.
Which way do we go?
Oh, no, no.
Let's go here, I think.
Because this one's bigger.
There's a...
What is this?
Oh, I'm in this way.
Oh, I think we can go either way.
Oh.
Maybe.
There's, like, a few drugs here and stuff.
Yeah, there's some weapons here and stuff.
And some pills.
a man climbing up a ladder i don't know if he was good or
bad um only oh man climbing up ladders are bad and snakes
remember that is that a man i love my banana which one which
one jockey yay nice what was the gun i like was it this one
hunter oh what do i hear where
letting anime whip and get on top you like that that's very
unethical KK is better on this map wait pipe bomb what do
you mean yeah I got a pipe bomb oh I got AD what AD oh I
thought you said ADD I'm like me too I thought she was
saying ADD let's go here what do y'all think yeah this is
the way okay if you see zombies you know you're going the
right way if you see zombies better hit Wow, wow, he's
zombies in the five nights of Freddy's.
Hit him right between the eyes.
Would you like a karate patty?
No, but I'll take some free ice cream.
Yummy, yummy.
Free ice cream!
Oh my gosh, leave me alone.
Ugly
Thank you ladies Ye-ha to you What is this accent?
I don't think that was I'm Bethany Ann and I lost my left
nipple in a hot dog eating contest in Tucson, Arizona This
mission I'm starting to remember Ye-ha Hey, what are your
kids?
You about letting a building fall on top of you, Lactane,
you dumb bitch?
Um...
I can get you back up.
I'll get you moving again.
Oh, my, my, my, my, my.
What?
It wasn't me.
It wasn't me at all.
I put the shoe in the damn gas machine.
It wasn't me.
Oh, no.
free ice cream.
Ice cream!
Where are they going to be?
I have a Molotov.
Uh, me too.
I have a pipe bomb.
I have Molotov.
Oh, no, I have pipe bomb.
I have a pipe bomb.
Uh, there's a guy right there.
I'm allergic to those, baby.
Oh, sorry, baby.
I shot you.
Me?
I just shot you in the in the genitalia.
Honestly, I was just intimidated by how big it is.
I swear to God.
I thought to myself, if I can get here, him to have a little
smaller genitalia, I'll be less intimidated.
What are you talking about?
I'm inside.
Let's see.
I wish I was inside the warm.
I'm now stuck in here.
Let's go.
Guys, we still need you.
Get up.
What are you talking about?
We're killing.
That's the most patriotic thing you could do.
Come back, you unpatriotic, girls.
Oh, oh, sorry, I didn't know.
Oh, gosh.
Hi, Rupo.
Where are you going over there?
I'm drinking beer.
Am I dying?
Don't die.
Come drink beers with me.
There's a timer.
Oh.
And
it's okay.
Don't drink beers in the red wine blue.
Oh, there's a tongue knot.
Tong Tong Tong Tong Tong Tong
Tong Guys guys I need your help I got you Sorry he hit me
right as I was providing you Yeah I know Penny I need your
help Okay I'm coming Oh wow Oh gosh hello Leave me alone Hey
what am I Oh my god leave me alone You're so obsessed with
me I know Oh that's a gun Down here you bitches I'm seeing
like a dog I'm coming It's three dog what okay guys there's
another there's another health kit here if anybody needs oh
i need if i can have it yeah i have it have it here i'm
gonna do the other one weak weak as hell me who needs
medicine this day and age not you know what i just meditate
i don't think about the the consequences i'm already dead so
i don't even think about getting hit oh i saw you speaking
Taking a medicine in the middle of the night.
I saw you take them drugs.
It was a medicine.
It was a...
That one very American of you.
Guys, I have a pile.
Next time the zombies...
Oh, shit.
Oh, I got a donkey.
Oh, thank you.
Next time the zombie war comes.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
I need your help.
Oh, sorry.
It's okay.
I'm going to biobomb them.
It's a really good...
Weapons over here!
I'm gonna biobomb them?
Right now?
I did a little close.
I think I did a little too close, but it's okay.
That's fine, probably.
Whoopsie daisy.
Your Honor, I plead Whoopsie Poopsie.
I cannot even see where I am.
Oh, from up the stairs?
The stairs?
The stairs, the stairs?
I got you!
Oh, okay.
No, we go down here.
This way?
Go down.
Where do we go now?
Where do we go?
Where do we go down here?
Uh, Haruka, I think you had the wrong one.
Whoa, it's right here!
Oh, it's right here!
Oh, sweet!
Yeah, I'm ready to get stinky smelly!
Oh, wait, I'm actually stuck.
Wait, how do I get out?
Oh, there we go.
Where are you?
Whangy-whangy.
Nice, nice.
Behind.
Oh, there's a witch!
There's a witch!
Where?
I hear her crying.
Where is she?
aggro her let's be careful i think i heard her he doesn't
speak by her well we can just aggro her oh charge it where
okay i think we found the charges oh my gosh i think we
found the charger thank you i don't think we should aggro
the witch because then they bring a hoard and we'll die why
don't we just man up wait where did they come from the witch
where did they go they've been married a long time guys
there's a little secret way here There's a witch.
Oh, there's a witch.
There's a witch.
There she is.
Let's kill her.
No, don't kill her.
Okay, fine, fine.
Let's go.
Just avoid her.
I think this is going to bite us in the ass.
Yeah, let's go over here.
That guy is dead.
I think this is going to backfire.
Like, you know what?
I don't like the rules.
We're not going back.
It'll be fine.
I'm just a little follower.
I think you just want to kill the witch.
Guys, guys, here, here, here.
I want to kill everything.
I'm ready to kill.
I'm going to kill Bill.
Oh, there's a secret passage over here.
What's this?
Yeah.
What is this?
Ah!
Guys!
Oh, okay.
You did it, honey.
Thank you.
Molotov.
Wait, is there another witch?
Uh...
Huh?
No, I just made the ring.
The witch is the ring.
Like that girl with the ring.
Oh, really?
That's so freaky.
Yeah.
Oh, I see her.
I see her.
She's up there.
Yeah, yeah.
We went around her.
Smart girls.
I think it's here.
Stop crying, you baby.
Wait, no, I think we went around.
I think you went in a circle, yeah.
Um, you're not- You're not excused.
I don't think it's this way either.
I don't know where to go actually.
Oh.
Oh, nice.
Nice!
Nice.
what about so the witch is there i think we have to go to
the left yeah we're hard to win that way yeah we're higher
wind i think okay okay wait for the bio wait for the bio oh
there was a guy crawling through it that's so freaky it was
wet in here it's because it's a sewer
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, wait, I can't, oh, I can't say anything.
What happened?
Okay, the waste is over there.
Be careful, be careful.
Yeah, come to the, where Hanya is.
This way, this way.
Hanya, let me go ahead and use that.
I don't accidentally shoot you.
Oh, you guys are headed towards her though.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Wait, is this a trick?
Hanya, Hanya, don't go!
Hanya, Hanya, come back!
Oh!
Uh-oh.
Um, you guys?
I'm no scared of bitches.
Hell yeah.
I got him.
Reloading.
So not this way.
Ah!
Are you guys...
Do you need ammo, Haruka?
Oh, hold on.
Let's come back here.
Wait, I don't have the ammo.
Okay.
No!
Haruka's her old witch!
I'm scared no, Haruka!
You're gonna be okay Well now that the witch is dead It's up
here, it's up here, it's up here Oh my god, it was here the
whole time This one What a thrill No, that's not a good guy
No, there's no good guys in this game I could really use
Wait, how can I not get up?
You have to look up Bunch of guns over here Bunch of guns
over here Safe house over there Oh, safe house right here?
Are you sure that's a safe house?
Well, it says house with a plus sign.
Do you see?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's right there.
You jerk.
I didn't know.
Yanta!
Are you sure there's a safe house over there?
There's a med kit right here.
Wait.
Oh, I love to have it.
Let's see.
Yeah, I'll get you inside.
I'll get you inside.
Thank you.
Let's close the door.
Okay.
I'm going to walk to you, baby.
Oh, my.
I got mid you're kind of killing it.
You're kind of cracked with it.
Nice!
I like to kill.
What did you say, mid?
Come here.
Oh wait.
Are you?
Oh, here we go.
Oh, thank you.
Girls, girls, girls.
There's three med kits over here.
We are not leaving here without you bitches healing.
I'm watching television.
Haruka, you...
There you go.
It's my favorite channel.
Is that a shotgun?
I think that's a shotgun.
I think I'm gonna do this one, right?
Sorry, grandpa.
Grandpa, grandpa grew up as an iPad kid, clearly.
Guys, there's...
Okay, I'm gonna take it.
Oh, we're in the hospital.
This is so scary.
I am terrified.
We're in the hospital.
Hospital time.
fall in oh you guys already i am happy medication sunshine
in a bag oh that's a oh oh freak me out freak me out freak
me out oh oh freak me out freak me out oh freak me out oh it
was like an oxygen tank before you go go why are skeletons
so funny
Oh, I see him.
Oh, jumper, jockey, jockey.
I have some jockey.
I got him.
Doe, tashi, marsh.
Don't move.
Oh, wait.
Oh, are we got killed?
Oh, watch out.
Watch out.
Sorry, I was scratching.
my nose oh my god now you made my nose itchy scratch scratch
scratch scratch how do you say like itch itch or scratch
scratch in japanese you're like you got to come through the
doorway kai ue is uh itchy oh wait wait how do i get to you
guys i'm lost so much damage oh that oh this way Oh, thank
you.
What does this oxygen do?
Does it just explode?
Oh, I found out that it exploded.
I think that's the answer.
Yeah, I got the answer.
Thank you, everybody.
I got him.
Jockey!
Oh!
I thought that was a sparkler.
Nice blast Thanks.
Busting makes her feel good!
Busting, Busting, Busting.
Oh!
I got you, princess.
Thank you.
Busting made me feel good.
Busting, Busting, Busting, Busting, Busting, Busting.
I didn't know she was there!
Oh.
Don't worry, I think that's the point, girl.
Um...
Hehehehe.
So you're probably wondering how I got here.
Funny story.
It's kind of funny.
Oh, thanks.
You're welcome.
It was like... It was like...
I actually saved you guys because I took care of her, you
know?
Oh!
Is it gonna... Oh!
you i didn't know you were that close this is the infectious
area oh this is so creepy so creepy there's gonna be a
horror coming in if we call this elevator a horror there it
is
among us oh my god oh my god
the night are we good oh almost oh whoa oh he did hurt me
through the door oh annoying i'm about to die i only have to
oh my god i got him oh you got him one more hit and i am
dead okay oh oh spinner
where's the elevator why is it so slow it shouldn't be this
slow at a hospital that's dangerous among us among us coming
among us coming Oh my god.
Oh my god.
There's so many among us!
Oh fuck, big guy, big guy, big guy!
Guys, I am...
Oh you guys are down!
Oh no!
He got him?
I got him.
I got you.
I got you, oh he made some money.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh.
Grab some more.
A bio.
Oh, there we go.
Oh, four's my lucky number.
4's my favorite number.
30 is my favorite number.
4 is my favorite number.
Miss, hit your own favorite number.
Oh, wait.
Is that your favorite?
I got this number first.
It's dead.
Why's everyone picking four?
Miss, I liked number four before you were dead.
I liked four forever.
Four as old.
Four as.
4 plus infinity!
It's the day that I was born, my flesh woman!
Hence, it's mine!
Okay, how do we both like the number 4?
How about that?
How about we both can like our number 4?
If we like 44, we can split the 4, you know?
No, I like 2.
I like 24.
Oh.
Oh, sorry.
I keep like timing out of my game and then clicking back in.
Just right click back in, that's what I do.
Behind you, Haru?
It says stay out of the line of fire.
Wow, this is such a beautiful scene.
I'm sorry, you scared me!
Don't come running up on me, old man!
I was getting pushed over.
I was just looking over.
Wait, did you fall?
Yeah, I did.
Whoopsie poopsie.
Oh, there's a smoker nearby.
Hey!
I'm coming.
Oh, I'm coming.
Smoker.
You got her?
Yep.
Smoker.
I got you.
Listen, we both collected number four.
This is a truce.
Good job, girl.
Yes, the truce.
Take your medicine.
Good job.
Wait, what about me?
You both didn't make a truce with me.
I don't have enough.
My brain's not calm enough to meditate right now.
Okay.
So I need to find a nice, calm spot to meditate.
You know what I'm saying?
There's a thing to blow up.
Blow it up, Mint.
No.
Listen to the demons in your head.
No reason to...
Oh.
Reloading.
Smoker.
I hardly even know her.
Is it this way?
Careful.
Did you blow up the gas tank?
For funsies, what if there was enemies?
Oh my.
What if we had to go that way?
Well, we could wait.
Uh-oh, I hear music.
I hear a little guy.
Nice.
Poor toes.
I got the boomer.
I killed Matara Khan.
So you're seeing Peter's head being ripped apart.
What?
Honestly, living with you is worse than death.
I don't even live.
You're not living with me at all.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I like to get shot by you.
Oh, nice.
You can shoot me as many times as you want.
Yay.
Just you.
Is that a spear?
I'm going to bleed out here soon, guys.
let you know i'll bleed it out take it deeper just to throw
it away wait there's a safe house safe house safe house safe
house safe house safe house safe house safe house i'll bleed
out in here get your bombs and your coffee look at her go
healing up silver the hedgehog oh
Yeah.
Beep, beep, beep.
I only did the most damage because she was on top of me.
That's the most action you'll ever get.
It's true, actually.
Dang, why'd you have to tell the truth like that?
Hold on, I gotta meditate real quick.
Why are you such a truther?
Girls, get your health packs.
Get your med packs.
Ooh, that was a good meditation.
Don't forget them.
There's a Molotov and a pipe bomb and a pipe dream No, it
doesn't three days.
What's a better gun, everybody?
This one?
Number one?
Or this one?
Oh, it takes four days to change.
No, it doesn't.
It takes two and a half pounds.
Number two.
Move during the day.
Or this one, number three.
Only come out at night.
That's not true.
They're here all the time.
No zombie is safe.
No zombie.
I'm keeping this gun.
I like Chicago.
I saw it happens in five minutes.
Let's go!
Oh, he wouldn't have that one.
Did we take all the med kit?
Let's fucking go!
Kill, kill, kill!
Oh, I should have reloaded.
That's embarrassing.
His little butt!
I saw his butt!
I saw his little butt!
That's embarrassing.
What?
So embarrassing.
Oh my god.
Why was your butt out like that with dummies on me?
I saw your butt.
embarrassing hello hello hello oh god oh god oh god oh god
oh god oh my god oh my god oh my god my god i had help and
now i don't what's going on was it here well which one of
you's non-americans
Damn.
No, no, hey Nick, come here, come here, come here.
I got
it.
I think the jockey just, or the cutter, I think he just fell
to his death.
Come on, goat.
That was so funny, I listened to him scream.
I've heard his final words.
Oh, how do I get up here?
Wait, how do I get up here?
Oh, there we go.
You climb, bitch.
I'm trying.
Oh, this here.
Right here.
Oh, this kind of looks like a Batman.
Oh.
Oh, this is a perfect time for a sniper.
Get away from me!
Get away from me.
I'm talking to you!
I'm talking to you, Batara!
You freak!
Get away from me, you freak!
Barrel gets obsessed with me!
I'm not even listening to you anymore.
I think we have to go down here.
Batman!
Oh, I didn't miss, all right, I didn't miss at all,
obviously.
Yeah, that'd be crazy if I missed.
Why do I, oh, oh.
Sorry.
I'm trying, oh, help me please, I'm getting, I'm in an
anime.
Matara, I'm not Matara, I'm coming, okay, never mind.
Did you just talk to yourself in the third room?
I called you Matara, my ex.
Listen, I am all video games out.
I am old and this game is a lot for my old women brain.
It is a lot.
It is so much.
It's okay.
I'm Mataura now everybody.
Hi, honey.
Hi, everyone.
Hi, man.
I love me.
There's a grenade launcher here if anyone wants to.
Wait, there's a medkid over here.
And a medkid.
Oh, medkid.
There's a medkid, there's ammo, and there's a gun.
Why do you say like it's a bad thing that I like boobies,
you know?
I love boobies and cute girls and cute girls with boobies.
There's a grenade launcher over here.
Yeah.
I like my gun.
I love you.
Yeah, I'll take it.
Take it, take it.
Rescue's coming, girls.
Defend yourselves.
Let's all stand together and then, yeah.
Oh, there's health kits right here, by the way.
I'm throwing...
There's health kits where I'm at, guys.
I'm throwing, um, I'm throwing gasoline if anyone wants to
blow it up.
Okay, maybe I like my gun better.
Spitter.
Where's the spitter?
I don't know.
Oh.
Oh my gosh.
There's a health kit near me guys if you want.
Hanya?
No!
I got you.
Girl, don't worry.
Oh god.
Hold on.
Wait, who did I just see?
I'm here trying to help Hanya, but I need your guys.
Hanya, can you keep shooting the ones in front of you?
I'm trying.
Oh no.
Oh, we got the Jackie.
I got the Jackie.
I can't help you.
I'm saving Hanya.
Um, I'll just die, I think, actually.
I think I'm just gonna die.
Yeah, I'm down.
I'm sorry, I was down.
I wasn't near you.
Hania, dyeshobu, use your medkit.
Oh, sorry if I shot you.
Use your medkit, Hania.
Okay, okay, I will.
There was medkit nearby me, but I don't know if you guys
heard me.
Yeah, we're coming.
I have one, so I just gotta get revived and I'll be good.
I'm coming, you jerk.
Oh, spitter.
Francis, let's go.
Get up.
He's a quitter.
Francis.
Who was Francis?
Oh, that's me.
How was Francis?
What a suit.
Haha, he's showing his butt.
So embarrassing.
Ah, your dog.
Lucky me.
Oh, I'm reloading, I'm reloading.
Oh, you got him though.
Silly zombies.
What do you think?
I really want to stay at your house.
Tank?
Oh, this is behind you.
Oh, behind you.
I got taken.
Thank you, Hadou.
My angel.
Uh-oh.
Metal gear!
No!
Wait.
Oh, my gosh.
Throw!
I'm throwing a pipe bomb!
Uh-oh.
Wait.
Oh, oh.
Watch out!
Oh, my gosh.
Please reload.
What's taking so long?
What was taking so long?
Hadou!
I got you!
Oh, fuck, I can hide that.
Oh, fuck.
Thank you!
See you!
Oh my gosh!
Get right.
Uh, Bio spit her down.
Bio spit her down.
I see her.
Oh, Mint, Mint, I can heal you.
I don't see her anymore.
Where are you?
A guard.
Thank you!
My angel!
I'm gonna throw a bottle in the middle.
I'm not a guy.
Min, get out of the way.
I'm trying to, I'm trying to.
I'm trying!
What?
Is there any ammo anywhere?
Yes, on a lot of spots.
There is?
Why can't I find anything?
Oh, here, here.
Oh, thank God.
Reloading.
Firing a home.
Oh, big guy, big guy.
Oh, fuck.
I need help.
I got him.
Thank you, girl.
You're welcome.
See, isn't it a good thing that I reloaded?
Oh, I need his help.
He's gonna die.
Thank you.
Die!
Zombie!
I like when their body parts fly everywhere.
Getting tongue, getting tongue, getting tongue!
Oh, where are you?
Oh, I got you!
I got you!
Hold on!
I'm reloading!
Are you good?
Tommy.
Oh, I can't see.
Uh-oh.
Oh, gosh.
Get off of me!
Get off me, stupid zombie!
Oh, sorry, that's you.
Oh!
Holy!
This is a really long we're coming to save you guys.
I know, right?
Clearly, oh, I'm pinned.
Tank here.
I'm pinned.
Oh, thank you.
There's ammo up here if you come to us.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
There's tank here.
I hear Thanos.
I'm coming.
Okay, okay.
The tank is coming.
Do we have any bombs?
He's here, he's here.
I see, I see, I see him, I see him.
Oh, wait.
I can't go this way.
Oh, shit.
Bombs away anywhere?
Any waddle the way?
No.
Waddle, waddle.
Get him, get him, get him, waddle, waddle.
Metal gear, I'm sorry.
I love you.
Nice.
Oh, sorry.
Oh, my gosh, you scared.
I'm sorry.
You scared.
That was my, please.
Oh, the chopper is here.
Guys, uh, boomer.
And we got a final ward.
Where do we go?
Final ward?
Fuck.
Please don't shoot me up right here.
Oh, guys, there's a charger behind us.
Guys, guys, guys, guys, guys.
Can you revive me, please?
I don't know about that mint I'm gonna shoot you oh my god
we're coming I'm just gonna chill in here honestly oh hey
hey hey this is an exclusive club shit oh my god oh my god
oh my god oh no Rex please
There we go.
Nice!
I punched the shit out of that tank.
Good job.
Look at him.
Look, he's so cute down there.
He's so upset.
Yeah, he looks so upset.
He's so cute.
Oh, he just fell down.
Okay.
Yay!
I'm so tired from This game is so overwhelming But it was so
much fun It was Should we call it there then?
Yeah, maybe I'll hear you Yeah, we can We can Zero deaths,
let's go baby Are we all zero deaths?
All zero deaths All zero deaths Drugs used me Yeah Yeah, um
I bombed me You have a bit of a problem Maybe Oh Oh, the
melee kills.
Good job, girls.
That was so much fun.
Yay!
Nice.
That was so fun.
I'm sorry if I yelled a bit much.
Oh, girl, this is a yelling game.
Don't worry about it.
You're fine.
Yeah, this is a yelling game.
Okay, I'm sorry for the 51 friend.
It was you last time, too.
Oh, my gosh.
What?
I revived the most.
I protect it and I healed the most.
Still getting that headshots, baby.
We're perfect.
Girl, you got 11%.
It's nothing to flag about.
That's still better than new you.
That was a lot of fun.
Yeah, it was nice to revisit this game again.
I know.
I loved it.
Yeah, it was fun.
It was fun.
I feel like I can only play it like once a year.
Like not once a week.
It's so like, oh man.
It feels like so overwhelming.
It is very.
It's every like emotion I feel and it's just like, Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Who is still gonna stream for a bit?
Me!
After this.
Okay.
Yep.
We're gonna do something fun and I'm gonna try to give you a
manual raid on your YouTube, okay?
Okay.
But just act surprised when it happens.
Manual raid.
Manual raid!
Bye bye everybody!
Thanks for playing!
Bye bye!
Bye-bye.
Bye.
I smell good.
I smell delicious.
Bye, stinky.
Bye.
No.
She said stinky and she thinks both of us are stinky.
I'm stinky in like a good way.
I'm a minty stinky, you know?
Mmm.
Oh, God.
I love the smell of mint.
I know.
Why did I say it like that?
Bye.
I'll talk to you later.
Bye bye.
Hold on, give me a second.
I need to.
I need to actually like simmer down from all that craziness.
Every time I play that game, it is so just all yelling, all
running, all screaming.
It is just a crazy.
Okay.
you guys let's relax now actually hold on this is called
rain relax what does it sound like what's it sound like oh
okay this is relaxing yeah we're relaxed
oh oh nice to see you playing it for the first time with
henna yeah she's such a game where Two, thank you!
Fun.
Thank you.
Mint carried not even a little bit.
Not even a fraction.
Well, I guess technically a fraction because I was in the
game.
Takizo, thank you for the five gifted.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Oh, Iron Notive's not on here.
Now they're showing up.
Sorry about that.
You were MVP at one point.
Notice that we're off the screen.
Yeah, I noticed.
Thank you.
Murphy, thanks for the 20.
Oh my gosh, I'm feeling so relaxed right now.
Oh, Kmart, thanks for the 10.
A.K.S.C.F.
Thank you for the 10.
Oh, Doug Dimm a Dome Carry.
Actually.
Oh my gosh, it was so fun to see Ray and then also Rex.
so fun so fun so fun raymac thank you for the pop goof dude
oh sorry if that was just like everything overload i know it
was for me holy cow but it was it was fun your mod choices
were top tier thanks i like looked really hard for some
really silly ones.
Thanks for that.
Haven't seen a good L4D in a long time.
Thanks.
Maharu is like really carrying.
It was so funny and listening to
Mata really trying to like ring everybody in and everyone's
like nah.
I kind of felt bad though.
Free!
I cream i'm gonna hear that in my sleep yeah it did get
funnier and funnier i was just like you know that picture of
like of like of one person like holding on to three
different um leashes and everyone's going everywhere that i
think that was matara today oh see more thanks for though
for the 10 gifted thank you had a rough day dealing with
computer issues glad i could watch oh wait hold on sorry my
music glad i could watch you girls be goofy to keep my mind
off things yeah well it's friday you can also have the
weekend to just relax cool thanks for the time gifted thank
you thank you for the 50 gifted stop why also if you haven't
noticed i fixed the membership thing so the notice won't
show up a bajillion times and clog it up.
I figured it out.
Unfortunately, it won't show like if someone joins normally,
but I'll try to keep it.
I'll try to notice it when it happens.
What was the problem?
It wasn't really a problem.
It was just that if someone gifted a lot of Donut or a lot
of memberships, it would just like be like, so-and-so became
a member.
So-and-so became a member.
And it would like, it made the like really backed up.
What do you guys have planned for the weekend?
Mitro, thanks for the turn.
Well, the second things for the five.
Cinco de Mayo this weekend.
Woo!
Uh.
Favanos.
KBBQ with friends tomorrow?
Oh my gosh, that sounds so good.
Oh my god, KBBQ in so long.
Just chilling.
Zomboid server with friends?
You haven't had enough zombies?
I think I've had it.
I'm all zombed out.
I'm zombed out.
I'm a ghost.
Not a zombie.
I'm dead.
Not undead.
Going to a convention next to day.
Sorry if I don't catch change.
Wait, what con?
What convention is this weekend?
I, um...
Oh, Saucon!
I think that's every weekend, though, actually.
Why can't I remember Saucon, but I can't remember the names?
Oh, well.
Plants vs.
Zombies 15th anniversary this weekend.
No way, really!
Wow.
Meep!
Thanks for the 10!
Gifted!
It's a local convention in Mexico.
Oh!
Awesome.
Wait, they have a convention during Cinco de Mayo?
I guess, I mean, I guess it's kind of the same when, like,
uh, what's it?
Anime Expo does theirs on, on, uh, 4th of July.
Thanks, man.
What did I do?
Hooray, thank you.
When I started watching you, I just quit my job.
Leaving was scary, but watching you inspired me to push to
the fear.
Monday, I started my apprenticeship because...
Airplanes!
Thank you, Mint, for being my push.
Oh my gosh, Ray, we need you in the world right now,
actually.
Oh my gosh, I was looking at my flights for some of my
upcoming events that I'm going to.
You guys, two of my flights are Boeing.
If I don't make it, go on without me.
I might be seeing the light this...
Not this weekend.
Chiron-chai, thank you for the toladi gift, thank you.
Uh, but they're not...
Can I call dibs on your stuff, sure?
Um, no, it's not the 737 max, but it is a 737, so I'm kind
of scared, legitimately.
But, uh, um, I would say YOLO.
But I'm already dead.
And I can't.
I can't change it.
Which is the worst part about it.
Don't worry.
You'll be safe.
What's the worst that could happen?
I'll just make sure my Yoda.
You only die once.
Momo Raid.
Thank you.
Hi Mataro.
Mose.
Hello, hello.
Momo Raid, Manuel Raid.
Momo Raid.
What are you guys doing here?
What?
Oh, my gosh.
Where did you all come from?
Why are you gifting 15?
Stop that.
Batarokan, I'm going to tell your mother.
Batarokan.
In case anyone is watching, Mint Knows Information is about
to blow the whistle on it.
Get her!
Bleep, bleep!
What if the door blows open, though?
And I just float away.
I just float.
What if I land in Ohio?
Oh, no.
Paperbacks.
Thanks for the 10 gift.
Thank you.
Morris, welcome to Mambushup.
I think you have five minute follow mode.
So my take of...
It was so fun.
Matara, good luck with your tournament later this month.
I hope...
It's probably good that you played this time because imagine
not playing before the tournament and seeing how
overwhelming and insane it is.
My message doesn't show on the screen.
I see you right there.
Ropewash!
Thanks for the 10 gift.
Thank you.
The game is crazy.
Just like, you have to like, put, okay, are you gonna be
streaming it?
Because if you're not streaming, you can literally like put
yourself into a trance and not even like talk.
You can just, oh, you could just, like,
like this.
Also, do you like my, do you like, do you like my really
calming music after all of this?
Can you just play the bunny game again?
Sasuga.
I have to continue because I want to get to the parts where
you play with the cameras too.
But did I even leave space in my schedule for next week?
Let me see.
I have another collab next week actually.
I'm not going to say you...
Oh wait, I do.
I do have a room.
Okay, bunny garden.
I can do it.
Hmm.
Um.
Uh.
Matara already said who it's with?
Huh?
I don't think I told her.
No, that's not next week.
They're thinking of Deep Rock Galactic.
Oh, yeah.
Deep Rock Galactic's not next week.
No, no.
Hippicuma.
Thanks for the vibe, Kipta.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
you rock and stone but that's eventually that's eventually
um yeah i know that matara and i have been collabing a lot
and we also have the podcast it's because i'm like nervous
to talk to people so she she kind of helps facilitate some
things sometimes proud of how much you've been networking
i've been trying i've been trying for real so You know...
I'm trying to talk to people.
Borrowing that extrovert energy.
Prince Wendru...
Thanks for the five gifted!
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Gotta get to the 500k.
I gotta get to the 200k first.
I don't even...
What am I even at?
I don't even know.
Oh, 98.
98.
Crazy.
Did I make it in time for the stream?
I mean, it's kind of over, but not like the gameplay is
over, you know.
The gameplay is over, you know.
You might get them this weekend.
Who knows?
zero and thank you for the 50 thank you thank you thank you
oh i'm not worrying about it at all don't don't take it
don't get me wrong i'm not just like why why am i not at
200k no i'm just i'm just i think it's cool that i mean uh
when i when i left i was at 10k and now i'm almost at 200k i
think that's a huge accomplishment so i'm not worried about
it at all to be honest Yeah, I'm just vibing.
I'm having a good time.
Yeah.
Hashtag carried by Matara.
Slash sarc.
You have to put the sarcasm in there.
Bravo!
Thank you for the 50 gift.
Thank you!
Vivi Gore, thank you for the 10 gift.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
That's good that you're having a good time.
I'm not going to have a good time next week, though.
Because, um, I might do an Atlantis non-Nazzo Interim.
Um...
So, I might have a really bad time next week, actually.
Uh-oh.
Why do I do this?
An accomplishment?
What's so bad about it?
It's like...
Peak Kusuge.
The game is just...
It's...
It's notoriously difficult and obtuse.
And love the piano in the back.
Yeah, we're calming down after a very stressful and crazy
game of Left 4 Dead.
Yes, trash NES game.
Exactly, it is a trash NES game, for real.
Which game?
Atlantis No Nazo.
I must try it.
I've been wanting to for so long.
Yeah, we're calm.
We're calm.
If you hear my voice, you are going into a trance.
And you will...
You will drink water.
I love it because it's the first game, Arino Challenge, and
Game Center CX.
That's kind of why I want to play it.
I saw him play it and and Korone play it.
And I admire Korone's endurance and skills as a gamer.
So it's not that I'm like...
How do I say this without seeing me?
It's like, I don't want to copy her, but I'm like, oh, she
did this challenging game.
I want to do it too.
So I'm like, I will try.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm inspired.
I admire her.
Yeah, inspired.
Matara told us to give you money, so we obey.
Why would you listen to anything she ever says ever?
Finally caught you live!
Are you planning on replaying any of the MGS games?
Corky, I'm glad you asked.
I plan on replaying all of them!
Yeah!
Well, I'm still deciding on MGS 5.
Also, oh, wait, I almost said something.
Well, Snappy, thanks for the 10 gift.
Um, like the, when I, when I was, like, the last time I
played five, I was on the fence about playing it before two.
But I ended up playing it because I was just craving.
I was, I was, I was starving for the, uh, for the more Metal
Gear content.
So, um, hmm.
so i've based my personality on me anthony anthony you based
your personality on a silent protagonist
um but i think i think if i play v again maybe um i might do
something similar to how like with april 30th i only did the
skateboarding game like maybe i'll do certain missions or
something like Oh, made headband for one year win.
Um, didn't I have that?
Uh, but it, but, but YouTube erased it.
Um, I have to re-upload it.
Holy cow!
Oh my gosh, sorry.
I just opened up YouTube to go check that.
And I saw the amazing digital circus is at 9 million views
in five hours!
Holy cow!
What?
oh my gosh the kitties went crazy in five hours nine million
views what is like the i wonder what like the record is for
like most views in a certain amount of time the episode is
good um i got to the part where like they were riding up on
the gators and then i went and took a shower yeah there's an
episode two out there's episode two so if you want more palm
knee action monthers are chomping at the bay oh you have six
a month calm down no um i tried re-uploading the headband
before and it said that it was not one-to-one so i have to
just i just have to what's the word um resize it if you ask
me made mint channel mintofan told you should get 100
mintillion views every hour of every day yeah obviously
Mintillion.
I haven't opened up Cookie Clicker in a long time!
Oh my gosh, wait.
Cookie...
Oh, uh-oh.
Cookie, cookie.
Cookie Clicker.
Play.
Let's see how my cookies are doing.
Happy May the 4th and Revenge of the 5th from Australia.
Oh!
Is there any clone trooper class type squatter legion that
you like is your favorite, both from Legends and Canon?
Um, I, um, I, uh, um, oh my gosh, I've harvested 26 sugar
lumps while I was away.
Um, I've, um, uh, I've watched one Star War.
Yay!
Thank you for the ring!
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
But I really like, um, I really like the Stormtrooper
design.
like a long time ago I tried to get one printed for myself
I'm such a fake fan I did never even see I'm such a poser I
was gonna dress up as a star trooper and I wasn't even going
to I've never watched Star Wars so every time I think about
Star Wars I just want to watch Indiana Jones again you know
and Every time!
Every time I...
Aren't you a little short to be a stormtrooper?
What are you talking about?
There's no height requirement?
Members watch along of Star Wars, please.
We can only... We can watch just the first three, right?
That was a quote.
That was a line from the movie.
Wait.
I'm gonna guess.
Does Han solo say that that's my guess is he did he did did
he say that oh no go with captain hauser he's pretty close
to your color it's funny because i um he was whispering the
samuel jackson story time did i use this in that video i do
remember that video though but i don't remember if i did
music in Oh, and welcome to membership.
No, I meant the first three, like, the original first three.
But I do kind of want to watch the prequels, too.
I do kind of want to watch the prequels, also, because I
don't know.
I want to laugh.
But I've seen...
It's so bad.
I've seen Plinkett's reviews on...
From Red Letter Media.
I've seen his reviews about Star Wars.
But...
I never watched anything myself.
Doki Bird, FPS, VTuber, Facebook, TTV, YouTube.
Thanks for the five gifted.
Thank you.
Be there, they come.
In fact, Sheperton designs the studio.
I mean, the original Stormtrooper suits is selling the full
suit with the helmet and the blaster.
How much is expensive?
I'm curious.
How much is the...
I clapped when I saw it.
never watched them but i'm watching in chronological order
is it one of those is it a series that you like okay wait so
it's the prequels and then like the original three movies
that were made and then
and then uh what was the recent ones that were made um wait
four five six one two three seven eight nine 7-8-9.
I thought there were just two.
The sequels.
Wait, they just call it...
So it's the prequels, the originals, and the sequels?
It's only six.
Ha ha.
And then I have to watch...
The Mandalorian.
When does the Clone Wars happen?
When did I watch that?
I can't believe I'm surrounded by a bunch of fakes I'm sorry
clone trooper armor looks cooler I ammo especially Captain
Rex I'm like hold on Captain Rex oh I do like that I do like
that wait you said the the clone troopers um I don't know
they just don't look as I mean I think they look cool, don't
get me wrong.
But I think stormtroopers are cuter.
Yeah, I like the stormtrooper.
I like how his mouth is like a little triangle down.
It's so cute.
Oh wait, it's like that on the clone trooper.
But I also like that his head is bigger.
It's really wide.
He's got like a massive chin.
The helmet or the armor in general.
I don't really like the helmet.
Clone troopers have colors.
Clone trooper.
Trooper.
Ah!
The clone trooper armor looks almost the same as the
stormtrooper.
I should do have them side by side.
Storm.
Trooper.
Do you know about the Ewoks?
Are those the ones that go...
Rrrr!
Hold on.
I got this.
Rrrr!
Hold on.
Oh, that was pretty good.
That was pretty good.
That's a wookie.
Wookie.
Wait, so what you?
Oh!
Ewok.
Oh my god, they look like my old dog.
What?
I don't know if I like that.
Because I didn't like that dog.
It was really my mom's dog.
Star Wars only becomes watchable as an adult when you
realize that the Jedi are crocked Crooked cops and Luke
Skywalker was an android slave.
Oh, what is going on?
What?
Jawas are cute.
Jawas.
Oh!
Oh my gosh, they look just like...
They just look like...
The stab guys!
Final... The Tom...
Tom...
Tomberry?
Tonberry!
They look just like a Tonberry!
They look so cute, the Jawas.
Oh my gosh, even the plushies of them are so cute.
Oh, they're so, so cute.
Taunbury's from Final Fantasy.
I like them.
I have to, wait, what did you say about, they make a funny
noise too?
The Jawas?
sound like.
Jabba the Hut is really... I know that guy.
I know that guy.
He's the one that's... that enslaves Leia.
Uttini!
Please look.
I know Jabba the Hut.
I always thought that this guy was, um...
Emperor, Emperor, Emperor, Emperor, Emperor, hold on, no,
no, no, Emperor Palpatine.
I thought it was Emperor, Emperor Palpatine.
Stop making fun of me.
Emperor, Emperor Palpatine.
They look kind of similar, I think.
It's just kind of, they're both really wrinkly.
I think that's why it was.
I'm Pupapapap.
Stop making fun of me.
That's an old man.
One's an old man.
One's a slug.
Close enough.
And he talks like this.
I'm Pupapapapap.
Okay, I did it again.
What's wrong with me?
Marrow, welcome to membership.
I'm Emperor Palpatine.
He says, do it.
Do it.
It's like he's really here.
Palpatine is wife material, to be honest.
Is it like a gap moe?
Minter, you okay.
No, I think Leopard Dead really took a lot out of me.
I think Leopard Dead really took a chunk out of my brain.
Hold on.
I'm finding a good emote.
There we go.
Cute.
I'm embarrassed.
Okay, I'm embarrassed.
I'm embarrassed that I cannot speak properly.
I need to go to enunciation classes.
Actually, I've been really thinking recently how much I want
to take improv classes.
I've been thinking...
Zionia, look at the membership, thank you.
I've been thinking about how I want to do...
I did improv classes as a kid because I took a lot of...
I did like acting classes, I did dance.
I went to...
a school of the arts basically and so i um uh i was there
for like years um but i want to get back into improv for
like you know sometimes i like watch improv stuff and i'm
like how are they so quick how are they so witty you know
it's like oh my gosh i really want to and i like try to
consume a bunch of different kind of media and like you know
i know tick tock gets hated on a bunch but like honestly
because of how short form tick tock is and how much i'm
consuming like i'm watching i'm watching skits i'm watching
facts i'm watching dumb stuff like i'm able to like absorb
so many different topics within such a short amount of time
that it actually like i feel like it helps me drop out tv is
the who whose line i've been watching so much dropout oh my
gosh game changer is like the funniest show it's so good
like they man they saved college humor like dang game
changer is if you haven't watched it before it's so funny
it's really really good um but i've been here the whole time
it used to be called humor and then they um they changed it
but i watch i watch i only watch game changer and um
actually i only watch those two brendan is my wife they're
they're really good um konen o'brien recently released a
podcast video with dr arroyo it's like a whole improv video
a podcast one i will watch it konen o'brien is also just a
comedic genius.
There's so many comedians, so many people that are just so
witty.
I'm like, man, I need to, I want to study.
But it's also like, it's also just like, at the same time,
it's, it's, it's, what's the word?
It's like not overthinking stuff, you know?
You have to just be able to, if you overthink it, then you
can't pull it out of your, out of your brain so fast.
Sorry if this is talked about before, but I'm curious if
you've ever played the early Kojima game, Snatcher.
If not, you play as a police detective.
I know a lot about Snatcher.
Dude.
2-2-0-7-2.
Thank you for the super chat, by the way.
Actually, I do intend on playing Snatcher.
I own police knots.
I don't own Snatcher.
But I would love to play Snatcher for sure.
But also, I would have to get it in English.
You know, I would have to get it, like, translated and stuff
like that.
But I really do want to play it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Conan's an actual genius, too.
He graduated from Harvard.
Yeah.
You've got to be smart.
You've got to be quick on your feet.
Hmm.
So.
Um.
It's not sure I was an English release.
It does?
Wait, why was I looking for it in Japan every time?
Oh, the Sega...
Yes, the Sega CD.
Yes, I, that's why, okay, I do remember that's why I was
struggling because that's why it's so expensive.
Thanks, slow beef.
That guy.
Internet dude, welcome to Bamboo Show.
Which version of Snatcher?
There's several.
They all have meaningful differences.
I recommend SD Snatcher personally.
Oh.
Wait, what's the difference?
Also, Skeleton, I love your cat.
Post more of your cat.
very expensive getting it though and i don't have a uh i
don't have i might actually have to emulate it to be honest
but i could do that now i can i could do that so um uh yeah
usually i like to um i don't know i feel more authentic if i
play things as they originally were like you know how i
played twin snakes with my actual game cube and stuff like
that Thank you for the five gift.
I feel bad calling you that.
Mike Tyson.
Thank you for the five gift.
Thank you.
Mr. Rass.
Um.
But yeah.
Don't call him that.
Sorry.
Sega City is hard to set up, and Sega has been cool with
emulation.
Oh, okay.
That's good to know.
Because I don't even have a way to...
Like, I would have to...
I haven't looked into even a way, like, to port the console
onto my computer, you know?
Divert, thank you.
If the notification for this doesn't show, you can call me a
simp direct- Yo, oh wait.
Which one was that?
I think there's more than one.
Having a list actually made me think about what I can do and
want to do.
A summer list was a good idea.
I'm glad!
Have you watched very important people?
It's so funny.
I have not.
I have not, I have not.
I think actually, wait, are the donuts actually backed up?
I'm confused now.
Maybe they don't show on the screen, but they do actually
get backed up.
Hmm.
Interesting, interesting.
They seem to be.
Yeah, because I see yours too, Vera.
Good luck on the karaoke relay.
It's such a stacked event.
Have fun.
Yeah, I'm still, I'll be honest.
I'm still trying to, uh...
I'm still trying to think of what songs I want to sing.
but um maybe you'll like very important people oh by dropout
oh it's by dropout if you want more improv ah interesting
interesting the summer list that you would do a existential
crisis why it's just thinking of stuff you want to do it
doesn't have to be like a goal list or anything it can be
just like I want to I want to I want to eat a hamburger.
I want to grill my own hamburger.
I think I have an idea for what I want to do for the karaoke
thing, but I'm also kind of like
mmmmmmmmm like, I don't know.
I don't want to be that person is all.
Because I wanted to do like all Metal Gear songs.
But, and have it, like, kind of Metal Gear themed, but...
Um, I don't know.
People have asked for, like, a Metal Gear karaoke.
I'd totally be down for that, but...
There's honestly not that many.
Haruka!
Thank you!
Hamburg!
Hmm.
Do it.
Oh, man.
Metal Gear Rising does have a lot of songs.
I guess that's true.
I was always thinking of Metal Gear Solid.
Instead of a...
How long is each person's segment?
About 20 minutes, so...
That's why I was just like, well, you know, if someone's
just like, wow, maybe Mint is kind of cool, we have to know
the brain rot that they're getting into as well.
Just a little bit, maybe.
And also, even though...
Even though it's Metal Gear songs, they're still good songs,
so...
It's not that they're bad songs.
Only Limp Biscuit.
It's another improv show where they take comedians and put
them in costumes and makeup, and they improv their way
through the interview with Vic Michaelis.
It's so funny to see their improv.
Also, good luck with karaoke.
Thank you!
All the licensed songs.
Oh!
That's kind of fun, right?
Where it's, like, technically Metal Gear songs.
Have you played Death Stranding?
Actually, I was just thinking about that.
Oh my gosh.
I was just thinking about how I was like, man, I think I
will start playing more Death Stranding in my off time.
I say more, but I haven't touched it in a long time, but I
have definitely been thinking about it.
Take on me, take on me, take me home, take on me.
I'll be home in a day or two.
Strangling is an experience.
Wait, it's home?
Oh, I don't know.
Take.
Take on me lyrics.
Take on.
Oh, I'll be gone in a day or two.
I need water.
I've been out of I've been out of water for like two hours
now.
There's an English patch for police nots and options for
either PS version or Sega Saturn.
Oh, I will look into it.
Though I don't know much about emulation stuff.
So, um, it might...
Oh my gosh, they're so behind.
They just don't show up.
Oh my gosh, there's Mataras, Membo's...
there i'm sorry guys i thought i fixed it i guess it still
backs up in the stream labs part
stop playing the sad music i'm gonna cry it's not sad it's
relaxing it's relaxing time in fact it's making me tired
it's making me sleepy overall oh wow oh my gosh it's almost
midnight i might actually head out in about five minutes so
that I can get rest for tomorrow.
And, um...
Hmm.
Yeah.
Why do I have so many messages?
Oh.
Nice.
Oh my gosh, wait, I have so many messages.
Okay, I have stuff to do tonight.
Matta played Halo recently.
Fancy trying.
Oh, yes.
Actually, we talked about that earlier.
Um...
And yes.
I am interested.
I just have to... I have to just do it.
I was kind of like, though, I was kind of like...
I don't... Halo is one of those series that... Like, kind of
like...
With Metal Gear, I was overwhelmed by...
I was overwhelmed by...
Where to start and everything.
Um, now I feel that way with Halo, you know?
Good night, Mint.
Thanks for the stream today.
Good night!
No, it's not that I dislike FPS.
I actually very much like FPS.
I'm not good at FPS, but I like it.
I like it.
I'm just, I'm not good at it, but I think it's fine.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Sorry, we overwhelmed you.
No, it's not you guys.
It's overwhelming for me to know where do I start, you know?
So once I'm to that point, though, I will ask.
Once I'm to the point of saying, like, hey, I'm ready to
play.
I'm ready to play...
Uh, uh, uh, uh...
Ready to play, I almost said Metal Gear.
Uh, Halo.
Then I will.
Yeah.
Release order is always a good way.
What, so just start at Halo 1?
My aim is good?
You think so?
Oh my gosh.
It's like the first time anyone has ever said that to me.
My aim is good.
Do you think I'm a gamer for real?
This is maybe the best day of my life.
Oh my gosh.
I have a good aim.
I mean, someone in this room, and I mean, there's only one
ghost, some ghost in this room had the best headshot
accuracy, and I'm not, my hands are up.
Hands are up, I mean, Halo is my second favorite series of
all time, Seeking Mata and now Mint talking about its
overwhelming brain.
Stand proud, Mint.
You are a gamer.
Your hands are always up.
I mean, my hands are up.
What about Splinter Cell?
I have thought about Splinter Cell.
But truly, honestly, from what I heard, like, I don't like
stealth games.
I don't like stealth games, and what kept me going with
Metal Gear is the story.
And so knowing that the story, I've heard that the story for
Splinter...
You can correct me if I'm wrong, but I've heard that the
story for Splinter Cell is just kind of...
But also is, like, more stealthy than Metal Gear.
Right?
Am I wrong?
Metal Gear's a stealth game?
Yeah.
Down to play Devil May Cry?
Yep.
I am.
Tom Clancy.
Who is that guy?
I know it's Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell.
You know what?
You would probably never believe this, but a long time ago.
I don't remember how I acquired this.
But I used to have a full Splinter Cell standee in my room.
Never having played it.
Not knowing anything about it.
I don't remember how I acquired it.
Let me see if I can find, like, okay, if I look up Splinter
Cell.
If I can see, like, what the image was.
Maybe if I look...
I wonder if I look up Standy.
I wonder if I can even find it from that.
If I can find, like, a similar one.
What the hell?
What?
Oh, my God.
Wait, what?
I just, okay, wait, what?
I just looked up in Google.
Splinter Cell Stand-E.
And this is what appeared.
This is what appeared.
Me!
Why am I here?
Oh my gosh, that's so funny.
so funny i cannot believe that that even showed up it was
from our virtual youtubers on reddit wow that's really funny
wow i see a standy that's like on ebay but that's not the
one i had because the one i had distinctly had the uh it
looked he was like holding his gun up and he had the little
goggles on his eyes you're more loved than you think i don't
i don't know if that's love i don't know if that's love baby
don't hurt me don't hurt me no more i may be touching chairs
that's funny that's so silly i wonder when that was posted
um but yeah so that's my only exposure okay no no not my
only exposure that's one of my exposures with splinter cell
and my other exposure is watching that cutscene where it
references metal gear i just realized i sent the stream labs
without my name so it's from me also can you sing me a happy
birthday of course oh wait is it the one that's the akadono
oh my gosh kais me why why would you another super chat
after that.
Can't wait to hear you sing for the karaoke relay.
Glad it's happening on my birthday.
Good luck, boss, and have fun.
Thank you!
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, dear Heisman.
Happy birthday will you amitara accept gifts at off kai if
so what are some guidelines oh uh i don't know actually i
don't know anything about that let me write that down and i
will get i will i will say something on stream don't tell me
what to do stop um uh accepting gifts uh off kai i would if
i am able to accept gifts which i don't see why i wouldn't
be able to i would only ask that they are of a small size
because um i will be going uh i will be going somewhere else
i won't be going back home after i i cut off cut so uh no
bombs yeah obviously so yeah nothing too big please I took
the garbage out by myself this week so I bought myself the
$1,600 arcade cabinet as a little treat tip bringing you a
big crapper got it if I can find one in Japan I will maybe
get a big crapper I will and then I'll leave it on during
streams so you can hear it in the background all the time
you'll always hear it All the time.
Smash them on stream.
Ask Kusu!
Thanks for the five gifted.
Thank you.
Set it up to react to donos.
No one will donate again.
No one will ever want to send anything ever again.
Oh, you mean clapper.
No.
Wow.
No pipe bombs that have off-kite gifts.
Oh my gosh, you give me a gift and you're like, check your
inventory.
It's like when Acelot leaves the bomb in my inventory.
Ghost of Mint!
Thanks for the stream.
Work has been brutal the past few weeks.
New micromanager.
Oh no.
Changes in work environment, etc.
So this was my much-needed dopamine to start the weekend.
Otsuminto!
Full bomb in my pocket.
You hand me a package and it's like beeping and you're just
like, here you go!
My present to you!
Here you go!
Well, I talked over them what I was initially gonna do.
My bad.
Otsumito everybody Do a 24 hour cam of the clapper When you
were on vacation And be like You never left Exactly Thank
you Gato Ruffin Thank you I will see you guys tomorrow If
you come for the karaoke Um And uh Oh Yeah I think that's
all I got Um But yeah Karaoke tomorrow So be there Or be
square or something i don't know no one wants to be a square
wisp everyone wants to be a round plump wisp right big me
thank you leopard dead 2 is such a rush even just as a
viewer i know sorry if it was frustrating or loud or so much
at any point but i hope you guys had fun thanks for watching
and thanks for hanging out with me as always bye bye What's
a bastion?
Oh, bastion, bastion, bastion, bastion, bastion, bastion,
bastion, bastion, bastion, bastion, bastion, bastion,
bastion, bastion, bastion, bastion.