Hello!
Sorry, I took so long.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Hello, everybody.
Welcome to...
Duck detective.
I'm watching while on the toilet.
Don't tell my boss, Tihi.
is safe with me.
What the duck is going on?
There's all sorts of ducking and going on in here.
We're solving a quacking case today, everybody.
What the quack?
Detective Min solves the case of the crying wisp.
There's no solving that one.
Yes.
Actually, I saw this game on Twitter, and I was like, oh my
gosh, I love Detective Game.
Oh, heyo, gozaiyama.
I saw this game on Twitter, and I thought it looked really
cute.
And actually, this is not a sponsored stream or anything,
but they reached out to me, and they gave me a key for it.
So, thank you!
Happy Broccoli!
Thank you for the key!
Thank you.
Pilled!
Welcome to my booshah!
Thank you!
So, um...
Yeah, but, uh...
I was, uh, I was, like, wondering when I would play it.
Um, but, um, recently my throat has been, like, pretty bad.
So, um, I believe this game is, uh, voice acted from what
I've seen, so I think...
I'll be able to mostly just sit back and relax.
I think.
I saw this recently on Steam.
It was tempted to Supa asking you to play it.
Well, here we are.
Here we are, baby.
Thank you.
Haruka played it yesterday?
Oh, really?
Nice.
Cool, cool, cool.
Yeah, I'm so excited.
It looks so fun.
I don't know really anything.
about it i think well rather it looks very cute so um hope
your throat feels better soon thank you yeah um i think i
don't know ever since i really got sick my throat has never
has not really recovered so i'm hoping that while i'm in
japan um i won't be talking so much uh so i can hopefully
rest it even a little bit you know oh mint you me up thank
you I'm ready to duck around and find out the answer to this
mystery enjoy goes thank you for the 10 gifted thank you so
much thank you let me I'm gonna actually gonna turn down the
volume even though this soundtrack is awesome what's the
difference between sound volume and music well the sound
like overall volume.
That should be better.
Sound effects probably.
Ah, okay, okay.
Um.
I'm gonna turn the voices down just a little bit too.
This so far isn't so bad, but well, just in case.
If we can adjust anything that we need to.
If we need to.
I'm gonna get right into it though, because later on, in a
couple hours, I have a meeting which I'm very excited for
because it involves something that Matara and I are cooking
a little bit for the podcast so don't know if I can see the
whole stream pod squad but I hope you have fun with this
game and hope to get you a gift done for you wait hope to
get a gift done for you in time for off guy oh my god Luna
thank you see you there see you there hmm So, um, yeah,
let's just jump right into it then, right?
Would you like dialogue to auto-advance?
No, no.
Oh, detective mode.
Feel like a true detective.
Less information provided when incorrect.
Story mode.
A smoother experience for fledgling detectives.
More information provided when incorrect.
I don't know if you guys know this, but...
I was once a detective.
I've thrown in that towel.
I've thrown in the magnifying glass but somewhere deep down
in my soul well I am a soul deep down in in my one soul self
myself I still have it in me watching you and Matamama at
the same time because I can't sit well thank you for for
sticking around thank you for watching both of us mintante
made tante oh mid tante is actually so good right so
detective mode it is life wasn't easy oh my god being cheesy
i was a freshly divorced duck divorced not able to pay next
month's rent what do you mean thank you what do you mean
divorce Wait, hold on.
Can I change his audio?
Oh gosh, okay, we'll have to wait until...
He's a little loud.
I'm just going to turn it down just a bit.
Not able to pay next month the rent.
Not that I had paid for it this month yet.
Oh, no.
My brain felt foggy.
And I was trying to remember.
Where did all my money go?
I don't...
I ask that myself all the time.
And then I get an idol merch.
in the mail and metal gear merch in the mail and I'm like oh
divorce bro I probably end the divorce man his voice is so
good I had to retrace last night's steps mmm okay deductions
are a vital part of a detective's work find clue words by
questioning persons thank you I don't believe you where is
your duck tech badge I wasn't a duck detective I was a
detective deduction is so good find clue words by
questioning persons and inspecting your surroundings enter
clue words into blank spaces to solve deductions the nest
egg probably me spent his Last money on rent for blank.
Okay, cool.
Okay, one second.
Let's see.
Options again.
Voice volume a little down.
Okay, that should be better.
Sorry, I'm going to be adjusting the audio a little bit.
Duck detective's wife took the eggs in the divorce.
Oh my god, look at him go.
Oh, sorry, my bud.
Oh my god, I'm playing Rocket League.
It's so cute.
Squidward!
Thank you for the 20 gifted.
Thank you.
I've finished watching Ghost Trick at Work.
I've been wondering if you would play AI the Somnium Files
in the future.
Oh, maybe.
Maybe, maybe.
I can't believe Anna actually filed the divorce papers.
Anna!
Wait, so, Tab.
Oh, wait.
I'll go back.
We have items.
My last of money is one ish not enough to take a return bus
trip oh no and where are we somewhere okay second overdue
notice oh my god is detective okay I wonder at what point
they start kicking people out oh my god this is our bed this
fresh smell oh wait there's bread in our bed oh Sweet spongy
loaf.
You'll keep me safe in night.
Bread added to clues.
Oh, no.
Um, sir?
He sighs.
I took that photo of her in a secluded tulip field.
Wow, she's kind of hot.
Look at that long neck of hers.
We spoke for hours under the stars that night.
Oh, my God.
You know what I'm obsessed with?
I'm obsessed with pictures of those geese that saw the
meteor And how like they're so like blue and beautiful and
he's like looking up at the sky I'm obsessed with those
pictures
They're so cute And now and now she doesn't even answer my
texts.
Oh my goodness.
Don't don't be I mean you guys are divorced Get a grip man
get a grip.
No messages.
Oh You haven't even cleaned up the papers on your floor.
There's loaves on the floor.
This is wasteful.
This is wasteful Wasteful I won't be needing this badge
anymore.
I want to be wanted the way he wants that bread He is
something's going on with that bread in him.
I guess I can keep it as a souvenir.
Doesn't it say police?
My new job as the duck detective isn't going any better
though.
So he quit the force to become a detective well if things
keep going badly I can always sell it online I don't think
that's legal I have everything I need to solve this now okay
me the duck detective spent his last money on rent for the
duck detective what
Oh, on bread.
For the duck detective.
Not my proudest moment.
Oh my god, he's addicted to the bread, the spongy loaf.
Divorces like algebra.
You look at your ex and wonder why.
But the toast helps me to forget.
No, you got it.
It's not healthy for you.
Hannah!
Oh!
Mushy, Mushy.
I'm a different duck now.
Anna, take him back.
I haven't had a slice of bread in weeks.
I don't believe that.
I don't believe that at all, Detective.
You have to believe me!
Oh my God, he's so loud.
He's toasted.
You have you speaking to the duck detective.
The duck detective?
Why does he sometimes sound like Bo-Joy?
Jack let's discuss this in person now be there in an hour
his voice is out as they get that low I'm a doctor better
bus oh no your book your book's gonna get soaked I spent
more than half of my remaining cash on the bus fare oh my
god and here I was in front of their bus office some sort of
rundown call center.
Oh, I don't think you have any room to talk, mister.
I better crack this case or I won't even have enough money
to make it back home.
I'll come back.
Thank you.
Alright, let's see what else we got in here.
Oh, woo!
Oh, there's a koala over there.
Wait, what?
I'm just knocking everything.
I'm a menace.
I'm a menace!
Yeah!
Litter!
Who are you?
I'm staying here until I get my money back.
Oh, no.
So I found him with a hard loaf.
Bear bus?
Huh, more like scam bus.
Ooh, scam bus.
Ask for details.
You, uh, sound unhappy.
You bet I am.
Their stupid buses always arrive late.
The murder victim was the dodo, and they have already won.
Stop, no.
I came back from a work trip to the West and arrived here at
three of them.
Oh my god.
They don't even want to give me a refund.
How much did you pay?
Yeah, how much?
Um, yeah.
Too smart.
Smark?
That's not the point.
Oh.
Where did all my money go to Supertest?
Oh, thank you.
Don, thank you, Rico.
Thank you.
It's about the principle.
So true.
That is true.
It's the principle of it all, right?
What's over here?
Any evidence in the leaves?
Nope.
I think we're good.
He was going to go to therapy, but the therapist was a
quack!
What's over here?
Some- oh, a sign.
New bus routes starting in August.
Visit the scenic mountains of Salsichia.
Salsichia?
I'd always tell Anna we'd go there one day.
No, you have to stop thinking about her.
You know what?
At least she's alive.
Usually in these games, they're dead, right?
Okay, let's go inside.
Sao sitcha.
Bear butt.
Oh, wait.
What's in here?
This office looks like it'll worsen my depression.
Waiting for the bus in the rain.
In the rain bus, wait for...
Can I trade in my 500 mint coin for schmarks?
No!
Mint coin is priceless.
the highest price what are you talking about one one mint
coin is equal to probably 500 million quadrillion bajillion
macho million mint trillion of schmarks no
duck don't have depression you're too hot ducks are
excellent skateboarders oh my gosh sephia overload I can
already tell based on her face that the receptionist was a
tough one she's a tough cookie she wouldn't make life easy
for me my way into the office um weren't we called here to
investigate something shouldn't we then oh sorry sorry
probably she's not probably gonna like that i like the cat
little plushie right there oh sorry sorry no stay out it
says server room it's locked oh so sorry i'm so sorry okay
you know i'm the duck detective i'm here to investigate a
case i have to make everywhere look like my office
apparently okay okay do you work here i just said i'm a duck
detective okay the music's a little loud i'm gonna turn it
down no well then i can't let you in the rain was reminding
me of a name sean but i've been hired by someone from Bear
Bus.
Yeah.
Who hired you?
I didn't catch their name.
That's like the most important part, Detective.
Listen, buddy.
Buddy.
You better get out of here, or I'll have to call security.
There's always more to people than you might think.
Hey, Detective, where's your pipe?
Paige, what are you talking about?
I gave up the pipe long ago.
the half pipe, the round pipe.
What?
Daniel!
Thank you for that, Akasuba!
So it's a very stressful couple of days I work for Minstream
Heals.
My mind has been boisterous, so thank you!
I should take a closer look and figure out what she's about.
Okay, hold on.
Sorry, I know I'm...
There we go.
Okay, I think that's... We'll just keep it all at the same
levels, right?
Inspection.
Use the magnifying glass to find clues and press E to
uncover them.
Oh, we got a name here.
Name tag.
Last name.
Winthimer.
Oops.
Oh, sorry.
Uh, size shoe.
Size.
Oh, wow.
Suddenly they grow.
Ew, they grew.
Toes.
It's so gross.
Oh.
Keychain.
Boy band.
Oh, K-pop.
K-pop fan.
Oh, she grows.
Ew, she grows fingers.
Oh, God.
Oh, she's been crying.
Tear.
Sad.
Oh, no.
Her favorite boy, Ben.
Her favorite, her, oh, she just announced graduation
probably.
Nose.
Nostral.
Oh, it's so...
Oh, oh, oh.
This is so weird.
I like it, though.
Oh.
Oh wait, I pressed the wrong thing, my bad.
You're still here?
Um...
I'll leave you alone.
No, but we have our information, right?
Can I... Oh, I can investigate this too.
Let's see.
Oh.
Smiley.
Happy.
Okay.
Oh.
What am I looking at?
Giraffe.
Cute.
Okay.
September.
seventh seventh today cute what does the drug what does the
cute giraffe have to do with it Wow it's so cool how like
everything changes when you that's so fun tomorrow is Friday
need to remember to collect my dry cleaning this is making
me remember how much I miss watching you gaslight people and
goose goose duck it's locked what are you talking about
literally just told you you need to stay out oh sorry sorry
oh this thing what's this i swear to god if someone steals
my mug again i'll end them mug stolen threats oh suggestions
okay laura from cs is way too loud i can hear her keyboard
all the way to my desk
It's Sophie's birthday.
Hef.
Thursday.
Next!
They really should enunciate better.
Just saying.
Sophie, first name.
Why'd they write it?
like that it looks like half though right it looks like half
i was like what even what is half what is a half thursday
suggestions there's one more thing we're missing oh birthday
okay wait is that today these are quite mundane it's her
birthday i'm surprised nobody wrote something more
scandalous you would want that huh it's important to work
out a suspect's name to their first and last name into the
slots below, their portrait in the journal suspect page.
C, what does C-S stand for?
Handwriting be wild and right?
I think this detective might be a quack.
F-F.
Oh, customer service!
But this is not customer service.
This is uh, this is oh my gosh uh why can't i remember the
crime scene counter-strike this is um yeah front
receptionist thank you oh my goodness so let's go with
sophie wind timer okay i should be able to figure out what's
going on with her thanks david no one wished me a happy
birthday today not even my parents my days in August oh my
god you made me feel bad for you I need to check my notes in
the deduction section the deduction section okay so so the
duck detective nobody Sophie is feeling sad because nobody
has remembered her birthday
Ah, that's why she's making such a face.
I should try and cheer her up.
She's watching K-pop to make herself feel better.
You're still here?
Sophie, what if I just tell her your first and last name?
Good observation, Sophie, Windheimer.
Get out.
Aren't you impressed I deduced your name?
Deduction.
I'm wearing a name tag, Nidwit.
Oh.
doesn't say your first name though yeah that part is creepy
but i'm choosing to ignore it it's even creepier that i know
your birthday huh here happy birthday i'm just here to wish
you a happy birthday how's the audio by the way i know i've
been adjusting it but let me know if it's too loud or too
quiet i don't think it's too quiet but how did you know just
another one of duck detectives great deductions huh
Is it a long way to your heart, Sophie?
No, we're not trying to risk, Sophie.
Anyway, that was really nice of you.
No one else remembered.
Can you believe it?
Remembered.
If you know my birthday, you must have a connection to
someone here.
Here's the keycard to the office.
Oh, that's it?
Wow, I don't know if that's how that works.
Fairbuzz, office keycard.
Very good.
Thank you.
It says it's locked.
Oh, okay.
Just kidding.
Here we go.
See you later, Sophie.
And by the time I leave, there won't be a dry eye in this
whole building.
But not because you're sad that nobody remembered your
birthday, but because you'll miss me.
A stained carpets and peeling wallpaper exuded a stench of
stale coffee in abandoned dreams.
I knew I couldn't stay long or rub off on it.
Happy birthday, Sophie.
I got you a wedding.
Why are we risen Sophie?
This is the last straw!
How do they do that with their...
How do they do?
How do they do that with their mouth?
Frederson needs to be fired!
I'll see what I can do.
Frederson.
Can I?
Oh, hello.
Who are you?
I'm Duck Detective.
Do you have a problem?
If you have one, just call our damn hotline.
I'm Eugene McQuacklin, the Duck Detective.
Eugene McQuacklin.
A client hired me to investigate a case.
Why didn't you just say so?
You interrogated me first.
It's time we put an end to the awful lunch theft.
Lunch theft.
we need to fire him is some evidence for the upper
management okay i'll be in my office Eugene McQuackman I had
to find out who works here and what their jobs are I needed
to find my client as well yeah who the hell hired us I
remembered the piece of paper I had in my jacket from taking
notes during the call okay
client note all right let's Let's check it out.
Uh.
Where's the notes?
So we have Sophie, Mystery Man.
Here.
I hastily wrote this before heading to the client's address.
So I guess it has some stuff that, uh, is important.
Tricky deductions might require new perspectives.
Press H to get additional guidance at any time.
Alright.
Oh, sorry.
desks on this side look unused let's look around real quick
oh sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry who's this guy he looks really
like he doesn't need any more cups of coffee it's a list of
all the bus drivers oh the most busy driver out of all four
seems to be petrovich petrovich interesting cute oh let's
see what we got bear bus brazil Station bread.
Oh, I thought that was somebody's name.
The pretzel.
Oh, salad.
Salachica.
Escargo.
Okay.
Hall and days.
Nice.
Okay.
Their buses don't go very far.
They're cheap.
Whose office is it?
I shouldn't go outside yet.
Oh, outside.
I need to find out who the people in this office are first.
Did I remember to write down their professions and my
deductions?
Oh.
I don't think...
Not yet.
Oh, sorry.
My bad.
This guy looks...
Are you okay?
Let's observe you first.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Strained eyes.
Insomniac.
Different brand.
own headset dedicated dedicated to the job oh my god are you
okay are you okay their claws are out well energy drink bad
habits interesting okay what else we got in here
someone whitlock last name whitlock just like me for real
for real haughty Posing.
Me and...
Wait, password and me in sexy aliens?
What does...
What does that mean?
I don't know what I'm looking at.
Oh, password.
Accessible.
Is it?
Me in...
I wonder if there are clues to her password.
I don't think I have enough information to crack it.
yet i don't think i want the information sorry what's this
i'm gathering everything before we talk to people employee
of the month here we insert photo here oh come on layout
lazy who is making the noise freddy sucks first name freddy
Rufus Cedaris.
Last name.
No, no, no.
Let's get the first name, Rufus.
Stop with the post-its.
I'm not sure I'd feel particularly appreciated.
I got a achievement.
Complete five inspections.
The kitchen.
In here must be the crime scene.
First, I want to find out who the people in the office are.
Freddy Fazbear?
I'll need to remember to write everything down.
No, this is Freddy after he got the divorce.
He didn't get to keep the last name.
You know?
All right, so we got this in here.
It says come in.
Oh!
Hello!
Hearnished.
The dimly lit room seemed to promise well-kept secrets and
rumors.
what we got here it's a letter for an application for a
promotion to senior customer service agent oh signed by l x
l x we died thanks for the five gifted
he's got kids oh my god look at this loving family baby one
kids identical age twins baby two tell the difference.
What else can we notice here?
What else do we notice here?
Just the twins?
Oh!
A secret.
Hinge!
The safest behind there.
Framed.
High quality.
Is it normal to have a huge painting of your family in your
office?
I think so.
Secret secrets.
We have secrets in here.
Number one, dad.
We'll talk to him in a second.
Oh, it's the R.
What a fancy nameplate.
This guy is...
He says Ernst.
Oh, Ernst.
So we gotta...
I gotta remember to start writing people's names down in
here, right?
Oh, we don't know his first name yet.
It might be Freddy.
Because he is a bear.
No.
Freddy's last name was different.
Ayrst.
Let's observe you.
Oh.
Angry brow.
Stir.
Okay.
Your ears are clean.
Oh my goodness.
He's buff.
Tie.
Expensive.
Branch manager.
Ayrst.
Oh my god.
Look at these arms beef.
Ew!
Stain, baby food, family man.
Nothing in your pants.
Your fancy little shoes.
Okay.
Alright, I guess we'll start talking with him.
How are the detective things?
Donald, things are the five gifted things.
It's Mr. McQuacklin.
Mr. McQuacklin, please, sir.
Right.
Apologies.
Well.
Right.
Added to clues.
Why?
Are you planning on staying in my office much longer?
Oh, why are you doing secret things in here?
I'll have to inspect the entire premise to do my job
correctly.
Well, hurry up.
Mm-hmm.
What is our?
Oh, question.
Was it you who called me?
No.
I never heard of you before.
That's unusual.
It's good you're here, since there has been some...
Unrest, you say.
Well, I'll see myself out, Mr. Ernst.
Ernst.
Hmm.
Suspicious.
Yeah.
Why is...
Also, what is the stain here on the ground?
I'm hearing ghost typing and it making me nervous.
Let's talk to this stressed little fellow.
Oh, just kidding.
She answers a call.
This is Veribus.
How can I help you?
This is the third time you're calling.
I'm telling you, your ex-wife did not cancel your booking.
she looks busy I'll come back uh oh oh just kidding I didn't
mean to press it again uh I meant to press our question what
is your relationship with Sophie Wintimer excuse me for a
second oh man I don't know how I'd survive the office
without her sucks that she's at the reception I would have
loved to have her in the office interesting I'm back yes
please collect your toddler from the bus station toddler
like the way she pronunciated that toddler so much divorce
in this game I know right or the devs okay no I'm sorry you
can't take your 12 trombones on the bus what can't you see
I'm talking to a customer oh it's company policy nothing I
can do she's very busy she's very busy you know anything
about who called me here yeah there's what are you talking
about listen I have a million emails to answer and there are
50 people in the phone queue where's the rest of the people
I have worked 10 days in a row including three night shifts
and Manfred still doesn't want to give me a raise Manfred
huh just leave me at peace so you have no clues for me damn
mr.
McQuacklin How does she do that?
Okay, let's go talk to our little gator friend over here.
Oh, first of all.
What's this?
Receipt.
Expensive.
West currency.
What else we got here?
Salami?
High quality.
Mmm.
Salami, eh?
Oh.
Spotless.
Good condition.
Takes good care of a salami.
Let a man have his own amount of salami.
Who's to you to say how much is a lot of salami?
Okay.
Oh, look at all those teeth.
Laura!
Custom mug.
Wait, are those glasses?
Thick glasses, strong prescription.
Bad eyesight.
Oh my gosh.
The way the nose just like...
clothes anything in your pants oh velcro shoes lame you guys
recently most of my shoes have become like slip-on is that
the same I was like it's not the same as velcro right like
they have shoelaces on them but I don't need to tie them I
can just slip them on slip-on life yeah it's so much easier
when when you like get home and you have to take off your
shoes and or if you're leaving you have to just slip them on
you know it's so nice slip on is classy okay we're the slip
on life everybody all right let's talk to our little gator
friend i'm the only one here in the operating office can you
imagine can you imagine i plan all the bus routes and make
sure the buses are on time i want a voice and duck detective
next game isn't that so cool isn't that so cool Don't you
have an angry customer shouting outside about the buses
being late?
I uh, really?
Really?
Uh, yes, really?
Do you have any idea who picked me to investigate?
Why are you not?
No idea, but I'm so happy you're here.
I don't think, I don't believe that.
I think I sense a little tension.
I have a copy of your book.
The early bird catches the criminal.
Oh, he's a fan!
I'm not signing anything, though.
Can you sign it?
No.
Maybe.
Later.
The fact it was a prompt.
Oh, okay.
I'll just keep the copy right here.
So you could sign it.
Later.
Yeah, later.
Yeah.
So, I guess now we head to the kitchen.
But he has a cup name, but that's written Laura.
I don't know, is that your cup?
In here must be the crime scene.
First, I want to find out who the people in the office are.
When you said your shoes became slip-ons, I was thinking
they were regular shoes, but slowly became slip-ons because
your feet were shrinking.
It will make things easier.
I'll need to remember to write everything down.
Oh, okay.
Let's write everything down.
First, what's, uh, not Freddy.
Um, what was it?
Hold on.
For Rufus, Rufus.
And then, Freddy sucks.
Um.
I'm so bad with names.
Oh my goodness.
Okay.
Um, Gator is forever rejected.
Um, oh yes, it was Manfred, right?
probably you are you Laura and you're Rufus no wrong wrong
oh just kidding oh wait oh wait it was Freddy wasn't it oh
no it's not okay just kidding oh no let me stop I don't want
to take it out the bear is man Oh!
Oh, Freddy's a nickname!
Wait, how did he get employee of the month then?
That's kind of icky.
He's the branch manager.
This doesn't make much sense.
So, Rufus, what was the last name, though?
Was it Pet...
No.
Oh, gosh.
Whitlock was the girl...
Was that the sexy lamb?
Who's angst?
Hold on.
I gotta go back and look.
Check stuff out.
This is...
Yeah, Whitlock is this lady.
Hmm.
I can't tell if this is Laura or not.
What if this is Laura?
Where are you anyway?
Hmm.
I shouldn't go out.
I need to find out.
I remember to write.
Okay.
Rufus, Citrus?
I thought it was Freddy, Citrus.
Guys, I'm really bad with names.
Please forgive me.
Oh, it is Rufus.
You're so right.
Okay.
But didn't we try that?
Yeah, it wasn't him.
Are you Laura?
But we don't know Laura's last name, do we?
What other things do we have?
Laura from...
Customer service is way too loud.
We got Sophie.
Bag of salami.
Oh, I can just go here.
It says there's a photo here, so, and this kind of looks
like a duck by my very, very astute deductions.
Imagine the aroma of into gaming chair.
Bob, Bob, you didn't need to type that.
You didn't need to.
You didn't need to send that.
Oh, oh, no.
You okay?
What was this one?
It's a list of all the bus drivers.
The bus driver out of all four seems to be Petrovich.
Petrovich is the driver.
Okay.
Let's see.
I don't think Laura has a last name though, right?
What was the angst?
Oh!
Just kidding.
When did we learn her last name?
Am I, I don't wanna just like, just guess around everything.
It fits her.
I don't want to guess around everything.
Intuition.
Those are the bus stops.
The promotion note.
Oh, yes, you're right.
And then she said that he refuses to give her a promotion.
Maybe if we sign his book, we'll learn.
Oh, true.
Promotion to senior customers served.
There we go.
El angst.
Okay.
Oh, you're right.
We probably do have to sign his book so that we can learn
his name.
Who do we make it out to?
Alright, let's go talk to him.
Ah.
Okay.
Oh, hello.
Hi.
How are you, Mr. Duck Detective?
I'm good.
Oh.
What do you know about Manfred Arrest?
Arrest.
I think he likes me.
He's the only one who...
who doesn't shout at me.
Oh, lucky.
I'm the only one here in the operating office.
Can you imagine?
Oh God, no wonder things don't get done.
I plan all the bus routes and make sure the buses are on
time.
Isn't that so?
Don't you have an anger?
I, really?
Okay, it was this one though that we, um.
So, you?
Nope, but I, oh no.
Maybe we can't ask about the book.
Oh no, wait, no, that's a slimy.
Maybe we can't ask about the book anymore.
What do you think about Manfred Ernst?
Manfred Ernst.
Oh, he's a great guy.
I just wish I'd finally get a raise.
Oh, Laura.
Yes, sorry.
This is Bear Bus.
Your bus will be three hours late.
It's on the desk behind him.
No, I think what I'm seeing...
The little bubble above him, I'm pretty sure is his personal
bubble.
You know?
three hours late baby let's go how do I how do I autograph
your thing also why are you using Laura's mug your name is
not Laura hello how are you hmm how am I supposed to get
this maybe I should have maybe they didn't expect me to be
an asshole the book behind him why are you yelling at me
this book book right here?
This?
Do you don't you realize you're stupid now?
You yelled at me so much, the book is behind him.
Do you feel dumb now?
There's no bubble above it!
Don't yell at me!
Maybe if you click on it some more.
But have you tried the... That's clearly in the plan.
Yeah, it's on the other side of the table in the plant.
Hmm.
Well, all we have is Rufus or Freddy?
Fredderson.
Where do we learn that last name from?
There's still stuff.
Oh, maybe we can go talk to a reception again.
Freddy Freddersen.
Let's ask her opinion on some of these people.
What can you tell me about Laura angst?
Laura needs to chill out.
Dang.
I do love her.
But if she keeps living like this, she'll have a heart
attack by 23.
She's not even 22.
Oh boy.
So, do you have an idea?
who would have hired me?
It's about the incident, isn't it?
The incident?
Um, sorry.
Thank you for the raid!
Wait, hold on.
Leah!
Hi, Leah!
Thanks for the raid!
Oh my gosh.
Hello!
Thanks for the raid, girl!
Murphy thinks we're 10 gifted.
welcome welcome where we're just kind of started this case
it says it's locked dang we still can't get in there
basically i don't even know why i'm here i was gonna say i
was gonna give you what what has happened so far but i don't
even know i don't even know ducky thanks for the gifted
Raymack, thanks for the five.
Fun.
Thanks for the ten, Gifton.
Oh, my gosh.
Implode, thanks for the five, Gifton.
Rock for Rabbit, thank you for the five, Gifton.
Brandon, welcome back.
Okay, Draco's, thanks for the five, Gifton.
Rico, thanks for the five, Gifton.
Thank you, guys.
Thank you, thank you.
Oh, my goodness.
Thank you, guys.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
We're trying to figure out this dang crocodile's name.
But I think I missed a prompt because the game didn't expect
me to be a jerk.
I'm sorry I was a jerk.
Jerk to you, please.
So, you really...
Nope, but I always talk about you, so someone must have
gotten the idea from me.
No, let me sign your book.
No, Minnie's good.
Thank you for the 50...
Oh, it's gone.
Cool, thanks for the 10 gifted.
Thank you so much.
Oh, my God.
Is that another raid?
What is happening?
Alien.
a mixture thanks to the right thank you what is going on oh
my god our little duck detective he's humming to himself
look he has a he even has an afk pose it's so cute i'm the
only one here in the operating off i'm playing don't you hi
really okay also let's go ask um i guess we can go ask the
boss man i guess you have to do a thing to the bob gifted
Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
Thank you for the words installed.
You.
What do you know about Laura Angst?
Oh, she's a fantastic employee.
Yeah, you're gonna give her a raise?
She basically does the work of five people.
And she deserves the pay of five people.
That's it!
Is that why all the desks are empty?
Because...
Because there's no one else?
You guys, I'm not quite sure what to do here.
I mean, you know what?
Detective work isn't easy.
Ponder details.
The thing that bothered me in particular was...
Suspects?
I couldn't wrap my head around the suspects.
Could you hit Q for me.
Names.
Once I knew someone's name, I had to write it down on the
suspects' page.
Only then could I interrogate suspects about their opinion
of other people.
finding out people's names was a whole other task yeah how
am I supposed to get the gator's name often there are clues
in the environment that they work in okay be that documents
digital or analog or remarks of their co-workers it won't
let me go into this room yet in here must first it will make
things I'll need to remember it won't let me go in here and
it won't let me go in here I shouldn't I need to... Did I
remember to...
Hmm...
Is there anything written here that I missed?
Bear Bus.
No, not his name.
Oh, someone said... What's Q?
I'm scared.
What does Q do?
Ah!
Uh,
my bad.
She answers a call.
This is Bear Bus.
How can I help you?
Third time you're calling.
I'm telling you, your ex-wife did...
She looks busy, yeah?
Oh.
We did this one.
I don't know.
This is the bus drivers.
Is there anything in here on the cash payment?
Wait!
To Mr. Brandenburg.
That must be him, right?
But it wouldn't let me give it as an option.
Have I soft-locked my game for real?
It's not an option.
See here.
Oh,
it's a part of Germany.
Oh, just kidding.
Suggestion box.
If someone steals my mug again, I'll end them.
We have Laura.
I'm pretty sure Laura is Laura.
Oh, wait.
This is Laura.
Just kidding.
mug on the desk no there's nothing else this what you're
seeing see when I get close to him it expands that's the bub
the bubble is to talk to him so I'm totally lost what you
have the info you need I do no we're just gonna Freddy
anyway um let's ask what she thinks about Freddy can you
tell me more about Freddy Fredderson Freddy Fredderson let
me put you on hold while I find the route for you Freddy she
just hiss at Freddy this is this is Leah every time she sees
Fred that's Leah's reaction to Freddy Fazbear Freddy can
you imagine that what an incompetent waste of office space
Hello, this is Laura again.
I checked the bus routes and found that...
Okay, she hates Freddy.
Freddy?
No!
Okay, what about you?
What do you think of Freddy?
Oh, never mind, you have no opinion.
You don't care about him at all.
Whore, whore, whore, whore, whore, whore, whore, whore,
whore, whore, whore, whore, whore, the voice acting in this
game is so fun.
oh god what why don't why don't you also have an opinion on
freddie weird okay onwards to the kitchen finally here must
be the first i want to find out what people in the it will
make things eat i'll need to remember to write wait what am
i missing oh something in here oh okay okay okay um sophie
the giraffe works as a receptionist the bear There is
Manfred as the branch manager.
Laura the Cat works in customer service.
The crocodile called Freddy works in operating office.
Deck approved, baby.
Now that I had worked out these names, I was ready to check
out the crime scene.
The crime scene.
Let's see where that lunch got stolen from.
Then I could finally talk to my client.
be able to keep track of everyone, what they do and
everything.
Average of five duck per square meter?
To cheap white toast entered my nostrils.
Oh no, no, no, you can't relapse, Detective.
I knew I had to stay strong.
Our detective is addicted to the white, to the white bread,
not the wheat, not the whole grain.
The cheap white bread.
this wasn't what I was here for the milk toast just one
crumb no no stop eating the icing oh can't you wait a couple
hours Margaret if it wasn't for these pants almost bursting
I'd have this for breakfast every day Margaret yes yes and
you can have it and so much more later when we're done
preparing why is this place a mess aren't you at work what
are you doing why are you cooking so a mark right here.
Oh, just kidding.
Not yet.
Let's observe her, maybe.
Oh, oh, God.
She's catfishing the whole office.
As soon as you...
As soon as you hold a magnifying glass up to her, the truth
is revealed.
Inpeccable hair, well groomed.
Whisk, Baker.
Motherly.
Aww.
Oh!
Why is everybody divorced in this game?
Why is literally everyone divorced in this game?
Oops, my bad.
Oh.
Halloween party!
Cute.
Cancel.
Oh no.
Budget cuts.
So she's single.
Party.
Hungry, get your own lunch.
Where did that?
There we go.
Angry note.
Hungry.
Looking for editor unpaid.
And then some...
I think that's Laura and Sophie.
Office parties are a bad idea anyway.
They stop doing them at the precinct after the jam incident.
Do tell.
Spill the tea.
I doubt they washed their hands after leaving that greasy
handprint.
Eww!
Let's pull what we got in here.
Whatever this is.
Thanks for the food.
Salami Bandit!
Hamprint.
Greasy.
Sharp claws.
RS.
Margaret.
First name, Margaret.
Salami Bandit?
There's a real salami bandit.
A sandwich.
What else we got here around here?
What am I missing?
Did I... this?
Oh!
The note.
There we go.
I thought it was the sharp claws.
This must be the crime scene.
This note is curious.
Let's observe you, sir.
Whoa, eyebrows.
Oh.
Toes.
Worker shoes.
Practical person.
Okay.
He's got his little toolbox.
He's the janitor.
Well, you're not...
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry, actually.
You have a lot of work ahead of you, mister.
Oh, it's my fault.
I'm really sorry.
Sorry.
Sticker.
Sci-fi fan.
Oh, interesting.
He's a nerd.
All right, let's talk to Margaret first.
Yes, dear.
I'm Eugene McQuacklin.
And I need to ask some questions.
A detective?
How exciting.
Everyone hide their salami.
What's the most gruesome murder you've seen?
Oh, no.
She's into true crime podcasts.
How many dead bodies have you encountered?
I could just leave wait five little pigs
teething turtles what does that mean let's give her let's
give her the the most gruesome no one died oh no one died I
investigated the case once where five little pigs robbed a
bank caught them red-handed and got myself an article in the
goose times the goose times they called it the piggy bag
case did someone get shot why do you why if margaret is out
for blood what no beaten up margaret wants violence
oh okay interesting what do you think about sophie what do
you think of sophie wind timer she doesn't have easiest life
you know oh she just had a terrible breakup with her ex but
don't tell anyone oh spilling the tea margaret can you tell
me anything about laura angst she probably what do you oh
she's such a hard-working girl yeah i heard she secretly
studies for her online bachelor's during work oh well you're
not doing the work so you need to keep this a secret though
dang she's spilling everybody's secrets Do you know anyone
here who could have hired me?
To be honest, everyone was quite shocked by the launch
theft.
And no one told me they've called a detective.
I don't know what's going on at all.
Okay, calm down, Margaret.
Sheesh.
Okay, you're all right.
Let's add her.
Margaret with luck.
To the list.
And about you, sir.
This was just broken again.
broken again.
Where are we?
Where do we live?
What's wrong with these youngsters?
Don't know how to treat things with respect.
With respect.
Why would they put the mugs in face up?
Okay, that's really devilish, actually.
That is so evil.
Okay.
What do you think of Margaret?
What is your relationship with Margaret Whitlock?
Yeah.
She's a true sweetheart.
We have our weekly Mahjong evenings Mahjong evenings
Okay You're just playing my Oh my gosh is that the new
Forget Netflix and chill everybody Mahjong evenings Is the
Is the new hot stuff Do you get along with Manfred Arrinsed?
Arrinsed He's a stubborn one Hmm I do respect that.
Would you say you enjoy Freddie Ferderson's company?
Does anybody enjoy Freddie Ferderson's company?
Huh?
If anyone needs to learn to respect their elders, it's that
moron.
It's over for me.
Oh, he doesn't like him.
Okay.
I'm a private detective.
And I'm here to investigate.
Who hired us?
Is that so?
I need to find my client.
Do you know who it could be?
Why is there nobody who...
Yeah, Freddy's a bit of a weird one.
So I'd imagine you were called, Detective.
What?
Personally, I feel we're doing just fine.
I don't need no messing about our business around here.
Okay, suspicious, sir.
Why wouldn't you want a detective to solve the mystery lunch
disappearance, huh?
Interesting, interesting, interesting.
Let's see.
So, are you Rufus?
He's our employee of the month.
The janitor.
And then we have one more character.
This must be the person that hired us.
Where else can we go?
I guess we can ask other people about these characters.
Such as...
Freddy!
What do you think of Margaret?
What can you tell me about Margaret?
Margaret Whitlock.
She gets really angry with me when I don't return mugs to
the kitchen.
Yeah, you have four right there and one in your hand.
Why don't you just return them?
Yeah.
I do.
Just not every day.
This guy is so gross.
There's bananas.
Why don't you just pick up your stuff?
Me?
No.
Don't be messy.
you guys don't be messy this guy for real for real I forgot
I think to ask a Margaret what her opinion is of Rufus not
me no oh here we go are you getting along with Rufus to
deris oh you know the two of us are from the older
generation oh but you got your young at heart you got that
young spunk don't Margaret which means we understand each
other well mm-hmm he is quite harsh towards the younger ones
though mmm interesting he's a real respect your elders kind
of guy I see she's strong at heart oh yeah that's right we
got to figure out a way into her computer what about you sir
Rufus.
What is Rufus Cedaris like?
Cedaris.
Not the greatest janitor.
Then how did he get...
Then how did he get employee of the month, huh?
He came with the building.
Oh.
That's it?
Okay.
Poor Laura is so underappreciated at this place.
Are you okay, Laura?
Do you need a second?
So the password hint was...
Me and sexy aliens, which...
Still, look at this.
This is like when grandma discovers filters, Snapchat
filters and stuff.
Me and sexy aliens.
I'm so...
The PC is on, but the person who works at this desk seems to
be on a break.
Margaret got some dubious...
Activities?
Yeah, someone did like sci-fi.
They only have a single person answering the hotline right
now.
That's crazy.
Yeah.
Surprise.
Let's see.
What do we have here?
The client.
Blank hired the duck detective because his, her blank, was
blank.
The lunch was stolen by a coworker known as the Salami
Bandit.
We know that a little bit.
More suspects.
Oh, Margaret.
is the sheep who works in customer service.
Penguin is the salami bandit.
Rufus works as the janitor.
Buffalo.
Okay, let's go outside.
Maybe we'll find him out there.
Here we go.
Yeah, I knew that the penguin is a Star Trek fan, so...
Oh, there he is.
So he'll probably have the answer.
Ruffled my feathers.
I wondered what kind of sorry soul was standing all alone in
the rain.
I need the soundtrack for this game.
It's so good.
I'm sorry.
What else?
Is anything over here?
No.
What's this note?
How mysterious.
I want to read it.
Why are there post-it notes everywhere?
What's this?
Someone left their bag here.
Ugh.
It's full of dirty chim clothes.
No.
Nice.
Double bag.
Get.
For my own personal collection, of course.
Let's see.
Oh.
Well.
Well-proportioned nose.
Handsome.
Look at the top of his head.
So neat and clean.
Oh.
Hands and pockets.
Bad manners.
What?
That's bad manners?
Is it really?
Hands and pockets are...
Oh.
Boris!
Embroidery.
First name.
Boars.
New character.
Let's go.
Everybody's got an accent.
I'm not here to take a bus.
Yeah, I'm a detective.
It's cold out.
But if I go inside, I have to face Sophie.
Is that your ex?
What's your relationship?
What do you think of Sophie Windheimer?
Yeah.
He saws.
Man, I wish she'd let me talk to her.
What does that mean?
Do you like Freddy Fredderson?
It's rude in certain situations.
He's a pretty funny dude.
Loves to rant about detective novels.
Okay.
What do you know about Rufus Cedaris?
I don't think he likes me very much, to be honest.
doesn't feel like he likes anyone at this office you're rude
you're a rude youngster except for Margaret I guess mmm
gossip gossip gossip gossip I don't work here I thought you
were a detective what okay I'm investigating a case here at
bear bus oh do you mean the lunch that got stolen yes you
know who called me
I don't talk much with the customer service folks.
Bore, so what, you're a bus driver?
Do you know anything about this bag?
Majonging all over the place?
He's gonna roan her, he's gonna poan her, he's gonna...
Oh gosh, east, west, north, south?
Oh, man!
It's really strange.
Riti!
He's reaching all over the place.
Vala!
Thanks for the dono, thank you.
And others appeared.
Very suspicious.
What are you even talking about?
Is this your bag?
No.
Everyone here has been really unhelpful.
It's true.
Why is everybody so overwhelmed?
Like, nobody's giving, like, a good answer, like, a solid
answer.
Hey, man.
This isn't, you'll have to...
What?
I'm not here to...
Okay, so typically they each have, like, a, um, what's the
word?
A, uh, two dialogue.
So he is our main bus driver, Boris Petrovich.
Petrovich.
Ducks in a row.
Fill out all suspects' names.
Let's go!
And here.
Oh, um, more suspects.
Boris is the buffalo is a bus driver Awesome Now that I had
everyone's name and job It would be easier to figure out
what was going on Uh-huh The only person we haven't been
able to talk to That could tell us if they hired us Is Laura
because she's been so busy So I wonder if it's her
Nice So it was Laura who called me I needed to discuss the
case with her you're my client why didn't you tell me yeah
can i put you on hold for a second uh what you should have
told me you're the duck detective i did say i'm a duck i'm
wearing a trench coat so is freddy getting fired or what oh
i'm uh working on it It can't be that hard.
Sorry, I'm back.
Yes, let me walk you through the booking process.
It was time that I found out what happened with the lunch
theft and what they were planning in the kitchen.
In the kitchen.
Blank is planning a blank, blank, blank for blank.
Margaret is planning a surprise birthday party for...
Sophie.
Was planning a surprise birthday party for Sophie.
I see.
They didn't actually forget her birthday.
Elementary, my dear wisp.
How did you know?
I'm telling you.
I'm a duck detective.
Oh yeah, there's other stuff here too.
Let's see.
The culprit.
Blank is being blank by blank because blank picked up the
blank blank.
So and so is being framed by blank because blank picked up
the blank blank.
The wrong mug.
I wonder.
I wonder if...
Freddy is being framed by someone because...
Wait, hmm.
We still don't know this one quite yet.
I need to get into her computer so I can see any evidence
she has in her emails.
Nice size.
Welcome to Bamboo Shep.
Thank you.
Let's see.
Okay.
Do you know whose bag this is?
Isn't that?
Freddy's?
Freddy's bag!
So it was swapped out.
He has the bag.
His bag is actually the bag with the...
With the gym clothes.
But they swapped it out.
Do you know anything about this bag?
Why are you going around pushing bags into people's faces?
What's that awful smell?
Embrace it.
that dirty gym clothes embrace it the bag of 87 oh yeah okay
we looked in through there oh that's so sweet that she's
actually doing surprise party though oh let's ask let's ask
uh freddy about his uh his bag is this your bag huh no
mine's over there the salami you know the salami bandit yeah
why do you need so much salami that's not mine it was just
there a really nice surprise oh nice do you get along with
Boris Petrovich he's a chill guy I take the bus sometimes to
go to bouldering conventions and then we get to chat
bouldering
Is that climbing or...
What is bouldering?
Oh, Freddy.
Rock climbing?
Okay.
It's climbing without a harness.
Yo, Freddy goes hard.
Freddy's a bit of an adrenaline junkie.
What kind of a person is Boris Petrovich?
Oh, I don't know what I saw in him.
They were.
That is it, that is Erex.
I mean, I guess he's good looking.
but good evening officer Brent how you doing I'm great thank
you my god is he boring oh how are you getting on with
Margaret Whitlock she's sweet and all but but she can't keep
her mouth shut okay that is so true it seems like the office
knows more about my personal life than me than me the office
I wonder how this guy is doing out here i can't leave now i
need to solve just kidding
boris is into tall chicks it's based okay let's see go on in
what can you tell me about boris petrovich he's uh not the
most reliable worker Yeah, but it's difficult finding
replacements nowadays.
Mm-hmm.
We still don't know what's behind is, uh, this, you know.
What are you doing with my family's portrait?
Sorry.
It's just admiring your lovely, your lovely life, you know?
Just admiring your lovely wife.
are they only have that surprising how do i get in
accessible maybe we don't access it maybe
maybe maybe someone else accessed it because they knew the
hint aka our little penguin friend over here maybe he got
onto her computer to do something with the note.
Salami.
And it's the sharp claws that makes me think that they're
framing Freddy, you know?
Well, I mean, they are framing Freddy because they gave him
the salami.
So...
Wait a minute.
It already wants me to...
Okay.
It already...
It already wants me to solve it.
Oh, okay.
Freddy is being framed by...
Um...
Uh,
by Laurel?
Because Freddie, two or fewer things are wrong.
You have all the information, just think back.
Think mug equals lunch.
No, well he had the...
She was so mad about him grabbing her mug all the time,
right?
Mug, not bag.
No, I don't think it was the wrong bag, right?
Or is it the wrong?
Okay, wait.
It's so clean.
Who you know who else was clean?
Margaret!
She was also clean.
And divorced!
Hmm.
Yeah, his gym bag or his dirty clothes are...
Yeah, so Freddy picked up the wrong bag.
I love how Bear Bus...
He's just being framed by Bear Bus.
Everybody's out to get him.
Everybody hates Freddy!
Everybody wants Freddy out of here!
No...
Why am I blanking out on this so much?
Okay, hold on.
I think maybe because I'm...
Okay, there's Margaret's sandwich.
Why is it wide open like that?
RS is the janitor.
What's that sound?
And then...
This is...
Oh,
they're brewing coffee.
Oh, I hear it.
Yeah, you're right.
Why am I blanking so much with this?
So maybe Freddy is being framed by...
Um...
It wouldn't be manfred, right?
But would it be...
Not the wrong bat.
They...
Use your brain mint.
I have no brain cells right now.
Just look through the names.
I don't think it's Boris.
Is it Rufus?
Email bag X.
I mean, he picked up the wrong X.
Ah!
Unless it's Manfred's lunch.
It's available.
the game is like uh by the way um this is so wrong just
please give up okay i think i think it is the bag then
time for what happens if i do oh it doesn't change anything
we're fine
why bag you were what you were about you were were you're so
you're hired to solve the missing lunch then what does the
bag have to do with it I think they just switched out the
bags right so Freddy is being framed by it's a Margaret you
evil conniving sheep what
do you carry lunches in a bag or your hands I don't know why
am I Why can't I figure this out?
Am I stupid?
Think about the lunch was stolen by who?
Well, I don't know.
Who would have won it?
Because each person in here he has his own lunch.
Margaret has her own lunch.
This is...
Well, I'm assuming it's Laura's lunch.
I'm assuming it's Laura's lunch, but what if it's not?
Try looking through all the names, nouns, and choices.
Suspicious.
I think it's framed.
By...
The Salami Bandit.
Oh wait.
Oh, Freddy!
Freddy by Freddy!
Freddy is being framed by Freddy because Freddy picked up
the wrong one.
And who didn't like who, right?
Bad manners.
Maybe Boris ate the lunch.
Who knows?
She also has bad habits.
Lame.
So sad.
But he has bad eyesight.
So he picked the wrong thing, right?
On accident, probably.
It was Freddy all this time.
Don't trust anybody.
Not even yourself.
So maybe he's being framed by Boris.
One day he'll complete this puzzle.
It's because I did the other one so quickly.
Laura does hate Freddy.
Look at the pits at this point.
It's painful.
I'm sorry!
Laura wants Freddy.
I tried though.
I tried Laura.
And Freddy is being framed by Laura.
But I don't...
It didn't work.
What?
Keep cooking, but don't listen to the haters.
At this point, I have no idea.
At this point, I'm so confused if it's a bag, if it's a bag,
if it's a mug, if it's a salami, if it's a lunch.
I have no idea.
Is it because the salami band had picked the wrong lunch?
things must be wrong.
So no.
Oh, whoops.
Uh, wait.
Back.
Hmm.
You gotta think like a dog.
I'm not a dog.
I'm a ghost.
There's twists.
The double cross is Kochi Mahoom.
And with Chad, I think the mug did it.
Oh, did we try clicking on that book on the desk somewhere?
Is this all because I didn't sign the book?
Dang it.
the colonel i don't think the hints are literally going to
give anything though detective work isn't easy ponder
details the thing that bothered me in particular was the
culprit to figure out the situation about the culprit i had
to consider important objects what objects stood out in this
case i had to check again which objects the people involved
interacted with i had to take into consideration who the
note in the fridge was signed by and why they to take action
I had a feeling something bigger was going on than meets the
eye thanks duck detective clearly Ocelot must be responsible
wait so so who signed the note that's a great question this
little the This, this, I thought, honestly, if you had told
me it was like a poorly drawn sun, like a sunrise, I would
have believed you.
But it's a claw.
I thought it was a sun at first.
So who has the claws?
Freddy's got claws.
Manfred's got claws, doesn't he?
I have to go back and look at everybody's claws.
She's got divorced.
This guy has no hand...
Wait.
He's got claws!
Everybody's got claws, I think.
Oh, sorry.
I pressed the wrong button.
Or did I?
Maybe I pressed the right button.
Oh, yeah.
This is baby food.
I was like, wait, he's got evidence on him.
I'm so glad Vintez realized that I'm framing Freddy.
Oh, this way.
Hold on.
Laura, let me see her hands.
Oh, those are really claw-like.
But why would she steal...
See, that's...
I mean, she's stealing her old lunch, but she's also trying
to get this guy fired.
She's like, fire Freddy.
Fire Freddy.
She hates him.
Oh.
Oh, that's a cap song.
So I feel like it's gotta be Laura, right?
Because...
But he picked up the mug.
I feel like that is correct.
That Freddy is being framed by Laura because Freddy took her
mug again.
But I don't understand why it's wrong.
What Freddy do.
He took her mug.
And she said, I hate when people take my mug.
It's obvious the duck detective.
But planted the evidence himself that gave himself amnesia.
The perfect crime.
You're too far ahead.
What do you mean?
Change the name?
The Salami Bandit is being...
I
feel like it has to be...
Like, being suspicious by who?
That doesn't make any sense.
Someone is being suspicious by someone.
Huh?
The answer is more simple than you think.
What?
Just tell me at this point!
I should say these are the five gifted.
Oh my god!
That was three things wrong.
I hope the, I hope the, I hope the, um...
The devs are not watching this right now.
How am I overcomplicating it?
Please have a meeting in an hour!
Oh my god.
There's only so many things.
I feel like framed makes the most sense, right?
The duck detective is being framed.
Freddy is the correct thing here.
Suspicious.
It's actually a good sound.
I don't know how to simplify this anymore than I already
have.
I don't know how to simplify this more than I already have.
This is why I gave up the life of being a detective.
I'm gonna go get more tea.
I'll be right back.
I'm gonna just go get more tea.
I'm back.
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay, thank you.
Oh, wrong thing.
Oh, this too.
Did you catch any fish?
I got a whole boat load.
A whole boat load.
Okay, back to my...
It just messaged me something really stupid.
It was the Colonel Mustard in the library with the candles.
Like, I knew it.
I knew it.
Oh, my gosh.
Will the fish fit in your hat?
No, they're really huge fish.
Why would they fit in my hat?
That makes no sense.
Okay.
So is it?
The Salami Bandit?
Picked up...
No.
Is he being framed maybe by the Salami Bandit?
Yeah, I'm having a mental breakdown.
The wrong back.
It was as I thought.
Really?
Was it actually detective?
VOD watchers can resume from here.
Yeah, make sure everybody timestamps this moment so
everybody knows when to click back in.
Freddy Fredderson was actually being framed.
That's what I said!
This office wasn't as boring as it looked.
When Freddy took the bus back and he went to pick up his
luggage, he must have picked up the wrong bag this happened
because there was another bag that's identical to his the
bag that he picked up belonged to the bandit oh i almost
said the sausage bandit i can't even remember and to get rid
of freddy the salami bandit decided to frame him why didn't
you just say hey that's my bag it's time for you know what
salami van and just say hey man that's my bag
oh my god thank you for that super super detective your
investigative skills are second to many first
oh god yeah resting your voice by the way okay get into
position me my throat has been really bad lately also me i
wonder why i just texted her so she should be hearing hmm
huh what's this surprise surprise no way this is all for me
huh a letter oh it's more salat oh oh no salami What a
terrible present.
No, you silly idiot.
The real present got stolen and switched for salami.
Oh, it's the salami bandit.
I think it's for the five-gifted.
I saw an awful lot of high-grade salami in Fredrickson's
bag.
Oh, that's really suspicious that you would immediately name
him.
You screamed about Freddy being framed just now right as I
was re-watching the part from yesterday's podcast episode
where you started yelling, Freddy, his name is Freddy, and
it's...
And now there's no question who the perpetrator is.
I've been telling you all along, we can't trust Fredderson.
By the end of the day, he'll be fired.
Whoa!
My words.
Ooh, oh.
Seems like a bit of an overreaction to a present being
stolen.
What are you talking about?
She's crying.
Is there more to it?
So Sophie received the following presents.
Okay.
I really don't want to get involved.
Anyway.
Oh, wait.
Oh, we did all this.
Just kidding.
That's not nice at all.
The moment you said surprise, my browser decided to reset
itself.
I know what.
Haunted.
yeah who messes with someone's birthday let's see someone
gifted Sophie a plushie a plushie it says limited edition oh
where do we see the cat plushie before it was it's a
heart-shaped necklace looks tacky oof that's probably Boris
this one wait this is the sexy alien book right sexy aliens
want my number
Captain Brightbeak stared deep into the alien's eyes.
There were 12 of them, and they were red.
The eyes, not the aliens.
All the aliens were blue, and there were 43.
All of them wore shiny metal armor, which shined like
something shiny made of curved metal.
Captain Brightbeak could tell it was the lead alien because
it was the one which stepped forward.
It was also the most beautiful, the only one with purple
eyes.
It made a noise that sounded a bit like talking.
From a hole that looked a bit like a pretty lady's mouth.
The translation device the captain had invented word into
action, translating the words into words he could understand
hey you look cute a mechanical voice whispered into his ear
can i get your number why is that page 252 621 total pages
also um that name isn't that rufus's last name or am i
stupid questionable title adult novel Oh, oh, God.
What did I just read?
Yeah, I want some more.
Buong, buong, buongiorno, everyone.
Everyone, not just Sophie.
Weird message.
Also, E is underlined.
B.
Quite a lot.
Unbelievable, I entered the office really easily.
Sayonara, edge lords.
Cocky attitude.
Salami.
Why is the B?
B-E.
They're the only two things underlined.
Suspicious.
B-E.
I wonder what the purpose of that letter is.
I think it's Boris gave the necklace and then something got
stolen let's talk do you think she liked my present I mean
now she's crying but I think I saw a sparkle in her eyes
when she opened mine I should really get back to work yeah
Oh, whoops.
I'm depressed.
Oh, wait.
I should...
It's a...
Oh, it's R.
My bad.
Uh, this one.
Can you tell me something about this letter?
About this letter?
Sophie won't even talk to me about it.
I don't know what to do.
Mm-hmm.
And she won't talk to me either.
Err.
Okay.
Let's keep going.
Let's ask other...
Is this Hades too?
What do you have to say about it, huh?
So...
What happens to the cake now?
Rufus...
Oh my gosh, I almost just spilled something.
What do you think about this letter?
Hmm.
People don't know how to write letters by hand anymore.
This guy is back in my day.
Oh, because he's an author.
because he's an author he's all he's all like it's got to be
perfect you know okay they they really think i've done it
detective you have to help me you you know it wasn't me
right what's bag mean did you not think it was strange that
your bag was full of salami uh i don't know i thought
someone gave me a salami surprise that's you know what
that's a typical you know Mass is life and boob is hometown.
Don't change, man.
Thanks for the super chat, Led.
I'll eat salami sandwiches for breakfast, lunch, and dinner
from now on.
That's not the point.
Dufous.
I want to get into the server room.
Wait, maybe we can get in now.
Because no one's here.
It says it's locked.
Dang.
Let's go.
She likes the cats, though.
So I'm guessing that one's...
from and you know uh laura is a cat so guessing that one's
from her and then boris and then but who did it get stolen
who's got stolen unless it's uh freddy's got stolen probably
because they're framing him right do you know anything about
this letter well it's obviously a cheap Right, right,
Frederson.
Hopefully, he would find this funner.
I'm guessing you're ready to present legal evidence of
Frederson's misconducts.
It wasn't Frederson.
Everything is pointing towards him.
I will present the true culprit soon enough.
Soon enough.
Well, I don't really care how long it takes you.
This will be Frederson's last day.
Oh, wow.
Whoa, everybody, everybody wants him fired.
Ducks are 70% more...
likely.
Also, yeah, someone said that her that Laura's computer is
free.
What's this one, though?
This folder says manual for CS agents.
How and when to create vouchers correctly?
I'm falling asleep just reading the title.
I think it's great reading.
Alright, let's see.
What do we got here?
Sophie.
Chat to friends.
Okay, what are they talking about?
But something returned but they're sexy now by now the
aliens have returned but they're sexy now OMG lol is he
serious what a dumb pen name haha it's just his name
backwards complaints can the oh oh please clean their desk I
could smell it until here she's a complainer jeebus crossed
welcome to my bishop thank you so she's a complainer eh You
definitely don't want to be Laura's enemy.
So Laura gave the plushie.
Rufus gave the book.
And maybe...
Oh, uh...
Something got stolen.
Books.
Letters.
Necklaces.
Plushies.
Nothing got stolen.
Everybody...
So, nothing got stolen after all.
Okay.
that the salami present was intentional.
Very interesting indeed.
It's a conspiracy.
Yeah, they say salami banned it, but people's stuff was
there.
Hmm.
When can I get sexy alien, alien, sexy aliens want my number
two?
When can I get that?
Okay, I'll...
I'll comfort her.
You have the duck detective here to figure everything out.
What can you possibly do?
I'm a detective.
Leave me alone.
Okay.
Sorry, ma'am.
Um.
Is there something in here that we're...
Oh.
The message.
Receive the blank.
Oh, wait.
We have to talk to Boris.
I don't know where he is.
Oh my goodness.
Completely forgot about him.
And oh yeah, there's also Margaret's PC.
So now, blue skinned alien.
Meat and sexy aliens.
Blue skinned alien.
Purple.
Red-eyed alien.
Uh.
Shiny.
Armored.
Wait.
Wait, wait, purple-eyed alien.
Nice.
She's the main alien.
Let's see what secret she has on her computer.
Ha-ha-ha, secrets.
Let's see.
West VPN?
Secret cake recipes.
Never gonna give you up that wave.
Bus bear internal vouchers for CS agents.
compensation, booked on next bus, a vacation, eh?
Planned trip, interesting.
Oh, delete everything!
CUTY!
Illegal activity?
But the alien, it has to be Rufus.
This makes me never want to work in an office.
This is exactly what it's like, even.
Who is this person she's messaging?
I don't think I have a clue.
Oh, wait.
We've already talked about it.
Okay, let's go see what Boris thinks, though.
We haven't talked to him.
Oh, what's this now?
Customs procedures for passengers entering from the west
border.
Allowed goods.
Personal items worth less than 500 schmark.
Notify the local police about suspicious activity.
Prohibited goods.
Oh, there better not be salami on this list.
Weapons.
Gun.
Scary.
Over 10 trombones.
Meat!
Potatoes.
Books not in the interests of the eastern states.
Plants.
Luggage will be checked at the bus station.
For more information, visit this place
But also books not in the interest of the...
Uh-oh.
If they're going on a trip...
He can't... He has his books.
What do they have against potatoes?
Potato famine is not a joke.
Maybe it was too romantic.
Did Sophie ask about me?
Um...
What do you think, guys?
Should we give this guy some follow-up?
hope or should we should we give this guy some false hope or
do you think uh no um she didn't ah i see now he's rude true
something more expensive i did say it looked cheap i did say
that okay so yeah we definitely knew that let's see so
gonna put Sophie received a romantic book that contained a
scary message ha ha ha ha
or Margaret received a role a message
the contained I don't know actually well I was gonna say
message like because they were messaging online but the book
is contained a scary message you guys scary aliens it
contained a scary salami the message so my Sophie Received
a...
Nice...
Well...
A nice salami.
That contained a scary salami.
Oh no!
It wasn't a nice salami after all!
It was a scary salami!
Wait, hold on.
Let's go back inside.
I don't want to be, you know, doing my work in the rain
after all.
Let's go in here.
So would it be this?
B-E.
I don't think anybody's initials are that, are they?
Boris.
That's a B.
Hmm.
It's salamis all the way down.
Salami, salami, salami.
So what is the message?
Is it this message?
Or is it...
I think it's a...
Oh no, here we go again.
Is this message, though, right?
That's what I'm assuming.
So, Margaret received...
So it's the message in the box, not the message she received
on the computer?
In the box.
Oh, okay.
Well, Sophie received a nice salami.
A scary message.
That contained.
A nice salami.
Take a closer look at the note.
Well, it said, like, it was like a...
It was like a cocky message.
It was like...
It was like a...
Yeah, a cocky attitude.
A weird message!
Quite unbelievable.
I entered the office really easily.
But also, why is this whole part blank?
Why did they write it like that?
A cocky salami.
This is the content I come here for.
Also, rip your throat.
Oh wait.
Just wanted to say that your laugh is extremely charming.
I feel happy while listening to you laugh.
Thank you.
Your brain cell.
Oh my god.
Oh they're kind of behind.
Oh my goodness.
The brain cell you took with you after leaving heaven really
put in the work.
Okay.
So she received.
None of these are strange.
A silly message.
It's not a romantic.
She received a...
A silly sal- Salami.
Letter.
A scary letter.
Not scary.
It's not a nice letter though.
It's not a silly letter either.
Scary letter.
That contained...
I'm so confused by these adjectives.
A romantic salami.
I think a romantic salami sounds really correct.
You're us.
Thank you!
Mint, my voice hasn't really recovered.
Also mint, has a mental breakdown and guard these creatures.
Maybe in reverse?
Contained a...
nice salami?
Hmm.
A silly salami?
Oh, maybe silly letter?
Scary salami?
I think B.E.
is Bema Emmerich.
What's wrong with B.E?
A.
Is there a present in here?
No, there's no present.
There's nothing in here that says, like, she received a
present, you know?
She's received salami that contained a letter.
I guess?
What else is in here?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, a silly letter that contained a
scary message.
Why is it a silly letter, though?
Why is it a silly letter?
I needed to find out why.
Okay, it was a letter that contained a message.
Got it, got it, got it.
Oh, oh, no, there's more.
Blank are being blanks, blanks from blank.
Books are being...
illegally imported from...
Wait.
Where was the...
Oh, no, not this one.
The vacation?
Brazil?
I don't think there was a Brazil.
Brazil!
That's from Brazil.
Unless it's not books, unless it's salamis.
That explains all the high-grade salami.
Yeah, because it was on the letter or on the receipt, right?
We just needed to find out who was behind this.
The mystery of the salami bandits was slowly getting
unraveled.
It was on the receipt.
Western goods are prohibited from entering and being sold in
the East.
this is why the salami bandit decided to make a business out
of buying high-grade salami in the west oh and that's why
you didn't want him to take his bag and selling it at a high
profit and then they're gonna go on vacation with the money
also for some reason sophie received a letter from the
salami bandit because they were making fun of his book and
had a hidden Threatening message.
Wait.
Why are all the letters there?
They look different.
This was serious.
I had to question all of the employees.
All of them.
They were making fun of his book, and so they're upset.
Thanks for coming, everyone.
Well, everyone except for Sophie.
Where is she?
Slacking off.
Playing on her computer phone.
Computer phone.
She's having problems with her family.
Oh.
She was at her desk and said she needed a moment.
No.
Romani, welcome to membership.
Thank you.
I will start then regardless.
I have made my deductions and drawn some serious
conclusions.
Serious conclusions.
Finally.
Is Freddy getting fired then?
Oh gosh, Freddy's not getting fired, you guys.
This is pretty bad.
Laura's gonna be so mad at me.
Who is the murderer?
I... what?
No one died.
I went to check out hives for the first time since braiding
them, since the washboards and the roads out there were bad
enough to where they rattled my windshield.
Wait, are you okay?
Just wanted to let...
All of you are fine.
Oh, glad they're okay.
I'm getting raped!
I'm telling you!
You are, but not by Laura, who I originally thought.
Want a load of baloney?
No, actually.
Salami!
He is right, actually.
He is getting framed.
Laura's VA also does shift to Yanike.
No way.
Ah, that is the question, isn't it?
Why would anyone bother?
Get to the point.
It's through my observations that I uncovered.
I uncovered.
Oh!
Yeah, I mean, yes.
I did uncover that.
gasp this is ridiculous I told Hanukkah I don't believe in
the supernatural but now I do love the voice acting in this
it's so good listening to a random duck that waddling to
this office I'm leaving oh no no sir stop right there oh or
I'm a certified private investigator and it's okay just tell
us what you know maybe made was the friends along the way or
something salami is being smuggled from South Sitchia using
your very own buses huh what's going on okay this is going
too far I really have more important things to do oh
everyone's leaving now that is really scandalous does that
mean we're losing our jobs maybe Oh!
Why is everybody leaving?
Listen, everybody!
It's really important that no one leaves the premises.
I need to get back to work.
Wait a second!
Everybody's leaving?
I'm still here, Mr. Duck Detective.
Nobody cares!
Yeah.
Um, I guess we'll just continue our illegal activities.
Wait, whose phone is this?
Oh.
KT Senjoyer.
Oh, KTS-
KTS- Enjoyer!
Almost dead.
Are your parents still angry at you?
Min-ten-joy.
That's nonsensical.
Did she get kidnapped?!
This is curious.
I think she got kidnapped, you guys.
Why would she write like this?
Uh-oh.
Someone forgot their phone.
Oh, the music changed and everything.
It's kind of fun.
This is getting intense, isn't it?
Maybe you could need a little help?
I don't think so.
You seem lonely.
Oh.
I could be your assistant.
Lonely added the clues.
This game is targeting me.
do decipher messages talk someone into telling us the truth
follow people around i'm pretty good at that just stay here
yeah like this yeah yep you're doing great okay um everybody
went back to work which is really great sophie's probably
kidnapped oh they seem a bit worried uh oh my god Oh god,
there's a mess of a scene here.
I think she really was kidnapped.
Or it was me.
Uh-oh.
This is like, oh, the cat is on the ground!
Um...
Sophie left!
And she left a note on the desk!
Oh, she did now.
Did she?
Was this...
Let's...
The last dialed number on this phone is 03...
Miss some streams.
How did Sissel become a duck?
Oh my gosh, they just doxed my phone number!
What's this?
Unknown number.
Any more.
I'll tell them everything.
Don't.
Fight.
You block this number.
Click here to unblock.
Interesting.
Am I the asshole for expecting my coworkers to remember my
birthday?
It's my 20F birthday.
And no one congratulated me.
I don't need much.
But at least a handwritten card would have been nice.
I can't believe she complained about this online.
She went to Reddit for it.
It's crazy.
Wait, where's the no?
Oh, here it is.
That's it.
I quit.
Sudden news.
You'll never see me again.
Wait a second.
Sophie Winthimer.
This is not her.
This is the...
This is the Bandit's handwriting.
Sophie.
Let her off.
Uh-oh.
What a dramatic turn.
I should keep this as evidence.
Better than I.
Get.
she left just like this just like this maybe she's at home
should I look for her did you read Sophie's letter I did
something's off something's different the handwriting the
handwriting is different this is the note Sophie left can
you tell me more and you know who was the first person to
leave?
The penguin.
He had all the time.
He was the first person to leave the room.
It's totally him.
It doesn't make sense at all that she just suddenly leave.
She definitely needs the money.
And she would have told me, I'm her friend.
Mm-hmm.
No, the bear was?
No, it was definitely the penguin.
Would you ever do a stream where you just read Am I the
Asshole Post while playing Minecraft?
sure oh we can also check out his computer hey Eugene
McQuacklin throw bread to the fine beak of lady justice
that's me stalking looking for a job we'll do almost
anything buy my book murder at the beaver's dam when the dam
broke Beaver, Bichel, lost his mind.
Oh my God.
Crime and thrillers.
Kidnapping and a kingpin.
Never kidnap a kingpin on his birthday.
Murder, kidnapping, stalking?
This guy is such a criminal.
Someone is clearly obsessed with detectives.
You can't have a hobby anymore?
Okay, it's just obsession, sure.
What do you think of this note?
It's no surprise she's left, is it?
Would you want to work with someone you've dated in the
past?
Whoa.
Who would hire me at this age?
No, it's in demand.
Maybe I can be a real estate agent.
Oh my god, so true.
I always wanted to be a rich real estate agent.
Live your dreams, Margaret.
You sussie mix suss pants.
Oh, I can't ask you about anything.
Why would Laura recruit you to deal with the theft?
Aren't there any other detectives who are actually qualified
for the job?
Wow.
I've been doing very well so far.
If I do say so myself, the truth will be revealed in the
end.
There's only one truth.
Suss.
Suss, suss, suss.
I'll be able to go back out.
Wait, where'd he go?
Uh, I'm just gonna open this.
Manfred is out of his office.
Move the painting here.
Time to see what's behind his precious family portrait.
A safe.
CS00BD.
Calls.
Customer support is too.
Okay.
Zero, zero.
Uh, zero?
And birthday.
Do we know it's birthday?
Oh, operating office, so one?
Bus driver!
Oh.
Nope.
Wait, no!
We have...
Wait, uh, we have four bus drivers.
Yes!
I did it!
My god!
I always wanted to open a ridiculously big safe.
Let's see what secrets he has in here.
Okay, we got some keys.
Keychain, server.
Server, Robeke.
Dear Ingrid.
Wait, this is his handwriting.
I haven't been there for you and the kids recently.
But things are looking up.
I would love to take you to a romantic getaway to
Hollandeis.
Love Manfred.
The handwriting!
Different handwriting.
Demands!
Me, employee of the month?
TV in my room?
Keep quiet about the thing.
Do all these things and nothing will happen to you.
He's being blackmailed!
He's being...
Wait, so he is probably being blackmailed.
put up to doing the bandit stuff by the penguin maybe.
Awful lot of security for a branch manager of a bus company.
Uh-huh.
Wait.
This keychain.
Here it is.
The key for the server room.
Yes.
Nice.
Okay.
Oh, sorry.
My bad.
Oh, no.
Wait, should I shut the... You know what?
Never mind.
It's fine.
It's probably okay.
Oh.
What's this tab?
Maybe Sophie got kidnapped because...
...kidnapped...
...blank wanted to...
Oh, no.
Sophie got kidnapped because Sophie wanted to snitch.
Sophie got kidnapped!
There must be more to this!
Yeah.
Dun, dun, dun, dun...
Oh my gosh.
so crazy the story is so crazy now let's go to the server
room i've been wanting to go in here the whole time let's
see what's hidden in here yeah uh what are you doing uh
secret detective business yeah secret detective business
don't mind me don't mind me agatha minty
created a claustrophobic atmosphere.
I don't think they should be sparking.
I definitely felt that I wasn't supposed to be here.
My meeting time?
I have a, it's in 45 minutes.
Or 40 minutes.
35 minutes.
I'm okay.
This is his room.
This is the penguin's room.
He got his little TV like he wanted, eh?
Me!
Oh, oh.
Packs under eyes.
anxious i look way worse than i expected to tattered hat
poor no no no we're just unassuming just like colombo we
wear we wear an ugly frumpled hat and an ugly frumpled um
jacket because we don't want we want them to think that
we're a bad detective when we're really smart breadcrumbs
Those fingernails, man.
He looks like he's been biting them.
Has that been there the whole day?
Oh, my gosh.
Duck Detective.
Go watching your Instagram streams.
Thank you.
Okay, let's start here.
What's he keeping in all these boxes?
Books?
Salami?
Why don't you open it up?
I don't think it's meant to do this.
I don't think so, either.
Okay.
Oh, hold on.
Honestly, this is nicer than my apartment.
Don't say that.
We'll rough it up a little bit.
Easy.
Bear bus 100 schmark voucher.
No one used 100.
Now selling for 80 schmark.
They're using the vouchers to get rich.
Bear bus.
Bus 100 Schmark voucher.
Lisa.
How to delete.
Delate.
How to delete EZ selling history.
Manipulate history.
Confusing message.
Computer illiterate.
Dad, this is not Google.
Camera O3 playback.
CCTV.
What's up with these Bear Bus vouchers on EZ?
mmm oh my goodness whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa so rufus
blackmailed manfred to make him stay quiet about
is it is it i guess rufus legally selling lovers vouchers
one that provides the blank to blank so one that provides
the oh uh margaret is the one that provides the vouchers to
to rufus dun dun dun this is what rufus and margaret were
doing with the vouchers that might be illegal but this
wasn't what i was here for i needed to catch the salami
bandit yeah i quickly needed to find out where sophie was
being kept i also couldn't let the salami bandit get away
with this no it was finally time to find out who was behind
everything okay oh sophie is at
huh cake sophie is inside the cake she's been baked oh my
god he's so cool the whole office is what are you doing in
there snooping around are we oh that room is strictly off
limits i even put up posters this is for important detective
work yeah stand your ground detective
oopsie did you kidnap her take winter back Was it you?
Hi Mentopia, have fun at Ace and Mwah!
That's cool!
Thank you!
Also, but wise operator.
Welcome to Mambusha.
Thank you.
Okay.
But he was looking at the CCTV.
I wanted to check real quick.
Ducks are named after Sir Jeffrey Duck.
Okay, one second.
I think he dropped something.
Oh, did he?
Wait, did he actually?
Did I miss it?
I go check.
La la la la, la, waddle, waddle, waddle, waddle, waddle,
waddle, waddle.
Uh, no, this is here the whole time.
Let's... the last dialed number on this phone.
I don't know what that has to do with anything.
The number.
But I wanted to talk to... what's his name first, too.
La la la la, waddle, waddle, waddle, waddle, waddle waddle.
are what do you think of this have you seen sophie's
resignation no i can't say it comes at a surprise but you
wrote the letter she never particularly enjoyed her job it's
difficult finding replacements nowadays though uh-huh it's
not really a detective's job to spend crazy conspiracy
theories is it sometimes the truth is pretty crazy it seems
a bit cheap
Cheap added as a clue.
Where are these clues anyway?
Oh no, I'm in the...
You've hit rock bottom, Eugene.
I can only go up from here.
Who am I kidding?
This is so sad.
Yeah, the handwriting is the exact same.
It's all in all three of these.
Okay.
What am I doing?
Oh, the kidnapping.
And the salami bandit.
Blank is a salami bandit because blanks and his and her
blank.
Oh.
Okay, we got two things we got to figure out.
Sophie is at Bear Buses.
Well, um, maybe.
Maybe, uh, what's his name?
Manfred's office.
in wait huh oh in a oh wait where would she be in a box we
have all things we need apparently apparently yes we do
everything to solve the case and everything is she in the is
she in the cake no way that'd be crazy
she's in the in the box just a box everybody
wait unless she's in um rufus's office in a box dang well he
even was just like what's in these boxes unless she's in is
she on the bus did he take her to the bus oh bear bus his
office oh my god that's where she is being kept She's in a
fight.
It's important that I stayed calm now.
She's in a fight with her, for her life.
I couldn't alert the culprit, or all of this will have been
for nothing.
I needed to first figure out who is behind everything so I
could confront them.
Yeah, I thought it might be the bus because he's out here.
So I figured maybe he took her to the bus.
The most trendy duck hairstyle is a mullet.
Nice.
And also, this is closed now.
So, um...
Hey, you.
Salami Bandit.
Manfred is the Salami Bandit because...
Maybe Rufus and his...
Whoa, there's so much here.
Oh, wait.
Because...
The Salami Bandits and his handwriting are identical.
yeah manfred is the salami bandit rafoga welcome to
membership thank you that makes a lot of sense it makes a
lot of sense wait oh thank you for the raid sorry i have to
like lean in super far to be able to read the raid messages
now thanks for the clown raid thank you thank you stream
honk honk i'm just at the end of the game so if you guys if
you were gonna if you were gonna if you were gonna play it
maybe don't don't watch ironic that his handwritten note
meant to frame fredercent oh favor back thanks to the five
gifted and virulent thanks to the five gifted ended up
incriminating manfred instead done done something was
missing here who else was with this.
I had collected everything I needed.
I just had to organize my thoughts.
Okay.
Uh.
Oh, okay.
So maybe... That's why...
That's why she got kidnapped because Boris was in on it.
And that's why she was like, I'm gonna come clean.
The murdering!
The importing God I want I wish God I wish the salami bandit
wasn't working alone no it made sense for the bus driver to
be involved yeah oh there's more infatuation no he used to
date wait well Boris is the salon accomplice because he used
to date Sophie and the slimy bandit needed someone who could
convince someone into murdering no wait a second the
infatuation don't say that don't say that don't don't after
what happened earlier
He used to date Sophie.
Horace used to date.
But why would he be an accomplice?
He needed to convince...
Could convince Sophie into...
Dating.
What does that mean?
No.
Into helping?
Or...
Convince her to snitch...
Oh, selling.
Wait!
Um...
Who would be...
Oh, maybe...
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
Three or more things are wrong.
I thought maybe he would get her in on it.
Like, hey.
Like, hey, Sophie, we need a third person in here.
Switch Boris and Sophie?
Oh, maybe.
Boris.
No.
Wait, no.
Anyway.
So Sophie is the salami bandit's enemy.
So Boris is the salami bandit's accomplice because he used
to date Sophie and the salami bandit needed someone.
How?
Boris dates a boy.
Sophie dates Sophie.
Maybe you're thinking about it wrong.
Maybe accomplice is wrong.
You read her phone.
Yeah, and on the phone...
Oh wait, uh...
He... No, uh...
Here said, I'll tell them everything.
Don't.
And then she blocks them.
Right?
They were dating.
It has to be Boris about Sophie and Boris, because they're
the only ones that were dating.
Pretty sure Penguin Man and Margaret are still still a
thing.
Thank you so much for playing and enjoying the game.
My name is Deshaun Ricks, and I voice man for the bear!
Oh my god!
Thank you for dropping by!
It's so much fun!
And everybody's voice acting is so wonderful!
Thank you!
Oh, sorry if I'm like, um, uh, I just kind of, well, you
know, you're, you're, uh, I think I'm about to arrest you
maybe, but, um, you know.
Oh, thank you for dropping by.
Why?
Where are we thinking of the five gifting?
But I'm a little stupid right now.
Don't watch.
Oh, let's see.
I had a hair on my mic and I was like, it's tickling my
face.
I'm really glad it's not a spider.
It was a hair on my mic.
How did I get there?
What do you mean, gross?
It's just a hair.
It's my own hair.
I think it fell off my head.
Oh, gosh, I'm balding.
Anyway, what was it?
Okay.
Let's see.
Boris is the salami...
Or blank is the salami bandits...
Not lover.
Accomplice.
Because he used to date...
Sophie.
The salami bandit needed someone who could convince
the duck detective.
But I have three or more things wrong.
Hmm.
So close, but so far.
Would it be that she's an accomplice then?
Sophie's an accomplice because she used to date Boers and
needed someone who could convince... I don't think it's the
oh wait convinced someone else maybe uh salami bandan needed
someone who could convince into selling no convinced Boris
into selling well he oh into helping I feel like helping and
selling are like I believe Sophie managed to talk Boris into
this I feel like helping and Selling are pretty close, so it
was between one of them.
Aha!
I had it all figured out now.
It was time that I confront the culprits.
Time to confront.
But first?
More?
I had to free Sophie.
Sophie, I'm coming for you!
Oh, there she is, exactly where I know.
Ugh.
Sophie!
What's going on out here?
they're all in on it why is everyone yelling this looks
dramatic bump bump it's kind of a long story you're very
nonchalant for someone who was kidnapped and has
participated in illegal activity is missing and guess who
deduced said long story me the one and only duck detective
room oh my god this is how everything went down the britzel
bear bus branch was suffering losses and had their budget
cut as a result uh-oh manfred worried about the financial
stability of his family felt himself backed into a quarter
oh my god this is when he became the salami bandit he made
his grand plan of salami smuggling and realized he could
couldn't do this alone.
Dun, dun.
He recruited Boris, since it would be easiest for the bus
driver to load and unload the wares discreetly.
Discreetly.
The bus would go through a customs check at the South
Sitchia bus station first.
Uh-huh.
And then, Boris would take a detour to get the salami and
load it onto the bus.
Dun, dun, dun.
This is why the buses always had a huge delay.
It wouldn't be easy to talk bulls into crime so manfred
convinced sophie to join the team so messed up morris's
obsession with her would make it easy for her to manipulate
it so sad everything was going well until the duck detective
that's me infiltrated the office yeah Freddie was meant to
be the skit goat for the crime but I'm not fooled that
easily nope Sophie began getting cold feet and ultimately
wanted to confess to the police but who called the duck it
was laura could have this so he interfered laura called so
that she could figure out who stole her lunch and hit her in
the luggage compartment of one of the buses wow and this is
why manfred stole laura's lunch
everything is figured out but who is truly guilty Manfred
Sophie why would you do that though are all involved oh is
it to get get Freddy fired I guess who should get arrested
for their crimes Manfred was the mastermind behind
everything should Manfred get arrested oh wait we get to
choose hmm time to frame Freddy uh should we arrest freddie
anyway but
i kind of want to say no i kind of want to take freddie down
but um remember he was blackmailed that's right he was
blackmailed by a certain penguin he was the planner but he
technically didn't get his hands dirty not to mention what
it would do to his poor family wait he did get his hand wait
a second yeah that's that's i mean if you organize a murder
you still or just because he didn't commit the murder what
about sophie without her the smuggling wouldn't have been
possible she manipulated poor boris into taking the lobby
across the border wait do we get to choose for everybody
should sophie get arrested oh wow we can see who gets So
here we can say who gets arrested or not.
I feel like Sophie should get arrested.
I feel bad for poor Boris who got manipulated into this.
I think we should arrest Sophie.
And that's what they want you to think.
Maybe.
On her birthday.
She can watch KTS from jail.
What she did was clearly illegal.
Yeah!
She needs to face the consequences.
Boris was at the end.
end of the chain had he refused to take the salami on board
the plan would have not worked out mmm should Boris get
arrested no maybe he didn't even realize what was happening
I think he did I don't think he's that dumb maybe he is
someone all right I've made up my mind wait what about the
penguin though wait I will report to the state police we're
only arresting Sophie this is so backwards
this is
the person who was kidnapped the only person who wanted to
turn themselves in
Sophie what is this if I had known that calling the duck
detective would result in this I would have never done it
you were supposed to find out who stole my lunch i did i
told you my best friend of smuggling i did i did do i did do
that oh no she's crying again i know this was a bad idea
from the beginning this is so ducked up why the forest have
to lose the bag my god he is such an idiot i had no idea it
was that important
Oh, you see, he didn't know.
You said your cousin was ill.
Oh.
And the only thing that would make her happy was the
salsicia salamis.
Oh.
Oh, I should have known.
If you're stupid enough to believe that...
You know what?
Yeah, jail for Sophie.
Jail, jail, jail.
Then you're also too stupid to bring a couple sausages
across the border.
You know what?
I don't...
Jail!
You only let the bear off because he's here right now.
No!
Wow, you really did quack the case, Mr. Duck Detective.
Why'd you have to say it like that?
You're just as cool as I imagined.
Oh, he liked it.
Okay.
Not now, Freddersen.
I quack the case.
Saw the mystery of the secret salami.
I got an achievement.
The truth.
The truth is another.
mistress but it is my duty oh my god Manfred was in the back
smiling about it of lady justice
I'm the two percent I can't
oh my god oh
god my minutes hold on I think they're messaging me oh gosh
I can't believe this is probably 99% before this run 2% it
is the mint way all right I can't believe we are so vastly
wrong
Oh my gosh.
My ways are unconventional, everybody.
My Oshie is in the 2%.
Well, you know what?
Probably.
Probably any other playthrough you'll watch has Manfred
getting arrested.
So our playthrough is unique.
Thank you for the five gifts.
Oh gosh, thank you for ducking good time.
Eugene might not be a Colombo, but he's still a good egg.
Oh my goodness.
I love you.
I'm so...
The real free thinker, right?
I'm gonna recommend this just to do this.
I can't believe nothing happened to him or her oh gosh I'm
crying this is why we love you so much I don't know why
you're like this but please never change I think it was the
fact that it was so overwhelmingly if it were like even 90%
I don't think I would feel so but the fact that 8% is
insane.
One more thing.
Oh.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, crap.
Also, shout out to all the voice actors and actresses.
It did amazing.
I completely forgot to collect my payment from Laura.
Oh, no.
Everybody already went home.
Wait, we can't, we don't have...
How am I going to pay for the bus?
Oh, no.
Guess I'm walking home.
Here I go.
Oh, Freddy!
Ahem.
Need a ride?
I just booked this one.
It's been such a long day after all.
Nobody else does it like my Kamiyoshi y'all.
No, thank you.
If Freddy knows where we live, he'll definitely stalk us.
Come on, it'll be fun!
Plus, you must be tired after all the detective work.
I wonder if there will be a sequel and Freddy will be our
assistant in the sequel.
I really don't.
Please?
I'm sure even the VA in the chat couldn't believe he walked
great great now I finally have time to tell you all about my
ideas for your social media oh no please don't I could get
you tons of publicity oh yeah Freddie my manager desperately
need an LA noir playthrough now please please usually when I
play Kim's like that people get mad at me in the comments
they're just like why is she doing everything wrong why is
she such a villain and I'm like You don't give me the option
to be the villain if you don't want me to be the villain.
And imagine we can team up.
Absolutely not.
And I can be your sidekick.
Oh, Freddy's kind of cute.
I know why VTuber.
Oh, man.
The end.
And just in time for my meeting.
Perfect.
I have to pee so bad, though.
Oh, my gosh, I've had to pee for like the past half hour.
Thank you, guys, for joining me for Duck Detective.
If there's a sequel, I will play it.
This is so much fun.
Sorry for kind of skewing the polls a little bit in terms of
Manfred walking free, but it was great.
Baldur's Gate 3 Evil Playthrough.
I would do something like that.
I think Baldur's Gate is just way too long, you know?
So, um.
But yeah, I really thought something was going to happen to
the penguin and the, and the sheep lady, but nothing.
I guess, you know, justice can't always be served.
I didn't know my Oshi was a bad girl.
Oh, I would stick around and talk more with you guys, gotta
go, so thank you so much for joining me today, even though I
was a little silly to hear pero I'm sorry, I was so stupid
during that one part but uh we got the rest of it I got the
rest of it with my big brain I just took a, there was like
a, there was a salami stuck in my brain cogs, okay?
Anyway thank you guys!
Have a great night.
Oh!
I can show you.
Tomorrow.
I did make a schedule.
I got to post it.
I will post it after my meeting, most likely.
I think this is going to be really big.
Oh, no, it's perfect size.
So tomorrow, I will be doing a VR chat stream.
So, but we'll be hanging out in VR.
I'll be in full body VR.
So you can see me wiggle and squiggle.
And so we'll do that tomorrow.
And then afterwards, we'll be off Kai.
Sunday, I'll be heading off to Japan, so my schedule will be
a little inconsistent from Sunday, but I will be still
streaming from Japan, that is the plan, I bought a bunch of
stuff for it, so I, oh, and tomorrow I will be doing a test
stream of my laptop, and hopefully everything will work out,
I love you, please never change, thank you, thank you guys
so much, I will see you tomorrow for a wiggly, squiggly
time, and yeah, Otsumito!
Otsubasten Otsu Dark Detective!
Thank you guys, thank you so much, this is so much fun.
Bye bye, bye, bye bye, see you!