Hello, can you hear me?
Hello, howdy?
Are we okay?
I haven't talked today, so my voice is a little... I think... still sleepy voice.
Sleepy voice.
Good to see you.
Good to see you!
Welcome to the typing of the dead!
Overkill!
Are these songs the DMCN?
I hope not.
Also, I feel like I'm a little big.
House of the dead.
Overkill.
House of the dead?
It's fucking delicious!
No, no, this is typing of the dead, not house of the dead.
Critics said it's fucking good.
I am critics.
Maybe.
Sir,
your language!
YouTube's gonna get mad at me!
Prostitutes said I would suck that guy's dick.
Sir!
He's taking over my stream!
A ruthless crack whore said, give me a chicken dinner.
What?
What's happening?
What did he say, actually?
House of the dead.
Overkill.
Fucked up demons.
I'm playing typing of the dead for the first time ever.
I'm playing for the first time ever.
I just kinda wanted to do a typing game.
So here I am.
Oh my god!
Thanks Merlin!
It's covering my face though.
Why do you keep saying House of the Dead?
I know there's a House of the Dead right here.
Thank you!
I eat your... gifted.
Thanks Spank!
Thanks for the Tony!
I eat your doughnut.
Do you remember what your WPM is?
I think it was like 90 something.
I don't remember.
Andreas!
Thanks for the Tony gifted!
Oh wait.
I gotta wait for it to come up.
I'm waiting.
How does Mito type with her sleeves like that?
What are you talking about?
He's back.
Basically... wait.
Basically just an official mod arranged version of the House of the Dead.
Oh!
I used to play House of the Dead in the arcade so much.
Okay this guy.
This guy.
So I guess we just do story mode right?
Other critics said it's motherfucking good.
Can you let me speak please?
Casey thanks for the gifted.
A three corner prostitute says I would suck that guy up dead.
Stop!
We're gonna go to story mode.
Story mode.
I ain't no bitch!
A toothless crack horse.
I'm an MF-er!
Give me a chicken dinner.
I'm a mint phantom-er!
I'm an MF-er!
Should I try this one?
Is it very difficult?
Should I be MF-er?
Actually hold on.
Let me make sure I can put my...
Okay I gotta move my mic over a little bit.
So I can reach my keyboard properly.
Longer words!
Let's try it!
Okay this is putting my true OL-ness to the test.
Let's try it.
Intermission?
Okay let's play the game baby!
Watch Grindhouse if I like this game.
What's up motherfucker?
Tatsumi!
We met as adversaries.
What the fuck was that for?
A monster made them allies.
A secret agent.
Immaculate.
Intelligent.
A rookie.
He's got the rookie's eyes.
They call him Only G.
How's the audio by the way?
His identity?
A mystery.
Only G?
You ever gonna tell anyone what that fucking G stands for?
No.
A playboy cop.
Isaac Washington.
No.
Make him mad and he'll rip your balls off.
Not the license plate!
I'm gonna rip your motherfucking balls off!
Night.
These unlikely allies will confront terror most foul.
In the blood so tall.
This game is awesome!
Papa's palace of pain.
Be a courteous guest.
By tomorrow morning I'll have my motherfucking revenge.
Papa Caesar will be dead.
This game is so awesome!
If we don't stop this mutant outbreak by tomorrow morning we'll all be dead.
Wait have I been streaming for...
Okay a couple minutes we're good.
This will be your last.
Papa's palace of pain.
PPP.
Rated X.
Not for children.
Every kid get out of here.
The grown ups are playing now.
Oh!
Brains!
Okay.
Alright.
Nice.
Press tab to...
Okay.
Alright.
How do I tab?
There we go.
Oh.
What does this mean?
Exult.
Okay.
Mega Man X.
Nice.
Oh.
Okay.
This is not proof.
Oh my lover!
My lover baby.
Liver.
Ah!
Infected!
Quick!
Oh my god.
Opaque.
I never use...
Gutter.
Oh.
Meat bag.
I have to do the capitals too, right?
Is that what makes it more difficult?
Oh.
Oh my god.
Come down.
Cut him down.
Oh.
We're gaming you guys.
We're gaming.
Don't be long.
Oh.
We got him.
Oh my god.
I got an achievement.
A Gorgasm.
Oh my god.
Obscene.
I don't know how to spell.
It's not just...
It's not just typing.
Oh.
Hush.
They're sleeping.
It's not just typing.
It's knowing how to spell too.
Oh god.
Oh.
Library car.
Backspace.
Oh.
Wait.
I couldn't read that.
I was typing.
Elementary my dear.
Up and down.
Okay.
Hush.
Perfect grammar game.
I know.
Chemical reaction maybe.
Easy.
Game debuted on the Wii?
How is that possible?
Um.
Hello.
I'm already done.
Don't like Monday.
Oh.
Dry your eyes.
Ha.
Got the munchies.
Spell mint.
Not sick.
Just coughing.
Hup.
Oh.
Your dad.
Berkshire hut.
Skill shot.
Or attempt at flattery.
Your dad.
Oh my god.
Man slaughter of crows.
It's literally typing of the dad.
Crappy birthday.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
Big drum.
Quadruple double.
The mace.
I don't want it.
Okay.
Get out of here.
Oh.
I'm scared you guys.
I'm scared.
A crud.
Slice.
Filthy.
Rank.
Where are my feet?
Haha.
Dead.
Maintain a gorgasm for two minutes.
You guys.
I'm...
Gorgasming.
Last rise.
Napoleon ate the pig.
Is my health okay?
Where is everyone else?
Pitch perfect.
Go Curly.
Flippers.
Addressed by your moment.
Batting collapse.
Is my health okay?
I can't tell.
Go Curly.
Science fiction.
Wait.
Tap.
Oh.
Odds or evens.
Oh my god.
Bat of rancid cheese.
No damage?
Oh.
How can you tell?
But my character is like red in the corner.
Oh my god.
Exit.
Stage left.
Up past the mud.
Please.
Thank you.
Sticky fingers.
Oh.
Hold your fire.
Pizza.
Are
you gonna kiss me?
Or what?
Oh.
Head.
Shit man.
That ain't right.
Pizza.
Pizza saved the civilian.
Hello?
Hold your fire.
Pizza.
I got them.
I saved them probably.
Yeah.
We're good.
Almost free.
That's hard to say.
Oh.
Drowning.
Possibly problematic.
Okay.
Um.
Stop shooting.
Nope.
Hidden depths.
Shit.
I fucking hate these zombies.
Mutants.
How many times do I have to tell you not to use the Z word?
Tate.
Wait.
Unpro.
Oh.
Unprovoked.
Assault.
Oh.
Flooding.
Destructible crate.
Oh my god.
That was close.
Oh.
Stomach ache.
Tommy heart.
Flip the.
The bird.
Oh.
Stack the deck.
A vibrating peripheral.
These are hard words.
Oh my god.
I'm stressed.
A melon fiber.
Fizzy.
Make.
Me.
Feel.
Good.
I actually just typed me.
A melon fiber.
To hell going.
Shut up and press the button.
Press the button.
Oof.
What kind of bird?
Um.
A shoebill.
Tommy heart.
Oh.
We should have taken the stairs.
This ghost got head.
Washington.
You okay?
No.
I am not okay.
Asshole.
Shake it off detective.
Come on.
Let's move.
You don't have to be rude about it.
Oh.
I would play the heck out of this as a kid.
To learn how to type.
I'm not saying I did.
I'm saying I would if I had it.
You know?
Why are we going in here?
Oh.
I have a.
Okay.
I definitely read that wrong.
Room.
Serve.
Oh god.
Can't.
Do.
Stay.
Oh no.
I lost the health.
Oh my god.
Damned if you don't.
Oh.
Bad.
At.
Hards.
Oh shoot.
Button up.
Please use a mirror.
It's hard sometimes.
I just type what I.
What I.
Type.
What I see first.
Rather than.
Who taught these guys table manners?
What's coming at me first?
These guys ain't human.
Walrus badge.
I've never seen this kind of crazy shit before.
All right.
So what's the game plan?
What are they making?
You restrain the subject.
And I'll lead an interrogation.
Wait.
What are we taught?
Up that column.
Columbo.
Shoot to me.
Oh my god.
Oh.
Sex repellent.
Oh my god.
This is hard.
Ham toucher.
Columbo Mansion.
Let's go baby.
Oh.
Uh.
Okay.
Donut.
Consume donut.
Over there.
Thank you.
Pastrami.
Oh no.
I killed him.
Guys.
I thought I was gaming.
Um.
Don't worry about him though.
I thought we saved him.
A sadistic crime lord.
Master of a perverse science.
I thought I got the right one.
My darling Jasper.
Do you have a present for me?
They call him Caesar.
Papa Caesar.
A test subject at the hospital.
A show in progress.
You've done very well my boy.
We shall celebrate your success.
I'll take this tonight with take out, Chinese.
Oh nice.
A brilliant mind with a broken body.
You've gone too far Papa Caesar.
His talents turn to evil to protect the sister who raised him.
No he's Papa Caesar not Papa John's.
Oh my god.
Think of your sister before threatening Papa Caesar.
Papa Caesar.
Next time you speak.
Turn the volume to zero.
Fucking cabbage.
Nobody threatens Varla.
What the?
The ultimate sacrifice.
Oh my god.
What's happening?
Freeze bitches.
Because of the shocking nature of the following scenes.
They are definitely not recommended for the squeamish or the easily offended.
Are you guys easily offended?
Or squeamish?
What is?
Oh my god.
Oh no.
Oh ew.
What the?
Oh my god.
Who is?
I feel tall.
Call it a draw.
What?
Free at last.
Good evening.
Oh shit.
P. Oh my god.
X.
Man.
F.
Stupid stairs.
B.
Want to be loved.
Oh.
A bit.
Shit.
Oh.
H.
I like cabbage.
He's mind touching me.
Oh my god.
Move zig.
Kind of like it though.
You're not so fucking clever now, are you, bitch?
Cute and yellow.
It.
Okay.
Oh.
He's gross.
His fingers.
Oh.
He's nasty.
Mame.
Nice.
He's giving, um, Psycho Mantis.
Jump.
Oh.
Shoot.
I pressed tab for that.
Whatever it is, just shoot it.
Oh my god.
Back.
Live.
Vlog.
Not so fucking clever now, are you, bitch?
Oh.
Your face are being locked out.
My brain is beautiful.
Quick.
Shoot him.
I'm not even a mutant.
One.
Two.
I'm not even a mutant.
My palace of pain.
Oh.
Shit.
W.
Oh.
Shoot.
Ow.
Shit.
Take him out.
I can help you with the pain.
Yeah.
No, you can fucking not.
Shoot the motherfucker.
Don't you do tact.
That's what I am going to fucking do.
Yeah, but you stopped him.
You know, shut the fuck up and shoot.
Shit.
Stop.
You stopped.
Oh.
Happy now?
Fuckwit.
You fucking bastards.
You killed my brother.
You're his sister?
Oh my god.
Oh.
Guns.
A doting sibling to a crippled brother.
Forced into a life of vice.
Now she's filled with a primal hunger for revenge.
Oh, his sister.
Mankind's last hope now rests on the shoulders of two men.
Caesar's heading to the hospital.
We got to stop that asshole before he gets there.
Tasteful ride.
Don't disrespect my wheels.
She's my pride and joy.
Oh, I want to see the ride.
Oh.
Oh, the ride.
We'll take my car.
The plantation house has claimed its victims, but with Papa Caesar on the loose, nobody is safe.
Oh, sister.
You died trying to stop Caesar.
I won't rest until I've shot his fucking guts over half the county.
Yeah, you talk, Miss Gun- oh, there she goes.
Complete Papa's Palace of Pain.
Oh, my accuracy was 90.
97%.
Dang.
I got a gorgasm for 254 seconds.
Almost 255.
He got A rank.
Yeah, baby.
Don't look at this part, though.
Don't look at this part.
Comics found.
Okay, I forget how to...
Posters found.
Records found.
How do I find those?
I saw some...
I have to press tap...
Oh, no, wait.
What was the button that I pressed?
Oh, I forgot.
Oh, my gosh.
S17.
Thank you for the 50 gifted.
Thank you.
Oh, just tab, right?
Okay, tab.
I saw things glowing.
I think it was also health.
Okay, tab.
Okay.
Just spam tab when you're not shooting?
Good to know.
Nice.
This is fun.
Those LOL skills paying off.
Come on.
Wait.
Am I going to be okay with this?
Is YouTube going to be angry at me?
Wait.
I thought we were going to the hospital.
So long, baby.
I mean, I'm fine with it.
It's really just, you know...
YouTube is the one who gets...
Oh, see.
It's Pussycat.
She's not...
She's not in his chair.
A voluptuous vixen, vowing violent vengeance.
Papa Caesar, you better pray those fucking pigs catch up with you before I do.
What?
Oh, my God.
No nudity in this level?
In this one?
Okay.
She took his chair.
Oh.
Let's go.
Oh, my God.
Jiggle physics.
Is it going to explode?
Okay.
I was hoping.
Candy Striper.
Candy Striper?
Just your average girl next door.
But behind her wholesome image lies a dark secret.
What's that?
Hi, Jasper.
My special little chair baby.
Oh, no.
One day, we'll be free of this hellhole.
She was in love with him.
Forced to degrade herself night after night for cheap thrills and a handful of dollar bills.
Your brother!
You're just getting the guns ready.
Wait.
Does she know?
Does the other girl know?
Does Candy know?
I swear, Caesar.
I'm going to shove this gun so far down your side, you're going to have to burp.
Oh my god, she's awesome.
Oh!
Ah!
Viola.
His car.
Damn.
Oh no.
His car.
I know.
Oh my god, no.
Stairlift.
This dialogue is insane.
No!
I'm sorry.
This acting is grade A.
Oh my god, how romantic.
Where are the mirrors?
Anything else I should know?
Just that.
Oh my god!
Sorry.
I said there's a zombie invasion.
Never mind.
Get ready to be titillated, tantalized, and teased by tasseled titty temptresses.
But beware, these kittens have claws.
Witness naked desire, naked lust, naked terror.
Keep both hands on the controller.
My hands are on the...
How do you type in the weed?
How did you do that?
Naked snake.
Here we go.
Oh, frost.
Artists only backstage.
And strippers.
Get out of here.
And strippers, baby.
My lovely lady lumps, we are...
Shit.
I got the wrong guy.
Here we go.
Right.
I think I'm the only one who knew all of this.
No one knows.
It's the best.
I think I'm the only one.
What's this?
It's a...
I don't know what it is, but I don't know what it is.
Time.
Time, time, time, time, time...
Butterfly, shit!
What the...
Oh my god.
I got the wrong word.
Space, maybe?
I don't know.
Ew.
Was your hands.
Ew!
Reported you for spam.
Oh, I got it!
Sova-doodles!
A philosophical zombie gun in your pocket?
Are you just happy to see me?
I'm tapping, I'm tapping, I'm tapping.
Nice.
What kind of asshole locks a fire exit?
I don't think that's legal.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god...
We got him.
Here, baby!
I'm tapping, I'm tapping.
Oh!
Stroke!
One!
Looks like it's business as usual out here.
Another bunch of creeps pawing at your body and tipping badly.
Oh my god.
Sorry, that guy freaked me.
This crazy world!
Don't hit me.
A Q and R!
They're ready for a show, baby.
Let's give them one.
Oh and...
Slippers.
Ah!
That's my stage, bitch!
You tell her.
Uh, Q-tips.
Psychotic!
Psychotic?
Cat fight, baby!
What?
Are you kidding me?
This doesn't count as a fucking emergency.
Oh my god.
Oh shit.
Tea cakes, shit.
I did the wrong one.
No!
Oh!
Tabtab-tab-tab-tab-tab-tab-tab?
Tabición-tab replacement?
J hay que hacer una torre batidora?
Tab-tab-tab-tab-tab-tab-tab-tab-tab?
T.
S.
Tab-tab-tab-tab-tab-tab-tab-tab.
O و E.
Tam-tab-tab.
Oh, look at them go!
Oh.
Oh my god.
Oh god.
Oh no!
Shit!
Pirates.
Turn in this thing.
Oh my god.
Down with this sort of thing.
Umm...
Up, up and away!
Damn.
Take control of your place.
Oh well!
That's me!
Parkour, baby.
Our girl's hot and flexible.
What
the hell is this?
What the hell is a Triska 5 doing?
Oh, dang it, I missed it.
What am I typing?
What the hell did I just type?
Looks like closing time on a Saturday night out here.
Closing time...
There we go.
That was close.
That was so close.
Tab.
Clouds.
Ordinary.
Ordinary!
Genius!
Dang it.
Tab, tab, tab, tab, tab, tab, tab, tab, tab, tab, tab, tab.
I don't even know what this is!
Whiskey Sour!
Tab, tab, tab, tab, tab, tab, tab.
Very explained fresh.
Should I do this?
Hey!
Watch where you're throwing that thing!
Oh my god!
Eh!
Gosh!
That could have had someone's eye out.
Yeah!
Dang it.
Learning so many new words.
Risky cake robot.
I almost wrote freaky out of habit.
Oh!
Nice!
I saw that one.
Hehe.
Fist!
Filthy!
Oh!
Nuns are freaky!
Ah!
Hi!
Leo!
Titanium!
Electromagnetic spectrum.
Oh my!
Shoot me down!
I think we need to clean up an aisle too.
Sticks and stones!
Oh!
Fuzzy headed morning!
Ouch!
Save the civilian!
Oh shit!
I don't know how to write sausages.
Hahaha!
Hey!
You assholes in the tank!
Why don't you try using that fucking thing?
Yeah!
What are you doing?
Oh shit!
Under your bed!
Take your canvas bags!
Oh my god!
A maze ball!
This one's hard.
Oh!
God!
That one's not easy.
That's disgusting!
How can they do that?
With no barbecue sauce?
Hahaha!
Oh my god!
Haunted!
My accuracy though!
I'm gonna freak out you guys!
We're going to the saloon!
Ah!
Phrase and trombone!
Oh my god!
Oh nice!
Oh that was close.
I need health.
I need health!
Varla, look!
Here's your bike!
The bike!
No fucking keys though.
Oh!
Spurting?
Oh ferocious spinster!
I see the service here hasn't improved.
Oh my god.
Oh shit.
Hyperbolic trajectory!
I can't spell these things man!
This is not just...
This is not just typing!
Oh!
What was that?
Q or O?
I can't tell actually.
Eee!
Aye!
Okay.
Shushushusha.
What a bunch of freaks!
It was Q?
Oh okay.
What a bunch of freaks!
Ooh la la la.
Forever dancers baby.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Ugh.
Sport.
B2BO are you no type?
I'm getting performance anxiety!
I'm on hardcore.
I'm on...
I'm on mint phantom mode.
Right.
Which one of you bitches has my fucking keys?
Her pit is out!
Have you lost weight?
Where's her little fuck buddy?
Her bo...
Oh my god!
Cover up!
Look for...
Look at Cindy's stomach.
Oh fucking gross!
What are you doing now?
You take those bitches down!
Yeah!
Take them down baby!
Okay.
Here we go.
Coco and Cindy!
Oh great!
Uh.
Ew.
Oh god.
They're so gross.
Ew.
Oh god.
Ew!
Levato...
Oh.
Ew.
The music's so funky.
I like it.
Oh my god.
The boob I can't get...
I can't...
I'm just staring at the one boob.
Ow!
Oh.
Uh.
Stop running around please!
I can't read.
Mainly moist.
Ah.
Dolores Drinkers.
Dol...
Okay.
The music is... the lighting and everything is... oh my god.
Fabulous fetish!
The music is so funky.
Okay.
Breast isn't best.
What are you talking about?
Elephantine empress.
What do you mean breast isn't best?
This game sucks.
Oh, we're moving in.
We're moving in.
Z!
Okay.
This one is easier, I think.
Than the other one.
The previous boss battle.
Your bitches never could dance.
We took her out so easily!
Ass is gas.
Ew!
That's how you wanna go?
Flattened by...
By, um...
A giantess?
My bike better still be in one piece or I'm gonna come back and kill you fucking bitches all over again.
I love how aggressive everybody is in this game.
What happened to them?
How did they get like that?
Damn if I know.
But I bet that sick fuck Caesar has something to do with it.
Caesar!
Where is he now?
Being chased by two asshole cops.
Then we should go after them.
No, kid.
It's too late.
It's too dangerous for you.
I don't think Candy does anything.
Jasper wouldn't want you to risk your life avenging him.
But Popper Caesar killed him.
Popper Caesar.
Tell me something I don't know, girl.
Well, Jasper had this thing he liked me to do where I'd...
Fuck!
I don't need to hear that.
Now let's get you the fuck out here.
That's her brother!
Then are you going to try to find Popper Caesar?
Popper Caesar?
Listen, sister.
I don't try anything.
I just get up and do it.
And when I'm done, that fuck will be dead.
Now come on!
Riding into the night.
A trail of carnage, mayhem, and devastation behind them.
Driven by a single desire.
Revenge.
Revenge, baby!
I kind of love the writing in this game.
Complete naked terror.
My accuracy was still 93%.
I had no orgasms, though.
But you know...
A to C.
Cs get degrees, okay?
And I found a secret figurine and a record.
And I rescued both civilians, okay?
Okay!
Gotta use that backspace to switch words.
That's what it said!
Oh!
Okay.
Because...
I couldn't read it before because I was playing the game.
So I couldn't read what it said about the backspace.
I don't even know what the Gorgasm is.
I think it's your... I think it's...
Well, it had a 24 combo.
I have no idea.
Tab button to pick up and backspace will help you switch words, right?
Okay.
Oh, it's a no damage streak.
What's going on?
What's gonna happen next?
Ballis...
As you well know, I...
I enjoy pain.
It's like a good Chinese dinner, you know?
With the sweet...
Ballistic drama.
Expanding on that analogy.
I will smile with delight.
That's the sweet...
What was Player 2 doing?
Right?
That person sucks.
Sunday girl, welcome back.
Are we going to the hospital?
Is this Metal Gear Solid 5?
Let's go.
Oh, they're shooting behind me?
We'll see about that.
What?
This is making me want Chinese.
Haha.
Tonight, you have been admitted to Bayou County General.
Rest assured, Clement.
Clement.
I have a plan which will eliminate both of them.
And any evidence of our work here.
Your symptoms?
Cold sweats.
Irregular heartbeat.
Anxiety.
Oh my god, the nurses.
Oh la la.
The diagnosis, bleeding horror that cuts like a scalpel to the heart.
What are they doing to him?
There is only one cure.
There's only one cure.
A way-hot boot to the brain.
Ballistic trauma.
Wee-woo.
Left you point-blank prescription.
I want what they're having.
Same.
Here we go, baby.
I'm ready.
Doctor.
I think there's something wrong with me.
Time for some aggressive surgery.
Doctor.
Hiding.
Gooseberry!
Where's your warrant?
Ooh.
I got a fever, doctor.
Yeah!
Oh.
That one's hard.
Slippery.
That one is a little slippery.
What the...
I'm gonna make you mad!
I don't want.
She said I should have slept!
There's a present for you!
Hot dog!
Settle down!
Ugly is as ugly does!
Oh shit.
That was close.
Oh my god, she's running towards us.
Some of these zombies are crazy!
Sorry, mutants.
Chill out!
Doctor!
Oh my god.
She's hot.
Get out of here, dude!
Why are you taking the elevator out?
Pull my finger, monstrosity!
Where'd the other guy go, though?
Who's taking pictures?
Oh.
Anecdote.
Oh, why'd the music get kinda scary?
I'm psychotic!
Oh, that was so close!
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
Oh, you guys.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
This is... I gotta focus.
Spinal tap!
Oh my god.
Lung!
Oh, got it.
What is that?
Whoa, what's happening?
Metal Gear game.
This is a...
Oh!
Oh, it slowed it down!
That's awesome!
Yeah!
No!
Uh... Oh shit, it's sausages!
You're not gonna live, bro!
Okay.
I'm alive!
Can we save him?
Furious...
Giraffe...
I don't even know what half these words are, you guys.
I think I'm an idiot.
Oh, I saw that poster!
What the hell does that mean?
Violets.
I see the poster!
Grab it!
Oh, never mind.
Or something.
There was something there.
Evil Dead!
Okay,
we're back to the silly music.
Pork to bite!
Nasty rash!
Ew!
I left like a bit of a...
Pumpkin carving!
Oh!
Who's taking pictures?
Help us please!
Oh!
Never mind.
Sorry about your super title, read it.
I'm alive!
I'm motherfucking still alive!
I'm still alive!
Yeah, just my life.
Bitches!
Yes!
Oh!
I think we got the slowdown again.
Obey the crab!
Nice!
Oh shit!
No!
Oh my god, she did double damage to me!
Oh shit!
No!
I got the wrong one again!
Are we going in?
No orgasm!
I messed up!
Who is it called?
I saw health over there.
Give it to me!
There we go!
Nice!
Closer, baby!
Skip level!
Oh no, my alarm is going off.
Go, go!
That was close!
Towel thief!
Cranberry!
Please use a mirror!
It's hard to tell which guy is for like which word.
Chocolate teapot!
I've fallen and I can't get out!
God!
Oh!
Ew!
The whole scared of aging was pretty funny.
Chastity belt!
They're good at picking words that are really hard.
I ain't no mutant!
Uh...
I got him.
You're welcome!
Get out of here, mister!
Show me those fingers, baby!
Yubi yubi!
Beep beep beep beep!
Oh!
Oh, goodness!
That's a reason to go to the hospital!
Nice!
Come on!
Don't wanna waste my slowdown!
Wait, I'm wasting my slowdown.
What a waste!
Wait, what a waste!
Hahaha!
Oh!
You stole my sandwich!
Oh, I saw the health over there!
Thanks for the super chat!
No!
My health!
I see it!
Grab it!
Oh, dang it.
I missed it.
I'm spamming.
I'm tired of vanilla.
Oh!
Oh, shit!
Mardi Gras!
Extreme bias!
I'm scared.
I'm scared, Elias.
I'm not gonna make it.
I'm not gonna get an A.
Filthy thoughts!
Oh!
Freaky eye thing!
Oh, my God!
Sometimes I, like, think I'm pressing a letter and I really don't.
Hello?
Anybody here?
Oh!
Oh, my God!
Please!
Give me lemons!
Dead wrong!
The other one was too hard, man!
The other one was too hard!
They're speaking Latin.
Rufy!
Oh, my gosh.
I knew I wasn't gonna get that one.
Oh, this is hard!
Holy cow!
Oh.
Beach again!
Shoot!
Extreme violence!
Oh!
Chop!
Oof!
Sour mash!
Got a comic.
Okay.
Nice.
I'm just keep pressing tab.
Take it.
My arm!
My arm fell off!
You're a liar!
You had both arms!
Ultraviolence!
Oh!
This looks like a boss room.
Maybe.
Oh!
Eww!
Let's go.
Oh!
Gross!
Why did we go in here?
That was not very smart.
Hahaha!
Lying zombie.
He's like, my arm fell off!
He's like...
You are an absolute liar!
You literally had both arms!
Ma 'am, are you okay?
Move aside, diaper shit!
Let a man handle this!
Oh my god!
Motherfuck!
Eww!
Please, my ears!
Move aside, diaper shit!
Shoves her.
Screamer!
Okay.
Alright.
I turned down the volume just a little bit.
Because I don't want to hear...
Oh my god.
Where did she go?
No fucking idea.
But next time I see her, I'm shooting her right in the face.
Why does he sometimes sound like Snake?
Oh my god.
No way.
Ugh.
Oh my god.
Ah!
I don't know if I got the right one.
I don't think I did.
What the?
Did you say something, Detective Washington?
Wait, what?
Only one is real?
Oh my god.
No way.
Is there a way to tell?
Oh god.
Ooh, scary.
This one's freaky.
Oh, these are so fun.
Each boss is so different.
I love it.
Oh my god.
Nice.
Zombie ghost.
This is so awesome.
I love this one so much.
Oh.
Why am I so bad at choosing the right one?
How do you know which one is the correct one?
Oh, it doesn't flicker.
Okay, okay.
I'm too busy.
I'm not looking at her.
I'm too busy looking at the words.
Oh, shoot.
The correct one is solid.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
No!
Oh my...
Screw procedure.
Yeah.
Can't even speak anymore.
Oh.
I see it now.
Thank you guys.
That should be it.
There we go.
She can't spell with her mouth.
Procedure.
Screw procedure.
That's not my phone.
An unexpected complication.
The bitch is ringing.
No mother fucking way, man.
I manicured only yesterday.
You manicured.
What if I fucking do?
These ain't going inside that bitch.
No finger fucking way.
Yeah, you tell him.
Get in there, babe.
Oh my god.
Oh, he's treating it like an art.
Who could be behind such depravity?
That looks more like a bomb than a phone.
It's for you.
What the?
Isaac, darling.
Caesar!
Papa strikes again.
As you well know, Isaac, I enjoy pain.
It's like a good Chinese dinner, you know.
This guy can't get over his Chinese dinner.
Expanding on that analogy, I will smile with delight.
That's the sweet.
As you scream for your fucking life.
Of course, that's the sour.
Oh, ciao.
I think it's gonna...
Is it gonna explode?
Yeah.
Get out of here!
Succulent Chinese meal.
It's making me hungry.
All I had for breakfast was anpan.
Not the car second time.
This guy is...
a howling hellcat humping a hot steel hog.
The hog.
And you, crock and tug, jump on.
Hog.
A seductive she-devil beating a pair of pigs on a roaring rampage of revenge.
Oh,
we got a bee!
Okay, okay.
Okay.
And I had Gorgasm for just a little bit.
I didn't get any of the figurines though.
Oh wait, there were none.
Stupid.
I got everything!
Oh my gosh!
Bee.
95% accuracy.
Cranking the hog.
Yeah!
She's a pro, everybody.
She's a pro.
Player 2 is useless.
Player 2, we hate that guy.
If you pick 2 player, do you both use the same keyboard?
I don't know.
Has anybody done 2 player?
If Leo wants to come play, she can come to my room and then she can use...
I could use the laptop keyboard and she could use my other keyboard.
She's probably not even still here.
Why do you have 2 keyboards?
Because imagine playing games on a laptop keyboard.
It's the worst ever.
It was a shared keyboard?
Yuck.
Carnie.
Do you guys have a fear of clowns and stuff?
I can't believe that this was in arcades and stuff even.
No, I don't fear you.
I'm going to become the Joker.
I am going to literally I am going to I like clowns actually.
I fear I may be a clown.
Yeah.
We all clown a little bit.
We all clown around a little bit, don't we?
You know.
We're all a little bit funky fresh.
But actually, I'm so curious.
How do you play this on a Wii?
I'm like legitimately confused.
This guy is just talking to himself.
Wait, the Wii...
Oh, it wasn't a typing game.
Oh, I see.
I see.
So it's just a shooter.
Then why was it called typing of the dead?
Just shooting.
No typing.
Sorry, I misremembered.
Two keyboards.
Oh.
Like a sardine in a mother fucking tin can!
Was that a thanks for saving my worthless pig hide I just heard, Lieutenant Limp Dick?
We're both very appreciative of you coming to our rescue, miss.
Varla.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
Why is it so loud?
Ball of fucking guns?
What kind of name is that?
The name I was born with, dipshit.
Did you see my birth was celebrate.
Sounds like the best name ever.
What is this shirt?
Is it like a Mothman?
D D D D baby baby baby.
Top secret.
Is it personal or... wait why?
You could have just moved around him.
Why are we stopping in front of this guy?
Ew.
Sherlock.
If you're both finished admiring each other's dicks, can I remind you we have a fucking mass murdering psychopath son of a bitch to catch?
You wait there woman.
Agent Gwendolyn and me are gonna check this shit out.
Fuck you.
Everybody is so aggressive.
What happened to Candy?
Mother fuck.
What does a brother have to do to pacify a bitch?
I'm telling you G, I tried my best with her.
God be my witness.
Look at the way he's standing.
Oh you can't see my head, my head was blocking it.
Ladies and gentlemen, the infinite tact of Isaac Washington.
You do, truly you do, use your tongue better than a thirty dollar hooker.
And man, can I say from the bottom of my heart, you are a shining example to all of us.
Mankind.
Is this the time to be fighting?
Don't make me hit you again.
Yeah, stop fighting girlies.
Carny, a thousand tiny fingers clawing at your spine.
I need a, I need a tissue.
But no time.
Time to shoot some mutants.
Uh oh.
The clowns are loose.
Stop clowning around.
Oh my god, the leg.
Why are sometimes they're green?
Is this some kind of fucking sick joke?
Green is the furthest away.
Oh I see.
I'm just, I'm on like the, I'm on like the fourth chapter or something and I'm just now learning how the game works.
That guy.
Sometimes
they're all yellow.
It's so annoying.
Hold your fire.
Oh god.
Catch him!
This will hurt.
Do you?
I got him.
This is bad.
X.
Damn right this is bad.
Those hands in the...
Oh god.
I'm gonna make your fucking side split.
Wait, what happened to the...
Oh.
Oh, he was talking.
That's why.
Ice, ice, baby!
Okay, okay.
Getting the hang of it a little bit.
A little bit at a time.
Liar, liar.
Pants on fire.
Ice, ice.
Oh, before Wicked.
What the hell did I...
Oh my god.
Hold your fire.
What is it?
Roasted.
There we go.
Liar, liar.
Lambda.
How are some of these people still alive?
Like, where were you hiding?
Hurt me more, snake.
Uh-oh.
Wrong way!
Okay.
This way.
Oh, tab, tab, tab.
Oh, I got the slowdown.
No, no!
I'm wasting it again!
I'm wasting the slowdown!
Okay, whatever.
Why, the gentleman!
Oh shit.
Stay a while!
Egg and spoon break.
Oh, I got another one.
Okay.
Oh my god.
What are these words?
Wunderbush.
Never even heard of that before.
I'm not even thinking of what I'm typing anymore.
This does not look good.
Good, good.
I'm just like.
No, nothing good.
I'm seeing...
Oh my god!
Punch him!
Crack his head!
God!
Oh my god!
Koji!
Nymphomania!
I was a nymph.
Thank you for your service.
C-E-P-H-U
What about those guys?
Get them!
Get their butts!
Okay, we're just gonna ignore those guys, I guess.
Have you seen my cat?
That's not what I asked.
Lock, stock, and...
Oh shit!
I ask that all the time.
Have you seen my cat?
Golden goose!
Jolly Roger Outer Space I can smell him.
I miss my cat so much.
Oh shit.
Big dipper.
Thank god that I...
I was scratching the back of my head!
Procedure can kiss my ass.
Yeah, procedure can kiss my ass.
Are we gonna save that girl?
Oh my god.
My sweet bite.
He's asking...
He's asking procedure.
He's fire, everybody.
Not the five-finger discount!
Oh.
Tortoiseshell.
Okay.
Number one.
The only...
Xylophone fan.
Drinking from...
Oh yeah!
Yeah!
Aim for the chest!
Nice.
Tortoiseshell.
I just completely forgot to press...
Tabab tab.
Is there...
What's the word?
Oh my gosh.
Tab!
Sorry.
I'm so...
Vibrating peripheral.
I'm so focused on the words.
The mutant compound must have raised their metabolic rate.
Boy, I don't understand half the shit that comes out of your mouth.
Incinerate!
Oh, what the?
No, I...
Maybe I shouldn't do it in all caps.
That's what's slowing me down.
Why didn't we keep the hammer?
Why didn't we keep the...
Oh, we got another hammer this time.
Why didn't we keep the hammer?
Oh, there's no...
What happened to the sound?
Hello?
My head moved.
Oh!
Oh
my god!
We'll get her.
Maybe.
Munch?
Sound ok.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Vocabulary.
Oh my god.
Vocabu...
What the hell does that mean?
Am I...
Motherfucker.
N.
J.
Oof, that was close.
Oh my god, another civilian?
Ask Mr. Webster.
You're welcome.
You're not gonna make it.
You are not gonna make it.
You're like limping.
Saxophone!
More than mutants, it's mutant carnies!
Oh my goodness.
Oh.
Wailing plots, marching band.
To sing you goodbye.
Stay.
Oh my god, this is the perfect time.
To have the slowdown.
Oh my god.
Oof.
Cucumber confusion!
Oh, come on.
That one's hard.
The 50-50 is hard.
Donut!
Cucumber confusion.
Look at that guy back there dancing.
Where?
I couldn't see what those games were.
I don't know how to spell vengeance.
Yeah, I won't let you have the satisfaction of touching me.
Cue!
Fly, you fools.
Nice.
Nice, nice.
Mutant shot the food!
Oh shit.
Oh my god, oh my god.
A cranberry!
Thanks, game.
How am I doing that?
Oh, you shitting me, man?
How am I doing, actually?
Oh, into the house!
Let's go!
This place is pretty spooky.
Spooky!
Are you holding my hand?
Wait.
I ain't your mama!
Get the fuck off of me!
Oh.
Which ones are real?
Oh!
Oh, that was close.
Too scary for me.
Which ones are real, you guys?
Which ones are real?
Which ones are fake?
I don't know.
Look at all the...
They're just all the same animatronics.
I'm doing well.
Yippee!
U.S.
Breach!
Oh.
I got the slow-mo again.
Thank you.
G.A.W.
Oh.
I think I missed some of those.
I forgot for a second we were playing a game.
I was excited to be on the...
On the thing.
On the ride.
Jellied eels?
Oh, it's eel season right now.
Oh.
Shit, man.
That ain't right.
Vordae?
What are you talking about?
Oh my god...
How is everything breaking apart like this?
I thought the zombies...
Sadious relatives.
So true.
Euphonium!
Uh...
LeTude!
Dude!
Psychotic!
End of pain!
Easy does it.
Don't bark at Dennis.
Kinky words!
Oh shit.
Karaoke singer!
I know how to type karaoke really fast because of streams!
Is it Kinky Wednesday you guys?
What day is it for you?
Wait, I can't remember.
Is it Thursday?
It's Kinky Wednesday!
It's Kinky Wednesday everybody.
Well not for me.
For you maybe.
I can finally drink some water and blink my eyes.
Oh my god, I've been like... I've been locked in for so long.
Okay, just shoot him!
Just shoot him if he's yours!
Happy Kinky Wednesday everybody.
Kinky Wednesday!
You're fucking disgusting, Nigel!
Oh my god, he can speak!
AMS agent, put your hands in the air!
All of them!
If you be so motherfucking kind!
How is he able to speak?
How is he sentient?
Nigel...
Nigel and Sebastian.
He's like smiling in the picture.
He looks so friendly.
Shoot that freaky little motherfucker!
Yeah, shoot him!
Yeah, punk!
This music is... I'm not feeling it.
Here he comes!
Oh god.
I'm not really feeling it, the music.
Is it gonna pick up?
Back up!
Yeah, back up, back up, back up!
Oh god, sausage!
I can't smell sausage!
Alligator man!
Oh, shoot.
Is that their names?
Now that can't be hygienic.
You're worried about hygiene at a time like this?
Oh my god.
Oh.
Flopsy Parker!
Uh oh.
Okay.
Huh?
What's happening?
What's going on?
The music is too happy.
It's so funny though.
Oh.
He's getting too close.
Yeah, back up!
Back up!
Identity theft.
It's not a joke.
Nice.
Dang it!
No!
I was so close!
Why?
Oh, shit.
Aloha?
Who names their clown name Aloha?
People, people, but...
This is some pee-pee music.
Oh, shit.
Sibbity toilet.
Oops.
That was close.
People, people, people, peep, peep, pop, peep.
Come on, come on.
Just a few more.
Just a few more maybe.
Or one more.
You want to be my little monorail kitten?
People, peep, peep, peep, peep, peep, peep, peep, peep, peep, peep, peep, peep.
Motherfucker.
That bastard had to be the sickest mutant yet.
It's still alive.
Oh, God.
Oh, shit.
Anyway, it started blasting.
So now we're stuck out here in the ass end of nowhere with no ride and motherfucking Papa Caesar on a train to fuck knows where by now.
Who was that guy?
And where the fuck have you gone?
Oh.
Don't make me go calling your stupid ass name.
Gee.
Oh, shit.
Agent G.
Wait, where did I go?
No fucking way.
You know, Washington, a man driving a car with his own choice of music is one of the finest experiences he can have in an automobile.
All right, Captain Green Pie.
You call this an automobile?
You guys see the name of the thing?
Music, man, motor.
Captain Green Pie?
Isolated from the outside world.
The music making you nod your head with every beat while the outside's just passing you by.
Okay.
So, what kind of carnival is this?
Don't ever ride with your feet up on the dashboard, you guys.
Oh, my God.
Stop the curve.
Before knowing he can trust that motherfucker.
What kind of carnival is this?
These things take time.
Here I am, teamed up with a partner I don't even fucking need, forced to sit in the motherfucking passenger seat, which I have not fucking done since I was a kid, while he goes all soft, talking about his life.
I'm gonna take his feelings for his motherfucking tune.
Kyle, you take that Super Chat back right now.
Shit.
Just play your fucking music.
You take that back!
You take that Super Chat back.
What the fuck!
I was listening to that.
You fucking think because you scored us this fucking popsicle ride you can play that shit?
Hey, hey, hey.
That there is country westerns finest.
Yeah, country and westerns.
You are one fuck of fuck!
You know that?
That's offensive shit!
What is this game?
This game is insane.
Conver-mother-effin-sation.
Now what are you gonna listen to, huh?
Can I drive?
Can I have a lollipop?
This game is so stupid.
Oh, we got a B again.
But my accuracy went up a little.
My Gorgasm also went up.
Oh, I almost got all the comics and the figurines.
Didn't see what Kyle said, but I second it.
Wait, what do you mean?
Oh, no!
Give me one second, you guys.
I gotta get tissue for my nose.
My nose is kinda runny today.
Give me a second.
Okay.
No!
Stop!
Fuck it up!
What is wrong with you guys?
Maybe it's the pollen.
No, I think it's my brain fluid leaking out my nose.
Thanks for the gifted ducky.
Thanks for the silver tattoo, guys!
Thank you!
Oh, wait.
Someone sent me one earlier and I was too busy playing the game.
I couldn't read it.
I'll have to go back and see what it was.
Okay.
Also, this hotel...
Um...
Left...
They had like chocolates and I grabbed some.
Should I have...
Wait, I shouldn't have the white chocolate.
I'll have the dark chocolate.
It has...
It has some stuff in it.
Like a zinc.
Kyle...
How dare you show your face around here after that.
Do they give you free bottled water?
Most hotels in Japan have the free water.
If they have water bottles.
It's not like America where the water bottles are like six bucks.
In Japan, they're usually complimentary because they're not monsters.
In America, get charged for opening the fridge.
I know, right?
Alright.
What is in this chocolate?
It's crunchy.
Whoa.
Meat is murder.
Mmm.
I don't know.
I don't know what it's crunching in here.
I have no idea.
Oh, it's little pieces of cocoa.
Cocoa.
Cacao.
Not the Minotaur.
The Mintotaur?
This game is nuts.
I'm having so much fun though.
I've only been playing for an hour and a half.
I think I could probably...
Is this all the...
Is this all the levels?
Hold on.
I'm going to make myself a little bit smaller.
Sorry for not doing this way sooner.
And let's move the notifications.
We'll move them like up here.
I'm going to make them a little bit smaller as well.
That should be a better viewing experience.
Sorry for doing this an hour and a half into the stream.
Wait.
Why is it like sized like that?
Hmm.
But then it's cut off.
Maybe I'll just leave it down here.
There was a game in the background.
Stop.
Mintotaur Viper size.
What is this?
I can tell somebody.
Listen to the podcast.
Thank you.
If you didn't listen to the podcast.
I was called a viper.
I don't know why.
Anyway.
Let's see.
So one, two, three, four, five more.
I do have to go out because I'm actually meeting a friend later.
I sent them money and they're going to give me some cash.
I have to meet up with them so that I can get some money so I can go out and do things.
No.
I don't think my wallets.
So like my wallet was stuck in the same place for like five days.
And only yesterday did it move out of the United States.
So even though my roommate sent it on the eighth.
So it's been it's been over a week.
I'm so sick of this.
Before you have this.
Well, when they sent it, they said that it that the person at the post office said it would take.
Oh, for those who don't know, I left my wallet at my maid cafe.
And a little ghosty decided that ghost that stays at the maid cafe with me.
Sent it.
And the person at the post office said.
Uh, I think like four to ten business days, which I was like, oh, four business days.
So I'm just suffering now.
What is this super chat?
Thank you, Mike.
Yeah, I don't know.
I feel like I can't.
It's so frustrating because I just haven't dim sum for Papa's.
The name of the song is so funny.
Ten business days would be like two full weeks.
It was actually that long.
I actually feel like crying right now.
Shit, the place is wired to blow.
We're not dead yet.
Detectives.
No, it's so frustrating.
Anyway, let's play game.
Creeping flesh.
Not the cow mooing.
The candy.
What are you doing out here?
What the fuck are you doing?
I thought I told you to leave town.
Was that not?
I miss my Jasper.
I left his voice box at the strip club.
No.
I just wanted to hear him say.
I love you, Candy.
One more time.
Candy, please.
Candy.
Couldn't you just buy the software and type what the fuck you wanted instead?
You know my spelling ain't so good.
Your speaking isn't so hot either, honey.
Damn.
Don't be so mean, Miss Gunn.
What?
I don't remember her first name.
I said nothing you.
Nothing you.
What the hell are you talking about now?
My mama always said if you can't say anything nice, say nothing.
So nothing you, Varla Gunn.
Come on.
Let's get you to the train station before one of those mutants nothings the shit out of you.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
They're so hot.
They're so hot!
Deadly retribution.
Nothing you, Minto.
Nothing you!
That sound.
Who was it?
Was it Papa?
Does that come with salad?
Every time I hear the Papa Caesar, I think of the...
No, it comes with a serving of extreme prejudice and a side order of fuck you.
The memes from, like, Stranger Things.
I don't like foreign food.
Not since that time Papa Caesar force-fed Jasper Chinese food.
Poor Jasper.
He was shitting all night long.
What?
He knew Jasper's food had to be licky-fried.
We should licky-fry him.
What's a licky-fried?
It's fucking liquified.
Oh.
And you do understand, I'm going to eat, Papa Caesar.
Well, I was wondering.
You know, he did once ask me to...
Sugar, we don't have time for this.
He's getting away.
Licky-fried.
Okay, let's go.
Good girl.
Oh my god, her boobs.
Oh my god, good girl.
Yes?
Will there be cake?
Shut the fuck up.
This, too, is Yuri.
Two daughters headed for the slaughter in an abattoir of terror on a night...
What did he ask her to do?
...prepared to be butchered in...
Creeping flesh.
Vegetarians need not apply.
Minto is candy.
What are you talking about?
What do you mean?
Here we go, everybody.
I'm tabbing, I'm tabbing, I'm tabbing, I'm tab-tab.
Where are we going?
Oh, nice, I got it.
Oh...
Oh my god, oh...
This is already a disaster.
Not just a shopping cart disaster, this is a Minto brain disaster.
French, kiss.
I don't even know you.
Oh, worms make great pets.
Someone had a message.
And I approved.
They were like, I must get this message out through this game.
I've talked so much, I've lost my concentration for...
Oh.
For typing.
Barla?
Can I ask you something?
What now?
Don't you think it's odd how these doors seem to open and close automatically?
Shut up.
Is it...
She's thinking she's...
The candy is coming.
She's cooking!
Thanks for the super chat, by the way!
Oh, I got something.
Nice.
Open it up, love.
She's gaining sense.
Oh my god.
Oh, come on!
Run!
Easy for you to say.
Run, run, run!
Can you not run, candy?
You're not gonna survive, girly.
Candy, please!
You have to live!
Oh, what?
Oh my god.
Pickled onions!
Extra life!
Sultry vixen!
Oh my god.
I'm scared.
I'm getting chills.
We're in a freezer.
Why are they all shaking, though?
What are these 3D models on?
Oh my god!
Oh!
It's a literal attack on Titan!
Oh my god.
Uh...
What does the fox say?
Useless trombonist!
Oh, gosh.
I need health.
I'm not doing so hot, you guys.
I don't know what the sauce is.
Extra life.
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
Beep, boop, beep, bop, beep, boop, beep.
Oh!
I don't...
Oh, Liz lost.
I don't know how...
Too many E's!
Oh!
Too many!
Got attack on Titan at will.
We're not getting out this way.
Why are these bodies... avert your eyes!
Why?
Why are these guys in the freezer, by the way?
Why are there human bodies?
You is breathing.
Oh, no!
My combo!
Oh, trepidation.
I'm closing in.
Oh, no!
They chilling?
We're a little hot.
We're pushing through.
Whoa!
It's pretty alive!
Uh...
Giant!
Pretty freaky in here.
Karma!
Malph?
Okay...
Very not alive.
Yeah.
Your wish is my command.
Oh!
The T!
Control!
Asshole!
Why do you have to come out the door like that?
I keep forgetting to do backspace, but...
It is what it is.
Very nice that they each take their turn.
I like that too.
Oh my god, please!
Oh my god!
Oh, it's him!
Oh shoot, this guy's gonna kill me for real.
Holy cow!
Fruit salad!
Yummy, yummy!
Go
to the doctor if you have a chesty cough!
Fruit salad!
Yummy, yummy!
Yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy!
Fruit salad!
I don't wanna die!
How are you still...
Om nom nom!
How are you still alive though?
How are you still alive in here?
Girl, get out, please!
She's walking towards the zombies!
Oh!
Oh my god!
These are hard!
Oh,
he got some health though.
Nice, nice, nice.
Matorakann!
I always knew you were a zombie...
HG!
Oh my god!
I thought I finished it!
F!
I thought I finished it.
No, it's my fault.
F!
What the?
What the hell was that?
It's gone.
It's just girl rot.
Bingo!
Fat wings!
One, two, three!
Why did I do an S there?
I'm so silly.
My accuracy... my score is not gonna be very good this time, you guys.
I'm just gonna say.
Play, grit, bow!
One, two, three, shizumiya!
Made it over!
Oh, I tried to violence instead of violet.
Sometimes my brain just...
What the nothing is that?
I don't think I wanna find out.
What is... what is happening?
Oh god!
Oh, just sleeping?
Pasta face!
A barbarian princess!
Nice.
Nice, nice.
Nipple madness!
I love the nipple madness.
I don't think humor has a U in it, does it?
The music is spooky now.
Spooky now.
Her haircut.
British humor does.
This is...
Gatekeeper.
This is no British game.
Why are you down here again?
Oh my god.
Oh!
Dang it!
I was so close!
No!
It's the P. It was hard to type with my pinky.
Where are we going?
We're getting birthed, you guys.
Oh my!
What's that?
Statch!
Teeny hands.
I know!
It's hard!
That's why I had to stop playing the guitar.
It was too hard on my hands.
Oh
my god.
I can't even let her finish her line.
Meet Katie.
Now I've seen it all.
Right in the chops!
Shoot her udder!
Her other what?
Oh my god.
Her tits!
Her tits what?
Just shoot!
Shoot her!
Kangaroo surprise!
Oh, no.
I missed it.
My.
My eyes are up here, baby!
Oh my goodness.
I love...
I love monster...
Girls.
Don't call me Daisy.
I wonder if the capitalization really...
If it adds, you know...
If it adds more points.
Sometimes I do it, sometimes I don't.
Oh.
I regret nothing!
Okay.
I love monster girls, but this is a little much.
Ah, this is some prime rib, baby!
Oh shit.
Tommy!
That hurts, you bitch!
Oh my god.
Real me!
That was hard.
That was really hard.
Holy cow.
That was hard.
Super doggy bomb.
Uh?
Utterly delightful.
I am reminded of a certain book you read and told about Mato on the podcast.
Yes.
Oh!
Oh my god.
Oh,
movie!
Nothing!
Candy!
Is Candy gonna die?
Put it back on.
Stick it back on, stick it back on, stick it back on.
Candy!
I can't believe she became a pauper on the line.
It's too late.
Feels so weak.
You be strong, Angel.
Be strong for Jasper.
No, Candy!
I can see him, Varla.
I can see him.
No, she's not gonna die!
Coming down for me.
It's quite slow.
But they have to be.
Something about health and safety.
Oh, it's stuck.
No, it's moving again.
Don't you dare die on me.
You hear me, Candy?
Candy's gonna live, I know it.
Leave me, Varla.
Go.
Find Caesar and kill him.
I can't leave you here.
I won't leave you here.
She needs the voice box so she can hear Jasper one more time.
Jasper is here.
You came for me, Jasper.
That was a good bit.
I love you, Candy.
We can be together again.
And Papa Caesar will never split us up.
Oh my god, no.
Just hold on.
She's not gonna die.
Oh, Jasper.
Will I have my arm in heaven?
Will I still be able to do that thing you like me to do?
Huh?
She talks a lot.
Sweet dreams, baby doll.
She's dead!
This time, Papa Caesar, it's really fucking personal.
Was it because I got below a C?
There she goes.
Was it because...
No!
I didn't get below a C, though.
Oh, I almost would have had everything here.
Why is she keeping the arm?
Wouldn't you?
Wouldn't you keep the arm?
Hold on.
I'm gonna get some more water.
Then we'll go to the next one.
I got these...
I got these Hi-Chews.
You guys know Hi-Chews?
They're typically really...
They're kind of hard, right?
But these ones are like mochi.
Kind of.
They're still a little hard.
But they're softer.
But they're very, like...
gummy?
I love it.
Actually, what's the inside?
Is the song's a bop?
I can't hear it.
I don't know why.
I don't know.
Ooh, I like it.
Wait, I wanna go back real quick.
I wanted to see all the stuff that we've gotten so far.
Oh, Candy, I'm sorry.
It says we've been unlocking like 3D models and stuff, but I don't know where to see them.
Seductive she-devil.
AI, for some reason, Matara's arm fell off.
Is it under memorabilia, maybe?
Oh!
Oh, here we go!
Why is she laughing?
But I've unlocked!
Oh, here we go.
Oh, I don't wanna read it out of order.
Let's see.
We've got some 3D models...
Characters...
Oh!
Wow!
Moving, moving!
She's moving.
Oh!
Flesher.
Oh wait, I can turn him around!
The way he moves is so stupid.
His bootleg attack on Titan.
Wait, let's go back to this lady.
Come here.
Think of the ads you can put on the VOD.
Who cares about monetization when you can see it all!
The monetization is in my eyes, baby!
Candy!
I just noticed this.
Oh, I noticed it earlier.
The thing on her leg, but...
I wonder what it's for.
But there's even 3D models of weapons?
That's so awesome.
Oh, yeah!
Look at that!
Something, something engravings.
No tactical advantage.
Hahaha!
Oh!
No way!
It's our ice cream!
Oh no, it's the ice cream truck.
Stop, look at this.
Wait, this is...
Oh my god.
It just gets...
Oh my god!
It gets worse and worse the more I look at it!
I'm trying to read what the ice creams are.
The ice...
The cream pie deluxe.
Chocolate...
Bubbly?
Jubbly.
Filthy snowball?
I can't read this one.
The chocolate...
I can't zoom in.
I don't think it'll let me.
The back of this thing is insane.
The chocolate...
I can't read it.
Look...
Control...
Shift...
No, it won't let me zoom in at all.
This is...
Holy moly!
Okay.
Let's keep playing the game.
That was fun though.
The scream train!
Okay.
They weren't caught...
They weren't kidding when they said the scream train.
It keeps getting worse.
It really does!
Oh no!
We're back at the...
YouTube!
Don't look!
Don't look at it.
Oh!
Oh, the difficulty changed?
Uh oh.
Wait, can I leave?
Hold on.
I'm gonna leave.
We'll rewatch it.
I don't wanna play on the easiest difficulty.
That's too lame.
Quit.
Yeah.
I didn't even realize.
Why did it put me on the easiest difficulty?
I didn't even do that.
Easy mode!
Kimoi!
I'm a G!
Oh my god, is he gonna say what the G stands for?
Nobody motherfucking move!
Paula put the gun down.
We got him.
She got it first.
It's news you lose.
My brother died trying to take down this sick fuck.
I need this.
I gotta do this for Jasper.
Caesar's mine, Paula!
Papa Caesar, you're under AMS arrest.
Take him out.
Take him down.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can...
Fuck that shit!
This bastard can't live.
Wait, don't turn your gun on them.
He's gonna leave.
Let me contact my agency and we'll take him into custody.
To hell with that.
Fucking A, sister.
Why are you turning your gun on them?
Caesar ain't leaving this platform with his eyes still open, G.
Have you both lost it?
Ahem.
I'm afraid I'm going to have to disappoint all of you.
This isn't the time to fight!
You got the most reason to despise me or anybody here.
I'm a business expert.
Urgent business.
What's the backstory?
What's the whole story?
You piece of shit!
I'm sorry.
Do continue.
See you in...
hell...
Washington.
Scream train.
200 tons of unstoppable terror burning through the night.
Yo mama, by the sound of it...
Enough with the kissing competition.
We're gonna take down...
Oh my god!
I should have...
Should have been faster there.
What's her name?
Vanessa?
Miss Gun?
Okay, here we go.
Happy birthday!
Crappy birthday.
Like, totally.
To you.
Crappy birthday.
What the hell is that?
Oh my god, oh my god.
Reluctant...
Oh gosh.
Ouch.
Oh my god!
Composing!
Punch it.
Swing!
A biggie!
Take him out.
Grab the knife.
Ah!
This motherfucker is from the county jam.
And that can't be good.
Uh oh.
Are they gonna be hyper...
intelligent...
donkeys?
Better type fast C!
Oh gosh.
Upright man.
Standing man emoji.
Oh my god.
What the?
This does not look good.
Oh my god.
No, not the animals.
No, the cows!
Oh my god.
I was looking at my...
Sorry, I was looking at my...
something on my...
mixer.
Oh shoot,
I got the wrong one.
This is my wedding suit.
Phantom!
That's me!
It's like sleeping.
Being dead?
Being a zombie?
I did it!
You guys, I did it!
I did the backspace.
Oh!
Okay.
Oh, what a plan.
Pick your wish.
How did they come up with these, I wonder?
So funny.
Nice dodge.
Trick or treat!
Can't wait for Halloween, you guys.
I'm so excited.
Jump!
Oh god.
Thoroughly thoughtful.
Thank god.
Oh god.
Oh, thank god I had to slow down on those.
I would not have made it.
J!
You!
American Dream!
Got him.
Nice.
Can't wait for Halloween!
We got something.
What is going on?
What is that?
Did you miss me?
Hahaha.
Now this is my kind of place.
Traveling in style, baby.
Wow.
Wow!
This is like the very naughty boy!
This is like the, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Yeah, aggressive!
This is the first class!
First class babies!
Oh, sorry.
Shit, man!
Eww!
Where were the ladies on the wall?
Naked ladies!
Winter is coming!
Winter
is coming!
Dry your eyes.
Woah.
Oh my goodness.
You're so violent, you guys.
Did I wake you?
Haha.
These are, these props, or prompts are so funny.
I like the ones that like kind of make the zombies seem like they're aware.
Oh.
Like the one, the one that was just like the zombie unification, whatever.
Ah!
Thief jerky!
Haha.
Oh, these seats are nice.
I've always wanted to go on a train ride like this.
Oh my god, oh my god.
Why?
Thank you for the 20 gifted!
I can't spell.
I don't know all these...
I don't know these words.
With zombies?
Maybe.
I wanna go on like a murder oriented...
Express.
I wouldn't have no ticket.
Yeah!
No, no, no, no, no!
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Taco!
Some old guy ran through here and these monsters didn't even touch him.
Oh.
Papa.
Papa, I want to play video games.
Haha.
Hahaha.
What does that mean?
Taco.
Oh my gosh, and then wandering taco!
It was fate!
Wah.
What a kill-thrill.
Nice.
There we go, baby.
Holy moly.
Oh.
Oh shit.
I need a bigger boat!
The music's all freaky now.
Oh, never mind.
Boom, bang, eat!
Boom, bang,
eat!
Boom, bang, eat!
I hate these ones.
Nice.
What a fucking waste!
You are...
Stop insulting me!
This game is so mean.
Hahaha.
Nice.
Okay.
We're slow motion.
That's okay.
Get
this guy some soup, man.
This game need a hug.
Yeah, they insulted me and then...
This isn't a costume, this is my work uniform!
I think we've got all the authority we need right here.
Right here.
My right hand and my left hand.
Get your claws out of my motherfucking face!
Yeah!
Oh my god.
What are you doing on this train?
Ding-dong!
Counter attack.
Mint is cute.
Oh!
This looks like a control panel.
Don't touch that.
We've got enough problem without these guys getting out.
What are they doing in here?
Limpa is lettuce.
Oh!
I'm gonna start it.
Limpa is lettuce.
Oh shit.
My combo.
Two up, two down.
Okay.
Oh my god.
Okay, I'm starting to...
Strike your out!
Baby!
Oh no, they're starting to get out!
They're starting to get loose!
Oh...
Why are you so mean?
No...
Holy shit!
Christmas came early!
Let's go.
Oh!
That's me.
I'm a niche appeal.
Motherfuck!
Oi!
That was close.
Up we go!
What's been going on here?
Hmm...
Ugh!
Extreme violence.
What was that?
Word list is brutal, I know.
This is your driver.
Papa!
I'm pleased to announce, we're running ahead of schedule.
And we'll be reaching our final destination far, far sooner than expected.
Uh oh.
Well...
Choo-choo, everybody!
Perfect time to use my choo-choo emote.
You ain't protecting your papa this time, you bug motherfucker!
I'm a Tarakhan!
Kids today!
Kids tomorrow!
Oh my god.
I wonder what the...
What the secret's gonna be for like, you know...
Wheeee!
April Fools!
Choo-choo!
Oh gosh!
Don't you know it's rude to spit?
Oh my god!
Oh no no no no!
Oh no no no!
We're introducing Numbers!
Oh.
Numbers hate.
Yeah.
Here she comes!
Centrical!
Here
we go, Numbers!
Oh cute!
Nice!
Oh!
Oh, never mind, never mind.
I thought that was it.
What the...
I got
both eyes!
Is that it?
I think we ran it over, right?
It just fell off the...
Oh, we're on the...
That shit's ick!
Guys, we're on the highway to hell right now.
Are you kidding me?
Alright, Rambo.
Don't get all fucking macho.
I hate bugs.
And that was their fucking bug king.
And speaking of bugs...
Speaking of bugs?
You fucking in there?
Yoo-hoo!
Yoo -hoo!
Still a C?
Come on!
Come on, game!
I got a C after...
I don't think I did that poorly, right?
I guess I got no Gorgasm, so...
No!
I got a C.
It was too slow.
It wasn't slow, it was...
Accuracy, right?
Nearly 97% though.
Yeah.
Am I proving my O-L-ness to you guys?
Daddy, can I be a mutant?
One day, son.
But for now, you're too young.
But daddy!
No means no.
Stop sniveling, you little shit.
By the way, I'm not your daddy.
Huh?
I just kinda fuck your mom.
Talking of fucking people, I have a story for you.
What is this song?
Well, I took myself to Bayou I could not believe my eyes The folks had been mutated Not quite dead, but not alive Wasn't really looking for love But they say that's when it strikes She had that look of being dug up But that's the type I like Yeah, free world,
man One man's meat Yadda yadda yadda Yadda yadda yadda Well, she came towards me Said no words, just kinda snarlin' As she tried to eat my brains out I just had to kiss you, darlin' Think I kinda rushed it, though Cause as her lips had touched my mouth Her cums broke free from her face Thought it rude to spit them out You know those travel programs That's on the television Where they eat all that weird shit Yeah,
she tasted like chicken Didn't wanna make a scene As her mouth was in mine So I chewed around Swallowed it down, went in for a second time No, no, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done It's so gross, I'm sorry Ew, I'm getting a visual I think I'm good No, please Oh my god They're in the bayou This is real Resident Evil now Hey Isaac,
you finally found the G-spot, huh?
Sorry to ruin the moment Isaac's back Here I am Good job, Isaac You saw nothing, you hear?
Isaac, baby My lips are sealed Hey Wake up, sleeping beauty Yeah, come on, G Stop calling me Gwendolyn Hi there What happened?
You were having a fucking wet dream Where's Caesar?
He was on the train, right?
He was up front driving Let's take a look Do people talk like this normally?
Be gentle, Isaac You know that's how he likes people Yes Please continue, my dear Oh my god, Papa Usually I have to dial premium rate for this kind of entertainment Don't mind now, motherfucker Careful, Washington Isaac It's not a dick he's pressing into my back I hope not Apparently young Jasper wasn't the only genius in the family You bastard You truly are your father's son,
Isaac Like him before you You have failed to apprehend me And while I may not have the satisfaction of ending your life I will take some small comfort in knowing you have been denied your revenge once again Then it's true?
You did kill my old man?
No way!
Sorry, I was messaging the person that's giving me money My friend I have business to attend to at the county prison You dickheads better come rescue me, okay?
We'll find you, Varna You die tonight, Caesar Goodbye, Isaac Bye-bye Bye-bye Washington, I...
I don't know what to say, man Then don't say anything, dipshit!
You heard where he's taking Varna The quickest way to the prison from here is through that Lead the way, detective Yeah, let's go, I guess Oh my god
Oh, the mixtape The mixtape!
Why didn't he just steal the bike?
Because wouldn't you want a pretty lady to take you?
In this state, you do know what part of the country you're in, right?
I have no idea where I'm at, actually Oh Talk to the hand!
Oh
Oh my god It's already so fast Tell your friend thank you Well, I mean...
I sent them the money, alright?
They're just withdrawing it for me Super... oh Yeah, that was close That was close Why is this guy still here?
Why is this guy still here?
Oh shit
Why are you still there?
Yeah!
This guy is still... this guy is not gonna make it
But I got hit in the process!
Uh, oh!
Green main I took a hit for him I took a hit for him Excellent Thanks!
Jimmy!
There
we go Sheesh!
Tap, tap, tap, tap Oh Cue!
Curse of my nerve!
That guy...
They're fighting back there, the girls are fighting Balls for monkey Monkeys!
You can type it!
Thanks!
Uh...
Stop shooting!
He's like, I'm on your side!
Words will...
We had...
I'm good with words and words will never hurt me I'm good with words and words will never hurt me
Stop fighting!
Uh...
Oh, what does the box say?
Don't touch me, I'm dreaming!
That's not what the box says!
Another day, another brain Oh god
If there's one thing I hate more than mutants It's redneck mutants Oh my god F!
Wait, hold on Play better The game is insulting me Ghost prince?
What's that?
I'm not a princess T!
L!
O!
Dang it!
Oh my god, I'm not doing so hot, you guys Shoot the weak spot!
Shoot the weak spot!
Oh my god They're trying to get me really bad Uh oh For the wings of a dove For the wings of a dove Oh!
Oh my god!
Oh no!
No!
I'm not doing so hot, you guys Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god Oh my god These are hard
I like your shoes Kick in the balls!
These words are so...
Flamboyance of flamingos!
These words are so hard to type Holy cow!
Burn her!
Oh, we got her Oh my god It's not just typing It's also...
Spelling!
Nice save,
thanks!
Thanks!
Hats for all!
Holy cow, my...
Oh gosh, I don't...
Oh god What's up with this?
I don't know how to spell schizophrenia!
Oh my god
Freaking freaks freaking I'm
a...
I'm a...
I might
be...
My favorite one so far Where did these motherfucking mutants come from?
Easy does it...
Yeah, that's what I'm wondering There's rats...
Uh...
Grains for dinner!
Yeah, I'm a...
A thirsty...
Ugh Killed a hundred fat mutants Wow
Extreme violence I'm hearing all level-headed Are you afraid?
I'm getting tired, actually I think that's what's slowing me down the most Is I'm starting to...
My eyes are starting to hurt From, uh...
Having to keep my eyes so, like, focused Too much brawling Too much brawling Too much brawling Right now...
Oof And I'm, like, kind of hunched over, so, you know Oh Can we focus here?
Boy, these threads don't come cheap Yo, yo, yo Oh
Getting her posture
Ladyboy It's like a mama's boy Itchy!
Cruel!
By the way, G...
I mean it to ask...
Why are we immune to this mutant shit?
We're not.
Say what?
I ain't turning into no mutant The compound's got a short lifetime Only those who came in contact with it hours ago are affected Got it!
I was at my mom's I mean, a strip club At my apartment, not at my mom's Don't worry, detective.
Your secret is safe Oh my god, see...
What?
Shrimpy ghost...
The desk is a little low But that's okay I have a desk Honestly, I'm, like...
Really grateful Wait, hold on Why does this stew have a hat?
Keep running!
Oh, oh
My original room didn't have a desk My original room didn't have a desk My original room didn't have a desk Um, but because I'm here, you know...
Um, but because I'm here, you know...
Man, that is some repugnant shit, fam Man, that is some repugnant shit, fam See, you didn't get a sample of that bio for forensics Oh my god, no way Ew, come here, stinky Ew, come here, stinky This is a whole camp This is so nasty I see you Harpy!
I see you Sometimes I add extra letters that I don't mean to Come here, you!
But yeah, my original room only had a table But yeah, my original room only had a table And then, um...
Uh...
But, uh, Sakana Upgraded my room for me so I could have a desk Shit, this is like that film with all them birds Which film with all the birds?
You know!
The bird film!
Fuck!
So...
Happy about that
Like...
I'm just like...
I'm just like, you know, a guest in their...
In their concert But they're treating me well Which I'm like, wow I'm not used to this But it's always...
It's kinda, you know, like...
You know, uh...
Oh my god!
Like,
you know...
I guess it's, uh...
I guess it's just, uh...
Where I used to work Because, you know...
When I hung out with, like...
When I hung out with anyone that's...
Uh...
They are very nice I always think...
Like, you know...
When I hung out with Gun Run 2 Um...
I think about, like, at my old company When we were doing recording one time Um...
We had been in the studio for a long time We had been in the studio for a long time And we were really hungry They were like, can you please get us some food?
They were like, okay...
Give us your credit card Hahaha Hahaha Hahaha
Oh god, hocus pocus
Put your motherfucking hands away from my brain AAAAAAH Oh my god, no, no Not that guy
Engle fibers Cha-cha-cha-cha I'm not gonna make it, you guys, oh god Hahaha Oh god I'm
paying attention, I promise
Leave me alone!
Hahaha Get the health, grab the health Oh no, no, no, no
Adrenaline Okay There we go, nice, nice, nice I'm locked in, don't worry Oh, Ocelot!
We caught that motherfucker on the can I didn't realize that was a component of mutant behavior They had to go to the bathroom?
You're mentioning a mutant Taking a dump in your report Hahaha
Wow Madness unleashed by human error From the murky depths of mystery It has come to maul It has come to murder It has come to feed To feed It came from The Fetid Water The Fetid Water The Fetid Water Can you give us a fucking moment?
Hahaha I know you!
Yeah Are we gonna do like a bro handshake?
My paper beats your rock I'll fuck it!
You have the right to remain fucking silent You have the right to an attorney This guy is really just in there waiting for him Anything you say can and fucking will Eww Eww You just made my fucking day Take him out!
My paper beats your rock Hahaha Hahaha Lobber Are we aiming for his boobs?
Or is that the no zone?
Don't touch the boobs Can't tell
This game is so crazy Okay Come on buddy!
Eww Eww what the hell was that?
Pretty teethy Oh dang it I missed it That was too slow
My suit Yes that's interesting First world Dang it I always miss the last one I always miss that one We got him I think Oh yeah nice dodge Nice Nice.
That gave me a little bit of a... what's the word?
Motion sickness.
Trust to kill!
There was no way I was gonna get that one.
There was no...
oh!
Got him.
Easy peasy.
You guys, am I good at typing?
What do you think?
Am I good at typing?
Bad breath.
Yeah.
There's no way I'm gonna get this one.
I give up.
I'm pretty good.
You're pretty good.
Are you winning, Mint?
Yeah, actually.
See, I was an OL.
I was an OL, you guys!
This was my... and I did data entry.
That's how... but I was always good at typing, ever since I was a kid.
You know?
You know, the first time... like...
When they introduced the...
typing classes.
I was all in on that.
I did typing classes all the time.
But I never...
did anything like this.
Ah, so close.
I was so close!
Cheat rate for this one.
I sucked at typing classes.
I loved it, though.
I was obsessed.
It was my favorite class ever.
Hahaha!
Ewww!
Beow!
Beow mention.
Hahaha!
Certified nerd.
That one was close, actually.
Hahaha!
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da!
Don't call me!
Dang it!
Hahaha!
Just a few more!
Maybe one more.
After this, right?
Here we...
Excuse me!
Maybe right here?
Oh.
One more?
Right...
What in the scum?
Hahaha!
Woo-woo-woo!
Thanks for the super time!
So nice meeting you at Vexpo.
Thank you!
Oh, this is my Oshii shirt!
Hahaha!
You're all good!
I think I spilled the most spaghetti.
Don't worry.
I'd rather not!
Thanks for the five gifted.
Thank you!
Oh my god.
All that I stretch.
Ugh!
That was not a shortcut.
I mean, what were you...
Oh, quit whining, you pussy!
I got us here, didn't I?
Oh.
Fuck!
You about to get all country and western on me again?
Isn't it just country western?
Is it country and western?
I just want you to know, if it comes down to it, I won't stand in the way of you getting even with Caesar.
I'd like to see you fucking try.
I'm serious.
I like his glasses.
I appreciate the fucking sentiment.
But it's not needed.
I do what I gotta do.
I gotta get justice for my old man.
And as I see it, you're with me a fucking percent.
Yeah.
And I appreciate that too.
Aww.
But we've been through shit.
You don't need to go articulating every fucking thing.
Country and western.
I know you got my back.
That's enough.
You dig me?
Aww.
I love you too, man.
Right!
That's fucking it!
He pulled a gun on him for them.
Fucking leave the way.
Wait, that was a car.
There's still people.
A B.
I got a B this time, you guys.
I keep getting all the civilians and the comics and the figurines and everything, so we're doing well.
I even Gorgasmed for 110 seconds!
Hold on, I need more water.
I'm so sorry.
My throat is starting to get a little icky.
Give me a second.
I have some cough drops too.
But with all this water I'm drinking, I'm gonna have to go to the bathroom soon.
Good place to stop if you need a break?
No, we're almost.
How much do we have more?
Three levels?
Oh!
Two levels left!
Beauty was her crime.
Her sentence?
Worse than death.
Wow, it's already been almost three hours.
Ladies and gentlemen, the infinite tact of Isaac Washington.
I'm making... I'm eating my cough drops.
I'll be working crew at Mainstage on Saturday.
So I'll be letting people into your life, among others!
Also, any quitter on Friday.
So it's at the same time as another live.
Oh no!
But thank you!
Thanks for working our show!
Haha!
Get funky!
Yeah, yeah!
Dude, thank you so much for the 50 gifts!
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you!
Laying down the law!
Yeah!
I do have to go meet up with my friends soon though.
So I gotta finish the game.
I'm so invest...
And now.
What happened here?
I'm so invested.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir?
You two gentlemen smell like shit.
What the?
I'm gonna do my very best not to base our relationship on this first impression, but first impressions count for a lot.
Why are you so rude?
So if I meet a couple of men who not only neglect the common decency to introduce them themselves, but simply walk up to me smelling as shit, well, it's gonna take an effort for me to get to know them.
You look like shit, you know, so my first impression's not very good of you.
I'm Agent G, AMS.
You're Warden Darling, right?
That's entirely accurate, Detective Washington.
You see, I'm not the only individual whose reputation precedes them.
Now if you'll excuse me, I need to piss.
My dick's on fire.
I've been on the road for at least three quarters of an hour with a bladder full of steaming hot piss.
Stop, you're gonna turn on my cat!
With every turn of the road in a way that a bladder full of steaming piss tends to... Stop!
Do excuse me.
Do you have any idea what happened here, sir?
Ah, shit!
There you go, distracting me.
Now I got it all down my left leg.
I'm gonna look like I pissed myself.
Imagine if I had to meet anybody besides yourselves today.
They'd be inclined to think I was the sort of man who pisses himself.
Now that'd be a poor first impression.
Indeed.
We ain't got time for this shit.
With all due respect, what the fuck's happened here?
He reminds me too much of these videos.
Mutants, you say?
Can you fancy I have any idea what you're talking about?
Ew, oh my god, he's not gonna wash his hands.
I got a call in the middle of the night.
I got told there was trouble at my prison.
I came down.
And here I am.
That's the math of the situation right there.
He even sounds like those videos of the dogs with the really long face and he's just like, riding a motorcycle?
How the fuck do you know that?
Well, there's a motorcycle dumped right over there.
How did you miss that?
It's like you, gentlemen, have your own cares to deal with.
I'll be hanging inside to see what's what.
If I see your friends, I'll be sure to let...
They're not our fucking friends.
At least, look, if you see them, don't let them go.
Don't let them go.
I'll be sure to do that, detective.
This guy is...
Do not shake his hand.
I'm so sorry.
Call me Clement.
Ew.
You coming, motherfucker?
Do not sh... Oh my god.
Don't shake his hand.
He didn't wash his hands.
Nice voice.
Why would you do that?
Clement.
Wait, someone mentioned Clement earlier, did they not?
Maybe we should wait for backup.
Or maybe you should grow some balls.
Ooh, I love Isaac.
He's always got a...
Oh my god.
a...
a clapback.
Snitch!
Ponzi scheme!
He set me up!
Guys,
I gained that right there.
Guys, I gained that right there.
Holy cow!
That was crazy.
Well...
Earth
coin!
Thank you.
Oh, I keep forgetting the question...
Tab, I keep forgetting.
Well...
Wow.
Nice...
Waiting for him, guys.
Tabbing it up.
Oi!
Suppers.
Rainbows.
Sunshine!
Everything is sunshine and rainbows, you guys!
Don't worry about it!
What are we gonna kill him with?
Everything is slippers, sunshine, and rainbows.
Actually,
I don't like when they talk over my shooting because...
No!
Just us!
Because I like... I don't feel like I'm... What's the word?
Hitting.
If I don't hear it, you know what I mean?
Kills your flow?
Yeah, pretty much.
Nice suit!
KWI!
Is the how in the...
My combo.
No, I saw the slo-mo!
That's me.
Far too much distress is literally me right now.
Get me out of here!
How many of these mutants are there?
The slo-mo...
Switzerland!
I love... I love how they line up.
They are very polite.
Is he in jail for forgetting his tickets to the opera?
How could they?
Cake.
Fabric.
This guy is all into sewing.
Kill him with the broom!
Nice.
Okay.
Onward.
That's me!
Yes!
What the?
Where did you come from?
Grandma!
Nice.
Shit!
That G stands for genocide, motherfucker!
Girl, are you good?
Oh my god, girl.
Girl!
Girl, are you good?
You're looking good.
Where are you looking?
You know how it is.
Oh my god.
Oh god.
Tell Grandma I love her.
I thought I was on the wrong one for a second.
So I exited out of the wrong thing.
Grandma,
I love her.
Shouldn't it be Grandma?
Grandma, police are real.
Thank the Bismarck.
Oh my god, that one was tough for me.
Okay, nerd!
Oh, I thought it said hater.
Be a voyeur.
Not an angry pig.
Could have fooled me.
Looking around.
Oh, plasma lingerie!
What did that say?
Angry Buddha.
Nerd hater.
I thought that's what it said.
I was gonna be like, no, man.
Why were there three things?
There was just one guy.
Plasma lingerie?
Should
be, uh, in the same, you know, area, right?
Uh, maybe I will, but...
You
gonna tell me what the G stands for yet?
Not yet.
What the viola?
And Papa fucking Caesar?
Papa effing Caesar.
No shit!
That's me, actually, right now.
So slowly.
I gotta get some food.
Me and mine.
Oh la la, he's coming on to me.
What the?
He's coming on to me.
Chinese food?
I don't know what I'll get for food.
I have no idea, to be honest.
What about that guy over there?
I guess he's not bothering anybody.
We leave the guys who don't bother us alone, right?
Ignore this notice.
Nice.
Hello?
Game?
Lost in Space.
I love that movie.
Chewie finger.
Nice.
And you went through behind me.
Why did you come out of there?
You should have just stayed in there.
You were safe, civilian.
Did you see a freak-ass pimp with a hot bitch at gunpoint?
Sure!
They came through here just now.
Some weird shit going down tonight, man.
Huh?
What?
Big wet kiss.
Nice.
Tie to the chair.
Mashed potato.
Why are you in jail?
Oh my god, what if it actually dots my password?
That'd be crazy.
Oh, dang it.
F.
I never have spaghetti shame.
The judge was wrong!
Check his vibe.
What's in there?
Larceny!
What's larceny?
When your friends...
Beer.
Oh, I thought it said bread.
Uh, fingers... sent to jail because of the crime of... mashed potatoes.
Oh, stealing.
Okay, that's what I thought.
Nope.
I knew... I knew it was gonna be like that where one guy would be faster.
What the hell is a... What is this word?
The old switcheroo.
I live for the applause, applause, applause.
I did the switcheroo.
Exactly!
Uh, uh...
Oh, that was close.
I got the slow-mo!
We got them!
Skateboarding in public!
I don't think you should go to jail for that!
Oh, they're coming!
Where'd they go?
They went that way, didn't they?
Uh...
Skateboarding is not a crime!
Oh my god.
Score one for the motherfucking cavalry!
Now let's move!
Let's go!
Oh my god, they took them all out!
Oh, not all of them.
Oh...
That's not even a good wig!
Legis...
I don't know how to spell privileges.
Pequod.
That man was very old!
Fate worse than death!
It wasn't my wig, it's your wig.
Man, these motherfuckers need to chill the fuck out!
So true.
Whatever you do...
First offense!
I don't know how to spell offense either.
I don't know how to... uh...
Cheat!
Okay...
Oh!
Nice!
Over-egging the pudding!
No, how could you?
Oh god, they're coming.
Why is it spelling in British?
Why?
Oh, I'm not British!
The pudding...
My eyes are getting so dry.
Oh my god.
Boys, boys...
Oh my god!
Don't be so melodramatic.
Put those guns away.
Take a seat.
Enjoy the show.
What's happening?
Sir, what's going on here?
Yeah, what's going on?
You're behind...
That's right.
Yeah, I have eye drops.
I'll do it after this.
I'm behind the whole thing.
Piss man!
Me, I'm responsible for...
Don't interrupt me, detective.
I have quite a lot to get through.
Who would have thought that this freak was behind it all?
You're responsible for all of this?
For all those dead freaks?
Well, I didn't kill your dad, Washington.
Perhaps my esteemed colleague here has something to comment on that one.
He's got the ball gag and everything.
Clement!
What the fuck are you doing?
This wasn't part of our deal.
I got the compound refined for you.
I...
Shut the fuck up.
In fact, shut up permanently.
The... the looking at the camera...
Oh, shit!
You were to do that, right?
To get revenge?
The looking at the camera and shrugging his little face?
Ouch.
Fuck.
No, I think he's a goner.
Oh my god, that was so fast.
That was super fast.
Look, what do you want with Barla?
She's not part of this.
Let her go.
You're actually quite wrong, whoever the fuck you are.
I'm Agent G!
What does that stand for?
I'm afraid that's...
Don't care, right?
I have someone to introduce you to.
Very exciting.
What the hell?
Will you two please sit down, okay?
What?
Be polite.
She's a real stickler for manners.
I love how janky this game is.
Oh my god, it's so fun.
Mother, meet Isaac Washington.
He's a homicide detective.
Very good at his job.
G for grandma?
I'm sorry.
I didn't entirely catch your name.
Agent G!
Clemmon!
Where's my medicine, Clemmon?
You don't need your medicine, mother.
Remember what I told?
Where's my fucking medicine, you factless pissant?
Let me give you some context here, boys.
I love my mother.
I bet you boys love your mothers too and would do anything to keep them happy and healthy.
Uh huh.
Well, my mother is dying.
Clemmon!
Don't ignore me!
Uh huh.
And dying really quite rapidly.
People die.
And unfortunately, there's only one way to fix that.
See, the compound that's been turning my inmates and half this county into mindless mutants can be used to sustain life.
What?
In a manner of speaking.
Oh my god!
She's got small tits!
Don't use the one with small tits, Clemmon!
I forbid it!
That's small!
Calm down, mother.
You're insane.
I'm just a very loving son.
Oh no.
Why?
I'm going to fucking puke!
Oops.
Time for your treatment.
Mother.
Wait!
I'd rather not.
Bye!
I can't believe Caesar is finally fucking dead.
Hey, snap out of it.
We've got to find Varla.
This game is insane.
You.
Who.
Now.
Boys.
He's a kid!
One last thing.
If you'd be so kind as to look towards the stage, please.
Oh my god.
It just keeps getting weirder.
How does it happen?
In this game.
Between them, 21 counts of armed murder.
Is...
17 counts of aggravated assault.
12 counts of sexual assault.
Three bombings.
One.
I'm sorry if you heard my computer.
Boys.
Puppy.
Fight them in Old Sparky about six months ago.
And since then, I've been tinkering with them on my weekends off.
See how you fight them?
AHHH!!!
They're ticklers.
They're ticklers?!
ughh!
What the fuck?
Did they say that they ate a boy's puppy?
It wouldn't have
been better if they bought together?
You guys could have gone after the both of us!
Brutus!
Ehehehehehe that's frivolous!
Oh my god.
Oh, we're hiding.
Oh, that was health right there.
But I don't need it yet.
AWOL!
Hopefully we come back.
MMORPG!
8-8-2-3!
I don't know what some of these acronyms are though.
HTTP!
E!
Carlos!
GTFO!
Not you, Carlos.
Sorry.
Stand by.
I
hate motherfucking mutes!
AWOL!
Strappin'!
Oh my god.
They set me up.
I don't think they did, buddy.
Chain link fence!
Checking.
I thought it was shaken.
Ian, welcome to my mission.
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Okay, check his Bible.
Are you winning, dad?
Actually, yeah, I think so.
I wonder what's... we'll probably... maybe a B on this one?
Tom, Dick, and Harry.
I think it's also... I don't...
Dang it.
I don't do the capitalizations anymore.
For the most of them.
Sometimes it's habit.
But...
It's
affecting my score too.
C!
X!
Crazy child!
He's recharging!
Nooo!
Wait, is he getting his health?
Oh!
Shit.
Is he getting his health back?
Ew!
Ay!
What if it isn't Scary Jack?
Oh my god, am I gonna make it back?
Final Fantasy...
War Team...
ZRG!
Lost history right there.
I don't recognize that one.
Come on!
In your own time.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, my bad.
I'll beat your presentation.
Jailhouse judgment will resume after these messages.
They look so iso!
Posing as they go downstairs.
A B!
Okay, we got a B.
We got a B.
We got a B, everybody.
Blue commercials...
There's something someone asked earlier...
Sorry I missed the Super Chat.
But, um...
Something about...
Something about Hennya, I thought.
Genius that says dayo.
B for blue!
Bo-he-ka is bend over, here it comes again?
What?!
What does a brother have to do with this?
I have to do to pacify a bitch.
I'm telling you, G, I've tried my best with her.
I X'd.
Thank you for the doughnuts!
Thank you guys for all the doughnuts and superchats.
Thank you.
...under fucking standing.
But that is the last fucking straw.
This...this...wait!
Is this a reference to, um...
What's it called?
It looks like a...
Evil Dead, almost.
But also...
It also looks like Doom a little bit, too.
Okay.
Last chapter!
Let's go, baby!
I was thinking Doom.
It does look like Doom.
Is anybody by the House of the Dead, guys?
Doom is a reference to Evil Dead?
Oh.
I love the split, too.
Super Soldier.
The project failed.
Today, the bunker that was home to these mysterious experiments and the last remaining samples of Formula X lies sealed and hidden.
Its location unknown.
Until now.
Heaven forbid anyone should ever open that bunker and learn of the secrets contained within.
Heaven forbid anyone should discover Operation Overkill.
Overkill!
I just...
I won't let you fucking do this to me!
Hold still, please.
This is a very delicate procedure.
You can't!
Please!
No!
Oh, God.
So how are we gonna do this?
I figured we'd kill every motherfucker who stands in our way.
Okay.
Fourteen.
Worked so far, I guess.
Ready?
I kinda love Clement's character, cause he's so weird.
He's just so... all the characters in this are so funny.
This is doing nothing for my elevator-phobia!
Why are there zombies even down here?
Oh.
Uh...
Jim Reed Comics!
Oh, God.
Last level, guys!
Italy!
Blizzard Panic!
That's me.
Blizzard Panic is so real.
Dang it, I almost got the A.
Asteroids do not concern me.
Thank you.
Oh!
Scumbag Billionaire!
Oh, that one was hard.
Oh, wait.
Which one?
Oh, Shark Infested Custard?
Improv... Probability!
Oh, gosh!
The monkeys aren't working!
Alabama Slug.
These ones are getting hard-hard.
Ugh.
These ones are getting really difficult.
Okay.
Uh... W.S.
Frisky Cake Robots.
Compromising Position.
No monkey, no monkey, no monkey, no monkey!
Yes, sir.
Oh.
Okay.
Keep... Oh.
Nice, sir.
Go to your brother.
They're hiding out.
And then we're gonna ambush them.
Gnome Issue.
Eat my dust!
It's okay, game.
I'll be more efficient.
I'm sorry.
Oh, gosh.
That's a big guy.
Oh.
Nice,
sir.
Doom in tights.
Good.
This Zeppelin is Inflammable.
Oh, that one was hard.
That one was hard.
Stealth Move!
Only you would think that.
Beyond Passive Pistol.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
Oh, my God.
Huh.
Thank you.
You're well-reasoned.
Debate.
Flagellates!
Next to me!
Beans.
Back to school.
Raspberry Fields.
Why do some of them just...
Oh.
Oh, God.
Dang it.
I did it twice.
QB!
Some of
these are really hard.
Look over here.
Look and touch.
Ex-F.
Heriot.
A Moth Mention.
Why you asking me?
Things have gotten tricky, tricky, tricky, you guys.
Oh, my God.
Oh my god.
Run!
I think that was health.
Oh well.
I'm just traversing tab all the time.
No one needs you alive.
Pixie dream, girls.
Last level you can do it.
Yeah.
My eyes.
Oh.
Saucy recipe.
I can't spell that.
I can't spell recipe.
Don't give up.
I got you.
Chocolate!
Nice.
Slow-mo came in handy there.
I don't think...
I don't think I would have saved him if I hadn't had the slow-mo.
To be honest.
Soapy fighters.
We are soapy...
...fighters.
Fighters...
That one is evil.
That one...
That one was so evil.
What the hell.
These are hard words!
I don't even know what these are.
The guitar malfunction kind of went crazy.
What did I just do to him?
That went hard.
Looks like your computer just crashed.
Plank stars.
Hot and warm, baby!
You're getting on that plane.
Extreme violence.
Oh my god, sorry.
This scared me.
Jump!
That could've been us.
That could've been us, man.
Hear me woof!
Toboggan warrior.
Oh
my god, these are long.
When two become one.
Oh my gosh.
Instant poodles is so good.
I swear you get up on this.
Cow!
It's not nice to yell cow at a lady.
By the way, c'est fromage.
It's not nice to yell when a lady comes up at you, you know.
Why waste it?
No.
Argentina mansion, baby!
Some of these are so hard.
Gotcha!
Minister!
Who's next?
Lanto!
Bump this thread!
Oh my gosh, I remember doing that on Gaia.
I'd be like, bump!
Which one is closer?
Your shadow has horns!
Bump this thread, everybody.
Bump.
Not the thread, Necro.
No, it was my favorite place to roleplay.
And if it was quiet, I'd be like, bump.
Bump.
Oh, shit!
Uh, sorry.
Damn.
That wasn't me!
Ten of them.
One of them.
Don't feel too bad.
That wasn't me!
You can be one cool motherfucker at times, you know that?
Why did we come in here?
Shut up and figure a way out of it.
The chef, go.
Now.
Go, go, go.
Oh my god.
We were gonna burn alive in there.
Fuck!
That motherfucker nearly had me.
Shit!
You ever feel like dialing down the curse?
I don't seem washed.
No!
Fuck that motherfucker!
Oh, hold on.
Take highlighter is the best!
Speak your truth!
Oh
no, I missed.
I wasted it, I think.
Oh my shit.
This blood is p- working.
Oh, whoa!
Wait, those aren't... Is this actually Metal Gear?
Oh my god.
Don't give in to hate.
The socks with sandals!
Oh, I should have saved the health.
Filthy nuns!
Come
on, let's find the trip.
Socks and sandals are cute!
I stand by that!
Depends!
What kind of socks?
With the sandals!
Lizard.
Uh,
waiting for paint to dry.
Uh, fixing my toasties.
Oh my god.
Sometimes they're just all like...
Sometimes they're too close, but it's okay.
It's like, uh...
Oh.
Oh my god, that was close.
But they're all yellow.
One guy is really far away, though.
It's confusing.
Next generation soldiers!
He's emoting.
Here's the bulkhead switch.
I'll unlock it.
Okay.
Uh.
A cat dancing detective.
Got him?
Yeah!
Next generation special forces.
So, where's Varla?
She's right here, boy.
Varla, are you okay?
Uh oh.
Better than okay.
I've never felt so turned on in my life.
It's grandma!
Oh my god, it's grandma.
Say what?
Don't worry, detective.
Ouch.
Oh my god, my contacts.
That's why it said go to your room!
Because of her!
Varla, no!
Don't you ever talk to your mother like that!
Oh my god!
Sorry, mommy.
That's better.
Mommy?
Oh my fucking...
What have you done?
I should think that's pretty self-explanatory.
Your friend is in that jar over there.
She's alive, too.
What's left of her.
Then your stock just fucking crashed!
I love you, mom.
She's got psychic powers!
Ew!
I don't understand!
The formula should've worked!
No, Varla!
Say night-night to mommy, asshole!
Well, I guess there goes Varla.
And I think it's past your fucking bedtime, young man!
This game is intense.
Oh my god, the boobs.
I guess this is it.
It's certainly been an adventure.
Yeah.
You wanna do the honors?
Varla...
This is for you.
Well, we have our...
Oh my god.
Why are we just gonna...
Huh?
How we survived that, I don't know.
What?
If we hadn't found these miniguns just lying around, we'd be fucking dead for sure.
I'm just glad Varla got the justice she deserved.
Wait, what?
So, what do you plan to do with your life now, Isaac?
Well...
I figured as soon as I got home, I'd go pay my respects to my old man.
And then?
And then Washington's going to fucking Vegas, baby!
She's still fucking alive, ain't she?
Oh my god.
I was gonna say, no way.
I'm at somewhat of a loss.
Then let's just make this look fucking cool.
Those were...
You guys...
Um...
What?
You got...
Mother.
Oh my god.
Let's go after mother, baby.
Final exam.
Word association.
Type anything as long as you type like a motherfucker.
Wait, what?
What should I type?
Oh, feet.
What?
Feet?
Oh god.
Um...
Enemy types.
Ah!
Shitting?
Puking?
Puking!
Zombie!
Oh, words associated?
Okay, so I have to type words associated with the thing that is...
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Score?
Yeah, yeah.
Continue?
Yes.
Agent G!
Sunglasses!
Cool!
G!
Awesome!
Agent... oh shit.
Oh, country music!
Western!
Country!
Sexy!
Stripper!
Candy!
Sister!
Lover!
Hot girl!
Hottie!
Patootie!
Ass!
Nice ass!
What else?
Tattoos!
Tits!
Titties!
Baddie!
Yeah, bad ass!
Isaac Washington!
Fucker!
Motherfucker!
Puking!
Bitch!
Fucker!
Assfucker!
Bitchfucker!
What else?
This is...
Yeah, lollipop!
Appropriate!
Oh, Jasper!
Jasper!
Oh shit.
Oh my god, I'm not gonna make it.
You're dead.
I didn't realize it changed.
Okay, this is fine, everybody.
Oh, Jasper!
Genius?
Hot girlfriend?
Glasses?
Oh, we did it.
Okay.
Suggestive?
I could have said brother, you're right.
Candy, yeah, we had candy.
It's okay, we did it.
I love the WT difference between struggling with other problems but locked in at Barlow's.
It threw me off so much!
I can't go on in a world without my mommy!
Oh my god, he's gonna blow us all to hell.
I would never accept him.
You're fucking right there!
Into the potty mouth.
I'm sorry, it was the game!
It wasn't me, it was the game!
Please!
This is a dead man's switch.
I'm sorry!
We've nothing to live for.
It was the game, it wasn't me!
Kill me and the self-destruct for the lab beneath us goes off.
This whole prison will be leveled.
Then what do you want?
I'll go wash my mouth out with soap.
I want to undo all the wrongs I have done.
I want to return to the womb.
Please.
Just this one last thing.
To the womb?
You fucking handle this freak show.
I need to sit down.
When revenge seemed the only option.
You've broken a hundred laws.
You're responsible for the deaths of countless thousands.
You've threatened the safety of every man, woman and child on this planet.
And you put our friend's brain in a jar!
I have a lot to atone for.
By returning to the womb?
That's right.
A final noble act.
Give me that.
Thank you.
That was all that was needed.
Huh?
Don't fucking thank him.
As soon as we're in a helicopter out of here, I'm chucking that thing out the fucking window.
Then I can die happy.
Goodbye, boys.
He's crawling to his mom.
Are we good?
Did you not find this all slightly ironic?
I fuckingronic?
Yeah, ironic.
You know when something occurs after you...
I know what ironic is.
...it means, motherfucker.
You say you did it again.
Throughout this whole episode, you've been motherfucking everything.
Yeah.
That's my thing.
That's how I fucking speak.
See, that's why I associate it with him.
There we were, face to face with a real motherfucker.
Oh, no.
Clement more than likely fucked his mother.
No.
Stop talking, Agent G.
Stop talking.
When indeed he was most probably a real motherfucker.
So what does that tell you?
I don't fucking know.
It means you don't fucking mean what you fucking say.
It's all shit.
Say what, motherfucker?
See, you're doing it fucking again.
You like me.
Deep down through all your fuckisms, you really like me.
I'm the fucking nearest fucking thing you've ever had to a fucking friend.
Don't fucking do this to me, man.
Wrong fucking place.
Wrong...
Go on.
Say it.
Say the fuck what?
Say you like me.
This is Yowie.
Get the fuck out of my space.
Never repeat fucking talk of that shit again.
Or what?
I don't fucking know what.
The music, even.
Okay, man.
Okay.
We made progress here.
You did good.
When we're back home, I am going to get myself a car, play my country music, and if you want to ride back to where the fuck ever you live, you are motherfucking welcome.
Fuck you.
So that's a yes, then.
Can I drive?
Yeah, fuck you.
Washington is washing off on you.
Yeah.
He really did chuck it out the window, like he said.
Oh my God.
Barla Guns.
Barla.
If you can hear me, I'd like you to know I think you're the most beautiful woman I've ever met.
Now that just ain't right.
I think if we've learned anything from today, it's that love ain't always right.
Hey, I love my old man.
You saying that ain't right?
What is happening?
Well...
And your fiancé in that jar there loved her brother.
I was just making an observation.
Frankly, Casanova, I'd be more worried about reading the past 12 hours as a damning fucking indictment of contemporary feminism.
Beg pardon?
I just think two dick-wielding cop clichés taking down a 100-foot...
What is going on?
...burping mother is a statement fairly limited in its interpretations.
I'm not sure you can read too much into that.
Not to mention, the strongest female role model in this whole affair...
...ain't much more than a gherkin in a pickle jar.
Washington?
They had met as adversaries.
She's, like, covering her ears.
What the fuck is it?
They had fought as allies.
I love you, man.
Shut the fuck up.
But to their enemies...
And you?
Me?
One-way ticket to motherfucking Vegas, baby.
They're talking to me!
They were righteous motherfuckers.
Yeah!
That was amazing!
That was so fun!
We never knew what the G stood for.
Who was...
Who was the Clement?
I didn't see his name.
They call him James.
Well, never saw him.
Jesus.
Sounds of a great game.
That was so crazy.
Why do you enjoy this spectacle game?
Thank you for playing it.
Great Shenmue for you, Thank you!
Good playing, everybody.
Good playing.
Thank you, Sega.
For this game.
I can't believe this is real!
That's me like you.
I do push through in getting this game to work because this was a WoW game.
Thanks for this MFing adventure.
Sorry, Washington rubbed off on me a little bit at the end there.
Never would have guessed that ending.
100 out of 10 game.
Oh, so fun!
I wonder if there... there is DLC for this.
It would be great to see Sonic in this game.
Hold on, hold on a second.
I'm telling my friend I'll be there soon.
I'm so hungry with eyes.
I'm so hungry.
Thanks for playing this funny game.
Yeah!
That's so fun.
So much fun.
DLC doesn't add anything to the story.
Yeah, but what if there was DLC to add Sonic the Hedgehog?
That's what I would do.
Eww.
I
got an E.
Does Sonic say FF?
Actually, maybe he would.
Ending sequence?
XOL power in action.
I did pretty well, I think, sometimes.
Oh, sorry, was the music too loud?
Hello, Isaac.
This is Caesar.
We've never seen eye to eye, you and I.
But I wanted you to be aware of some important things.
I find myself burdened with an inexorable sense of moral duty, Isaac.
And in the absence of a friend to confide in, I turn to you.
Am I better now?
Yes, darling, yes.
The Cretan prison warden?
Yeah.
It was he who originally discovered the mutant compound.
In a secret lab beneath this bridge.
Rin Hanamaru Arena.
Clement's ambitions are small-minded, Isaac.
But he has friends.
Powerful friends.
Yes, sir.
And they have had access to the compound for some time.
No, sir.
So...
He wasn't the bad guy.
And...
Oh my god!
His dad was still alive!
Typing of the dad, typing of the dad!
93% accurate.
I think that's the lowest I've gotten, but that's okay.
Yay!
Typing in the dead hardcore mode.
Become a zero-tolerance keyboard warrior.
What does that even mean?
We did it!
A doting sibling to a crippled brother.
Forced into a life of vice.
Now she's filled with a primal hunger for revenge.
Oh, Candy.
Oh, wait.
Where was it?
Was it in the story mode?
Oh, here we go.
Memorabilia.
Let's look at some more of the 3D models.
This game certainly got big cowabunga energy.
Thanks for the stories.
Dave.
Oh, all of them are unlocked now.
Let's go.
Redneck.
Captain...
Stop, Poker.
Oh, wait.
Just kidding.
They're not all unlocked.
I'm a liar.
I would have to play again.
Why is it Washington?
I've been wondering what his shirt is this whole time and it won't let me zoom in.
This game is so cruel.
I've been wondering what his shirt is.
Candy.
Clement.
This guy is such a freak.
Look at his yaoi hands.
You are such a...
Look at the way he stands.
You're such a freak.
Mother.
Oh my god.
Mother is mothering.
Grandma.
She's a freak, too.
Yeah.
Secret written on the back of the stripper zombie?
There is?
Wait, but we looked at the back of the stripper zombie.
Did we not?
Yeah.
There's something written here?
I just see the claws.
I don't see anything.
Wait, was this a ruse?
I hate you guys!
Please, I'm actually really gullible, so please!
No, wait, I think I saw... Oh my god, it's the SMG!
No!
Oh my gosh, I'm actually so gullible.
Oh my gosh.
I hate you guys so much.
Ice cream truck.
Wait, what does the ice cream truck fall under?
Oh, it's its own thing.
That's so fun.
Well guys, this was fun.
Thank you for hanging out with me.
I wanna see some of the comments.
Concept art.
Oh my god, it's terrifying though.
Thanks for the five gifted!
Thank you!
The twins!
Ewww.
Did I get my wallet yet?
Nope.
I'm actually off to go meet with a friend who I sent money to.
I'm gonna...
Woah!
Icky.
We die!
Thanks for the gifted.
Why did it take me so long to realize this is House of the Dead?
But instead of using a mouse and a controller, it's just typing.
Yeah!
That's basically it.
Puker.
I hate that guy.
H&G!
Did you know that the ice cream truck license plate reads...
Gullifuss?
I hate you all.
Oh my gosh, wait!
I love the hat!
I think they should have kept the Zune hat.
Oh, Varla.
This is all concept art though, so...
It all changed, right?
Oh, the three of them!
Why don't they include Candy?
Woah!
Candy!
Wowee.
She's so cute.
This game makes me wanna play like...
Lollipop Chainsaw or something, you know?
Or, um...
Oh, what's that other one?
That one that's getting the new remake coming out.
Uhh...
Uhhh...
It's also Grasshopper.
Dead Rising!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Dead Rising.
The Fetid Waters.
From the putrid depths of mystery.
It has come to maim.
It has come to kill.
It has come to feed.
It came from...
Dun-dun-dun!
I love these, like, old school pictures, right?
Oh my god, Sega, right there!
Two months of Minto.
Thanks, Urban!
50,000 dead.
They're just getting started.
Overkill.
House of the Dead Overkill!
Nice.
In the comic book.
Prelude to...
Oh, prelude.
I don't think Dead Rising is being censored.
That's not what I heard.
Oh, okay.
Okey-dokey.
I'm gonna go eat.
I'm gonna go get some money.
I'm gonna go out.
On the town, maybe.
I don't know, it's pretty hot.
Not the mom song.
Pathos, happy birthday!
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, dear Pathos.
Happy birthday!
No, Jomar is also your birthday.
Oh my gosh.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, that guy Jomar.
I clicked out of the game.
Okay, guys.
I gotta get going.
For real.
Because I don't want to keep my friend waiting too long.
And I want to go eat.
Because I'm starving.
I'm so hungry.
Thank you guys for watching today!
This was so... I just expected House of the Dead.
I did not expect... Rather...
I don't remember House of the Dead being like this.
You know?
I don't remember it being so...
So... this.
But this was so much fun!
Thank you guys!
And I hope you guys have a good rest of your night or your day or whatever.
And I'll see you guys... Not tomorrow!
Sorry.
I...
I will not be streaming tomorrow.
But...
I have actually... Wait, can I show you guys?
Hold on.
I have a new thing.
Shut up, game.
I'm gonna quit the game.
There we go.
I have...
I have something.
Hold on.
I can't stop.
My brain is so dead right now.
How do I actually export this?
Actually, I'm not even quite sure.
Oh, there it is.
Export.
I can't type anymore.
Oh my god.
Everything is...
I'm so... My brain can't even think.
Oh wait!
No, no, no!
Oh my goodness.
Hold on.
Export.
There we go.
I think that did it.
Yeah, I think that did it.
Uh...
No...
I just wanna show you guys real quick.
I have a new schedule!
See?
It's a new schedule type.
So you'll see it.
It's obviously not accurate at all.
And nothing is right at all.
But...
New schedule!
Lorem ipsum!
So...
Yeah.
Once I...
Once I have a schedule for next week...
I will...
You'll see this schedule being used.
I love stream title here.
You should.
You should love it.
You should love it very much.
It's so cute though, right?
It's like a maid cafe...
Here, I'll show you again.
It's like a maid cafe menu and everything.
Ciara did such a great job with it and designing it.
So...
Yeah.
Lorem ipsum.
Anyways, guys.
Thank you for watching.
Thanks for hanging out with me.
And I will see you guys later.
Bye-bye.
Otsumito.
Itterashai.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
You are going to remember flowers.