Not too long ago, Zumbini's enjoyed the good life.
Though they all looked slightly different, different eyes,
noses, air, heat.
Such differences meant nothing to the Zumbini's.
And so they lived happily on Zumbini Isle, making small,
useful products which were prized the world over.
The Zumbini's had a sense of fulfillment and inner peace,
not to mention healthy bank accounts.
What?
Then one day, who should show up?
But the bloats.
No, I hate those guys.
The bloats offered to help the Zumbini's grow their
businesses.
Expand their trade routes.
their quality of life.
Being trusting sorts, the Zumbinis agreed.
Oh wait, no, we do hate those guys!
They're bad guys!
But before long, the bloats had taken over everything.
No!
Stealing profits, cancelling holidays, high holidays!
Oh my god.
The Zumbinis were getting pretty stressed.
Oh, they're stressed.
Well, you can push them only so far before they take matters
into their own hands.
Viva la revolution!
Zumbinis!
Oh my god.
For so they decided to escape.
Escape.
And build a new home in a distant land.
Doom, doom, doom, doom, doom.
Oh my gosh, sorry.
Hello, everybody.
Hello, hello, hello, hello.
Welcome.
Oh, I guess I could have gotten to this part and then
clicked watch intro.
But I wasn't sure if it would be okay.
So, hello, hello, hello.
Welcome to a Zoom.
Peace.
I love this game.
From my ghostly childhood.
When I was a Wii Wisp.
And I would play this game.
I would.
I can remember so many sound effects from this game.
I'm so sorry I'm going to be so annoying.
But this one is like I guess the remake.
I guess technically it's a remake.
And it has like new art.
And I don't.
I think that's it though.
to thank you like can you guys hear the don't know i turned
down the volume quite a bit because the zoom bini game was
so loud uh but i can hear them so i can see i can see your
stuff it cracks me up how much this of the story of zoom
binis went over my head as a kid yeah i i'll be honest i
remember them they having to leave i remember them having to
leave thank you for the don't know because
Because of something, I couldn't remember why.
It's actually missing some sound effects, I think.
Don't tell me that.
I might cry.
I might actually cry.
They did that to me in Spiro.
There was like, it's the smallest thing in Spiro.
In Spiro 2, Ripto's Rage when they remade it.
And the one world with the guys that...
that do the ice skating, and there's the evil spirits that
you have to exercise.
They go, why I am?
Why I am?
They do that in the original, but they changed it for some
reason in the remake.
I don't know why.
It makes me so sad.
But, you know, it is what it is.
Here, I think at least the voices are the same, as you could
hear from Crunchy, narrator, San.
he sounds so the zoom beanies
that's what it talks like let's enter my name
we don't now i'm gonna have the smiley all right so this is
a game where we're little zoom beanies and if you don't know
what this game is yeah we're little well we're not we are
guiding the zoom beanies to salvation we are leading them
from the terrors of the working world to a new world where
they will have holidays again.
Yeah!
And, um...
Mm-mm-mm.
Do-no-do.
Boom.
I remember I used to sit on the screen because there would
be a crab.
Boom,
boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh my god.
Ronin, thank you so much for the dono.
I don't know if you'll see this or not, but I want to know
that you inspired me to follow and support VTubers and
showed me the beautiful world of them.
I wouldn't be a VTuber fan today if it weren't for you.
My dear Kamioshi Mint Boss!
Sorry for taking time.
Not at all.
Thank you, Ronin.
You're, you know, if you found where you belong, you're not
a Ronin anymore.
Isn't that the case?
One of us, one of us.
Amy, thank you.
Tyranzo, thank you.
I love Zumbini's also fart.
So, where if you thank you, I start my new job tomorrow.
Congrats?
Oh my gosh!
Submit kips, thank you.
Usually I will read the donos at the end of the stream, so
uh...
Yes, thank you guys so much.
Thank you.
Okay.
Oh my gosh, we get to create our zumbinis!
Wait, what's the multiple dice versus the one dice?
Ah!
Oh my god!
No!
No, no!
Go back into the hole!
Get back in your hole!
No!
What are these strangers?
They don't stop!
Stop!
Stop it!
No!
Oh!
I don't know who you are.
Get in there.
Oh!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Get in there.
I don't know who you are.
You are not welcome on my boat.
Can't get in there.
Sorry.
This is an exclusive club, okay?
Yeah, this is...
This is...
You know...
Okay.
Thank you so much.
idea what this game is about, but I look forward to find out
why this holds a special place in your heart.
Already starting strong.
I think the puzzles in this are a lot of fun.
I would have to say my favorite one would maybe be there's a
froggy one where you release little frogies and they have to
follow a certain path.
Wait, I can't name it myself?
Oh no!
I wanted to name...
I wanted to name love after you.
Joan!
Have fun again today.
We love you our most beloved ghost, Ray.
Joan!
Oh my god!
I hope you're good.
Oh my gosh, Isashi booty, Joan.
Are you still doing nursing?
You're still good?
we can change our names to them no don't do that don't do
that okay well maybe it would be easier to just no no okay
alright guys oh my gosh she's so cute with the backwards hat
and everything
thank you guys for the total thank you Let's see.
Okay, our first friend.
The cool glasses.
Green, like me.
Floating, like me.
Oh, ah!
Okay.
All right.
Journey, Nuhagi!
Release!
Yeah!
Kwaru is dead.
Oh, sorry.
Also, Cyclops.
Cyclops Skater.
Katie.
Release.
Jernuaggy goes hard.
Kwaru is dead.
No, no, he's not.
No, he's not.
He's...
He's a...
Dezo Uh oh Okay hold on I gotta not go so fast I might pass
it These are some crazy I don't know how to pronounce any of
these Frofa Release Frofa
Um Say so Dezo Yeah Frofa Cthulhu names Yeah Let's see Oh
the beady eyes are is so funny.
I like the springy ones too, but they're a little slow.
Let's do...
Segu!
Boing, boing, boing, boing, boing.
Sounds like my name is Quaru now.
No.
Um.
Crazy hair.
Sneeflu.
Sneeflu!
Like I just walking.
Walk, walk, walk.
I'm going to call her walk.
Who am I missing?
We got flying, we got skating.
Okay, we need a lot of guys, though.
I'm very going to get this one random.
Lado!
Release Lato!
You and Pauline?
Red nose?
Oh, we do need a red nose.
Oh, yeah, we need a lot of colors for the future things.
Oh, we also don't have this hairstyle.
I think that...
Hi!
Emma!
It's EE!
Oh my gosh.
Hold on.
E!
It looks just like Emma.
So cranky.
Let's see what else do we need.
Rebruel!
What's wrong with E...
Rob Bracio!
I think they're siblings.
Denise!
You know what?
I am just gonna random...
random generate them now because...
Iggyagga!
Iggyag!
Muscus!
We need another Cyclops.
Cyclops.
Stay!
Wait, you have the same hair, though.
Let's give you this hair.
Two!
Thank you.
Oh my gosh.
It's been forever.
Hello.
There's zombies that was taken from the hole.
Neither truly a wisp nor truly a phantomie.
Stop.
Let's see what...
Oh, sorry.
Everyone's gotta be different.
Daffiro.
Um...
What other...
Oh, Kaisu!
Wait, we have a lot of...
Glasses.
Hold on.
What do we need more of?
We need more BDI people.
Fleens.
You're not fleens.
Well, Whatever you are.
Make me a pizza.
We have a couple sleepy eyes.
We need more beady eyes.
Come on.
Emiano!
How many more people can I have?
Thank you guys for all the donuts.
Thank you.
Oh, you don't even have a name.
Oh, oh, this is it.
This is the crew, everybody.
The journey begins here, Zumbini Isle.
Select traits to create a crew of 16 Zumbinis.
But remember, each Zumbini and this crew must be unique.
Oh my gosh.
Okay, guys.
I think it's time.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom,
boom, boom.
Oh, hey!
Do-do-do-do-doom, do-doom, do-doom.
Why is the music...
Just about by a stormy sea, the Zumbini's reached the shore
of a peculiar land.
Wait, that's a huge crab!
Okay, so our first puzzle is getting across the bridge.
Why was the crab so big?
Okay.
So this puzzle, each man...
This game is kind of creepy.
This game is a little scary.
So, why is there a face in that cliff?
That's what I'm about to tell you.
These cliffs are alive!
And they're also very picky.
So we have these bridges that the Zumbini's can cross either
one or the other.
So some traits this guy likes, but this guy doesn't like.
And we only have this number of tries.
to figure out where the Zoombie knees go.
So he's gonna sneeze.
Alright, Denise.
Let's check.
Let's try this way.
Okay.
That was fast.
Okay, so we'll put you over here.
But what trait did he not like?
They got a type.
Yeah, they do.
Sniffer.
Wait.
Okay.
let's try the hair let's try the hair oh oh okay a simp a
soup Sigma cliffs look at even even the rocks have faces
does that mean the ground is alive too am I like stepping on
like this guy's got face this guy it's all faces okay So
maybe it's glasses, no glasses?
So glasses here?
You think?
Glasses?
Oh?
Yo.
I think we're geniuses.
This children's game got nothing on us.
YAHOO!
Oh!
Our theory has been debunked.
What?
Is it two eyes, one eye?
So everyone's going on this side.
What's wrong with Cyclopses?
Two eyes.
That would make sense because I put, I mean, with glasses,
you're going to have two eyes.
Yippee!
Oh my god, they're so loud.
I'm going to be adjusting the volume like crazy in this
game.
I'm so sorry.
How fortunate for Zumbinis that you are their guide.
Yes!
Me!
Oh wait, what is this?
Oh wait, oh no, no.
Stay with them.
Stay with me.
Feeling stuck?
Don't worry, Brave Explorer.
all you have you have all the information you need to
complete this challenge and get all your zoom beanies
through take your time look for patterns and don't be afraid
to make mistakes allergic cliffs why are you allergic to my
zoom beanies if a few of our little blue friends are left
behind they'll be waiting at zoom beanie aisle oh no we
could have lost them okay first trial these Their own guards
have their rules, so do proceed with skill.
Zumbini's one guard won't allow.
The other guard surely will.
Okay, so it's similar.
It's similar like before.
Hello, Mint.
They're blue.
The floodgates are opened, it seems.
Um...
Okay.
They're blue!
What about it?
Actually, I'm green.
I'm mint.
A little bit of blue.
Okay, let's just...
Katie, you're up first, baby.
Oh!
Why are you so rude?
Okay, so basically it's the same as before.
Just a little bit more.
And if they like...
If they pound...
If they ground pound enough, the rocks will come flying
down.
so this way uh-uh this why you say it like that to my girl
katie okay okay thank you grandma well she didn't even say
anything okay so all right let's try the hair again let's do
hair again
Okay.
Jernuaggy.
Hat or hair?
Well, I think that hairstyle or that one always has a hat.
Let's try ponytail.
Ponytail.
Yolto.
Ghost laughter.
Yeah, that's the good stuff.
Let's see.
One of the chosen few.
Oh, you scared me for a second.
You scared me.
No, there's no chosen few.
All of my zombies.
Step in.
All of them are chosen.
All of them.
Granny Ada Ada.
Okay, let's see.
Let's get the sniffle right here.
Go ahead!
I can't let you in.
That's so rude.
That's actually...
You can't just reject me for no reason.
Well, you're okay.
Everyone in this game is so superficial.
They all just judge on looks.
They judge on how our appearance, it's so messed up.
I'm glad that it's just hair, though.
It's pretty easy.
Okay, Dafferil.
Alrighty.
Look, Granny's got a harem.
Granny's got it going on.
You're sad.
You're a sad man.
What, do you want Frofa?
Uh-uh.
Okay, Frofa, try this way.
Oh my god.
Not all doors are open to you.
That's so rude.
Oh my gosh.
Gran, he's collecting them all.
Are you gonna have anyone?
Oh my god, he's so lonely.
Certainly.
He's just so grumpy.
I know.
It's so rude.
All right, Rebrisio, I believe in you.
Someone.
uh-uh uh-uh okay hold on this one this one
okay fine not all doors are open to you you deserve no one
you know what you can live your sad lonely life it's your
fault you you shut yourself out from the world you beg for
touch but you're the one who doesn't allow it you beg for
someone to love you you wish that someone could just you
wish that you that someone would just come in but you shut
the door on everybody you tell him Emiliano you're our last
little guy I feel called out I feel attacked done quite well
you've done quite well how delightful thank you and so Our
brave travelers continue on through this dusty wasteland
until they meet.
Arno, the almost omnivorous, one very hungry pizza troll.
Yes, yes, pizza, pizza, pizza, pizza!
Oh, fleens!
You're not fleens!
Wherever you are.
Make me a pizza!
Yes!
oh my gosh okay so basically we have to make him a pizza and
make it exactly as he likes um we don't know what he likes
so we just have to go combo by combo let's do cheese just
cheese
okay so if he throws it over here that means he doesn't like
any of the toppings but if If he throws it over here, that
means he'll still eat it.
So he does like the cheese.
More!
Topping!
Thank you!
Thank you for all the great past adventures here to many
more.
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
I was just trying to check out the stream on my break, but
things got way too real, way too fast.
I'm so sorry.
I gotta keep it real.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
More toppings?
Let's just do mushroom.
and eventually there's three guys something must go oh he
does not like the mushroom he's just like me for real for
real okay I like when he says there's something on that I
don't like it please I kind of want to put it mushrooms
again just so he says it there's stuff on that I don't like
oh he says it a different way though he's so cute the way
his mouth is so like wait wait his mouth is so hold on hold
on i could do that i could do that too it's so it's so
there's something i'm not i don't like
Okay, cheese, peppers, pineapple, no, pineapple, cheese,
pineapple, the goaded combination.
I know you love it, trunk man.
I know you love it.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
You did it!
You saved them all!
I saved them!
Somehow, good job, whoever you are.
Eventually, if you get it wrong enough times, they'll punch
you, and your little Zumbinis will fly away.
Oh!
A camp!
It's so good.
The music is so awesome.
Hold on.
What's this?
A campsite with hot soup all ready to eat?
Looks like a fine place for Zumbinis to relax.
But when they're ready to move on, they'll need a group of
16 along the path.
16.
Yeah, so we have to keep our whole crew.
And this also boils.
I remember all the clicks.
Actually, that's the only two I...
Oh!
Let's change it to green, like me.
Oh.
More minting zone.
It's great seeing you be so passionate about the things you
love.
Man, the audio of this game brings back so many memories of
that era.
Right?
Now, we have to decide.
Which way do we go?
I'll be honest, I don't remember.
I don't remember which one leads to which path.
So we have to make a decision.
Corn soup?
I wish.
I'll be honest, when I would see this as a kid, I used to
think it was poison.
It doesn't look like a good soup.
It doesn't look...
Ah!
I don't like that.
He sounds too close.
He sounds so like in my head.
ear didn't like that one this this one looks a little like
it's got a butt cheek okay guys let's make a poll let's make
a poll let's make a poll when I click out of the game you
won't hear it anymore so start a poll which direction
there's two I'm pretty sure there's another time when we get
to choose so left or I'll go up down check the map no no
we're in adventurers.
We are adventuring.
We don't know what the road will go to.
It's all about the discovery, baby.
Down for down bad.
Team up.
Adventurers also check their maps.
No, they don't.
Not the Zumbinis.
They are full of whimsy.
Okay, oh.
All right, it looks like it's up.
Let's go upward.
I think we're going through this game so quickly, we'll be
able to play again and we can go downwards next time.
Oh!
I remember this one too.
Oh my god, it's so soulful.
Wow, the art looks so good.
Welcome to the booth.
Now hurry yourselves up and find your seat.
Okay, so they have to have something in common.
This is easy.
I sit wherever you want to.
I don't really care.
here okay ponytail this one's easy this one's so easy there
you go you got it there you go you got everything's rushing
back to me even the things that i was like oh i didn't i
don't really remember this part so much we'll go by eyes
there you go you got it there you go you got it or well
first it yeah we're going wait i went eyes eyes to hair oops
it's fine though if we have to adjust we can we can do that
if we have to adjust anybody we can do that there you go you
got it oh like like we have to do right now
uh yep uh yep hold on okay hold on uh there you go you got
it
um let's see i actually don't remember what happens if you
put a wrong guy down Crab's alive!
Crab's alive!
Oh dang.
Oh are you okay?
Let's see.
They have springs and they have sleepy eyes.
Hey what are you doing there?
Oh, excuse me.
Oh, oh I need the sleepy eyes.
Let's see, hold on.
Um...
Okay, hold on.
Uh...
blue noses hmm
use the noses yeah let's go by noses instead we'll go by
noses instead green green green green there you go you got
it oh I can't see everybody separate separate stop being so
close to each other okay and then we'll go pink I shouldn't
have separated the...
Ah, sure!
Now a red nose.
Now a yellow nose.
But I'm probably gonna have to...
Switch it again, I think.
Wait, what do you have in common?
Oh, there we go.
Ah, sure!
There you go, you got it.
Oh, I'm done!
Mr. Mr. Oh my god.
I could have left at any time.
I could have...
The frogs!
Flower and Lily bad shape too.
Maybe the kids could have just left them.
There.
We could have just left them.
That's so sad.
Oh yes!
Oh my gosh.
I love this one.
This one's so fun.
Okay, so each frog.
Froggy has a pattern, right?
And you have to, they can only go...
I don't... I think they can't go diagonal.
So they can only go...
You have to drop them on the correct spot.
That gets them to the other side.
So, like, say we go with the X guy.
But they can only be used a couple times.
Like, you can't say, like, oh, okay, let's have all 16
Zumbinis get on this one guy.
No, no, no.
Only, like, a certain amount.
So, it's like, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
No.
See, we can't go that way.
Let's see if we do...
Boom, boom, boom.
boom boom no boom boom boom oh I don't think we can use the
X okay never mind okay next he I don't I think he's out I
think he's out let's try oh and then there's also like the
shape of the lily pad so boom boom boom boom boom boom boom
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Boom, boom!
And they're very slow.
Where are you going?
Frog!
No!
Did you do this?
Wait,
maybe he'll make it eventually.
Okay, okay, this time.
This is the run.
Thank you guys, thank you so much!
I always thought it was a shame that you didn't get to use
this model much so seeing you come back with updated rigging
is awesome.
I'm so glad, thank you!
Ah!
Yes!
Oh, oh no no no no!
Okay, nice, there we go.
It reminded me, oh my gosh, you know what that reminded me
of?
You know that video of the girl who's like watching someone
put the shapes in the holes and he's just like, this is a
rectangle shape.
What shape does it go into?
And she's like, the rectangle.
And he's like, that's right, the circle hole or the square
hole.
She's like, no, no, that's how I felt at that very moment.
okay do we put ourselves through actually i just realized
the yellow one is an absolute straight shot so let's just
there's no there's no room for error here yes just go go go
all the way also the blue one you can do multiples at a time
so there we go there we go the pink one also go but you
don't want them like running into each other so it's
probably safer to do the colors together the teal one works
too you're so right oh my god speed run what about the red
one red also works there's oh my god frog mania
are good that's crazy do
you guys like this sound i hope i wish they would sink i
don't think there's a way for them to sink but if there were
if there were a way it would be really great yes there's
something about old games that just have like that they just
it's like oh my gosh have you guys ever listened to the
barbie movies like listen just look up clips of the barbie
Barbie movies like the the old old ones you know the
animation ones and how how crisp her heels are on the ground
oh actually all of them all of them like walking just sounds
so satisfying they just oh it sounds so good okay um should
we try this one again let's get it going while we look for
other side i think x works too it does i thought we said it
didn't okay he's he's going he's going he's going okay let's
try um oh three leaf one three three three three three oh
that one works Actually, was it here?
Do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do,
do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, yeah.
Nice.
Three leaf on the light blue.
Mint confirmed Heal click fetish.
Is that a real fetish?
Actually?
Oh, oh, he messed up again.
Okay, I don't think we're going to use you anymore.
I don't think you'll just get, you'll get a little too
confused, mister.
okay again if you have to ask i learned the other day that
um stepping on stuff is a fetish too i didn't know like
someone would be like oh i'm oh no i stepped on a slice of
bread i didn't know but i just wonder what's the what is the
like oh okay he's gone now gets you going about that well
maybe crushing I kind of like I mean I don't know maybe I do
get it maybe I learned just now maybe I understood in this
very moment okay
anyway let's see we have this pattern as well no no hmm what
else we got diamonds no we got flowers no four leaf no okay
so it has to be this one right the yellow axe this one oh
wait oh
oh oh oh Oh, he's going to get just as confused as I am.
He's going to get just as confused as I am.
IDK, I'm watching at 144P.
Is it for the true, like, 90s...
A 90s game experience?
Aesthetic?
Oh, he did it.
He did it.
He's a smart frog.
You're a smart frog.
You are, you are!
How do these guys live?
Nice.
Okay.
Last one, last one.
Beam.
Yeah, I never played Pup Pud.
I only played one game of Freddy Fish and this.
I played Mist a little bit.
Did I understand Mist?
No.
But I played it.
I played it.
Well, I would watch my dad play Diablo.
And never Winter Nights.
Beam.
Missed my beloved.
Bee!
Okay.
Thank you for the dono.
Do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do.
Oh, I remember this one.
These stoned hexes, if they can make the right connections.
The right connections.
I remember really liking the sounds in this puzzle.
Gosh, I love the frog ones so much.
Okay.
So this one, you just have to not be lonely.
Actually, this works perfectly because I only have two
people.
Oh, just kidding.
Um...
What do I do with him?
Well, I failed.
No.
Uh-oh.
Wait, Lato!
Sneiflu!
Oh!
Oh, sorry, Sneiflu.
Sorry, I didn't mean to burn your butt like that.
Daphro.
I love the crunchy sound so much We have one Cyclops Two
Cyclops Okay that one actually Shit Feet
This one
Oh this one also works All you have to do is have eyeballs I
guess
um oh wait i just realized oh i'm an idiot it's the same
feet oh okay you guys children's game this game's not
outsmarting me okay this game is not outsmarting me okay we
need okay maybe then not the hair for well okay you can be
match with someone else though.
You can have the same feet as him.
You can have the same nose as him.
And you guys can have the same hair.
But then we need... It's just the right difficulty.
same hair they don't have the same feet they don't have do I
have another rolly her can I switch around who can I switch
around glasses bottom right has the same hair that's true
that is yeah that's true but they also have the same feet
wait so if I can move someone okay hold on we rolly but they
don't have the same nose but they okay hold on sorry sorry
sorry sorry
Okay, and then, um, we gotta make this possible, you guys.
Okay, you, you guys have the same eyes.
You guys have the same eyes, so we'll take...
We'll die.
I'm just...
Same eyes.
Wait, what do you guys have?
You guys have the same eyes, too, but you don't have the
same fate!
Wait, I had it?
Oh, what did I do?
I did?
Where?
No, I... Oh, same feet.
Oh, you're right.
Same eyes.
You've got them all through.
Good for you.
Remember at the beginning when I was like, we need a lot of
variety?
This puzzle's like this.
Yay!
You can leave without them.
It's kind of sad, though.
Flute goes hard.
Yeah, you can leave without all of them.
It's so sad.
Me win pattern recognition.
Another relaxing campsite ready and waiting for Zumbini's.
They'll meet their list.
The darkest, most dangerous, part of the journey is yet to
come.
I think we avoided the forest of the guys that are actually
trying to kill us.
So that's good.
I love this guy.
He loves his job.
Are there any other clickables?
Hey, that's just the same sound effect from the Oh.
I do remember those.
Ew.
This game is so goofy.
Wait, so now we're at the lions.
We have the lions.
We have the crystals.
We have another face matching game.
I think that's it.
Throughout these gloomy mountains, strange carvings left by
ancient peoples are everywhere.
Yeah, the bubbles, the bubbles.
The bubbles is the...
what's it called I think that I called it wait the
I don't remember this one oh I have to go in order of their
nose oh okay that's easy blue
green do they have to have something similar though oh I
guess they do what the wait so they have to have oh sorry I
just for some reason reason I was only looking at the eyes.
Okay, hold on.
Uh, oh no.
It's like a, it's like the same thing.
I missed the blue.
Oh, I did.
You're so right.
Thank you.
I don't even see it because it was like partially hidden.
Alright, so green.
Green.
Oh, I only have two left.
I'm throwing, you guys.
I'm throwing for real.
throwing for real when it comes to red yeah we can do this
guy and then this guy i don't know if there has to be a
similar thing to the previous person but we'll just do it
anyway red
splendid job thank you narrator
i'm so smart what are you throwing ball.
The ball in your court.
Oh my gosh, I love the sound in this one too.
You use the crystal filters to change the Zumbini's
reflection.
It will give them crystal slamming protection.
All of them are fun.
I felt like that lion one was a little too easy though,
right?
So just me, wow!
It looks so fancy now.
Oh my gosh.
Okay, so look.
We have to match the reflection Wait, but this is exactly
them.
Can I just put another guy on here?
But...
Wait, so if I do...
Hold on.
If I...
Is it...
If I combine?
Or do I have to have the same person?
No, I have to combine, right?
So we need a Cyclops with blue...
Nose.
Do we even have that?
No.
Wait, I actually don't remember this one.
Match the characters, pull the lever.
Do they change each time?
Why is there a second seat?
Wait.
Oh, it does refresh.
Wait, it didn't.
I don't remember.
I don't remember this one at all.
I remember it, but I don't remember it.
Why is there a second seat?
I think.
maybe for when you go through it again is what i'm thinking
of i think uh i think like round two right ping it refreshes
every two zoom beans okay okay so who's this is our guy
the sound reminds me of the indiana jones ride
Nice.
Who's our next victim?
This guy.
What's your name?
Muskus.
I'm Paco.
Him.
try putting two on it wouldn't it won't let me it won't let
me i've tried who is the next you like it won't even let me
drag it it won't even let me pick them up i think it's for i
think it's for a future future playthroughs because the the
puzzles do get like Not more difficult, but...
Well, I guess maybe it is a little bit more difficult.
They realize you level up as a gamer.
You know?
I'll show you what happens when you get one wrong, though.
It's so sad.
Oh!
All the
other puzzles give you.
I don't even know her name.
I killed her in cold blood.
I didn't even know her name.
the other puzzles give you like a leeway.
This one's just like, no, it's too easy.
You need to know immediately.
Oh my god.
It's so...
We killed her, you guys.
We killed her.
Your accomplices now.
You also killed her with me.
It is not just me.
It is a we.
This is us.
We are in this together, okay?
I knew you guys were gonna be like we yes we we I just got
here I'm so shocked right now because I've been showing you
guys like kind of what happens when you miss the other one
so the frog one too if you mess up on the frog one the frogs
just jump forever like they just don't move like your don't
die they're just stuck in this never-ending like it's kind
of it's not kind of it's really messed up oh my gosh can you
charge a ghost with murder
oh my gosh
the game gets harder the more zumbini is you save when you
do new game plots Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's what I do remember.
Yeah, it may be we, but we'll get less time in the pen if we
turn state...
We... if we turn state's evidence.
Wait, no, no, no.
No, no.
No, there is no evidence.
There's no evidence that the VOD is gone.
Alrighty, buddy.
Here's our last one.
Yay, we all survived!
We all...
We all survived.
Search first for traps.
So easy to miss.
To get Zumbini's across, This one's fun too.
They're all fun.
It's always been 15.
I don't remember what this means.
Oh, that's a hairstyle.
Okay, so if it's...
Okay, so hairstyle, man, this guy has to go on this one.
Because otherwise he's going to he's going to get eaten.
So, Muskus?
Go.
Go, Muskus.
And go, Kaislu.
Go.
My children.
Go, my children.
Rofa.
Leave you to...
Maybe I should have...
Well, we know it's going to be fine.
We know it's going to be fine.
I was going to say maybe I should have let just one guy go
and see and tested it before i let all of them go but you
know Okay.
Now.
Sad eye.
We'll let you go.
Rabris-rabrisco.
Rabris- Rabrisco.
Oh.
Girl, I'm working towards my masters and criminal.
psychology, you were sort of giving me content to feed to
add to a report I'm doing.
Watching VTubers is educational, you guys.
Didn't you know?
Okay.
He goes... I'll go that way.
Yeah, he's fine.
We just have to...
Maybe I should have done a glasses.
Okay, this time I'm going to do this glasses.
I know
we're gonna have to switch between the two yeah we'll
alternate yeah yeah okay so now it's a cool glasses denise
oh my god at least denise is alive right okay now glasses
oh my god it's so crunchy Now...
Sunglasses.
Now glasses.
Now sunglasses.
And now everybody else.
Wait!
Isn't she the one that fell down the hole?
She's alive!
You guys, she's alive!
She's the one that fell down!
We're fine!
How do I play this?
On Steam.
Everything's all good.
Yippee!
Whoa, my!
You've done exceptionally well.
I know.
Carry on, carry on!
Thank you, narrator.
Wait, was that the last one?
I don't remember anyone after this.
Have we reached the promised land?
One.
Is this it?
Two.
Could this be the place they'd been seeking?
Three.
Oh, oops.
Oh.
No!
I'm so sorry, you guys.
It's okay.
We'll just have to play again.
a windmill.
This windmill was wrought to honor the Zumbinius who calmed
Captain K.
June, rode tattooed toads, and knew how to network when the
traveling was not so easy today.
Look at our guys.
Katie.
This clock tower was constructed for the Zumbinius who
ambled past allergic cliffs, cruised on by stone-cold caves,
and appeased Arno the almost omnivorous.
Who are these people?
Alright, guys.
Let's go.
Oh, oh, I see now.
Oh, you can also the oh spoilers spoilers spoilers spoilers
you can also practice some of the levels that are more like
on different different difficulties too what that's so cool
very very hard Wow oh so hard so that's why I said not so
easy because So we were on the easy level.
See, and we have...
16.
We still have 384.
Is that what that means?
Wait.
She's here!
You guys, she is alive.
Rebro!
She's right there!
See, she's alive.
She's alive.
Man.
She lives.
We're fine.
Oh, okay.
My bad.
The big, the bad, and the hungry.
So now we're gonna go to the campsite.
I thought there was another split, but I guess there's just
the one.
So we have a whole other set of puzzles down here.
Isn't that so exciting?
Scroogey!
Scroogey must live at all costs, you guys.
If anything happens to Scroogey, I'm gonna cry.
Oh you are too similar.
Aipu.
You're also similar.
Riyan!
Oh I think it...
Zygla, Zygla, Zygla, yeah.
Cool deal.
So prove.
Dezo!
You're back!
Oh my gosh, you guys, we got Dezo back!
We got Dezo back!
Let's go!
Screw key.
Afloak.
Lele ble.
A dry wheat.
Rawabu.
Ruhwabu.
What am I missing?
We have no skates.
Macy.
Doku.
No, we need skates.
I read...
I read the I read this lot wrong, I think.
Hi, Aura?
Oh my god!
Hello!
I played this when I was a kid.
Me too.
Hello, hello, hello.
Thanks for dropping by!
What else am I missing?
We have...
Um...
We need more ponytail.
Busk...
Buswask...
um you know what hard mode oh oh okay i thought it was just
the one guy i was gonna be like hard mode we won't decide
them at all and it was just one man that walked out would be
so funny
i would always do the frog one don't oh my gosh i don't
remember the uh second route so much i remember the hotel
one but i don't oh and the forest where they're trying to
kill us i don't remember anything i don't know i don't
remember the other ones fleens we're not fleens okay is it
glasses no glasses again it wouldn't be so simple right wait
are we on easy mode again still?
I don't know.
Or not glasses.
I said glasses, no glasses.
It was.
I...
Oh!
Okay.
It's not the hair.
But they have nothing else in common.
This guy is like almost an identical twin, so...
Okay.
doesn't help us so much thanks for the don't know after
trying to win a cinema role for over an hour in a UFO
catcher crane game I finally made it for zoom beanie's
nostalgia time I don't blame you I'm so bad at crane games
though oh do you guys mind if I have a snack I oh my gosh at
at the airport when I was coming home they sometimes have
like these pop-up stores that like sell little snacks that
you can that you can get and this one was called the butter
butler and it's a fancier little butter cake it's so buta
finasie buta buta oh that's just his butter butler finasie
fina finan finan fancier The butter fanciers.
And they're so good.
It's like a little...
Oh, I'm just smelling it right now.
It smells like...
It smells like a butter...
Like a waffle.
Like when you put butter on a waffle.
Oh, it smells so good.
Oh, wow.
If you can look up the butter butler.
It's so yummy.
It's so good.
Okay.
Let's try eyes.
Trying her.
Okay.
Trying you.
Daiso.
Don't let us down, Daiso.
Very good Daiso.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
That sounds good.
It's really good.
Okay.
Okay, we got through all the ones that we were sure of.
What about you?
No.
No!
Mm-hmm.
You.
He's allergic to...
He's allergic to nerds, for real.
Mm-hmm.
You like glasses though.
You're a man of culture.
What about you?
Not the...
You're even allergic to...
to Cyclops?
It's so sad.
You have no culture.
Splendid job!
Are these noses?
I just... I can't tell.
Hmm.
These stone guards have their rules, so do proceed with
skill.
With skill.
Zumbini's one guard won't allow.
The other guard surely will.
Splendid.
Strange looking bunch.
Where do they all come from?
Sorry, we just keep passing through.
Alright, is he going to be so sad this time?
Can't let you in.
Why not?
Why?
Like, I need...
Come on.
Sure.
Okay,
let's try the glasses.
Enjoy yourself.
Oh!
I mean...
What?
He has friends.
now maybe this he had a change of heart is it glasses is he
a glasses enjoyer hello oh my gosh hello mr stone wow don't
mind if i do yeah um okay well that's all the glasses we got
let's try um
wait that means we must be selective about our clientele
what does that mean What's wrong with A-Floak?
Huh?
I think you're just being very discriminatory.
Don't be shy.
I kind of...
I think I'm...
I think I like the rock.
I think I'm like, wow, for this...
Okay.
Have a good time.
Thank you.
I mean, he's just got a bit of a career...
I think I misjudged him before.
You know?
Oh.
So it's hair.
It's not the eyes.
Go ahead.
Enjoy yourself.
Yeah!
Okay, so it's the hair instead.
So these guys, messy hair and ponytail.
Messy hair?
Or, uh...
Sure.
I don't know.
I don't even know what to call that.
What?
A single strand?
Hello.
When can we start sending the Aka Supas?
Why are you so eager to do that?
But also, I think it might be...
I think it might be a little wild because YouTube says that
I need more watch hours.
So even after today's stream, I'm not so sure.
Okay.
So Pru.
Wait.
And so these are the guys, too.
Daiso?
Thank you.
Oh, my gosh.
He's just got so much charisma.
You know?
Sure.
Thank you, sir.
Oh, my gosh.
Wait, it's literally the opposite.
Hello.
It's the opposite of last time.
Okay, by me.
Don't be shy.
Sure.
Okay, it's the other side.
Oh, my God.
Hello.
Okay.
Hip hip zoobini!
I love, I love the, this is okay, this is where the cool
kids club, look how cool they look and this is everybody
else.
The narrator is the best guy ever.
Hip hip hip zoobini!
And so our brave travelers continue on through this dusty
wasteland until they meet Arno, the almost omnivorous.
one very hungry pizza troll.
One hungry pizza troll.
Fleeings?
You're not fleens.
I think we're still on easy mode.
Whatever you are.
Make me a pizza.
Okay.
Oh, it's up to you, buddy.
All right, we're gonna go down the line.
Actually, we're gonna make this a little interesting.
You know, we're gonna try two combos at once.
Something on that I don't like.
Sometimes he will actually just get like a plain ass, like
no cheese pizza.
He said the thing.
More, more, more, more, more, more, more, more, more, more,
more.
Okay.
He's begging for it.
Sorry, mister.
Okay, so he doesn't like mushrooms.
More, more, more, more, more, more, more, more, more, more,
more, more, more, more, more.
That's how you really get the girls, you know?
I'm supposed to be working, but this child's game is too
engaging.
Go work.
Okay.
Bellbuckers.
Wow, only three children.
He tries!
I think we're a genius.
You've done quite well.
Thank you.
Oh, sorry narrator.
Ah, base cap one.
What's this?
Okay, bye bye.
Nope.
We are no time to stop, Zubinis.
No, no rest.
No rest allowed.
There's no sense leaving it up to chance.
Lower the fleens off the tree branch.
The fleens are the guys actually trying to kill us.
The fleens?
These guys.
These guys are actually trying to kill us.
Woo, woo, woo, woo.
Okay, so...
So, you have to put a guy out and have...
I don't remember how this one goes.
I think certain traits a Zumbini has will have a certain guy
jump off.
But you need these guys to jump.
I don't remember how this one...
Wait, Yulman.
There's no sense leaving it up to chance.
Lure the fleens off the tree branch.
Oh, yeah, we are not so easy.
Feeling stuck?
Wait, no.
No, we're going to...
We're gonna get this ourselves.
We don't, we don't, I'm sorry, I didn't read it.
You are fleens.
No, we're not.
The tree guy just said fleens.
You're not fleens.
We're Zubini's.
We're not the fleens.
These are the fleens.
They are so high tech for like, is this, is this Metal Gear?
I like that sound.
Man, I hated this one.
I don't remember how it works, so...
No, no, Scrooky.
Scrooky, get behind me.
Scrooky, goodbye.
Scrooky, stay back there.
Okay, we're gonna get a Floak.
Okay, so basically we only have a couple chances because
they're gonna slide eventually and fall off the thing.
So...
Maybe...
it was either her glasses or the color of her nose or okay
so aggressive I know the fleens are crazy let's try one
completely different
okay the hair is correct the hair was correct yes oh okay so
we need you like Agla.
Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
So, we need...
No.
No, no, Skruki.
No, no, no.
I won't allow it.
Uh-oh.
Oh, that's right.
Wait, how am I supposed to get the right?
No, Scrookie.
No, no, Scrookie.
Daiso!
Oh!
Scrookie, no!
Yep, because it's the same.
legs.
Oh my god.
No.
Scrookey.
Scrookey has to go.
He's looking around.
He doesn't even want to look at me.
He's so scared.
He's like, mom, mom, what are you picking me up for?
Mom, why are you leading me over into the danger zone?
Mom, mom, I'm scared.
No, Please, please, Mom, you said you would protect me!
Scrooky!
Here comes the awesome music, yeah?
Yeah!
All right, Scrooky in the lead!
Nice.
Hurry, zoom penis!
Oolah, the forest's foremost.
and perhaps only, band leader is about to begin rehearsals.
She'll be closing the hotel for the night, so scamper into a
room.
Okay, we believe in Skrookie.
I don't remember how this one was.
Yes.
Ah, yes.
I'll be right down.
Make yourself cozy.
Yeah, but you're also picky.
Just when I was starting rehearsal.
You're just in time for tomorrow's concerto.
Okay.
Help yourselves to a room.
I got rehearsal.
Go ahead.
Find yourselves a room.
Where did she go?
Why did she talk to over herself even?
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Okay, so...
Alright?
Oh my god, who's sharing a room with Screw Key tonight?
Oh!
No!
Oh.
And we do have, like, a kind of...
That clock is terrifying.
Oh my gosh.
The clock is giving, like, over-the-garden-wall vibes.
It's so scary.
Let's put you over here.
Oh.
Is it the eyes?
Okay.
I don't remember what.
Is it the eyes?
Is it eyes?
Is it just eyes?
Is that it?
Is it so simple?
Am I overthinking it?
How do I do it with everything?
I think so.
because there's only this yeah there's only five slides I
guess I could have made it anything maybe I could have made
it eyes I could have made it hair I sorry my my said hair
and so I put him in there oh Rian is all by themselves so
Sorry.
Oh my god, it's spooky.
Just look at the time.
Gotta split.
See you in the morning.
This is the paint splatter one!
Strike the targets one and all and watch for a pattern on
mud ball walls.
Mud Ball Wall.
Best minigame.
You guys like this one?
The sounds in this one are immaculate.
Oh.
Oh!
Did you hear that?
My God.
It's so good.
Wait, I don't remember how to do this one, though.
Wait, I don't remember how this one works.
So we pick a color.
Oh my God.
a shape and we have to hit like here right i hate it so much
really you don't like it i kind of love it i don't remember
okay so we'll figure out let's see red nice okay so this is
the star area is this triangle let's just try it no and also
we need to figure out what this row is oh okay so it's
yellow something yellow square I'm calling it now for the
three or this three never mind oh wait we could do diamond
Nice.
Alright.
Get in there guys.
Hurry up.
Of the demo I played as a kid, this was my favorite.
They all had a demo of this.
They had a demo of this.
Nice.
I love how...
conflicted the chat is on um on uh these these sounds it's
so funny okay i think we can we basically have all the
information we need to to complete this piece of cake baby
well except for this one everything else piece of cake
have no idea how this works okay so each row is a color and
each column is a shape so you just have to see these are
star shapes these are triangle shapes see it's not so let's
try green i don't know i'm feeling green oh okay this is a
wild guess i think i'm getting a wild streak like a little I
think it might be pink.
Genius.
Nailed it.
And look, and you run out of ink.
See here?
You can run out, so it could be... Oh my gosh.
Can you imagine if Scrooky was left behind?
I don't even want to think about the plot.
I don't even think about the thought yay well done no wise
and trusted guide thank you i'm wise and trusted you guys
i'm wise and trusted
how do you get ink refills you don't if you run out of ink
you just have to leave them behind
it's coast so hard amazing indeed she's gonna have to stay
here relaxing campsite ready and waiting for zoom bini's
she's she's she's watching over the camp you know journey is
yet to come
Swap her in?
Nah, she's good.
Throughout these gloomy mountains, strange carvings left by
ancient peoples are everywhere.
Spooky.
Oh my gosh.
Okay, next time we play this, we're going to go on hard.
Should we...
We'll just go on the hardest mode, I think.
Oh!
What the heck is that?
Oh, those are the hair.
So it's like this hair.
We have a lot of these guys.
We have so many single hairs.
And then ponytail.
Right?
That is a pony.
And this is the high.
Okay, okay.
We have one pony.
Oh, two ponytails.
And we have...
Actually, I want to see.
Oh, they don't need to be...
connected to one another to one another so that makes things
so much easier I was making things more difficult on myself
than it really needed to be I think you all know who's gonna
be in the front our man Scroogey wait his name is Scroogey I
thought his name was Scroogey it's Scroogey this whole time
you lied to me you did it you saved I thought it was
Scroogey What?
Just Sruki?
She finally noticed.
Use the crystal filters to change the Zumbini's reflection.
It will give them crystal slamming protection.
Let's just pretend he's still Sruki.
Girl, boss, gaslit herself.
I cannot believe that I just...
That I just made that up.
I stole their identity, like I stole...
This whole time, they probably just like...
She can't even get my name right.
Gosh, this mid girl sucks.
She can't even...
read sorry yeah he's still scrooky in our hearts right guys
scrooky scrooky scrooky scrooky scrooky literacy is
overrated true so true bestie
Sruki in the streets.
Sruki did have that.
Wait, we need to ask who was it her?
Koldio.
How was he in the in the hotel room?
I wonder.
Hmm.
Um...
Yo.
Thanks for the doughnut!
Edutainment games proving its value by finally teaching
victory.
Just notice that you had a messy...
Sorry, I missed this one earlier, AJ.
You have messy hair, sunglasses, red nose, spring zoomini in
your party.
This one?
That combo was always my favorite as a kid.
I think his name was Ida Wonka.
even remember his name wow true Zumbini fan my favorite
combo was uh glasses and this hair and the um either the
roller skates or the um or the two wheels like that that was
my favorite combo because i i always thought it looked like
me you finally acknowledge me after all this time I'm so
sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Um...
Favorite hair color?
You can't change the hair color.
Right?
Um...
Oh, that's your favorite!
Oh, nose color!
Oh, it was blue!
It's blue.
Why does this get more difficult for me?
The less Zumbinis I have.
Why can't I find him?
Hello?
Oh, there you are.
Hip, hip, zoomini.
It's so funny.
uh beady eyes little beady guy i don't remember this eye i
style in the original why is the narrator so awesome he's so
funny he's like he's kind of like if the guy from the
stanley parable like was in a good game and like happy about
it you know not to say wait that makes it sound like this
wait oh oops that makes it sound like the stanley parable is
not a good game oh wait i was right it is a good game
but you know what i mean this makes me feel like he's like
oh yeah i'm enjoying my life now it's stanley parable i
should play it
the last time i tried playing it the game crashed on me so i
never actually got to beat it
search first for traps so easy to miss they are easy to get
zoom bennies across bubble wonder abyss
thanks for the don't know when i was a kid my mom would buy
these big styrofoam eggs from the craft store and i'd paint
them from them blue and decorate them like zoom bennies We
found one under the porch when my parents moved from a
family home when they retired 30 years later.
Oh my gosh.
That's insane.
Wait, this is the same exact pattern as before.
Okay, so all our scruffy heads.
Scruffy.
I'm going to turn this one down because it does hurt.
Scruffy
Scruffy All right, first Pony Right, she goes Yeah Yeah,
ponytail first Pony Wait Uh oh Uh oh uh-oh wait uh-oh uh-oh
well the scruffies have to go this way because if they go
this way they will immediately go in so they have to go the
other way but uh-oh we have a lot of single men um I
think it'll work out oh we do have another ponytail We do
have another ponytail.
Okay.
I missed you, Apooh.
I think I've missed you several times.
Not bad.
Thanks for the tunnel.
Happy to see you streaming again.
Thank you so much.
Okay.
Go, e-ble-ble.
Go e-ble-ble.
Okay.
we're fine we're fine everybody we're fine we're fine we're
fine i'm single by choice yeah
you then
last but not least so prue
i'm single by choice not mine oh no don't worry about being
single is fine you know it's being it's fine too right you
got them all through i did good for you good for me
thanks narrator
is this it could this be the place they've been seeking a
place of hope and prosperity.
Prosperity.
Oh my gosh, I can't believe I deprived you of that
magnificent performance originally.
I'm so sorry.
Zumbini.
Oh, we got a school and little houses.
A school house.
So it's the Zumbini's who flushed the finicky fleens and in
hotel dementia.
had pleasant dreams and catapulted cleanly over mudball wall
what else what's this one this bowling alley honors I love
how we just escape like this terrible situation that the
Zumbinis are in and their first thought is just like um yeah
we need a bowling alley like maybe a supermarket like you
guys gotta eat or something like nah bowling alley did not
lag in lion's layer solve the secrets of the mirror machine
and flew above bubble wonder abyss thank you for the rain
thank you so much thank you really appreciate it hope you
had a good stream
Thank you.
We're playing Zumbinis.
So the Zumbinis finally reached their new home.
They established a nation of Zumbinis for Zumbinis.
This independent nation would later be known to...
Very nice, isn't it?
But don't you have a job to do?
Zumbinis to free...
Did he just say this is good, isn't it?
You can't just say that in front of me.
Alright, guys.
How do I change the difficulty?
How do I make it more difficult?
Options?
No.
Oh, we have on-screen captions?
I should have done that before.
Hmm.
Do I have to do it on practice?
Oh!
Very, very hard.
Oh my god.
I'm scared.
I don't think I've ever done it this hard before.
Now we're doing difficult mode.
We don't know a single...
We can't, we can't, we can't cater to our...
Actually, hold on.
I'll make my favorite, though.
Okay.
There we go.
Okay, the rest are all random.
There, they...
Why do they all look the same?
Okay, stop it.
Ding.
Can't remember a single day in Hotel Dementia for some
reason.
Go for it, I believe in your mint.
Okay.
Let's go.
I didn't change it.
Wait.
What do you mean I didn't change it?
it's on very hard oh but here see it won't let me change it
i'm clicking i'm clicking but it won't let me change it oh
oh oh sorry sorry i didn't mean to abandon you guys okay how
am i supposed to change it oh they level up the more you do
it so this is just me practicing the each one okay i get it
i get it i have to grind to get to very very hard I'm so
curious though.
How is it so hard on the pizza one?
Okay, let's just do the prep.
Pizza for lunch and snack and dinner and dessert.
Baby would satisfy me.
Pizza time.
Okay.
Satisfy me.
So let's look at what's NG.
There is no ice cream.
Okay, ice cream by itself is NG.
So it's gotta be chocolate ice cream.
It's gotta be chocolate ice cream.
Cheese.
Doesn't like mushrooms.
Here, let's just try a bell pepper.
Make me a pizza.
Something must go.
Oh, okay.
That topping, not for meatbags.
Not for meatbags.
Uh-oh.
Okay.
Maybe it's not even the cheese.
They don't all like the same thing.
There's stuff on that I don't like.
Sorry!
That topping?
No.
Uh-oh.
I feel so much pressure right now.
Okay, so maybe it...
Okay.
Just the pineapple?
Don't kick him out.
More!
That topping?
Not for me, thanks.
Uh-oh.
Okay, so it's...
Probably...
Okay, so she doesn't like pineapple at all.
Wait, so maybe...
Can I do like a pineapple...
Like sausage?
Oh no, I forgot the chocolate!
Oh no.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
There's stuff on that I don't like!
Why do you not like the vanilla ice cream by itself?
But you're fine with it with chocolate!
Something's wrong!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Didn't like the peppers.
No, I don't think he liked the cheese.
Something must go.
There's something there I won't eat.
Uh-oh, there's something on that I don't want.
The guy on the right looks like he would, like, put his
fingers together and be like, Oh, go me, ooh.
Maybe it's sausage.
Just peppers, I think?
No, but he liked the pineapple.
He didn't like just the peppers, right?
We tried that.
No pineapple.
But this guy likes the pineapple.
She doesn't like pineapple, I think.
Some of those toppings are distasteful.
Don't punch him.
Gee, I wasn't expecting that one.
Gee, don't punch him.
Oh, okay.
More toppings!
Okay.
That topping, no.
That topping?
that's not good don't punch him okay they're so mean okay
this this is his combo right this is his combo it has to be
he said more toppings
please Don't get it!
What do you mean?
I don't like it!
No.
Something's wrong.
You wanted more.
He hates the cheese.
Uh-oh.
I think we're...
Oh!
Wait, can the dessert be...
Oh, it can be combined too!
Okay, so I think he likes the pizza as is.
Maybe he wants this.
Because this is bad, right?
Something must go.
What?
That topping?
Not for me, thanks.
Something's wrong.
Bunk.
Oh my god, he's gonna get punched.
It's kind of funny to watch him.
Oh, it's so good.
Is this it?
okay we got one this guy is so ridiculous yay oh my gosh
okay so we know she doesn't like a pizza she doesn't like
the pineapple this thing is gonna be so full by the end oh
my gosh it's tricky with so many different types of toppings
why they weren't kidding when they said very very hard it is
so hard mm-hmm so let's see I don't remember which ones are
my creation creations and which one are I don't know the
graveyard of lost pizzas I know hmm just plain and
everything I know right what do you like hmm
just I'm just gonna try it because I don't know what her
opinion is on the peppers some of those toppings are
distasteful it's still missing my favorites okay so he likes
the peppers
Okay, okay.
What didn't he like?
Oh gosh, I was only paying attention to him.
Maybe this.
You like that?
There's something there I hate.
This isn't about you!
Gee, I wasn't expecting that one.
We're going through them pretty quickly now.
My gosh.
Okay, it is so...
I can't remember what his opinion was on this one.
I don't know.
Do any of them like cheese?
Let's try this.
Do you like cheese, mister?
Do you like cheese?
Ah!
I don't care!
May I have more, please?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay.
Thank God this is just practice.
They're getting massacred.
This is so sad.
Do you want a little topping?
You want that?
This is making me want pizza.
Something's wrong.
What the?
The way he says it kind of annoys me.
What do you guys think?
What would you, what are you, what are you, what are your
ideas?
Hmm.
Sounds like he's mocking her.
I know, right?
Something's wrong, sprinkles.
Sprinkles.
I don't know.
I think I just gave him that one, right?
topping no uh-oh uh-oh someone says mushroom is missing does
he like mushroom let's just try it
something's wrong for me oh nice oh my gosh you were so
right good job good job good job good job okay She hates
everything!
I honestly have no idea what she wants.
Like, do you want just a plain pizza?
I don't understand what she wants.
An empty, give her a whole plane.
Alright, this one's for you!
So carefully crafted.
Is that all I get?
Yes!
Because you don't like anything else!
So she hates pineapple.
She hates peppers.
Maybe it's just cheese.
Just cheese.
Let's try just cheese.
There's something there I hate.
Oh my god, it's a pizza.
It's just a pizza.
My god.
She hates cheese.
uh this is ridiculous i don't even know just this just give
her yeah is this all you want you want your no way
what no way comrades would make their way back she just got
like a soup
Oh my gosh, we made it through, though.
I...
What?
Psychopath behavior right there.
Wow.
Wow, that one was really tricky, though.
It was fine.
Let's try something else.
Let's try another one.
Let's try the frogs.
I do remember the fairy.
I do remember, but I don't remember...
What was that?
thing.
I... Ooh, what is that thing?
What are you doing?
What is that thing?
I don't... Oh!
Oh!
Oh, I think I need to hurry!
Wait, what is that thing?
What is that thing?
Ah!
What's it doing?
Oh no!
I think it found the path and now it's taken over it.
leave.
I don't know what the magic wand does.
The pink, unfortunately, does not work.
Blue does not work.
Red does not work.
Yellow does not work.
These things are so annoying!
Try it out.
Oh, wait.
Maybe it will Well, um, what was one that was close?
This one?
Oh.
Oh my god.
Hurry.
Oh, we're fine.
Oh.
Go.
This game is so souls-like.
No.
Oh my gosh.
No, please.
Let's get over.
No, no, no.
Oh, no.
No.
Oh, he's following us.
Ew, he's creepy, creepy, creepy, creepy.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Oh, wait, what's gonna happen with them?
No!
Okay, no.
Oh, oh, oh my gosh.
It worked!
it ended up working out we got so lucky wait so with the
magic wand can I like like say if I want to move this one
and this one oh I can interesting there's a little I think I
see like the magic running out
why is that zoom Bean, they look weird.
I guess they all kind of look weird.
Uh-oh.
Oh, oh, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice.
Nice, nice, nice.
Why does he Fortnite dance?
Because he's excited.
Let him do his thing.
Don't judge.
Oh, I can also make the yellows work.
Okay.
Bing, bing, bing, bing.
Yeah, though.
What exactly is the puzzle here?
Okay.
So there's multiple types of paths that you can do depending
on what the frog is, right?
So the first one is by color.
The second is by the shape of the lily pad.
See, four, four.
Moon, moon, moon, moon.
I gotta give moon.
Moon, moon.
And the third is the type of the flower that's on the lily
pad.
Moon, moon.
There's just so much info on the screen right now.
I think that's why I like this one so much.
There's so much that you can like look at.
I hate these things.
I've never seen these before.
Clearly, I suck at the game as a child because I never got
this far.
Uh-oh.
No, no.
No.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, oh, no.
A traffic jam!
These ones, these guys are blocked up too!
They're blocking the blue path that I just made!
Uh-oh.
Guys.
Do I even have enough magic to finish the path for them?
They get clogged here.
Oh, it stops it.
Let's just do...
This one.
Goodbye!
Sayonara!
There you go.
There they go.
Yeah, yeah.
There we go.
Wait.
Why are you going back?
Okay.
Yeah?
Move.
Oh my god.
You're supposed to go forward.
Oh no.
He's too slow.
No!
Oh no no no no no!
Oh my gosh.
You.
They're all coming back.
They're all coming They're all coming back Oh my gosh No No
please Oh no
Please just leave Oh my gosh I don't think he's gonna leave
in time They're too slow They're too slow Oh no no no no
Wait Please leave Oh my god Existence is paid Oh my gosh,
please.
Oh, hot frog.
We made it.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, sweet.
Release.
Oh, my gosh.
Ooh.
Hip, hip.
Zoom-hity.
I don't even...
What other path can I take?
Which seat can I take?
I think I screwed everything up by using the magic wand too
much.
I played God and I'm...
I played God and I...
I'm regretting it.
I shouldn't have done it.
Oh my gosh.
Aqua blue?
Oh, you're right.
Did I make that one or...
Being God is suffering.
I wonder how many crabs are here.
I wonder how many crabs we can accumulate before we crash
the game.
Do they just end up be spawning or...
How many crabs can we grab?
I want to take that path, but I can't.
Oh my gosh, they just keep coming.
You can tell there's new ones because they're...
These guys just giving up.
They don't even move.
They don't care anymore.
There's only one way to know.
what else can we what else do we have here X oh flower the
flower could maybe work I gotta use my I gotta play God
again oh
wait where did it start where did I start the flower at did
I just mess up i'm an idiot i think i'm dumb you guys i
think i'm stupid hey
we we regained we regained we regained we we it's fine and
flower
is this modded modded zoom beanies only for the hardcore
Zumbini is fans.
Yeah.
You know.
Wait, what is that guy doing?
What are you doing?
Oh my gosh, I think they've...
I think they've...
Oh, nope, never mind.
They're still coming.
Hmm.
Mod Zumbini's into Wisps?
Oh my gosh, that'd be crazy.
What one was it?
The flower?
There we go.
Oh no.
Wait, there might be a clash.
Oh, okay.
It's fine.
He'll make it back.
I think...
I don't think I like this mini-game anymore.
Okay, let's go to another one.
Because this one...
The crabs are too much for me.
No, no, don't do it.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Back up.
Back off.
Oh.
Silence.
Finally.
No more brain-scritching sounds.
I'm just so curious what some of these other, like, puzzles
would be, like, super hard.
You know what I mean?
Like, what's this one?
Well,
what do we have here?
Okay, so, wait, so...
Go ahead and sit wherever you want to.
I don't really care.
So, like, they would have to have something...
Ah, and then they would...
Ah, oh my...
I don't think it's cross.
I don't think it's cross, luckily.
But, like, that...
Oh, wait.
No, she doesn't have a red...
Oh, my gosh.
Wait, this one works, though.
This one works.
Does this one...
Does this one go for the...
Wait, hmm?
I guess just this.
Ah, sure.
I'm going by nose color currently.
I wasn't in the beginning, but now I am.
Nose, nose.
Nose.
That's our only pink.
There you go, you got it.
What nose?
What are you talking about?
They all have noses.
Don't give me your sass.
No!
You're so cute all soaking wet.
Oh, okay.
I was gonna say, is he gone?
Hey, Mint out of curiosity, did you ever play a game called
Virtual Villagers?
I remember playing this game and Virtual Villagers a lot as
a kid.
I've never played Virtual Villagers.
No.
I had not played Virtual Villagers.
Played that.
Sure.
I think I screwed up with her.
See, but this one won't work.
Crabs alive.
What does that mean?
Oh my gosh, this one's hard.
This one.
Crabs alive.
This one's hard.
Don't like how the fish looks?
I just noticed them!
Ew!
Hmm.
Minecraft villager.
detal- Crave die!
Hmm.
Trying to figure out, like, what would be the easiest, like,
thing to focus on, you know?
Okay, redo, redo, redo, redo, redo.
Redo, redo, redo.
He's floating.
These poor guys don't even have names.
That's so sad.
Practice Zumbini one.
Okay, practice Zumbini.
and sit wherever you want to.
I don't really care.
Starting from the center.
So if I'm like, okay, let's just place these guys kind of
randomly.
Oh, oh, she works, but you.
Ah, sure.
And you are four.
And they each have different eyes.
Wait, this kind of works.
This kind of works, maybe.
Maybe.
Okay.
Is this...
Ah, no.
Wait, wait, no, which one does this go with?
How?
Oh, I see, I see, I see, I see, I see, I see.
I see, I see, I see.
Ah, sure.
Um, hmm.
The nose color always throws me off because it's like the
last thing I look at.
Um, red nose, Rudolph, the red nose, near you have nothing
in common hmm
oh no no oh
my gosh it's delay thank you praise the sun oh these
animations are nuts i know the one thing that like really
like it's so impressive to me and looking at like stuff like
Freddy fish is just how much the like the game is like all
animated I'm going to be out here hey calm down mister I'm
I'm thinking okay my brain runs a little more slowly I
wonder instead in the center maybe I should do the nose
colors because I feel like that might be the where'd he go
oh like if it's There you go, you got it.
I like red.
No, but they don't have nothing in common.
Ah!
They have nothing in common.
Oh.
I was like, oh no.
I think I just sacrificed her.
You.
Ah, sure.
To the crabs you go.
Crab's alive.
The crabs are alive with the taste of blood.
I never understood what this wanted us to do.
You have to, so the person next to them has to have one
matching feature.
Sorry, Zumbini.
Next to them has to have one matching feature.
So in this case, it would be like either the hair or the
nose color or the feet or the eyes.
Well, that's the only things that can match.
All aboard.
I'm getting bored.
up what wait no I'm so confused they have the same feet what
but they have the same
feet diagonal counts no wait wait okay hold on I'm gonna
test this it does go no diagonal does count.
That's so evil.
What?
I think the board is effed.
It's supposed to be a 4x4 board but it's all stacked.
That's what's confusing me about it.
So that's why I was just like, okay, I was counting them
because I was just like, okay, so even though it kind of
looks like it would go to this one, it goes to this one
because it's the third one.
But it's not It's very confusing.
Oh my gosh.
Wait, so because like this one, does it go to all three?
It must.
And then this one goes to two.
This one goes to three or two?
I can't tell.
It's like a hex board.
A hex board.
Yeah, this is very, very hard.
Wow.
Wait, so if it's just hard, is it like a regular grid?
It's very, very hard.
This is for children?
This is for...
There you go, you got it.
This is for babies?
Are you sure?
Oh my gosh.
Green nose.
Oh, oh, he didn't match with this guy.
Oh my god.
Oh my gosh.
Oh no, this feels impossible.
Is there actually...
There's only one way you could do this.
Might have to abandon some guys.
Hair?
Alternative title, only for baby geniuses.
So they must have at least one matching feature with
adjacent ones.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
yes that's that's that's that's the thing only one per seat
oh sorry you got it sorry no oh no because i at least he
came back thank you thanks for your generosity ah sure so
like her and then what even would match here oh maybe like a
cyclops no it's like i need a cyclops with a spring with
this hair it's so difficult this is too complicated next
puzzle what about Well, this one I feel like would be
impossible, like actually.
Hmm?
Wait, it's the exact same.
Hard crystal is fine, is it?
That's the one where you get to mix and match the Zumbinis,
right?
Mint realizes she can't do any very hard puzzle.
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm taste testing.
I'm seeing why each one is very, very hard, okay?
This one feels the exact same, though.
Am I...
This one feels the exact same.
So we need a roller skater.
You.
Oh, wait.
Oh, is that?
I...
Wait.
The nose.
Wait, but the nose...
Does the nose correspond with the skates or the eyes?
Does the nose color correspond...
Oh, geez.
Okay, hold on this one.
Okay.
Okay, the hair is completely different.
It's all mixed up.
It's all...
Everything is wrong.
Everything is wrong!
Okay, so the eyes are the hair.
So we need a scruffly hair with the booties.
The booties are...
Green?
I'm gonna guess this because I'm trying to get this guy it's
either this guy or this guy let's guess
this guy scruffed hair nose green yeah but both of them have
green noses let's do this one wait no this one yeah yeah
Okay, okay, okay.
So the first one, um, so its green nose corresponds to the
feet.
So we need a green nose and we need a yellow nose.
Right?
Green nose and yellow nose.
Mm-hmm.
hmm so i'm gonna separate you go over you everybody else go
over here green nose yellow nose and not scruffly hair oh
wait yes wait i'm forgetting what corresponded to what part
uh oh wait the hair corresponded to the eyes So, no scruffly
hair.
We need dotted eyes.
We need you.
Just kidding.
Oh, dang it, I got the hair.
Never mind.
Wait, no scruffly hair is what I said.
Wait.
Oh, it was this hair.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm so silly.
I got it wrong.
It's him, though.
It's him.
What?
We're gonna lose a few Zoombinis.
Is it not the...
Okay.
The green corresponds to the feet.
So it's her then?
Because...
Wait, what does the eyes correspond to then?
The hair.
The eyes correspond to the hair.
I can't keep track of this.
I need this written down.
I can't keep track of it in my brain.
I'm a visual person.
Okay, goodbye, goodbye, scruffled, scruffled hair, yellow
nose.
Oh.
He just walks off.
See ya.
Okay.
Alrighty, alrighty, alrighty, already, already, already,
already.
already the feet correspond with the nose color so what we
have all yellow thank you and we need the eye color or the
eye corresponds to the
to the hair it's her wait no hold on hold on hold on I'm so
confused.
Wait, I really need this written out for real.
I need this written out for real.
What went to the...
Wait, what changes the hair again?
What changes?
Yeah, take notes.
I need to.
My brain can't.
Oh my gosh.
Zumbini hair equals eyes.
So, okay, it's one of these guys.
Okay, it's not her.
It's one of these guys.
Feet.
Do we have any rollerblade guys?
We don't.
Feet become.
Feet.
No.
Wait, so...
Let's see.
What did that?
Feet change the nose color?
Is that what it is?
No.
Eyes change the nose color.
It must be, right?
Because they have the same.
But they...
Oh.
also have the same nose but also i think and then and then
what else can we change oh the legs legs determine some i
really need this right now i think it's the left boy hold on
i need to figure out why though if i what else is wait what
does uh what changes there hold on i'm writing this in a
hair equals feet for the zoom beanies eyes equals nose color
zoomini eyes equals nose color then then
then what changes the So, it would be...
What do all three...
Do these three have in common?
What do they have in common to get this hair color?
The nose is the feet?
Oh, you're right.
Oh, you're right, you're right, you're right.
Nose...
Wait, huh?
It's not the hair?
It goes with the... Wait.
No!
Oh!
Wait, wait, wait.
Nose...
Okay, sorry.
feet you're right yes Zumbini knows equals feet so what does
that leave I have oh I need Zumbini feet equals what do I
not have so the feet equals the hair but that doesn't make
any sense because these three have the same hair these guys
have nothing in common.
Seems like feet don't mean anything.
Thank you!
You see him, you strike me as the kind of ghost who grew up
with brain quest.
Confirm deny.
I don't know what brain quest is, so I guess I must deny.
Fleen hair is currently unbound.
Oh my gosh, so it's random?
So it's either, it's one of these guys?
Oh no It's just one of them We don't know I don't feel like
No way there's no logic to it Right like But seriously like
how could This hair And these three guys You know like That
doesn't make any sense
Okay guys Let's make a poll Let's make a poll Which What
Which Zumbini?
Left, right.
On the left, we have Roller Blade Madness.
He is insane.
He will do wheelies for hours.
He is always grinding every moment he gets Roller Blade
Madness.
On the left, I mean, sorry, on the right.
we have walk this guy can walk he is just
even the pole isn't sure then it's not just me ah man wait
so
hmm right's feet corresponds to fleeing cowboy boots no no
no Nelson Nelson Nelson You're living in the past.
This is the present.
We are on very, very hard.
Where all logic has been thrown out the window.
It is different here.
Why should not be either of these two?
Alright, 59% said left, so let's go with left.
Hey!
Okay, it's all the features!
It's all the features, but the hair.
No way, it's actually random.
Because look, this one goes to...
They have nothing in common!
Oh,
nice.
Sheesh!
That one was crazy.
Someone said the crystal one is...
Wait, did they say the crystal one was fun?
Oh yeah, yeah, with the...
Oh!
Wait.
Bing.
So we have to make...
Huh?
Oh!
Wait.
Huh?
Oh!
Do I have to wait for it to come back?
No!
That's not what I picked!
Huh?
Can you put one on the left as well?
That's a good question.
Oh, you can!
You can.
But I'm so concerned about it looking like it's yellow.
Oh, wait.
Oh, this is a combo.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on.
I don't know if it matters, but...
Now it's saying it's pink?
Okay.
Why is it changing colors?
Why can't you just be yellow?
This is so confusing.
The nose changed colors when you move spaces.
Yeah, it was yellow on this side.
So I think I have to get the right...
Com...
Oh, see, see, see, this is the right combination.
But there's no other...
Unless, unless it's...
No.
I gotta get the the wombo combo no?
Never mind?
But there's no other way to change the nose color.
Hmm?
I had it?
Oh, it's yellow!
Sorry.
Yes, it's yellow.
You're right, you're right, you're right.
Sorry, for some reason I was thinking a different color.
Okay, you're still right.
So that should do it what the who are you what a
stranger appeared you guys
i don't understand it at all i don't understand it at all
how am i supposed to do two hairs Saddles at once!
Try the question mark.
Things have changed as the path has become more difficult.
But the Zumbinis have faith in you, Brave Explorer.
You have all the information you need to complete this
challenge.
You get all your Zumbinis through.
Take your time.
Look for patterns and don't be afraid to make a few
mistakes.
Making mistakes is a life or death narrator.
If a few of our little blue friends are left behind, they'll
be waiting at Shade Tree to try again.
Use the crystal filters to change the Zumbinis reflection.
of them crystal slamming protection.
Okay, that doesn't, that doesn't make you feel any better.
These ones don't change.
There's, there's, I need a yellow, right?
For her.
What is going on?
What is happening?
How am I supposed to get this haircut?
It makes no sense.
No wonder I couldn't beat this.
It doesn't make any sense.
Am I... Am I... Am I
the...
No, I need a degree for this game.
Glasses plus nose and spring on left.
But why?
Also, does it matter?
Because it's red!
It's gonna make it red!
Two!
Thank you!
What?
I don't think I need the glasses.
Here, right?
I just need this?
Wait.
Oh, I see, I see, I see!
Okay, okay, hold on.
So, I need them to both have this hairstyle.
first of all because they're both gonna match the hair.
Okay.
okay, okay we don't need the nose because and we need the
spring.
So she is going to become like this.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Oh, but we need the actually we do need the nose.
Oh, shoot.
Wait, we do need the nose for her.
Can I do three?
Oh, I can.
Okay,
okay, this should be it.
This should be it.
Does it need to be in order or?
Yeah!
It doesn't need to be in order, clearly.
We cooked!
Yeah!
That one was...
This is crazy.
I get it now, though.
I get it.
So, okay.
Interesting.
God gamer.
This one's fine.
Okay, this one's actually pretty interesting.
Okay.
Okay, well, I'll just have the same hair.
Sounds good to me.
Now, just match these?
No.
Skates?
Hmm.
Big brain.
Probably matters the order of the mirrors.
It didn't seem like it before.
So I'm not quite sure.
Hmm.
Boom.
Wait, so I have a question.
I wonder if it, like, starts.
Wait.
Does it cycle through these?
Like, even when we're going through?
They wouldn't do that to us, right?
Okay.
We do definitely have to change the eyes.
Like so, for example, I do this.
No, that makes no sense.
Why are these ones flashing?
It makes me nervous.
Oh, because I can change it to something else.
Oh.
Front will replace the back.
It will.
Are we sure about that?
Wait, okay, so...
Hold on, I'm just gonna place some things on the side.
I'm just gonna place...
So if I have it...
Hair?
Wait, all we need for this one?
Okay.
If it's this...
first oh well this one's also never mind this one also is
gonna get the hair still need the eyes on the left yeah
you're right
boom this one turns into a plane this one oh oh oh oh ah uh
oh i think i'm breaking the game Is this the one I...
Wait, this one.
Take out.
My Oshi with the 998 IQ.
Think of it like Photoshop layers.
I think...
Ah, I...
Okay, I get it.
I get it.
I think.
But we need the eyes.
Here.
Okay.
but
well we only need okay essentially what I'm like struggling
with is this
one is this guy and this guy they have mostly matching
features we need the nose though ah ah ah ah
layer closest to the middle is the top layer yeah but i
think what i'm confused about is how it will work the second
round you know what i mean like
so the the spark will have so the first so i need this wait
will this last all ah ah ah
Yeah, the blocks won't change only the turntable and the
zombie needs.
So I need them to...
It feels like I need them to match on both sides.
Like, or have the same exact things.
But when I put the plates...
When I put these crystals down, they don't.
See?
We get a little propeller, man.
We get the...
Don't worry about the flashing.
Are you sure?
Okay.
Oh!
Okay, wait, I think I get it.
Okay, so because this is in front, it won't recognize the
wheel.
Right?
Is that what you...
Okay, so it'll be like, okay, the hair is on, the nose, and
this is on, and then the The eyes are on.
Ow!
So then, oh, oh, you guys, the game is breaking.
Oh no, he's stuck.
Oh, okay, we're good, we're good.
Okay.
No!
Uh-oh.
You guys, I think I broke the game.
I think I broke the game.
Oh, no.
Oh, we were so close right when I got it.
Right when I understood.
We, I'm, no.
Oh.
Okay, I'm going to try anyway.
It made a noise.
Who is that?
Wait, what?
Why is...
It changed the hair to the girl's hair!
Why?
What?
I think the game broke a little.
It was this hair before!
Okay.
Okay, let's redo, redo, redo, redo.
Redo, redo, redo, redo.
Okay.
No, the nose is fine.
Um.
Well, just to...
Does it matter if I...
What legs I do?
I guess.
I guess it wants me to do these.
Okay.
Because it gave me two of them.
Does this look correct?
It gives us the eyes.
The...
Two!
Thank you.
That looks correct.
Oh!
Yippee!
Wait, why does it have a pink nose?
Where did the green nose go?
You know what?
It's fine.
They made it through.
Okay.
Let's see.
Let's see what the other hair is.
Okay.
What's the glasses?
on the side?
Sad.
What was it on the side?
Glasses.
Okay, we...
Sad.
How logical are these Zumbini's chat?
There is something going on here.
I'm not going to play for too much longer.
Actually, you know what?
Because I do want to see a few of the other things on the
super hard let's go back um sorry i meant very very hard
we're like at the hardest like the this one it's the exact
same
it's the exact same maybe it's like tinier traits that he
likes and dislikes okay never mind yes but trickier i think
these ones are gonna be the same.
This one I know has a lot more rooms.
What?
Hello?
Guess what?
We're going on tour.
But thanks to you and your cousins, this place has grown.
You are too much.
Mwah!
Can't drop down right now, but have fun.
It's better than having none.
I didn't expect this many rooms.
Oh my god!
I've never seen this many rooms before.
What if I just stick you here?
But they all, they went into the...
This one is in half, though.
Why are there so many rooms?
What?
Huh?
Thank you!
Oh!
Did you see the first episode of the Blue Archive anime?
Yes, I watched it.
I actually watched it earlier.
I watched it before stream.
Oh my gosh.
They're so cute.
The opening is so cute.
It's 5x5x5.
Yeah, but...
Wait, is it already starting to get darker?
Is the time limit so much...
Like, it's so funny because you could see where it's like
the line of...
darkness but they also not showing you the clock but yeah
the blue archive anime is so cute that opening is so cute oh
they're so cute that's super duper cute i'm just gonna put
at random this is so this is so bizarre oh i did it is it
it's not by nose color unless it's by nose color and
something else but i'm locking up soon better get indoors
already ma'am i haven't even ula the forest foremost and
perhaps only band leader is about to begin rehearsals she'll
be closing the hotel for the night so scamper into a room
things have changed as the path has become more difficult
but the zoom meetings have faith in you brave explorer you
have all the information you need to complete this challenge
and kick your zoom meetings through I do?
I do?
I have all the information?
Do I actually?
Ow!
What about, like, you?
Okay.
Next one.
Let's see.
Oh, this one probably would be...
Wait, what is this?
Oh, the color of the star, too?
Oh.
Oh, wait.
Lucky us.
Wait.
No, no, no.
Oh, my gosh.
Let's just try pink.
This one's insane.
Thanks for showing us your childhood game.
blue archive love yes oh my gosh yeah it was so cute it was
really fun seeing like some of the um like the other
characters like the like the delinquent girls and things
like that them kind of in motion and everything it was it
was fun it was really cute so what what does
to be okay wait it's got to be green because I think it
corresponds to this grid right the five by five and so it's
the first one so it's gonna be star maybe let's try paint no
not pink yellow red No.
Blue.
Oh, wait, green!
Oh, wait, this...
I did the wrong one.
Green here.
I'm silly.
Wait,
then what's on the third row?
but I was right about the first column being the green it's
just classic splat dot wave so it's it's correct about the
green being here and the blues here what determines it down
here though is the question is the big Q a big question try
different shape but then why would this shape go there wait
the shapes are all messed up too wait are the shapes all
wacky whack-a-doodle too yeah i think they're different for
each one oh my gosh we did it
nice i think they're different for each one Because if I did
like a square here, would it go up there?
Let's test it out.
This is our...
No, I can't be wasting ink.
So this is a triangle down here for this, too.
Oh, not...
Oh, I was like, don't go wasting ink!
Huh?
What?
Oh yeah, I completed it.
I completed it and I'm doing hard mode for funsies.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm just testing out what the...
I think the shapes can't be in the same column.
Like, what is the pattern here?
There's obviously the color which we got.
Are they di...
No, they're not diagonal.
...
It feels so random.
So the one next to it can't be touching the same shape.
Is that what you guys are saying?
Like a Sudoku?
Kind of.
Ink don't...
What?
We ran out of ink so fast.
They don't even let you experiment a little.
No way!
Okay, so pink.
Let's try and get this next three.
but how will i
i figured this game would only have like 10 games total i'm
shocked that you're still playing it i'm going i'm going
through stuff i'm going through it no just um you have all
the info you need okay so maybe it's not a circle then thank
you so much thank you thank you thank you and uh oh so it's
gonna be red is the only one So close, so close.
Oh my gosh.
Square?
How would it, why would it be square?
You were right though.
But why?
The shape is two to the right and one up.
Huh?
I think we're out of ink.
Oh, we get one more shot.
We could save two more.
Or maybe.
Let's do the green because we know this one.
And it's red inside.
Mint is loading.
I need, hold on, isn't there a thing for this?
One second.
I think there's a...
Ah.
Wait.
Yeah, I got it.
this this this it's triangle
green yeah it's always gonna be yeah green sphere red
triangle why is it triangle though how are you guys so good
at this for this one we save the final tool No more ink
left.
Yes, Zumbinis were left behind.
But the knowledge was gained.
Press on Brave Explorer.
Oh no!
Yes, Zumbinis were left behind.
Oh my gosh, they encourage you to leave them.
What about this one, I wonder?
Oh, okay, anyway.
This one actually looks kind of fun.
I'm not gonna lie.
There's also, I knew, I remember there being another one up
here.
What is this?
What does this do?
What are these?
Wait, what happened?
Galaxy hole.
The music is like making my...
was not like this before was it this is new music i don't
think i've ever heard this before also how are you supposed
to just go across is that even possible i'm gonna send no
i'm not gonna send someone to their doom wait can i get you
over there oh how do i get you over there
did it play robocop for a moment What's this thing on the
left?
This is the thing that creates the bubbles.
What is the...
Okay, I'm going to test this because I want to know...
What the yellow and the...
What all this does?
I want to know what the green does.
I want to know what the yellow does.
Oh, wait.
Maybe it...
Aha.
It does.
Okay, what does the green do?
Huh?
Are you stuck?
Uh-oh.
I think my Zoombini is trapped.
If I push her...
Oh, maybe I can, like, push her over.
Maybe?
Let's send, uh...
I feel like some of these, I have to...
When I do them, it sends them to their doom.
Hmm.
Send another one?
Oh wait, I think I just uh...
Uh oh.
Goodbye!
Sayonara!
Let's try, um, this way.
Look, now we're safe.
Yeah.
Here we go.
Push.
Push her, push, push.
Dumbini's.
Oh.
You murdered her!
You murderer!
You!
You killed her!
I cannot believe the...
This is...
I'm disgusted.
I'm disgusted in this display right now.
even i can't even i can't i cannot even deal with these zoom
vines any longer hold on i want to see this one huh it
doesn't tell you it just says you figure it out that's very
hard mode it just doesn't tell you that is so funny thank
you where do the zoom vines go when they get accident lead.
They go back to camp.
It's fine.
They're fine.
I like the music in that one.
What one haven't we seen?
This one?
I think it's probably the same as like the bridge.
I think we've seen everything else.
Very cool.
They go to the shadow realm.
Crystal?
We did the crystal one too.
That was fun.
What a blast from the past.
Hold on.
I am going to go here.
Hello.
Oh,
I am too slow.
Ouch!
Stop it!
Let me close out of Zoom Viennese real quick.
Let me put on some BGM and give me a second.
BGM.
bgm bgm bgm
uh hold on i have to make sure it's there we go
thank you guys for for uh whatever that that brain battle
battle of the wits up in here
that was so fun oh my gosh that was so much fun it was
awesome revisiting that for sure my brain hurts from some of
those I didn't expect the very very hard to be as difficult
as it was But they surpassed my expectations entirely.
Good job showing off your mighty brain cell.
Thank you.
I know, you might be intimidated.
You might be intimidated by how well I was able to perceive
things.
But you too can become my level at some point.
Thanks for streaming, Mint.
Thank you.
Thanks for the stream.
I will be reading donations out.
So if you're going to head out, see you later.
Tomorrow I have off because the podcast will be released.
So, yeah.
And, mm-mm.
Podcast Mondays.
Yippee!
That really made me want pizza more than anything.
I'm buying this game now.
Completely missed it way back when.
Thanks for the stream, Minty.
Of course.
I think it's going to be an uptick in Zumbini sales maybe.
It is very fun, though.
And it's...
I didn't realize.
I never noticed.
that on the map it showed like how many Zumbinis were left
on Zumbini Island yeah, but Zumbini Island right and then
you move them to no Zumbini Island wait Zumbini Isle is the
new one right Zumbini Pachinko machine I hope never no yeah
Zumbini Island to Zumbini that's right Zumbini island to
Zumbiniville.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
what happens when you get all to the island?
I have no idea, because I think as a kid, I never noticed
that there was an amount.
But I always just played it.
I don't even know.
Maybe that's a new edition from the original game.
Who knows?
But as a kid, I just never noticed it.
Yeah.
I got to squeeze in a run to the Thanks!
No problem!
Let's get this off my head.
Goodbye!
Goodbye, goodbye.
Here, let's put something else on my head.
Um...
This is me.
I'm bread.
Ha ha ha.
Because I'm Braindead.
You're a soup.
Thank you!
Thanks for the fun stream.
Go see my friends.
Who doesn't watch VTubers, but loves Zumbini's was watching.
And had a blast.
As for those we lost, we won't see them.
And as ashes.
They're all diamonds.
They are diamonds, Zumbini.
So true.
I hope this becomes the next flavor of the month streamer
game.
So VTubers everywhere can show the world what they are.
That they are not, in fact, smarter than...
than a first grader.
Hey!
I proved myself.
I proved myself pretty well, I think.
Now that the Microsoft cops can't stop us, are you gonna fly
us all the way to Akiva in real time and flight sim?
I, oh my gosh, Koran, it's so crazy to bring that up because
I was watching something yesterday and they brought up
flight simulator and I was like, I can do that.
So, 12 hour stream, baby.
Let's fly to Japan!
We can fly!
I've always wanted to do that.
So, um...
It's funny.
Maybe I should have done it, uh...
back when I streamed three years ago, but...
Oh well.
How... I do wonder though like how much do i need to know
your boss of flying a plane to do it i i actually have
looked into getting a pilot's license before but oh my gosh
the cost of getting a pilot's license is actually insane not
that i have a plane to fly anyway but um my uh my um one of
my old bosses uh had a a pilot's license and so um i don't
know maybe maybe i should ask him hey can you teach me how
to fly uh it was a semi-popular thing to do in my union what
do you go to a uni of people like who sleep on gold getting
a pilot's license is so expensive I just want to, you know,
as a ghost, I can fly anyway, but I just kind of want to
look.
Well, I, not, fly is like a, I could float.
Fly is like a big word, you know, but, um, pilot's license
for small planes is easy and not that bad.
Okay, I'm going to say the price that I saw, and anyone who
wants to confirm can confirm.
I saw it was for $10,000 US dollars is that correct oh I
heard about 10k see?
See?
That's what I heard that's what I googled and it told me I
googled and yeah that's about right oh my god 10k is low oh
my god we got Mr. Morebucks over here
is like 150k!
You're a student.
10k is low for a pilot's license though.
Okay.
It's like seven MGS3 Apache slot machines.
Sheesh.
Do pilots make good money?
Like say if I were a pilot for some big company.
Do they make the that you have to pay 150 000 i mean
okay when i think about it okay hold on that doesn't include
school right because some some colleges in the united states
cost that much intuition and things like that so it doesn't
include school It's just like the test.
That's so crazy.
Not that I would get the commercial license anyway.
But actually, I don't know.
Like, what?
Okay, what?
What?
How commercial are we talking?
Because if I...
If I'm just like, hey, guys.
a plane but I need you to pay for my time is that commercial
I mean if I'm not like if I don't have a business if I'm
just sometimes like oh and you can tell your friends that I
have a plane but I'm gonna charge them a little bit more
because they're not my friends you know getting the 747 mint
You guys, I'm going to fly a Boeing.
Okay, next stream idea.
If I'm going down, I'm taking you all with me.
Boeing hand cam.
I'm not ready to die yet.
It's okay.
Your whips, your whips.
Oh,
it's so scary that I have to check every time now.
When I'm like getting a flight, I'm just like, this is, this
is, this is, this is, I don't want to have anxiety the
entire flight, you know what I mean?
Worth it.
The crash landing on a deserted island stream.
Rest in pieces.
Sorry, Mint, I want my pilot to be able to recognize their
Zumbini's name.
I don't think I could even become a pilot anyway because you
have to have good vision, right?
Unfortunately, I wear contacts.
Even as a ghost.
You're thinking, even in death, my vision would be better.
Oh, it's a myth!
Did you guys know that, actually, I don't know if this is
only Delta.
I saw videos on it, but I think everyone that I saw with the
videos did Delta.
But, um, some, some pilots have trading cards of their, of
the plane.
So if you're just like, hi, can I talk to the pilot?
And you can collect cards of the planes.
Isn't that so awesome?
I wanted to do it last time, but I was really, I was like,
what if they, what if they were like, what, what the hell
are you talking about?
I was like, I was nervous to ask.
Wait, really?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Look it up, look it up.
It's so cool.
I don't know if it's just Delta though.
But every time I've watched a video about it, the pilots are
so nice.
But I think because it went viral on TikTok, a lot of people
have been asking.
And so the pilots will be like, the pilots will be like, oh,
I'm out.
People keep asking for these all of a sudden.
Sorry, Minto, if I hear this is your captain speaking and
it's your voice, I'm jumping right out right there.
And then this is your captain speaking.
The local temperature is...
is uh you need a sweater but like a really light sweater you
know and we're coming in at an altitude of craziness so
buckle up baby woo
have you seen that furry who's a technician and writes oh
whoa on the fuel tank of all i have seen that i have seen
that so crazy so funny buckle up whisperoos we're going
shopping too thank you what happens if you lasik a ghost I
will never get lasik so I don't know do they just go
straight through there's so many mysteries about ghosts so
many oh I just went to, that's funny, I went to YouTube
because I was like, time to read super chats.
I don't have super chats.
Can I?
I don't even.
Yeah, I'll show, like, I'm almost halfway to the amount of
hours that I need to get monetization.
So we'll see.
I don't know.
I'm not going to worry about it, though.
I'm not too concerned, to be honest.
Force of habit.
Are they going to...
I'll get LASIK if they...
What's the word?
They put Shady Gun in my eyes.
How long do you have to be inactive for where it resets?
I don't know.
It was a long time ago.
time I can't remember though maybe like several months like
three months or something I don't know I'll I don't think I
have the emails anymore where it's just like hey you're
gonna not get have membership I mean you're gonna have
monetization anymore oh I don't have like a thing that says
don't know reading hold on
Next.
Donation reading time.
Thank you.
Let's see.
I need a font.
Oh.
Beep.
And then now let's outline it.
line it in mint like a little more like that cool yippee
mint mint mint mint mint you're a simp you might not become
a pilot but now that you're out of heaven you could get that
forklift certification i could i could get forklift
certified if i wanted to perhaps i should mint phantom
certified forklifter
let's put it right why is it so why is it like that why is
it space like that also i don't think i like the Everything
being capitalized.
That's better.
Are my box certified?
Look into the game DCS.
You get to fly fighter jets.
The game is very, very hard.
You need a HOTUS.
But you want to try...
Wait.
But you want to try to fly a game that is a step above
Microsoft.
Microsoft flight.
You can fly like Maverick and do air support for Snake.
The 15th Super Hornet is a play-the-key.
One step at a time, maybe.
My new job has me driving a forklift, and I can confirm that
they're simultaneously very fun and very frustrating.
It's not like, uh...
What's the word?
It's not a stick shift, but they're...
There's like a lever you have to pull and stuff, isn't
there?
Am I going crazy?
DCS is not a game.
It's a job.
But yeah, I'm going to read Streamlabs now.
Actually, I don't...
Streamlabs has changed so much.
I can't...
Okay, I think if I go to here, I'll be able to read it.
E...
Yes, wait, why is it showing me?
11 minutes ago and then 3 years ago.
Stop it.
Thanks for bringing back the good morning tweets.
Well, in the past I used to say, ohaminto.
But, I don't know.
I can say ohaminto or good morning minto or whatever.
Three years ago.
I think this is...
No, wait, hold on.
This doesn't work either.
No, Streamlabs, why do you have to change everything?
I can't.
Wait, this?
Okay.
Oh, I have to go here.
Tip history.
Ah!
I figured it out.
What's today?
Seventh.
Seven.
George Costanza.
Oh.
I think I just messed something up.
Come on.
OBS, I messed something up too.
Stop.
OBS, why did you...
Okay.
Everything is bad.
Offering to my local ghost.
Thank you!
He-he-haha.
I just got here.
Why are you bread?
Because my brain is dead.
dead.
My brain is dead from Zumbini time.
My brain is dead.
The heart was actually difficult.
I'm so shocked.
Okay.
Let's see.
I'm getting hungry for dinner, so I'm gonna read through
these and then I'll see you guys on Tuesday.
Oh my I know.
It's a horror game though.
Oh no, I'm scared.
I'm scared.
A soup.
She was a streamlabs from zero minutes ago.
Thanks.
Can I have a piece of that bread?
You're wanting my...
brain you want a piece of my brain bread equals brain is
dead yeah bread brain dead if we're airing our flight sim
rainworms I think that IL-2 Sturmovic is a better game for
learning the basics of basics of combat flight than DCS
flying world war two prop planes teaches you better
fundamentals oh my god start at the basics okay where's my
right brother's sim then guys if i'm starting at the basics
i'm starting at the basics i want we need the right brothers
here then i'll move on from that to basic never build it
yourself Icarus sim?
Oh, we're going way back then.
Oh, true.
We gotta go even further beyond.
Offering to our local Ryan costume.
He's not here.
Is he?
Mr. Ryan.
I missed Mint Phantom so much.
Mint cheer, mint cheer, mint cheer.
Thanks, Ryan.
Hopefully we'll have emotes again soon.
emotes when i do when i get um emotes back we'll do karaoke
hopefully my flight my flight dang it no my voice it's
because i read flight in the chat hopefully my voice will be
better by then
oh i'm too influenced this is why i struggle so much with
like um uh you know like how some sing harmonies immediately
like they'll be like I I like can sing along with the music
but instead of singing the song I'm doing the harmonies I oh
I struggle so much I like mimic what I hear I mimic what I
read it's so difficult yeah they have the ear for it yeah
but like how do they like I maybe have I plugged my ears and
do it along maybe it's better maybe The New York Times
published an opinion article that mankind was millions of
years from inventing powered flight nine days before the
Wright brothers' first flight.
Those silly New York Times.
They don't know anything.
They're the non-believers.
The Wright brothers, they were right.
Good night for me.
Good night.
Everything you hear is called Eccolololio
Actually, there's a game called Rise of Flight that has
World War I and earlier planes And there's an expansion for
IL-2 That has them added in Flight Sim people are crazy I
love that though Love the passion Okay Some of these are
from before stream And I will still read them I'm so I'll
just read the stream labs from today Kare Sana, thank you
Israfel, thank you sometimes I get what's the word I get
nervous seeing like offline donations I do appreciate them
very much but I get nervous because sometimes it's like a
hate message so I'm just if I have my OBS open and I hear
that I get a donation I'm like
But I understand if you can't make it to the stream or
something.
So I do still appreciate it, you know.
So, thank you.
Anonymous, thank you.
See, that's a nice message.
I really appreciate it.
Thank you so much.
Dado, thank you.
I played this so much as a kid.
Love the logic puzzles.
remake you're playing for my niece everyone deserves
zumbinis in their childhood it's just such a good puzzle
game it's so fun try to ignore the anti ones yeah i do i do
i do i mostly usually ignore them so uh thanks for the money
nerd i feel like i'm reverse bullying them i feel like give
me
Taking your lunch money.
Scyth spawn, thank you.
Ronan, Ghost Without Borders, thank you.
And Ronan, thank you again.
Amy, thank you.
Hope you're having a wonderful day.
You too.
Tyranzoor Catastrophe, thank you.
Murphy, thank you.
Good luck with your job tomorrow.
Oh my gosh.
Sub-zero mudkips, thank you.
Do you think we'll eventually get a dono wrap?
What's that?
Where I wrap the donations?
Whoa, yo!
Wow, this duck!
Thanks very much!
Joan, thank you!
See, uh, it's good seeing you again!
Ronin, thanks for the donation!
Mr. Yura!
Oh, oh, yeah!
Um, but I can't wrap.
Don't know where I'm and read the messages at the same time.
Can't believe my...
Oh, she is bullying me for lunch money.
Yeah, good enough for me.
Need a BGM for the beat.
Yeah, for real.
This game is etching to my soul from 25 plus years ago.
Always great to see someone...
else who can sing along with the soundtrack.
I'm telling ya.
I played this game way so much.
Oh, wait, hold on.
Um...
Wait.
Oh, wait.
Oh, yes, there we go.
Karma, thank you!
To...
Mr. Kome Jelly, thank you!
Uh, Mr. Yura, thank you you why do so many of the zoomini
names sound like setups for these nuts jokes
good luck guiding the zoom zoom zooms to salvation customer
johnson thank you ronan thank you uh k barn thank you fleens
jeremy abel thank you albin thank you Thank you.
Kazuko, thank you.
Kazuko, oh my gosh.
His anniversary!
Thank you!
So many names I haven't seen in so long.
Nan, thank you.
Sun Chips, thank you.
Just scam, thank you.
Rylin, thank you.
Bestest maid ever.
Nah.
No.
Not the bestest maid ever.
Stop.
No.
Zalfios, thank you.
Uh, Jeffy Cake, thank you.
man thank you is this scribble knot from maybe the
predecessor sorry oh neko thank you i'm fairly new to your
stream but for the short time i've been here i'm really
enjoying what i see you mint are such a delight thank you
thank you so much love being minty fresh oh may i know thank
you joshua hugo thank you i've listened to you saying snake
eater in heaven's divide so many times turn stream and i'm
always in awe of the power of your singing voice i'm happy
you are back and looking forward to more of your goofiness
goofiness my kami oh she wow oh my gosh i'm so embarrassed
though because my throat was giving out
ray mac thank you zoomini frog accent there you go you got
it there you go you get it didn't sound like it oh it
definitely was full of soul why do you spell soul like that
with the v soul soulvo savo full of savo
hey there pretty lady i feel like i'm reading speak you know
how like when when they put when they change the E's to
threes the T's to sevens tree bomber thank you mind master
thank you here's a chute for everyone in mint cord ah nine
thank you eating Mike Tyson's butt thank you Minty Fresh
Kyle, thank you!
Eric W, I thank you!
Maybe if you talk to him in a frog voice, he'll understand
and listen.
I should have.
Hi, I should have.
The legend.
Thank you guys for the donations.
Implode, thank you.
Mr. Yuta, thank you again.
Sitspan, thank you.
For great old PC games, you should look up.
Stay tuned.
If you haven't seen or played it before, it's so silly and
fun.
It's a bit hard to play nowadays as it doesn't have a modern
re-release, but there are ways to do it.
I, I'll be honest, I did try to find a way to play the
original of the Zoom mini game, but I couldn't, I couldn't
get it to work.
And, um, with the, with the, with the time, like, uh,
rather, what's the word?
How much time I had before stream?
I couldn't get it to.
work but that's okay I think this one was still good enough
yeah yeah Yanwei thank you staff member has died oh my god
Invictus thank you mint the murderer no I was just trying to
show you something cool a death uh panda paloosa thank you
the moment you mentioned Zumbini's yesterday I had a Pixar
flashback moment to third grade computer lab this and
treasure math store and we're my jam yes wow this talk thank
you meant to kill the Zumbini amazing mission complete that
right there is why you're the best boss Kaito thank you
Isabel thank you David titanium pp thank you mama just
killed a man but if i do karaoke once i get memberships what
kind of karaoke should i do what kind of karaoke
whatever you want so true nacho libra hosting
Black metal.
My throat is just coming back.
Black metal, please.
Do you guys want me to have a throat, a voice or not?
I'm not asking you guys.
I'm gonna sing whatever I want.
Ease, Jimmy, thank you.
Now we know why you're not allowed in heaven anymore.
William Luong, thank you.
Thank you.
Retro Puffy, thank you.
Rico, thank you.
Puff, thank you.
Takedo Extra.
Oh, X.
Thank you.
John, thank you.
Anonymous, thank you.
Never even heard of this game and somehow it's still giving
me nostalgic vibes, right?
I know.
For sure.
Steak Dane.
Okay, I can try that one.
Seven Colors of Niko Niko Doga.
Aokusen Man.
Oh.
Raven's back.
Thank you.
I've never played this game, but I would always watch the
trailer ads for it in the Clue Finder's Game Wanderer.
Did you ever play any of those games?
I don't think so.
I'm gonna look it up right now.
Clue Finder's.
Maybe if I see it, I'll remember.
Oh.
I, for some reason, vaguely remember the Pyramid one.
it maybe a friend had it I don't think I had this game I
think a friend had this one and then I don't think I had it
I don't know maybe the pyramid one was a nightmare I don't
know yeah I don't know mmm it looks familiar though maybe
because it looks kind of like you know how a lot of the like
animation from that time looked very much like like it kind
of looks like the magic school bus you know what i mean no
um dog strings thank you murphy thank you aj shell thank you
uh mr utah thank you shruki thank you to hear me able thank
you tv juice enjoyer thank you No, thank you.
Jubilathan, thank you.
Scrookster, thank you.
Mr. Yura, thank you again.
Thank you so much for all the donations.
Gotta beat a leg of the journey perfectly, perfectly three
times to raise its difficulty by one level.
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
But of course you can just try harder difficulties in
practice mode too.
Got it.
Okay.
For whenever I come back to Zoom, my niece.
Jamie D.
X.
Thank you!
What a stream for my birthday!
Oh my god, happy birthday!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, Jamie D.
X.
Happy birthday to you!
Oh, happy birthday.
Thanks for spending your birthday with us.
Hopefully you get some good cake.
That's a...
Wait, what time does the store close?
Oh!
Oh, I have an hour!
Okay.
I have an hour to go to the store.
I suddenly wanted a very specific cake that is only sold at
a certain store.
So I'm going to go get that.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Minty Fresh Kyle, thank you.
Um, I know, thank you.
Italian loves cake, thank you.
If they want pizza so bad, why don't they make them?
What's stopping it?
And the machine is right there.
Rico, thank you.
Kiki Kadaver, thank you.
I'll check out that virtual villagers thing.
I've never heard of it.
Minty Fresh Kyle, thank you.
Shinsular, thank you.
Osoz, thank you.
Seymour, thank you.
Dado, thank you.
People on Steam reported this as a bug, but it hasn't been
fixed yet.
Ah, I see, I see.
Kaito, thank you.
See you later, Mint.
Many thanks.
No, thank you.
Thanks for hanging out.
Really appreciate it.
Thank you.
I didn't think so many people would be here for childhood
baby game.
Kaito, thank you.
Minty Pashkayo, thank you.
Ume, thank you.
Babyko, thank you.
Akabar, thank you.
Virulent, thank you.
Ario, thank you again for the Akadono.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Nylok, thank you.
Mint stole another soul.
Thanks for Zoomingi's fun stream.
Looking forward to podcast Monday.
Fly high, Mint.
Yeah, I think next episode is pretty good.
So for people who thought that there were or had complaints
about the first episode, like certain things, I think we
improved upon it in the second episode.
So, yeah.
Cinderella, thank you.
Um, I know.
Thank you again.
Spank, thank you.
Uh, Kamendati, thank you.
Seymour, thank you.
Kevarn, thank you.
Rico, thank you.
Koran, thank you.
Savicticus, thank you.
Um, Mitya Fresh Kyle, thank you.
Isabel, thank you.
Can you give me a thank you?
Um, I never realized it was that expensive because, like, at
least four of my friends have pilot licenses for their crop
dusters.
That's crazy.
Everyone had to spend so much.
I'm surprised people had complaints about the first episode.
They were, I say complaints, but it was really, like, a
constructive criticism.
You know, and we asked for it.
We said, like, please, please give us constructive criticism
since we've never done a podcast before.
And so, So we are looking to improve as much as we can.
So yeah, yeah, yeah.
Will there be another Patreon video?
Yes, there will be.
Yep, yep.
Yeah, which actually is almost the same length as the
podcast.
Oh my gosh, what was that gif?
We ended up talking so much in the Patreon video too.
So yeah.
Yeah.
what was it oh the we brought up the spy animals it's more
fresh on my mind because we recorded it just a couple days
ago so can you cadaver thank you Kaurin thank you usni thank
you doc talk thank you commentachi thank you this is your
captain speaking if you want this plane to land someone has
to beat me in a children's card game that's what they should
do you know how like when sometimes they can't land because
they're waiting for like their spot to to in line to like be
able to use the runway they should just have it so that they
should just like invite the passengers to play games come on
captain that's what I would do I would be that oh my gosh
you know how there's like cool moms I'm the cool captain I
let you, I let you, um, land with your, with your tray table
down.
I, I, you know, you don't have to stow those belongings.
Don't worry about it.
I'm, I'm so cool.
Coolest captain ever.
I'm not like other captains.
I'm the cool captain.
Uh, Isra Bell, thank you.
sim is extremely accurate with the controls from what i
remember if you make it so it can be pretty intense wow cool
i'm excited kiki cadaver thank you corin thank you with me
thank you wait oh i read all these i'm so sorry oh my gosh i
just realized um corin thank you thank you if they can shoot
lasers into your eyes they can make lasers shoot out of your
oh can't they make Yeah, can't they make lasers shoot out of
our eyes?
So true.
Captain Welfare, thank you.
Mr. Fowl, thank you.
Sideways, thank you.
Nicole, thank you.
Wow, this is like, thank you.
Corrin, thank you.
J.
Ikea?
J.L.
Keda?
Is it?
I think it's an I.
Thank you.
Rabbit, thank you.
J.B.
Hut, thank you.
Corrin, thank you!
Derpy's Derp, thank you!
Oh my gosh.
Wrongful Rabbit, thank you!
Thank you for this stream, it was a lot of fun seeing you
enjoy your childhood game again.
Thank you so much!
Thanks for the stream.
Very nostalgic seeing this game again.
Thank you so much.
Thank you guys.
Appreciate it so much.
Um, blah blah blah.
Inane, thank you!
Rico, thank you.
Pinkerton, thank you!
Thank you.
Hypothetical lunch money.
I usually skip lunch.
But dinner funds are where I draw the line.
Maybe.
Sometimes.
That's okay.
I get it.
Oh, wait.
Where did I leave off on?
Oh, here we go.
Ria, thank you.
I don't have any money, but you can have the rest of this
moon pie I'm eating.
Why did you send that to me?
Mistress, thank you.
This game is a few years old.
older than me but it's really timeless even if the hardest
difficulties are so brutal thank you for the fun man i'm
glad i'm glad that uh yeah it really is timeless though it's
so true man thee rose thank you such a joy to see you live
i've started singing snake eater during my vocal practices
because of you oh my gosh you probably sound like you're
probably insane levels then but that's your practice song
mia thank you pirate six
Six, thank you.
I think you need a little bit more O's in your name.
Thank you so much.
Charlie Ram Rancher, thank you.
Mic-Mac, thank you.
Corrin, thank you.
Cobats, thank you.
I was, oh, I never played Zumbini's in my childhood, but I
was so obsessed with gizmos and gadgets.
I never played that either.
I didn't play so many kids games, I think.
I did do a lot of Neopets, though.
It was amazing watching you get so excited to revisiting
this.
Yeah, I haven't played it since I was a kid, so it's really
awesome.
Israfel, thank you.
Julian, thank you.
TV, dinner tray, thank you.
Looking forward to Podcast Monday, Fly Hyman, thank you so
much.
David, Titanium, Pepe, thank you.
Virlet, thank you.
Nixitava, thank you.
Adonymous, thank you.
Airborne Ninja, thank you.
I got a scholarship from my local.
experimental aviation association to get my like wait
experimental aviation association aviation association
aviation association aviation association it sounds so
awesome to get my license might be something to look into it
would be cheaper and easier for you to get the sport pilot
license which is mainly for ultra light planes or
paragliders okay I'm actually going to look into that that
sounds so awesome that are all the donations thank you guys
thank you for sticking until the very end you didn't have to
but i appreciate it so much i hope you all have a wonderful
rest of your day or your night or your morning whatever um i
guess day would be appropriate there but uh i'm gonna go to
the store and see if that cake that i want is there So I
will see you guys on Tuesday.
Tuesday.
Rico, thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Most of the cost of a pilot's license is renting a plane for
$150 to $250 per hour for the FAA mandated 40 hours of
flight time.
Plus however much extra time is needed to pass the check
ride.
If you already have access to a plane, the cost goes way
down.
I'm gonna talk to my old boss and see if he would actually
be willing to to teach not teach me but like maybe i can
shadow him and like see what goes into flying a plane i'm
gonna see oh my gosh i'm gonna become i'm gonna become a
pilot vtuber you want to borrow my plane is it okay can i
borrow your plane the webinars guy What do you mean by that?
Roshiko, thank you!
I was sick and missed the stream.
Feel better, feel better, feel better.
Alright.
Bye-bye!
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye!
Eat-bye!
Go Shuchin-sama, Ojo-sama!
Bye-bye!
See you!
Oh, you can still hear me!
I forgot!
I forgot it was loud I'm so sorry oh I forgot that I still
had the mic on me
Say what's a mean to I just said it's a mean to I just a
mean to me