Stop that!
Uh Oh, no, wait!
I actually forgot something.
Uh oh.
Very good.
Oh, no!
Wait, I forgot something!
I- Stop!
Stop!
I forgot!
I- Stop!
Wait, no, no!
I just realized- Oh my gosh!
Why am I just realizing now?
Oh!
I forgot my noise gain.
Oh, shoot.
It's fine for today.
It's fine for today, probably.
Hello.
I didn't think I didn't think I Oh gosh You guys The maid
cafe is so messy No one has paid the power bill It's all
There's not even any lights on
Oh, there's cobwebs even.
I haven't had a chance to really clean up.
I didn't think anybody would be back here.
You know, I...
Uh...
You're up soon.
Hello!
Hi!
You're up soon.
You can help me clean it?
You can?
Help me clean it?
Maybe I should turn off the note if so.
I'll turn them off for karaoke later.
Give me it, give me it, give me it, give me it, give me a
second.
Hold on.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
I think I'm...
Okay.
Hello!
Welcome to my...
Nice!
Cappy!
Well, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Hold on.
I have my trusty broom here.
So we can, uh, we can, uh, clean up the cobwebs, right?
See?
You see it?
Oh, okay.
Hold on, hold on.
Okay.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
Chew.
Yay!
Okay let's get the other side.
Thank you.
Choo宮.
It looks like i'm sweeping up the notifs.
Get out of here.
Wait, where is it?
It looks like I'm sweeping up the notifs.
This one.
Wheech wheech wheech wheech wheech.
Wheech wheech.
Okay, now I can throw it away into the garbage.
There it goes.
I never need to clean again.
Arigato, Arigato, Arigato, Choochoo.
Arigato, Arigato, Choo.
Arigato, Arigato, Choochoo.
Oh my gosh, this is already It's too much It's too much
already It's too much already Thanks for cleaning up You're
welcome Yeah It's nice and Refreshed Except Except it's kind
of dark I'm sorry Again I haven't I'm just the ghost
haunting here I don't pay the bills I truly think this place
was abandoned.
Aren't your hands tired?
No, my hands are like this.
Because I'm a ghost.
It's just naturally up.
Why?
Do you want me to put my hands down?
It's really cursed.
It's perhaps more cursed than if my hands are up, to be
honest.
Do you want to see?
Do you want to see my hands down?
You want to see?
My hands down?
Oh my god.
Oh, wait, hold on, hold on, hold on.
I have something for this instead.
I just flew in here and, boy, are my arms tired
that's it that's all I got you can go home now boo oh my
gosh you guys love it thank you yes boo boo boo yes yes yes
I'm a ghost boo yes yes yes yes you guys get it yes you guys
love it you guys love it I knew it I knew it I knew you guys
would be would be patrons of good cultured taste I had a
feeling membo ships when I saw multiple people asking before
stream even if I was going to open up memberships but I
can't do anything I can't have a super chats I can't have I
can't have hold on I don't like this anymore I I can't have
memberships I can't have super chats until I have three
videos uploaded so today is my first video so after three
streams most likely most likely I think probably anyways
hello thank you you're a simp gosh my weird hearing these
don't know sounds they're from three years ago it's so weird
hearing them my gosh it's so weird being here it's so weird
oh I was gonna introduce I was gonna introduce my myself yes
because I think there's many people here that that I that
don't know me because there's lot of people that i don't
know either but back in the day i was i was just uh you know
teeny tiny spirits so now um i think my maid cafe is at max
capacity there's like a five hour waiting line it's disney
world up in here i only know her from the podcast thanks for
listening thank you yes i I'm back because Matara summoned
me Oh goodness gracious Thank you so much I really
appreciate all the donos Thank you guys I will turn off the
dono sounds Eventually Because we'll be doing karaoke later
So But yeah, Matara summoned me for a podcast And now I'm
back Haunting you Yeah
what else oh my name is mint my name is my my name is my
name is mint phantom minto that's me what are she what what
are she no namai wa
I have to speak in Keigo because because I'm the maid.
I'm the lowly maid and you guys are the go-shin-sama and the
ojo-sama.
Oh gosh, I have to serve you guys.
Age hasn't slowed you down one bit.
does that one say you're a soup no i don't remember why i
made it it was you're a simp i think it was from segi you
guys i'm back and all my friends are gone well not all of
them but a lot of my friends are gone everything a lot of
things have changed in the three years it was segi yeah it
was segi wasn't it
A lot of things have changed in three years.
But I think I think I can say I think I can say I'm still
me.
I think I can say that.
I think.
I think I can say I'm still I'm still minty.
fresh.
Despite everything, maybe.
Oh.
Happy to have you back, Dayon!
Yeah!
Sorry, I'm getting, I'm working over a cold.
So maybe actually today's not the best day to sing, but I
don't know, I didn't know what else to do.
So I thought maybe singing when kind of uh oh gosh sorry
okay i'm gonna turn off the notification sounds because i
think it's a little overwhelming when it's only stream labs
and no and no super chats because i don't usually turn on
sounds for super chats okay thank you thank you i had a
great grand nostalgia hearing all these sounds i hope you
guys did too okay
Congrats on coming back.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Maybe it's a backlog.
Oh, there.
Sorry.
There are many messages.
I will read them.
Oh, hey, wait, wait a second.
Oh, wait.
I think it's a...
Um, um, um, um, um, um, um, um.
Okay, now I think it's done.
Unless it's just a backlog.
Sorry.
I said there would be a little bit of scuff.
Yay!
You're a soup.
A soup.
What kind of soup?
chicken and chicken no hold on i used to um i used to love
the cream of chicken i don't mint soup corn soup yes yes yes
yes my favorite how'd you know how would you know oh my gosh
i have a feeling we're already gonna be getting along pretty
well if you already suggest corn soup corn potage Mmm,
that's that stuff.
That's the yummy scrumptious dilly-ditty-dumptious stuff
right there.
Ectoplasm soup.
No, no.
That's not for consumption, I think.
I think.
But yeah, welcome to my maid cafe.
Can I turn on the lights?
actually will it be will it be a flashbang will it be too
bright I could do a sponge bob thing where I just like flick
around the lights or something turn them on flashbang us
you're ready for the big bang oh oh oh
Three, two.
Okay, now I can welcome you to my maid cafe.
Yay, welcome.
Welcome, welcome.
Welcome to my maid cafe.
Oh, I haunt this place.
Mm, light mode.
My eye.
Get used to it.
I see some familiar names in the chat.
Hello, hello, hello.
Let there be light.
Oh, sorry, I keep expanding sometimes.
Um, what do I say now?
Um, uh...
uh this isn't okay oh yes yes i have i have stuff that i
want to talk about this is not like a debut or even a
re-debut i guess it's just me coming back and saying howdy
duty to you all um
uh hold on hold on i wrote notes on my howdy duty yeah it's
me saying howdy duty oh oh sorry that's tick tock sorry
okay sorry i was watching tick tocks for the nerves okay um
uh let's see um okay i said that i would be answering
questions today right
I've been answering questions today.
BASAMIN!
Oh, Kairi!
Congratulations, Min-ta-chan!
Thank you!
It's a long time!
Oh, BASAMIN Um...
Akiba I want to see you.
Um...
What do you call it?
The tours!
Akiba no...
Virtual tour.
Wait, it's like in Akiba.
They have like some people sometimes around backpacks and
stuff.
Japanese language shows you.
Thanks, I just got back from Japan.
I just got back from Japan.
I'm so Nihongo Jozu right now.
What's special in my cafe?
Drinks are sweets?
Me!
This is, this, you can't find another ghost in your...
Well, there's probably actually other made ghosts, aren't
there?
Probably, right?
Right?
I'm sold!
Yeah!
But yeah, I said today I would be answering some questions.
Because it's probably just like, what's going on?
Me too!
I also wonder what's going on.
New phone hootis.
Thank you for the donuts!
Thank you guys so much!
Thank you!
There's a lot.
The notifications are not stopping.
I appreciate you guys so so much!
Thank you!
Um...
Where's my notes app?
notes oh here okay where is your nose hey you can't say that
anymore okay oh whoa no no no no look you can't say that
anymore you can literally can see my nose okay i don't want
to hear that from anybody my nose is actually so existent
okay oh my gosh i sound so scraggly because of my Karaoke
doesn't sound so bad.
What knows?
Look, if I look to the side...
Oh, like that!
Look!
Did you see that?
Look, look, look, look!
Oh, I'm off the screen.
Phantom knows.
Hannah!
Oh my gosh, everybody's here.
Why?
why why why okay let's see okay i have a notes called
questions for coming back stream questions that nobody asked
but i thought maybe people would ask so yeah yeah let's get
started i guess okay first question that i wrote down That
people might be, this is so awkward, I'm so sorry.
This is so awkward, I'm so sorry.
Did ask, do care.
I'm glad, okay.
At least you, yeah, you do care.
Yeah, you do.
You do care.
Yeah.
Okay.
Please answer.
The first question I wrote down that maybe people are
wondering, Is M.I.
coming back permanently?
Is this like, is this it?
Is this, is this the finale, the final return of Mint
Phantom?
Is this, is this everything?
Is this, is this, I, buh buh buh.
The simple answer is truly, I don't know.
Um.
I don't know.
Uh, but as long as the podcast is going, I'll be around.
Um, I wish I could give you a more concrete answer.
I wish I could tell you guys a lot of things.
I wish I could tell you guys everything that is going on in
my brain.
Everything that is going on behind the scenes.
But unfortunately, I can't.
So I'm really sorry.
Everything that my brain has been swirly, like, literal
ectoplasm leaking out my ears all the time.
Tell me all of it.
But, um, uh, yeah, just to be honest, I'm still trying to
figure out what I want to do.
And, um, yeah.
But I'm excited to be back.
I'm very excited.
to be back so yes i'm happy to be here i'm really even
though i'm so anxious i'm really happy to be uh meeting you
guys this is this is nice to meet you for a lot of people um
i i i know there were some people that knew me three years
ago but there's also a lot of people that don't know me I
hope you like what you see.
I hope you don't mind being haunted and stuff.
Is it okay if I haunt you?
Is it okay?
If I haunt you for a little bit?
If I steal some of your life force a little bit?
Is it okay?
I consent.
Yes, please do.
Yes, please.
okay
I'm gonna take it all all your life force that's fine it's
only like maybe like a few years off your life then maybe it
could be a ghost just like me not so excited
okay um yeah okay uh my another question will I be streaming
Regularly and I plan to be streaming about Right, I wrote
three to four times a week.
It might be more.
I think I'm I Think I like streaming Back back when back
back a couple years ago.
I could only do So little because I worked at another maid
cafe at the same time so So It was much much more difficult
for me but now i'm a free ghost so i mean i am kind of i
don't know i don't know if i should be looking for another
maid cafe or not i kind of talked about it on with matara if
you listen to the if you listen to the podcast um i was like
oh my gosh maybe maybe i'll get like a job at a like a
part-time job at a grocery store or something it would it is
surprising how expensive it is to be a ghost you wouldn't
think about it but there's so many things that i have to
take care of like i just frog blinked when i there's truly
nothing going on in my head because uh ghost dollars ghost
taxes oh my gosh you just reminded me i need the my tax
person's been ghosting me why not the good kind of ghosting
though this is so bad okay thank you for reminding me i'm
gonna write that down email hold on email tax person okay
never mind
Phantom talks Who are the patriots?
Lolli Lolleo Oh my gosh you guys Heaven Oh yes I probably
should talk about that right?
graduated three years ago Today actually Because I graduated
on 4-4 4 in Japanese And I think that's In other Asian
countries too is death it's a lucky number for me so um i
graduated on the luckiest day and um
yeah so now i'm back on the luckiest day you graduated on
death death yep death but i went to heaven and um i don't
know i think i think i'm more suited to being a ghost i
think i had too many unresolved issues you know like being
an angel was fun and all but i just felt still this urge to
to like haunt you guys and like i don't know being a ghost
feels more up my alley busting makes you feel good no no
that's not what you're supposed to do though you know you're
supposed to you know i mean i know i covered that but like
but but um don't don't bust me okay i'm afraid no sleep i'm
afraid of no bed
oh let's see what else uh um so yeah i'll be streaming
somewhat regularly it might be it might turn into more but i
don't want to um with the podcast i don't want to do too
much so or like overload so oh i wrote that down why did you
come back i wrote even in heaven i felt restless like i had
some unfinished business i don't think i was ready to go so
maybe i'm best at being a ghost than an angel Maybe.
I even got my wings and everything.
I think they were fake, though.
I think they were cardboard.
Couldn't even fly properly.
Question.
Is this a re-debue?
Nope.
It's just me coming back to streaming.
And if I decide this to...
What was that?
do not
Batara don't look
oh my gosh you didn't set that no that wasn't me I think
that was I think that was part of the the donation that's so
funny Hold on, I'm going to keep drinking my tea.
Will you play Delta?
Oh, hell yeah.
I'm going to play Delta.
Are you kidding me?
Yeah, I'm going to play Delta.
So excited.
Oh, my gosh.
But yeah, this is just me returning to streaming.
If I decide to stay, then I'll make it a bigger deal.
Like...
new outfit or new graphics or new shiny stuff
so yeah i already have plans if that happens
yes you will have to stick around and meet too but for now
I'm gonna be mostly sticking to this outfit I if you watched
me in the past you know that I had a original outfit at the
moment I don't plan on using it I'm sorry just like it's
really outdated and kind of embarrassing to use I think so
Matara was very generous to even get me rigged again so I'm
a little more shiny and new I actually we touch on that in
the in the next podcast episode so yeah this one is very
cute you like it
You're like...
I have faces.
I can show you guys.
I can show you guys all my faces.
Like...
Or...
But yeah...
Amu...
It's the same face.
No, it's not!
Can you do a surprise?
one though okay hold on i'll do a really good one
show us the chibi mode again okay patience patience let me
get through these questions first that i wrote myself and no
one wrote but me um um uh oh this one we talked about on
matara's stream but will say it here as well does the
podcast mean that you are joining vishojo and no does not
mean that i am joining vishojo i'm just collaborating
collaborating with matara so i can haunt her and suck her
life force and cause her discomfort in her daily life so yes
that's it
That's it.
But, uh, Veshojo has been helping with, um, with some of the
stuff like the merchandise.
Hashtag save Mata.
No!
Me!
I was summoned against my will!
What are you talking about?
I was summoned against my will.
Is this model all new?
No, just the rigging.
I got this model just before, or this outfit, this new look.
Just before I...
Was ordered.
Left for heaven.
Yeah, yeah.
So, mmm.
But yeah, everything is so confusing.
People always say that I'm doing this and doing that.
I don't even know what I'm having for breakfast tomorrow.
So let's just take it.
Let's just take things one step at a time.
Another question that I wrote down.
Why didn't you come back sooner?
I don't know.
I probably, I guess I could have come back anytime, maybe.
But I honestly, I wanted to take some time to myself.
Person shrugging emoji.
Yeah, basically.
I wanted to take some time to myself.
A little productive.
I just came back from studying in Japan.
So I just kind of wanted to take some time away from my
usual area.
and clear my head and figure out what I want to do going
forward.
And did I do that?
No.
I'm even more confused.
I have no idea.
Oh, that's the next question I wrote.
Did you clear your head and figure out what you wanted to do
going forward?
No.
Next question.
Will you unprivate your old VODs?
This one's like a tricky one for me, right?
Because...
I'm still deciding a lot has changed from back then and I
cringe every time I see an old clip I cringe at my old mic
quality I cringe at a lot of things a lot has changed I feel
I'm worried that like maybe if I if if people watch the old
vibes they'll be like oh she's so different than how she was
three years ago, now, you know?
So, I don't know.
I don't know.
And also, I know there's like, old, old, old, you boomers
out there.
I'm maybe, I'm not the boomer.
You guys are the boomers.
Get it?
I get it.
Boomer.
The people that I watched me before.
and you know might want to like bring up old jokes and
things that we did things that we you know talked about and
everything but I kind of want to like just I don't know make
this a place where even newcomers can can come in and be
like, you know, can enjoy right away.
You know, I don't want it to be like, oh, I don't get this
joke.
What is she talking about?
Things like that.
I want it to be welcoming for everybody.
Yeah, new chapter.
Maybe.
Does that mean no Metal Gear Solid jokes?
What are you talking about?
I can't stop talking about Metal Gear.
Heaven had Metal Gear, you guys.
It was probably the best thing.
not the best
um well anyway it had metal gear and I am I'm sorry that I'm
sorry that I must tell you that I've come back brain rotted
welcome back to the living hey I'm not living though I'm
Definitely deceased.
We can tell.
I'm so sorry.
Outer heaven.
That's literally me right now.
I think I am...
Oh my gosh.
The fan...
The phantom...
The phantom pain!
Have I been...
Have I been snake this whole time?
Oh my gosh.
It all makes sense right now.
It was predestined.
Truly.
The phantom pain.
Oh my gosh.
Let's see, what else do I have?
Oh, question.
If you decide to stay around longer, what can we expect?
Okay, this is kind of funny.
I wrote a lot.
More consistent schedule, comma, and then nothing else.
Oh boy, I'm selling it, aren't I?
You can expect so much from me.
You can expect...
And you can expect...
That's all I ever wanted, really?
Yep.
So...
I'll take your entire stock.
Sign me up.
Yes.
What a deal.
Expect redacted.
Something.
It's something big.
I can't.
I'm keeping you guys on your toes.
I can't let you in on all my secrets.
Hmm.
Why is Snake Fortnite?
emoting in my screen.
Oh, hold on, I got a cough.
I coughed.
A thousand.
What?
Thank you.
How are my studies going?
Oh, I'm done.
It was just a short program.
it was just a short study it wasn't well originally I wanted
it to be six months but the school could only do two and so
now I'm back I'm back home yeah so but it was good I learned
a lot yeah I learned a lot yeah what did you I study... I
study Japanese.
I study Japanese so I could talk to my idol Oshis better.
But a lot of it was like...
A lot of it was like Keigo.
It's just...
Iki.
Iki Japanese.
I mean, Iki Keigo.
Yeah, yeah.
Too based?
What do you mean?
Oh, sorry.
I guess I can show you guys now a little bit more of my...
What's the word?
My faces that I can do.
this feels like a real hold on oh do I have to do the vtuber
thing where I show my body do you guys want to see my body
here I am this is how I look I step to the left I step to
the right that's this this is what you see is what you get
oh Totemo Jozu Arigato Arigato Choo Tip it time I'm dancing
I'm grooving I'm smoothing Oh yeah Let's see what else
Faces Faces Faces
The drip animation is so shiny.
Oh yes, I was so shocked by that.
Look.
My thighs are dripping.
The chocolate is actually dripping.
That's...
Maybe my ectoplasm a little bit.
My...
Even the chocolate is possessed.
Even the chocolate's possessed.
Isn't that crazy?
Yeah, I mean.
Except it's not for licking.
It's decoration.
It's actually poisoned.
If you...
Lick it, you will die.
Um, okay.
I have.
Okay.
This is how I'm feeling this whole time with so many people.
So many people.
Actually, I don't even know what the number is.
I don't even...
I'm afraid to look.
I don't even know how...
In my brain, there's only two of you guys.
There's...
Okay.
At least two.
Yeah, exactly.
Don't say it!
Don't say the number!
We're just typing really fast.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't say it.
Okay.
I can blush even more.
I can blush a little bit.
I can blush a lot of it.
This is when...
This is when I'm still flustered.
Flustered, flustered.
I can't speak.
This is when...
...
No!
Oh no.
When you see Raiden naked, so true.
Oh my gosh, so true.
Hey, you guys didn't hear...
You didn't hear anything!
Okay!
Good, you heard nothing!
Okay.
Can I have a bite of my pizza?
Sorry, I forgot to eat.
I got...
My stomach before this was like...
Like, really growling at me.
I think we're comfortable enough now that...
I could eat on a street.
What the hell is that?
Who was that?
Who was...
Oh, you can hear me chewing on that, I'm gonna mute.
It was the pizza delivery man.
Oh, it was Ryan Gosling.
I uh...
When I'm on the plane, I usually watch...
I usually watch one of... or actually...
I usually watched two movies for sure.
Or three.
Actually, three movies for sure.
The first one is Indiana Jones.
Some Indiana Jones movie.
This last time I watched The Temple of Doom.
And then I always watched Top Gun.
Usually I watch Top Gun Maverick.
I think Top Gun Maverick is my favorite movie of all time by
this point.
I have watched Top Gun Maverick so many times.
oh I can't I I don't know how many times I have watched it
at this point I watch it going to Japan and going back every
time that I've gotten for like the past year and a half I
think it's so good oh my gosh I love the original Top Gun
too but Top Gun Maverick is just Oh my god, my favorite, my
favorite scene is when Maverick, Tom Cruise, that's, that's
him, right?
It's Tom Cruise, right?
Yeah, when he is showing, when he's showing the class, when
they have, when he's like, showing them that the mission is
possible, oh my gosh, wait, he's in mission.
But, no, I didn't mean it.
oops it's top gutting time when he is shown when he does
when he's like when they're just like oh my gosh we can't we
can't complete the mission in the time limit um and with the
enough accuracy oh my gosh thanks for the raid thank you um
but uh i love that scene and I love um uh what was it um oh
yeah that's the scene I love it's it gets me so hype sorry
are we talking about the same movie yes yes we're talking
about Top Gun Maverick
that's Ryan Reynolds no it's not oh that's what I was
getting at though the third movie i usually watch is la la
land and i think before then before la la land i wasn't i
wasn't so into ryan reynolds i know that he was like a meme
for a long time but now i think i i think i get it because
of la la land oh wait sorry that's ryan gusling
I know.
Sorry.
Ryan Reynolds is dead boy.
I know.
Oh, my throat.
I can't even laugh properly.
Sorry.
I sound so raspy, I think.
sorry i get them i tend to get them confused along with
other hollywood actors hold on i'm gonna mute so i can eat
oh my gosh thank you for the akadono thank you you guys are
way too generous holy cow yeah what do you think of making
old bob's members only maybe that's an idea that is an idea
that i can think of thanks for the suggestion oh my gosh
even before stream someone was already backseating me in the
donos
they were like don't join the discord i think you shouldn't
do it i hope you don't join it And I was like, why am I, why
am I already being vaccinated?
There's a Discord there, apparently is a Discord.
If anybody wants to join it, I suppose.
Where was I?
Oh, I can be, I could be sad.
I can be more sad.
Oh god!
My eyes are so wobbly.
I'm so sad.
I'm so sad right now.
That...
That you...
Um...
Don't want me to join the Discord.
Why can't I join the Discord?
Why can't I do it?
Why don't you guys whip me around?
It's abusive.
Not saying howdy.
You're not invited.
Oh, there was another gift?
Oh, no, I missed it.
I missed it.
Let's see, what else?
Oh, I can't.
It can be, you guys have seen this one before, I've seen
several.
Several people using this as a reaction.
I'm so shocked.
This is me joining the Discord and seeing everything that
you guys are saying.
Yeah.
And then, this is me.
Joy, this is me.
What the hell?
Oh, my God.
I was like, why are there naked men?
It's God's sake.
Say kiosi.
my gosh this is me five minutes after joining the discord
maybe
i didn't need to join the discord ah
yeah yeah hey
oh gosh there's gonna be wait i don't even know how many
donations there are i'm scared oh i declare bankruptcy i i
prematurely declare bankruptcy no i'm just kidding uh let's
see oh this one this is this is when any when metal gear
discussion metal gear metal gear metal gear discussion let's
go But also, then I think about the Discord.
You better not be saying crazy things in there.
The next one, I'm never going to use.
So, this is your one time to see it, okay?
I'm going to get in real close for you.
This is your one time to see this face.
What is that?
What is it?
What was that?
Hold on, I'm going to move the notives somewhere else.
I'm going to move you guys down here.
I'm never going to use this one.
So, just today.
Okay.
I have no, I don't even know what I would use this for.
This might be a mistake.
Showing you guys at all.
No!
gosh okay but the worst part is is oh god why why is there
steam coming out of my mouth
why hot pot this is me seeing corn soup
i want some more It's cold outside.
True, true, true.
True, true.
You don't want to see if I combine it.
Dreamworks, anybody?
Ah!
No, no, no!
No, no, go away.
Okay, we're fine.
We're normal, we're normal, we're normal.
Hop on Fortnite.
Get out of here!
Oh my god.
These gifts are so cursed.
I completely forgot that was a thing.
I turned it off before, so I completely forgot it was a
thing for Streamlabs to be able to do that.
No, we are not.
Mint looking at snake.
Snake.
No, this is me looking at Pliskin.
Pliskin.
He's so cool.
maybe i do have a reason to use it
i do have fortnite because i got snake but i have to change
my name on it my name right now is something ridiculous um
and also because they got my tongue
i'm not gonna open my mouth all the way though i'm not gonna
give you weirdos what you want
but i can give you a te te pero
don't combine that with the hard eyes i'm not gonna give you
guys what you want i know better i know better
Please, it's my birthday.
It's not.
So cute.
Wait, who was that?
Usami!
Oh my gosh!
Oh my gosh, it's been so long.
Hello!
Oh my gosh.
So many people have come back.
Hello, hello.
I think that was all I had.
Oh, I have, I can...
Top Gun!
Yeah, baby.
Oh my god, wait, Jakedo, you sent the other one before too.
The other gift.
Love it when Tom Cruise...
Oh, I missed it.
Wait.
Oh, shows that the mission is possible.
I can also be very smuggled.
Oh, I also...
I saw this one earlier.
Oh!
Oh, head empty!
No thoughts.
Nothing.
Nothing going on behind my brain.
And also I like combining I like this one.
Hmm Hmm Hmm
Yeah.
Konada face.
For real though, actually.
I think that's everything though.
Oh, can I can also?
Oh, that's not everything.
Oh my gosh.
But Tara hooked me up.
I can also...
.
That's the best one?
You think so?
The gifts.
What is it?
It was Brian Reynolds again.
Oh, I can also...
I could cross my...
Whoa!
I feel like a dream works.
Oh my gosh.
I think that's everything.
And now, I think.
Maybe.
Oh, there's also...
Well, this is like...
I can...
I can start sweating.
When I'm just feeling a little bit sweaty.
I'm sweaty.
Sweaty gaming.
Sniffer.
Hey.
That's my ectoplasm.
Stop it.
How much for a mint sweat bottle?
You don't want it.
Micro waves.
Ah.
okay are we ready to sing I feel a little nervous but how
are we feeling how are we do you guys I know I look a little
different I really I did talk about this in the podcast I
really did love Yua's rigging Yua did such an amazing job
and I love Yua so much she saved me at this sake When did
the sand burn?
Oh, the TV model, that's right, that's right.
Here, it's a little disturbing to watch me switch back and
forth, so it's kind of like body of where it feels.
But, uh, what was I gonna say?
Oh my god, curve it!
Minty fresh
I don't even remember what I was saying.
Oh, I was going to say, oh yes, I was saying I loved U.S.
rigging so much.
U.S.
as my papa was the best ever.
But, uh, and I mentioned this, uh, sorry, I know I keep
saying that.
I said it in the podcast.
um but the it was actually incomplete because we had to get
it done so quickly so um it it was it's a little incomplete
because or it was incomplete because of that so with this i
was able to get a bunch of stuff that i had originally
wanted here now yeah gosh this like enhances my chest I'm a
cheery!
And I do steppies.
Steppie-top.
Give them your razzle-dazzle.
Razzle-dazzle-dazzle them.
How can they see you with sequins in their eyes?
Yep.
I look like a baby.
I'm the baby.
You got games on your phone?
Do kids still play Roblox?
What do, what do, like, what does Gen Alpha play now?
If not, Roblox and, uh, they do?
Yes?
I have no idea.
Nobody puts baby in the corner.
You know, I only know that line from, from, uh, uh, How do I
say?
Okay.
I guess I'll be honest with you guys.
You know, in the past, I wasn't entirely honest with you
guys.
When I said I was going to go work at a maid cafe, I lied.
In fact, I only haunt this one maid cafe.
I was working an office job I was haunting an office.
I'm sorry to have lied to you.
You probably thought I was some super maid who was going
around to every maid cafe ever and being so productive and
awesome and like I was the best maid ever.
I'm a big phony.
But that's how I know that.
Who was that?
I'm getting a bunch of strangers coming in.
Ah, he pays the bills.
Play this like a damn fiddle.
But yeah.
So sorry to have...
To have lied to you like that.
Oh my gosh, it's weird seeing my normal face.
So, yeah, there was a lady at one of my jobs who would
always say, Nobody puts baby in the corner.
I don't know what it's from.
It's from a movie, right?
But she would say it all the time.
And she would say that and she would say,
Ding-go-a-cha-baby.
Dirty dancing.
I've never seen it.
I'm say-so.
I don't dirty dance.
I'm dirty damn.
Singing time.
Give me a second to set up.
I haven't used this in a long time.
Oh, wait.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, I think we're good.
Hold on.
Uh.
I think we're good.
Oh!
We're not good!
Oh my gosh!
Hey, yeah!
Thanks for...
Hold on.
Before singing.
I'm an idiot.
I should have done this at the beginning of the stream.
Um...
I...
I, uh...
This is a small introduction for people that don't know who
I am.
A small introduction.
I made this when I actually debuted this model a long time
ago.
Um...
When I have my 2.0 debut.
and I didn't change anything because I don't have Photoshop
anymore I was like, oh, I don't even know what to change
everything was pretty much the same so this is me I'm
forever 19 and my birthday is also my death day which is
October 1st maybe we'll celebrate it this year maybe we'll
celebrate it this year right I'm 149 centimeters and usually
you don't ask a lady her weight but since I'm a ghost I'm 0
kilograms so it doesn't matter my special trait is my toad
impression I'm pretty good at impressions actually I'd say
skinny legend I I
What would Toad say in a situation like this?
Skinny legend!
Any frog perchance?
Oh, I can kind of do like a Kermit somewhat impression,
right?
Hold on.
I have to really channel it through my throat.
What does the Kermit say?
Welcome to the Muppets.
I'm going to muppet all over the place.
I can't do it.
um he says hello canada he does oh maybe it's like a special
episode that i've never seen oh i don't know what you would
say hello canada like that is that how he would say it
yeah uh i have hashtags but I saw I think I don't know I
only had a general hashtag I never needed an art hashtag in
the past so maybe I don't know maybe we should keep it I
don't feel like I need more than a general hashtag and a
stream hashtag which the general hashtag is mintosinde which
is basically mint Ghost photography, ghost photos, ghost
photography.
When you're like, if you're searching like spooky ghost
photos in Japanese, it's shinde, shashin.
Please art tag.
Okay, maybe we can come up with one later.
And stream hashtag is minto live.
Maybe it should be minto dead, because I'm never alive.
I'm always dead.
You have to know.
But yeah, I mean, it's just a general hashtag.
I guess maybe hashtag Mint Phantom can be the general
hashtag.
I don't know.
Well, there's my Oshimark.
It's a ghost and sparkles in case you're curious.
My likes and my dislikes.
I like anime.
I like horror I like sweet things I like riding trains I
like idols I like REM I love REM So sweet Actually I think I
need to No not replace but I think I need to add someone
else Okay Yeah I think I need to add someone else Because
You guys I think I'm seriously in love with Freyren I think
I think I love Freeran too much There was a tweet going
around when Freeran was airing About it was a Japanese tweet
About how They were like If you say that you're too in love
with Freeran That's okay because Freeran is this
Generation's Ruri From Nadesco And I love Ruri I love Ruri
so much But I love I love Freyrin.
She's like burry with like a little extra attitude.
And I just...
I love her so much.
Need to add Metal Gear.
That too!
Oh my god!
My heart.
Thanks for the doughnut.
Thank you so much.
Thank you guys.
Thank you.
I think we're all caught up.
I think.
I love...
Oh.
thank you loyalty to the end yes
um but yeah I love I love Rem and I love Free Run I've been
so obsessed with Free Run recently um I love cute I love
anything that's cute I love anything Anything, moi?
Moi is justice.
Martian successor Nettuskoi.
Yeah!
It's one of my favorite enemies.
So awesome.
So, so, so, so good.
And I love dad jokes because they're funny.
I think.
Things I don't like are spicy food.
Don't like spicy food.
I don't like messes because I'm a maid.
And if there's a mess, I gotta clean it up.
like jumpy things like cockroaches and crickets sorry I
don't like the cold I prefer warmer weather and I don't like
it when you don't leave snacks if I'm visiting you if I'm
visiting you in your bedroom at night while you're asleep
I'm like I'm like a ghostly I'm like a ghostly Santa Claus
okay you gotta leave me like a little something a little
offering okay yeah so you're like Santa Claus so what I just
said hey yo my bedroom look um it's just part of like being
a ghost I go around and I haunt sometimes it's gonna be a
made cafe sometimes you know I gotta check out just leave
some snacks okay you never know that's all that's all you
gotta do
oh oh that's it that's it yay my introduction my
introduction okay now he's saying Woohoo!
Woohoo!
I hope we can sing.
My throat is getting gradually worse, I think.
Oh my gosh.
Thank you for the Akadora.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Welcome back to this world.
Makes us all smile knowing you're back.
Thank you.
I really thought that nobody...
Well, you know, there was people that watched me, obviously.
Back in the day.
But I didn't think people would...
remember me.
So I was really surprised.
Especially that there's so many people here.
So I'm just gonna sing for a little bit.
I don't know.
I don't even know what to sing.
Do you guys have any?
I will take requests.
Oh, hold on.
Let's do this.
Sorry, I only have this scene.
And no.
Nothing else.
I have my intro.
And this scene.
So we're just gonna do karaoke here.
I hope that's okay.
But I have...
Uh...
Hold on.
Setting up a little bit.
Get out of here, music.
It's...
This...
Time.
Uh...
That's not audible audio, is it?
I tested it before, but...
Is it audio okay?
Is it good?
Okay.
Hello?
Why isn't this one activated?
Oh, there we go.
Okay.
Nice, nice, nice, nice.
Uh, this is, this is, uh, joy sound.
on the switch.
So if you're ever like, man, I wish I could do Japanese
karaoke.
And I'm not just going to sing Japanese songs.
I can sing whatever I want.
Yippee!
So, yeah.
If they don't have it on here, we can see if there's like a
karaoke version of it on YouTube or something.
But, yeah.
What should I sing, snake eater?
You guys, I have a bat.
They don't have snake eater on here.
What am I searching?
Me.
They only have two...
I looked it up earlier because I was testing it.
They only have two Metal Gear songs on here.
And the first...
I kept saying this one at karaoke in Japan.
I have no idea what this song is.
The Phantom Pain by White Ash.
I looked it up.
And I had never heard this song before.
What is this?
The Phantom Pan.
I have no idea.
Really good band?
Oh, you know that.
Japan-only song?
Maybe.
Do they have Busted on there?
They probably have Ghostbusters.
But I could sing Can't Say Goodbye to Yesterday.
But I think maybe...
That's like... we need a better starter song, right?
We need a better starter song.
But you know what, let's do Ghostbusters, yeah.
Ghost, Ghost, Ghost, Ghost, Ghost...
Ghost...
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Ghostbusters!
I'm not afraid.
Didn't, what's that group?
I think they recently did a...
A...
What is the I'm Not Afraid version?
What's a fallout boy?
Huh?
Featuring Missy Elliot?
Anyway.
Ghostbusters.
Oh, they don't have the Ataarashi Gakko version though.
That's okay.
Utau!
Do you guys like my meme?
This is to get us a little warmed up.
Oh, it's kind of loud.
Oh,
there's something strange in your neighborhood.
Who are you gonna call?
Mint Phantom!
If there's something weird, then who are you gonna call Mint
Phantom?
Is the audio okay?
Pray to know ghost?
Things running through your head.
An invisible man sleeping in your bed.
Who are you gonna call?
Ghostbusters!
I ain't afraid of no ghosts.
There's no ghosts!
Oh, who are you gonna call?
Ghostbusters!
If you're all alone, pick up the phone and call
I ain't afraid I ain't afraid to know a ghost, Garfield.
I hear it likes the girls.
Is that actually the lyrics?
I ain't afraid to know a ghost.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I
have ghosts, mama.
Freaky ghosts, baby.
You better call.
I don't know that part.
I just know freaky ghosts, baby.
Freaky ghosts, man.
Freaky man, baby.
Freaky ghost band.
I don't know the original of the song.
Let me tell you something.
Buster makes me feel good!
Yeah!
I'm ready to know ghost.
Oh, don't get caught alone.
Ghostbusters!
When it comes through your door, unless you just want some
part.
I think you better call...
Ghost
toys!
Who are you gonna call?
Ghostbusters!
I think you better call Ghostbusters!
Who are you gonna call?
Ghostbusters!
I can't hear you!
Who are you gonna call?
Ghostbusters!
Ghostbusters.
What's the number?
No one gave me the number.
Ghostbusters.
have to Google it myself?
It's not very informative though.
What's the number to call them?
Yay.
Please check out Super Ghostbusters karaoke by Fat Bird
Karaoke for some good laughs.
I'll check it out later.
Thank you.
All right, what else can we sing, guys?
What else can we sing?
idol.
I don't... I don't know... Oh, I know it.
I know that song, obviously, but I don't know how to sing
it.
Ike Nye Borderline?
You guys aren't sick of me singing Ike Nye Borderline?
Really?
You're not sick of me singing it?
I sang it 50 times.
Really?
You want me to sing My Joy-Con is not very responsive right
now.
We haven't seen you in three years, Mint?
Okay, I guess that's true.
But I sang it enough times to make up for three years.
And then some.
Ike and I borderline 444 times.
Ike, what's up?
Okay, this will be the real test of my throat.
Of my voice.
I only got my voice back like, what's today?
Thursday?
Got it back like Tuesday.
So I'm more into the two-way world Ah Love, love, love,
love, love Love, love, love, love I believe in you, but So,
so, so, so, Seeming it's just a little bit Giri, giri, love
I can't avoid a lie I don't know, I don't know, Oh, I'll see
you I'll see you Killing, killing my Sardinari My mind's
mind My mind's Self-negotiating I'll say it's all I'll say
Fizzak 'a'a My friend, Fizzing with that other people And
I'll see you again For the day I'm glad I'm glad you're here
Our light will be dark, our darker light will be.
Our light will be white.
Our light is turning red.
It is a dangerous line.
Ah, our freedom, our peace, our peace, we are all happy.
we'll be happy, we'll see if we fall down, we'll die and
we'll die.
The end of our world,
My voice is a little
I can't go to the line I can't even see all I can't see
Kiri, Kiri, my Sala Nara Gigi, to the My mind's mind can't
see me My body's un-strivial I can't see you, I can't say it
Kiri, giri, I can't go to the line
I'm so sorry
Oh, I almost spilled my tea everywhere.
Yeah, okay.
Emily is playing Pokemon Violet.
I know what you're doing, Emily.
I know you're playing Pokemon.
Um, what else?
Let's see, what else?
Hmm.
Oh my gosh, I can sing.
so much.
It's hard to know what to sing.
It's been so long since I've sung that.
I have a cover for you guys.
Oh, Hamtaro!
A bunch of people have been requesting Hamtaro.
Of course I can do Hamtaro.
Also, it doesn't have to be just this program has English
songs too.
So, and like I said, you can request whatever.
Hamtaro.
Nope.
You can request whatever.
And, um...
Yeah.
I'll do my best to do as many as possible.
Without killing my throat.
Without killing my throat too much, I think.
Oh gosh, I have to be careful here, though.
Doing the calls.
Do you guys know Otage?
Okay, say no!
MEOHOTUSKEY!
Come
on!
HUMTARO HUMTARO HUMTARO DHHHHHUMTARO
DASIKI HUMTARO HUMTARO Tiger, Fire, Cyber, Fiber, Tiber
Tiber, Fire DUMTARO, DUSTARO Kasha DUMTARO DASI DASIKI
Why did the chat stop?
Hold on.
Oh, I think YouTube froze for me.
Am I still streaming?
Uh-oh.
I am?
I can only read you guys through OBS.
YouTube completely crashed for me.
Uh-oh.
Not even like going to youtube.com is working.
Oh, here we go.
Okay, hold on.
Uh...
Live stream.
There we go.
Well, Otake was too powerful.
Truly.
Truly, truly, truly.
Snake Eater?
Are you sure?
I've never, I've never, I've never sung it.
What if I can't sing it well?
I'm nervous.
What if I can't do it justice, you guys?
I wonder, hold on.
Snake Eater, karaoke.
Oh, I think this one would work.
It'll be fine.
You say that, please sing Break Stuff by Limp Biscuit.
I could probably do that one, too.
You guys have interesting choices.
Okay, well, this one is not...
Obviously, the joy sound didn't have it, so I'm going to
hide that.
Goodbye.
Oh, gosh.
I'm nervous!
Oh, I'm nervous!
Let me hear this real quick, make sure it's okay.
Oh, wow.
It's just the original karaoke, though.
I wonder if I'll get copyright struck.
This one has, like, like, 360p audio quality, 240p audio
quality.
So maybe that one's the safer one, even though.
Okay, we can try it.
You know what?
I think it's okay.
Okay.
Oh my god.
What a thrill with darkness and silence through the night.
thrill I'm searching and I'm melting to you what a fear in
my heart but you're so supreme I give my life not for honor
There'll be no one else Oh my gosh, I'm so nervous Cry, it's
the way I fly to you I'm still in a dream Snake it up
Someday you go through the rain Someday you feed on a tree
frog This ordeal, the trial to survive For the day we see
new life I give my life not for honor but for honor
My time, there'll be no
one's Crime is the way I fly to you I'm still in a dream,
snake eater
I'm still in a dream.
Snake it up.
Snake, snake, snake, snake, snake.
Oh,
that I need a cough drop.
Oh my god!
Oh my
god!
Man.
That was so fun.
Man, it was so fun.
Okay.
Sorry, you can hear a cough drop probably.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Uh.
Cynthia Harold will be proud.
I hope so.
If I ever get to meet her, I'm gonna be like, rate me.
No, actually, don't rate me.
Don't, don't rate me.
I'll cry if she'll be like, mmm.
Cough drop ASMR.
I'm sorry.
Oh, let's see.
Let's go back to Georgetown.
What else?
What else can we sing?
We could sing anything!
Practically anything!
The world is our oyster.
Oh wait, um...
There were some requests.
Oh, plastic loves a good one.
Actually, I do want to sing that one.
I hope it's okay.
Wait, uh...
The con... I wonder if it'll show up in English.
Let's try the English first, see if it comes up in English.
I'm just playing games, I know that's plastic.
Wow, was that produced?
101, 101 or whatever?
Plastic.
Plastic love.
Really?
Nothing yet?
Plastic love.
I thought.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Uh, juice, juice?
What?
No, wait, there's a juice, juice version.
Oh, sorry.
I haven't been, like, writing down the set list, but...
That was beautiful.
Thank you so much!
Thank you for the donations!
Thank you guys for all the donations.
You guys are way too generous, for real.
Oh, it's loud.
I only cried a little bit.
Me too.
She really cried a little bit.
Sorry.
Oh,
Matari's not a mod.
Sorry, I'll mod you.
.
Oh, Harry.
I haven't even seen her.
Where is she?
Oh my god.
I'm sorry, where is she?
Join me, join, join, join Join me, join me, join me I'm just
I'm just kidding Don't be really I'm just playing It's just
a game Just be fun, just That's all, it's all It's a closing
If you're here, say something.
Say something.
Where are you?
I'm trying to look at like we're sitting at the same time.
Spotted where?
I don't get night, but I get it.
I get it.
I'm just playing games I know that's plastic love Dance to
the plastic beat I almost put you in time out
just playing games i know that's plastic love dance to the
plastic beat another morning come
oh that's plastic love dance to the plastic beat another
Yay.
Oh my gosh.
It's like a pop drop in my mouth the whole time.
Yum, yum, yum.
You're doing great, man.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Love that?
Well, oh, she's requested what?
Lips of a...
What was it?
an angel with the lips of an angel i wonder if they have it
i don't i don't feel like i don't know why they would ask a
lot yeah with the lips of an angel oh my god there it is no
way they're pretty good
snake may I ask which karaoke software this is this is joy
sound on the switch you need a Japanese account to get it
it's free to download it but to sing you have to get like a
Japanese hold on I don't know why you calling me so late you
need a like a Japanese it's kind of hard to talk right now
because I'm singing so Sorry.
And honey, why are you crying?
Is everything okay?
I gotta whisper because I can't meet you loud.
Well,
the next.
Sometimes I wish she was you.
I guess we never really moved on.
It's really good to hear you.
your voice saying my name is sound so sweet coming from the
lips of an angel hearing those words it makes me weak put on
the cry and I never want to say goodbye but girl you make it
hard to be faithful with the lips of an angel Oh, yeah, you
need to have like a, oh my gosh, there's more?
It's funny that you come in me tonight.
And yes, I've dreamt of you too.
And does he know you're talking to me?
Will it start a fight?
No, I don't think she has a clue.
Well, my girl's in the next room.
Sometimes I wish she was you.
I guess we never really moved on.
It's really good to hear your voice saying my name.
It sounds so sweet coming from the lips of an angel There in
those words it makes me weak And I never wanna say goodbye
But girl you make it hard to be faithful With the lips of an
angel Okay, yes you need a Japanese account But you also
need to get a Japanese Nintendo, you need yen.
It's like 300 yen, no, 500 yen for 24 hours.
So if you know a site that will like sell like Japanese
e-cars, e-sim cards, not sim cards.
You know what I mean, Nintendo Box.
It's really good to hear your voice saying my name.
It sounds so sweet.
Coming from the lips of an angel Hearing those words, it
makes me weak And I want to say goodbye But girl, you make
it hard to be faithful I
say goodbye But it's hard to be faithful The lips of an
angel
And honey, why are you calling me so late?
E-shop card, yes, thank you.
Not someone saying those Spotify ads are getting crazy.
Man, so funny.
There's actually a song I want to sing.
I don't know if they have it, though.
Because every time I would go to karaoke to sing this song,
it'd always be some weirdo remix version.
I wonder if they have it.
Do you guys know?
Actually, can you adjust the...
Yeah, I think you can.
Oh, they don't have it!
Wow.
It's not called golden, wait.
Oh, slumbers.
I had me sweating for a second.
I did not read golden slumbers.
I like you so much.
Thank you for being my- Oh, I wonder if they have it.
I'll check it, I'll check.
Which one would it be, though?
This one, right?
Oh, they do have it!
Nice!
Oh my gosh.
Great, Billy Mays.
Thank you for the Akadano!
Did somebody say Nintendo Bucks?
Oh yeah.
I'll never... Actually, maybe I have sung this one before.
I wonder if it's the...
Oh,
my throat.
Oh, my throat.
But, you're a high-stead, and you're always going to go.
I'm always looking at you.
The final win, you're on the road.
I'm going to run.
I'm going to cry.
I
hope this stays archived.
Me too.
It would be really embarrassing.
It would be really embarrassing to come back and have my
first stream back be unarchived.
There was something else that I thought of.
While I was singing that, I can't remember.
Sing sing?
Oh, Fanta is also a good one.
Okay, let me start making notes, so I don't forget me.
Um.
I'll do Fanta first.
Wait, wait.
Oh, uh, fa.
Can it do a small...
Oh wait.
Fah.
There we go.
Fansa.
Crazy frog.
What?
Oh my gosh.
Wait, no way.
There's a hololive version of it.
That's so cool.
Wait, what's different about it?
What?
So I guess this is from the Hollow Live Honeyworks
crossover?
But what's different about it, I wonder?
Let's try it.
Ooh.
The hamster song.
Pina, pina, pina, pina, pina, pina, pina, pina, pina, pina,
pina, pina, pina, pina, pina, pina, pable.
Maybe the same.
I'll do everything, I'll do it all.
NG-N-S-C-N-S-D-A-T-R-I-T-Challenge
Ego-Sode-M-I-N-T-A-N-T-N-K-Me-Busage No, who's more than you
know who's better But it's okay, stay the way it's better
Everyone's better, everyone Let's go, yeah, I'll be back
And I'll be back again With the love-commoned, I'll give you
a kiss more more fun night I love Love love I love
love love love
I'm going to make it happen, I'm still alive Go ahead and
give it more I'm still crying, more The end of the world I'm
still holding up I'm still holding my heart My heart is
fully, more Still, still, still, still More, still, take
care of me I'm still feeling the world I'm still feeling
like
My throat is giving out My throat is giving out What's it
all?
What's it all?
Stronger More Love Love More More Don't forget Don't forget
It's a special day It'll be It will be Together we sing
Let's sing Together Let's move Always The words are
To-be-kiri L-O-B-E
I'm still eating this one cough drop.
Oh my god.
Yay, fan style.
Oh my gosh, that was so cute, the hollow beam.
Mint, are you taking a karaoke request?
I am.
Suzume by Radwims.
Oh, I don't know it.
I'm so sorry.
It's probably on here.
I could do another Radwims.
song.
Oh my gosh, thank you for the Akato.
I hope you know how amazing you are, how much you need to
us.
No matter what you decide to do in the future, we will
support you.
I'll set your taxes.
I will.
Thank you.
I don't want to do my taxes.
Red Knight Circulation.
Oh, I could do red Knight Circulation.
It's fast though.
I don't know if I can do it so quickly.
Hollow Live Songs.
I wonder what Hollow Live Songs are on here.
Actually, I'm curious.
like if we just search Hollow Live which one would it be
though the English one or the Japanese one also I am taking
requests so I will sing So Sen Aquarium
Whoa I don't think I I could sing many of them confidently
though.
Maybe another time.
Next time, next time, next time, next time.
Like I know shiny smiley story the mostest, but I still
don't feel confident.
But there's a lot on here.
I wonder if I do the Japanese if it changes.
Wait, so no, hello EM?
Oh, wait, wait.
Let me try...
Let me try if I search like a member.
Oh, what did I just click?
Oh, oopsie.
Kiss, kiss, kiss, kiss.
Kiss, kiss.
What advice?
Let's see.
Like, cari...
Cariope.
Oh, wait.
No.
Oh, no.
Oh!
Orki...
Ah!
Wait, it would be Takanashi.
Ta...
Takanashi...
Oh, okay.
No!
Ah, man.
That's okay.
In English, maybe?
Oh, we can try.
I actually have a video.
from the last time I went to karaoke.
Um, Kaleiope had a message.
Oh!
No way!
Oh my god!
Kaleiope is on here!
For real!
Oh my gosh.
That's so awesome!
Wait, hold on.
Um...
Wait, it's right below it.
I can't read.
Sometimes it's on No What if I What if I just put in Kiara
Kiara Sometimes it's more fun Going seeing what songs they
have on here Than actually like Singing Instead
If I search Wait Kiara Tiara is an equal love song That's so
fun Oh my gosh Oh Wait, this is the, this is the, this is
the, also the Honey Works, um, the Honey Works collab.
That's so funny.
Kobo and Kiara.
Mmm.
She's on here a little bit.
So happy.
Let's go, Kiara.
I love you.
Okay.
Let's see.
Yeah, unfortunately.
this doesn't have like as many songs as it would in like
maybe a japanese karaoke place but it does have a ton which
is really exciting it's really fun so stellar stellar oh my
gosh do you want me to die i don't think i could sing
stellar stellar but i'm sure they have it science game
There's so much hair!
Wow!
Oh my gosh, there's so...
There's so much hair.
Yo!
Baka Mitae?
I wonder if they even have it.
Would it be in Japanese or English?
What is...
Let's try it.
Baka Mitae?
I don't think it was in kanji though.
I don't think this is right, right?
What is this one?
Does it have blue clapper?
It did.
They did have blue clapper.
Love deterrence.
They unfortunately don't have love deterrence.
I'm so sad.
Uh-uh.
Odori ka!
That's not the right lyrics.
No, they don't have the actual baka mitai.
Wait, what's the lyrics for this one?
That's what I like about this.
You can kind of see what the start of the song is.
Dang.
Uh...
Odori ka?
Odori ka.
I like that song too.
You guys are requesting so many.
I'm not gonna be able to do all of them, I'm sorry.
Oh, Dorian.
Wait, I just saw it.
Oh, wait, I saw it.
Oh, kiss, kiss, kiss, kiss.
I think
I have to do plus two.
A love live song?
Maybe.
This is the key I usually sing it.
like they do I always get the part
Oh my god, my throat
me Hey, why why why love you I never had enough but you know
only two I hang out business same love together love
evitar my future and if I can come back again and if I
didn't get to stop it then when I finally stood that lady
and I was an and if I could be someone walk with her.
D-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-rr-rr-rr-r.
My voice!
My
voice!
I long as they say, As a time appears, I'll always celebrate
and get to know it.
What happens?
is a love-alienly love song, what lords?
As a time believes it, I'll always love and love it'll
happen with love, but what we'll get to know is a
love-alienly love and vocals along it
Yay!
Oh gosh, for some reason, doing the doodoodoo's was killing
my throat.
Let me drink some more tea.
Someone earlier requested, so say no query and I should do
that before I forget.
So say...
There it is.
Wait, which one?
I'll quit.
They're both the same.
Weird.
Oh, cool.
There's so many.
Oh, this is like the anime.
And then they're...
Yeah.
Oh my gosh.
Simple and clean.
I could do it.
I could.
The world's beginning of the life, in the life of the dead,
I'm still here, I'm still here, I'm still here, a long time
ago, I'm here for you to hear everything, all my loved ones,
I'm here to take you to take where you're going to go and
where are you going to go?
The answer is a dark,
Oh my gosh, I can't breathe.
A lot of guys, I can't breathe.
A lot of magic wadataki, more than a lot of I'm not gonna
know my own heart.
My own heart, my own heart.
I'm born and I'm born.
One, two, two, three, three, four, three, four,
I said macros, it's Aquarian.
What is happening?
It's my end to 2000 years ago, 2000 years ago, I've loved
you.
8,000 years from now, I've more so much I've loved it.
It's my end to 2000 years ago, I've loved you.
Till I get back to you, on that day From my own self to the
end of my world, Music is continuing You always go back and
become an adult and become far from the far away from the
world, I'm looking at my never-never-neighbor-no- I'm always
there, but I'm somehow, Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh!
To The thought that I'd sing To love One million years or
2000 I love you I've been loving Eight thousand years This
year, I've been having more and more loved you One year and
2000 Even after me, I've been I've been loving you
It can't kill me
twice.
The cough adds to it.
You think so?
Here, I'm going to eat some of our pizza.
We'll take a little snack break.
Mm-hmm.
A little snack break.
Does the ghost get sick?
There's ghost germs, obviously.
You know, just happens and stuff.
AKB?
I can't even imagine the amount of AKB is on here.
Do you have a specific AKB song?
I feel like I'm seeing so many suggestions of songs that
I've seen so many times.
Request a Haruko Momoi song.
Yes!
Oh my gosh, yes!
Actually, that reminds me.
I wanted to sing Love Yixi earlier.
I thought about it.
But actually, there's another one.
haven't um mint i've definitely never seen you before but i
can definitely tell already i would love your content really
thank you thank you floss on the menu i've never i could try
can we get a shiny days yes we can okay i have a list i have
a list you guys i have a list oh simple and clean break
stuff i have a list i have a list i have a list i have a
list 24-hour Cinderella If they didn't have Bakamita I don't
think they'll have 24-hour Cinderella
Look at all this It can be But yeah, I feel like I'm I don't
know Just seeing suggestions of songs That I've seen a lot
In other streams This is our opportunity to sing songs that
you may have not seen on stream before.
But you want to hear.
I can't guarantee that I'll know it.
But I can try.
Anytime anywhere.
Who's that by?
I'm not sure I know it.
When you see these puffs?
This is puff.
Feed them up.
God, there is so much...
Do you see the scroll bar?
Oh, she ate her mommy.
Actually, there is a...
There is an AKB song I want to sing.
I love this AKB song.
I love this song.
Any Lala Land?
I always sing Lala Land.
I put Lala.
I keep writing Lala Lady when I'm typing it.
Lala Lady, then I put Lala Landy.
And
then Mayuyu shows up and she's so beautiful.
What song was it?
The last song?
What was the last song I said?
Yeah, Aquarian.
Oh my gosh, sorry, there's a little bit of lag for me.
new carousy got a new carousy that's what I wanted to get
you know you were the best your own carousy 11th of the
Anklets I can't even even get rid of the two of you gave me
that day two of the two chivalry sayonara me hello If you're
more than a bit more than you, I'd be able to If you've
never seen me again, will you give me more than I'd be
afraid to give up?
Whoa, oh,
oh, oh, oh, yeah To be the happy news, no-no I'm not going
to be the next one to the other Keep you close, and you feel
like you're right here
Oh my god, I'm getting the timing wrong.
Where's my memory?
My super-atives are seen Oh, for me, oh, oh, oh, oh Pursing
the sun, watered, wicky, even getting it, my memories will
always be somewhere somewhere
somewhere.
My family's angrily together
Okay, I'm gonna try and write a set list.
Do we remember what we sang?
Oh gosh.
I gotta try and write a set list, you guys.
Set list.
One.
What was the first song that I sang?
Oh my gosh.
No way!
You have the whole thing!
Shimaji, thank you!
Ghostbusters.
Two.
Ike nai borderline.
Three.
Four, snake eater.
Five, plastic love.
Six, ikanaide.
Seven, fanza.
Eight, odori ka.
Nine, Genesis Aquarian.
Ten, the end clip of November.
Do Ichigatsu?
No, Anklet.
By Akebi.
This is probably nobody knows.
Oh, sorry, I just realized it's so big.
Hold on, give me a second.
Let's see, outline.
Let's give it a pretty...
black.
There we go!
We're back, baby!
back baby let's do a different font this one no that's ugly
why does it look like that why is it look even worse um this
one whatever it's fine how long have i been streaming for
Almost three hours.
I'm gonna probably finish up these songs that I have written
down.
And then I'm gonna call it, I think.
But that's okay.
It's still one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight
songs.
It's still eight songs.
Oh, Lips of an Angel.
He is missing.
You're right.
I trusted you.
When did I sing that?
Heavens Divide Final Added.
Okay, that will be the last song I sing.
Oh.
What happened?
Okay.
Oh, I have a list.
Sorry if you just heard the biggest gulp I've ever done in
my life.
I don't think I...
I don't think I've chewed that properly.
I think if I sing the song, I'm going to cry.
I don't know.
For some reason, the song makes me cry.
But I'll do my best.
Oh.
Um, wait, who's it by again?
Oh, there it is.
I hope
you're hydrated enough throughout the karaoke.
I am, thank you!
Okay.
Sing, sing a song.
Sing out loud.
Sing out strong.
Sing of good things, not bad.
Sing of happy and not sad.
Sing, sing a song.
Make it simple to pass your whole life long.
Don't worry that it's not good enough.
for anyone else to hear just sing sing a song
sing sing a song let the world sing a love sing of love
there
Sing a song Make it simple To last your whole life long
Don't worry that it's not good enough For anyone else to
hear Just sing Sing a song Just sing, sing a song.
Just sing, sing a song.
I don't think, I don't think my version does justice the
version that I like to listen to.
Sing.
Actually, there's another Carpenter song that I've been
listening to a lot.
Wait, what's it called again?
Oh, shoot, hold on.
Um, one second.
Uh, yeah.
Carpenters are so good.
I know, right?
I've never sung this one before.
So it might be bad.
I wonder if there's Final Fantasy.
Oh my gosh, every time I'm just like, this is all the songs
that I sing, that I will sing.
I change my mind.
I'm just like, wait, I wonder if there's Final Fantasy songs
on here that I could sing.
Close to you.
They are like eyes on me.
I want to sing it.
Ah, let's go.
I've never sung this song.
before I'm kind of nervous why
do birds suddenly appear every time you are near just like
me they long to be close to you why do stars Fall down from
the sky Every time you walk by Just like me They long to be
Close to you My throat is giving out a little bit On the day
that you were born The angels got together And decided to
create a dream come true So they sprinkled moon dust in your
hair and golden starlight in your eyes of blue That is why
all the girls in town follow you all around Just like me
they long to be close to you The
day that you were born, the angels got together and decided
to create a dream come true.
So they sprinkled moon dust in your hair of gold and
starlight in your eyes of blue.
That is why all the girls in town follow you.
All around Just like me They long to be Close to you Just
like me They long to be Close to you
What To
you Close to you
Close to you
Close to you Close to you Alright Haruko, Haruko, Haruko,
Haruko
Oh, no, no, no, no, kiss, kiss, kiss Oh, I wanted to also
sing maybe some Dempagumi.
There's too many songs I want to sing.
Wait, since I can't do a dot, maybe just the EXE.
No, no.
Okay, space.
E.
X.
No!
Okay, hold on.
Let me search Momo and Haruko.
Let's see what they have.
I'm a 10-hour stream for real though.
No, I'm not going to keep you guys so long.
Don't worry.
Do.
They do have under-17, which is another...
Pop-o-ton!
I wasn't going to sing Pop-o-ton, but I was thinking of
another under-17 song.
Wait, is this mouse?
Chew, mouse.
Oh, no, there's mouse.
Wait, they do have I Know Medicine.
That's the one I was going to sing, not Popatan.
Ah, they do have it.
I just had to search Baldur Force instead.
Okay.
I'll have to do it.
Yeah, I'll have to do a dedicated karaoke stream sometime.
Okay,
sorry.
Okay, let me have you.
I pray among the stars I pray among the stars
Oh, it's all you call it right away, be a moment.
Oh my gosh, kanji sometimes.
Exe!
Natsokashi, uta-goe!
Now can- Sinku no-naka-de-mong-ke-tolerant
Why?
T-t-t-t-t-t-t-t- T-tut-tut-tut This is the only way to
That's what you do with your art moments.
You kind of like making eggs.
Hey drink!
I'm having so much fun though Even though my throat is
starting to get worse and worse, I don't want to stop
Actually, since I did that one, no, I lied.
I am going to do that one.
I said I was like, maybe I'll only do one Momoi Haruko song.
No.
I want to do two.
This is one of my favorite anime ever.
The list gets longer.
It dies.
Wait, I need to also set list.
Y-E-X-E Y-E-X-E No, no, no, no, no, no, don't X-E-R Don't
X-E-X- Um,
M-Umm Futeyde, muc, muc, muc, d-r-duc, d-duc, d-duc, d-u,
d-u, Oh, yeah, there's no other way.
Oh, my god.
Oh, no, see-thens.
Oh, see, the show's-thens Even though you can't hear it.
Magical, magical, nice.
It's a wonderful, it's a lovely, but it's always good.
Oh, it's a good thing.
It's a good thing.
me me more more more
heart chibi semming ha ha ha I kikaru kikaru jenasi
yaki mochi kanaii kaii
I love this show so much Soul takers fine too but I love
Nursu Ichikamugi the most
I'm okay.
That was I know medicine.
I know medicine my that was my medicine Are you yeah, I'm
okay
next song Next song
Sorry guys, I already have if you're still sending songs I
already have a list that I'm gonna That I've already decided
I did unless I decide to add my own wait is it shiny with an
E or oh just a little oh there it is right right below shiny
smiley story
ahsaka i love asaka asaka maybe has become like one of my
top not maybe she is one of my top favorite anisong singers
she's so awesome she's so nice i love her.
I love her so so much.
Happy Yudocamp Day everybody!
Every day of the day, open the light of the light.
Right now, the beginning is the beginning.
Shiny days, a new wind.
How's it under?
No, no, no, no step.
Go my way.
Can you feel the sepidora's solar?
Mnecowagi, bring a brand new world.
Listen to the melody.
Talk a little bit.
If it's going to sound, we'll be back to the future.
Look, look,
look.
Look, look.
Cloudless sky.
So happy.
Cool, cool, cool.
It's a natural, small, cool.
One by one, Right, right, right, right there.
A little bit of courage, a little bit of courage to move
around the world.
All right, wherever you can go.
Shiny days, wherever you go, wherever you go.
It feels so good.
Can you sing?
Please save your memories Casting it to go To the future
Take it easy Take it easy Take it easy Take it easy Let's go
today
Oh god, I'm so sorry.
I'm gonna cut
some of the song list and have it cut some of it out I'm so
sorry
I'm okay
I can't stop I can't stop okay we'll do one last song If I
can make one more.
I don't even know if I can.
Oh, that.
I have another cough drop.
And I drink.
Um, sorry.
Someone suggested Diamond Crevice.
I really want to sing it, but I don't think I'll be able to.
Or break stuff.
Or la-la-lan.
Or simply clean.
But I'll just have to do another karaoke sometime.
Right?
Let me check if this is good.
One second.
Okay.
Yeah, good enough.
Last song, everybody.
I'm so sorry about that.
I wish I could sing more, but, um.
thank you again for welcoming me back so warmly I didn't
expect so many people to be here but I really appreciate it
thank you for all the donations thank you for subbing thank
you for even just remembering me even a tiny little bit I
really really really really really appreciate it I'm so
shocked but um yeah really happy to be here, be able to hang
out with you guys some more, and everything.
Look at that, the cough drops helped so much.
Maybe I can do diamond crevice.
No, I shouldn't, I shouldn't.
I'll save it for next time.
Glamathara introduced me to you.
Yeah, thank you.
Thank you so much.
I'm just a little ghost, and I'm just a little maid.
but I'll do my best to hopefully we can have a fun time and
make lots of awesome memories and yeah
thank you for the Hakadono thank you hope we weren't too
flustered by all your new adoring fans keep rocking and
being you we believe in you thank you thank you I can't wait
to do so many things that I own a Metal Gear patchy slot
machine.
I don't, I haven't thought, like, I don't know at all what
I'm doing next week.
I don't know when the next stream is even.
I don't know anything.
So I hope that you guys will be a little patient with me.
I kind of just really jumped back in.
I was just like, you know what?
I'll come back on Thursday.
And now, like, I don't think I'm going to stream tomorrow.
know i'll try and make schedules um yeah it's just uh how
about some block game i don't i don't know i don't have a
server or anything but i guess i should start streaming soon
so i can hit monetization or something i don't know it's
fine okay where did my other joycon go oh i dropped it okay
that's Yeah, back with our revengeants.
Yeah, back with our revengeants.
So,
I'm really excited.
Like I said, I'll keep doing my best.
Thank you guys for allowing me back.
So, here's to you.
Well, it's not here's to you, but here's to you.
Well, well, I thought the song would start sooner.
Petals of white cover fields flowing in grieving tears.
And all the hearts once new, old and shattered now.
Love can kill.
Love will die, give me wings to fly.
Bleeding this world so cold, I just wonder why.
Cold as the dark, now my words are frosted with every
breath.
Still the hate burns wild, growing inside this heart.
When the wind changes course, when the stars light, I will
reach out to you and leave this all behind but heaven's
divine I will see the choices within my hands how can we
ever protect and fight with our tiny souls let me shine like
the sun Through the doubts and fear Do you feel the storm
approach As the end draws near With heaven's divide Time
will come to softly lay me down Then I can see a face That I
long to see And for you I would give anything Leaving a
trace for love
I will dive into the fire Spilling the blood of my desire
The very last time My name scorched into The sky When
heavens divide The choices within my hands How can we ever
protect and fight with our tiny souls?
Let me shine like the sun Through the doubts and fear Do you
feel the storm approach as the end draws near?
When heaven say bye, time will come To softly lay me down
Then I can see a face That I long to see And for you Only
you I would give anything Leaving a trace for love To find
out Leaving a trace for love Find a way When heavens Divide
See
you guys Next one I see you Thank you, thank you, thank you
See you next one
Thanks a lot Thank you