Do you miss me?
You'll be hearing a lot of that today, I think.
You'll be hearing a lot of that today.
And my congested snuffle.
Don't die, please.
I'm already dead!
Min-to-chan-o-Kai-i-i-tadaima!
Still coughing?
What do you mean, still?
Um...
I...
I basically just got sick.
Welcome back!
Thank you!
Daaku!
Oh, kind of big.
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
Thank ye.
Hi!
Oh!
Hi, everybody!
I'm home.
I'm back.
Okaidino-san-i-mosei-go-shin-tama-o-jo-shama!
Thanks for the pink.
If we need to contact you for something, can we do it via
ritual summons?
Or a Luigi board?
Preferably.
Not a Luigi board.
I mean, you would think that those are like kind of great,
but...
It's not so good.
Because a whole bunch of lines get crossed.
cross, you know.
And Draco's thanks for the tag, gift, dude!
Welcome home, thank you!
Why not Luigi board?
Because, I just said, so many other ghosts are just like...
It's my turn to use the Luigi board, so you won't probably
get me.
They'll probably get someone else.
Some freak.
Oh my god.
They say it's me.
They'll be like, they'll be like, um, hello.
I'm Richard.
And so, I know, you're speaking to Mint.
Well, how can I help you?
You're like, wow, the connection makes you sound really
weird.
You're like, and the ghost is just like, Ah, yeah, I'm just
a little shy.
Voice reveal.
Are you saying we'll get frog burt even better?
That guy, he's not dead.
What are you talking about?
That guy's not dead?
Anyway, we can talk with some...
What's the word?
Some...
Balloon's BGM.
So, a couple things happen.
First, I went to Off Kai.
I went to Off Kai.
I didn't get to really talk about it.
Well, I talked about it in the podcast with Matara.
If you listen to that.
Um...
but uh that was a while ago now I guess right it was a quit
some time ago and um uh off Kai my beloved not mine well yes
I had a great time but uh saw you got swarmed at a on a
robot at off Kai I did I did I thought I thought I was going
to be able to go around and like explore.
No.
I just, I got carried to once.
I didn't even get to move myself.
I got picked up like a baby.
I felt like I got picked up like a child.
And I was carried to one location and people lined up.
That was funny.
But thank you, Oshi Live, for having that happen.
And, oh my goodness, what else happened?
We did a panel, it was a lot of fun.
And Matara and I, I mean as we.
And go, go, go, go, baby Minto, go, go, go.
And, I mean, if you want probably better, better, You should
probably go listen to the podcast episode.
The next podcast episode, we recorded.
We recorded and that was good fun because it's just the two
of us being little sickies.
Sick hags.
The stream summary I got is Progbert is no longer on the
streaming platform.
form and viewers are upset okay that guy give that guy a
break okay he'll come back eventually
um is that the one from the tiny room oh my gosh i did talk
about it in the last in the last in the last episode kind of
what happened with our hotel um i guess i could be a little
bit more specific now because neither of us are staying
there anymore i think i believe matara is still in japan but
um she moved to a different hotel so um but oh my goodness
the fake apartment hotel oh i was so i i don't think like
the the the i i would like matara to describe the look on my
face when we first stepped into that room and I was just
like, huh?
Like just pure disappointment.
For, well, shock and disappointment and confusion and
everything.
Angry ghost.
Oh, I...
Oh my gosh.
You got ripped off.
No, no, no.
I mean, I think...
I think what...
Okay, so I know what had happened.
I searched, I searched apartment hotels in Japan because
those are totally a thing and I don't do Airbnb.
I already said this on the podcast but I'm so, so angry
about it that I'll say it again.
Um, and so, but the hotel we stayed at, you know what, I'm
just going to name it because I'm never going to stay there
again.
out of, I'm just going to name it because I'm never going to
stay there again out of fear of, of, of booking the wrong
hotel again.
And I do believe that it was Expedia's fault because, hold
on, I'm going to Google it right now.
So it was called Monday Hotel, Monday Hotel Apprentice.
apartment.
Now, I need to know where I messed up.
How...
Where did the mistake happen?
I hate Mondays.
Oh my god, it actually is so funny because I was just...
I literally was like, I hate Mondays because of this.
So...
okay this is also where the confusion happened because I
booked the premium version of the hotel I see I'm looking at
the pictures right now and it says oh but it says apartment
premium that see when you think a premium hotel I was just
like oh maybe that's what they call their larger size rooms
right which technically they were kind of larger size than
like a normal business hotel
confusing and so i booked for the monday premium hotel and
not the monday apartment premium hotel which was literally
right down the street literally right down oh and there's
some there are a bunch of these actually wow actually i
didn't realize they were so abundant in in tokyo but That's
just bad naming.
I know, right.
Ah, that's so frustrating.
And the worst part is, is, well, not the worst part.
I mean, it was still a very nice hotel.
But if you are ever trying to get an apartment hotel, book
for the apartment premium hotels, not the regular premium
hotels.
Because also, I only booked, I booked very, not booked, I
packed very few clothes.
I was just like, oh, I'll just do laundry like every, day
because we'll have a washer and dryer in our bedroom no
worries so i had like no clothes and i was having to go to
the laundry like so much and it cost it's expensive it's 300
yen to wash your clothes and then 100 yen for 30 minutes in
the dryer it was so it was just i was miserable i was so
miserable and then i was stuck in my little room with madara
the whole The whole trip Was fine I got to go out for two
days And I bought some clothes So I'm glad about that
Because I did buy some clothes But I didn't get to get I
didn't get to get all the clothes Like I was like Oh I
forgot to get these other things that I wanted I'll go back
out tomorrow the day I basically was sitting in the hotel
room and I was like, oof, my body feels heavy.
I wonder if this is delayed jet lag.
And then I like took a nap.
And then while I was napping, I woke up like at 9 p.m.
And I was like, uh-oh, I have chills.
And I was like, uh-oh, I don't think this is just my body
being heavy anymore.
Oh.
Did you get to visit any maid cafes or idol shows?
Yes, luckily.
The day after we arrived, there was an idol show that we got
to go to.
And so we went there.
That was good.
And then the day after, the day after, we were actually
supposed to go to a theme park.
We were going to go to Fujikil with a couple people.
Matara was like I don't know man I'm starting to not feel so
good and I saw a lot of people saying that they got COVID at
off Kai but none of the people that we interacted with got
COVID so we were like hmm but she was like I'm really not
feeling well so I think I'm gonna I think I'm gonna test
because I don't want to go out with people and get them sick
you know like she was there was a few people a few other
vtubers that we didn't know very well either and we were
like she was like i don't know how you know how their bodies
are i'm a roach i can survive but she was like i'm you know
concerned about the other people and so um fujikyu
we couldn't go because she tested and then it was yeah got
covid and then i was like well if you're sick i'm probably
sick and then i tested because one of the things that we
were wanting to do or actually the reason i went to japan on
this trip i was originally not going to go on this trip but
the reason i went on this trip was for one reason and we
didn't get to do it because um and uh it was vishojo staff
was helping us um it up and uh basically they were like hey
you guys said you have covid so we're gonna have to cancel
and i was like wait wait wait wait wait i feel fine i feel
fine let me test let me test if i can still if i'm fine can
i still do it and they were like oh and then i tested and i
was negative and i was like i'm fine i'm fine i'm a liar i i
just posted because i assumed and you know what assuming it
makes the ass out of you and me so i was like oh no Please
let me go!
And then I ended up getting sick after all.
I can still fight.
That was literally me.
I was like, no, no, no, wait, wait!
I was like, what?
I made a mistake!
Because in Japan they're still very, very serious about that
kind of stuff.
So, especially if you say, Hi, I have COVID, they're just
like, Oh, cancel everything.
We will, we will quarantine, quarantine.
So we were like, Okay, well, mint's fine.
Send her in.
And then the next day, I got sick.
But it was maybe the next day, day after.
I think it was the day after.
And I was like, oh, shoot.
So we stayed in our hotel room the whole time, basically.
And, yeah.
I did go out.
The day before I started feeling bad, I did go to Akiba.
And Akiba, it was so weird.
It was really weird.
Like, the place was packed, first of all, because there was
an Atlas festival that was going on.
And there was just so many people for that.
And already, Akiba is pretty crowded because of tourists.
So, um, it was crazy, crazy, crazy.
Let me see if I have, I took, I posted, I think, though, um,
I didn't take very many pictures because I didn't know how
many pictures I could take.
Um, I think I, there was one.
Did I take a video?
I could hear, like, a concert going on inside.
No, I didn't take a video.
I only took, I only took the photos.
Um, but uh so that was crazy and then I was like I wanted to
go to um just a maid cafe to like chill um I was like I'll
go to a better you know not a better I was like I'll go to
like a you know a you know stereotypical maid cafe in the
upcoming days today I just want to I just want to like chill
I want to like so I was like I'll go to cure made cafe I'll
go to cure made cafe there's a oh like an hour and a half
two hour wait and I was like excuse me I have never never
ever ever had to get a reservation I was like what that's
crazy and so I put in a reservation and then I um I went
downstairs and there was a lucky star Haruhi 20th
anniversary pop-up store so I was like And I was like, wavy,
this is cool.
And you don't want to chill in line for the May Cafe?
There wasn't a line.
It was you put in a little, you apply for a reservation, and
then they call you back.
They were like, feel free to go anywhere and walk around.
So I did that.
Maya bones, I know, right?
I was like 20th?
I was like, I think there's a misprint or something.
I meant to go back.
Poor innocent me.
Thinking back, I was like, I'm not going to buy much of
anything because I'll just come back and get it another day.
So I didn't end up buying.
There was like a cute little acrylic calendar that I was
going to get.
So I ended up not getting anything from it.
I'm so sad.
I didn't want to carry stuff around.
um little did she know but uh and then i was like well i was
like in the store for a while and i was like man it's still
a lot of time before i have to go back to the maid cafe so i
was walking around some more and i was like you know what um
let's see you know cure maid cafe had a really long wait
let's go check out um jam jam is another really chill maid
cafe and so i went there and i saw that they had a Kagura
Nana collab and I was like oh my gosh wait this is so
awesome and so I was like I'll go here instead and so I
canceled my reservation for cure and they were like even
though they were like it's almost your time and I was like
no I want to go to this one instead and Nana mama is so cute
I know I know everything was so cute but I go in there and
there's they also they're like uh you have to come back in
an hour and a half is that okay and i was like
okay i think uh i think the collab at the cure made cafe was
like day a live so i was like i'd rather do nana mama um so
even though i canceled i was going to do nana mama anyway so
i was like Okay, I'll just wait another hour and a half.
I'll just do another hour and a half.
Wait, no worries.
Even though I had been waiting so much before.
And so I was like, you know what?
It's fine.
I'll go to Culture Zone, which is a big building of just a
bunch of stuff.
There's a bunch of floors.
The first floor was...
Oh my gosh, it was absolutely insane.
There was like, there was just, there were like children,
like, on the floor, like, playing with figures and stuff.
And I was like, what is going on?
Is this a Toys R Us?
Like, so I went upstairs because there's an idol store in
Culture Zone that I go to called Trio.
And I go there, I go to the trio, and it's gone.
And I was like, no!
But it actually, they moved floors, I believe they.
actually get to go because um i uh got distracted by some
other stuff and i went into one store okay this is why i
said like i when we first arrived in japan matara was just
like man that whole trip it felt it felt like we're the
we're in the twilight zone like and i was like that's i
think that's the whole theme of this trip it just felt like
the twilight zone everything just felt a entire time and I
was like what is going on what a curse trip it really was my
flight back was so cursed like the plane was having luckily
it was not a Boeing but it was having it was having tech
issues and like the lights kept flashing on and on like you
know how like in the middle of a international flight
they'll turn the lights off so that you can sleep the lights
would just
everybody's sleeping and then the music would start blaring
because they were trying to fix the sounds we didn't even
get to watch the safety video because they were having so
many technical issues and like sometimes the music would
they had like a radio that they would play and it would just
start blaring music in the middle of the flight it was so
cursed and um but yeah i was in culture and I was in a
random store looking around because sometimes I like to
just...
There's like these stores that have cubes of figures and I
like to see if I can find any Metal Gear stuff in there.
But I was in a random store and some guy came up to me and
he was like, in English, he asked me, are you looking for
anything in particular?
I said, no, just looking.
Which that has never happened to me before.
I was like, huh?
Like I thought he was a...
But I had never been in that store before Haunted plane.
My bad.
Sorry.
But you got tourists.
Like, that has never happened to me.
Or someone came up and was just like.
Hey, are you looking for something?
It was very strange.
I was like, oh, no, I'm fine.
I'm just looking.
Thank you.
And I left.
Because I was like, don't talk to me.
Even if you're a store attendant.
Please don't talk to me.
And I went to the next floor and there was a Toho collab,
which of an artist who specified in Remilia Sama.
So I was just like, ooh, yippee!
So I got some stuff there.
But the guy also, there was a guy there who also started
talking to me.
But this time in Japanese, he was just like, Toho ga Ski
desuka.
And I was just like, yeah, I love Toho.
And then he started talking to me and asking me questions.
worked here but i was like thank you did our covid cycles
sync up
but um but i was like huh why are you talking to me why are
you asking me questions but then the guy the guy from the
from the previous store comes to be again.
He walks into this store and he starts asking me questions
again in English.
And I'm like, wait, you weren't a store attendant in the
last one.
He was just some random guy asking if I was looking for
something.
He wasn't even an employee.
And he was, I don't even remember what he was asking me.
I was so shocked.
I was like, why are you here?
What?!
He works at both locations.
I was so confused.
I was like, I literally thought he was an employee of the
previous store.
So I was like...
He's the building manager.
I think he was asking me like, um, uh, uh, if I like was
studying or, you know, just those things.
kinds of like questions you ask foreigners I was reverse
haunted by this guy I was like so funny but it was so
bizarre I've never been I've been asked I've never been
talked to in Akiba like that so I was like maybe because
there was such an influx of foreigners that day I don't know
but um I got some of the I got some Toho stuff.
So that was fun.
And then by the time everything had finished, it had already
been an hour and a half.
So I got the hell out of there before that guy could come
back to the next.
He probably, I was like, I wonder if he went to the next
floor and was waiting for me there.
I was like, wait.
So I ran.
I was like, well, this guy surely doesn't have a
reservation.
for Jam Akihabara so I ran away.
Oh, he just really wanted to practice his English.
See, usually, like, that's, I don't find that ever to be the
case with people.
Very rarely do people want to practice their English.
Oh, my goodness.
But, yeah.
So that was a very strange time.
I was, I was like, what?
Akiba is just strange today.
The whole I'm in the twilight zone.
I didn't, it was just such a weird trip.
Um, and then, like I said, I got sick, so Matara and I, we
just laid in bed for four days, and then I went home.
So, yeah.
I'm very sad that, um, I do feel like it was a waste of a
trip.
I feel, um, hold on, let me take a sipie.
I feel very like I, uh, wasted a lot of money and time and
everything going, which, um, I mean, obviously we couldn't
have known, but.
It just really.
Would you have stayed longer if you didn't get sick?
No, no, I left.
I actually left a little bit early.
And a dot very early, like, just a day early, because I was
like, there's no point in me staying here.
So I just, uh, yeah, it was, it's, I just, I think I'm most
disappointed, or not, well, not disappointed, I'm most
frustrated because, um, in July, I've kind of really
overbooked myself, and so now I'm just, like, having to
plan, I was planning on going to, like, maybe, like, go
around Anime Expo a little bit, since I'm going for the, um,
for the virtual concert but I've decided that I'm just gonna
go to the concert and then head back immediately because
I've already missed so much time streaming and I'm also
going to have to probably go back to Japan in July sometime
so Matara and I are trying to figure that out too and it's
like it's uh it's uh yeah I I'm just really frustrated about
it.
Yeah, yeah.
But oh well.
Hmm.
Oh well.
Don't worry about us if that's the case.
But I mean I do.
Not.
I mean.
Wait.
Hold on.
I'm trying to do.
I worry.
like I mean It's just like that whole If I'm not making
content I'm not doing anything With my channel There was
stuff that I did Get to take care of while in Japan And
hopefully some cool things that Happen Of things that I was
doing But I didn't have to be in Japan for those things Is
the thing Because Matara was just like Look at all the stuff
you got done And I was like, I would have gotten that done
in my maid cafe too.
That's rough brosuke.
Why do you hate us?
No!
Um, I was rather saying, it's, it's like, I'm not like, oh,
I'm not worried about, like, what, I would have you guys
forget about me.
But I kind of worry about that.
I kind of...
I kind of worry about that.
According to YouTube, you are frustrated at anime expo.
So frustrated.
But yeah.
Hmm.
Were you able to receive gifts from...
Mintos?
From who?
Me?
Are Oshi's a little tundere?
What do you mean by that?
You'd have to do a lot better than that to get rid of the
worst.
Yeah, you're stuck.
You're stuck.
Good.
Wear mint toes.
I can count nine of them right now.
Anyway, yeah, so I really wish I could say more about my
trip, but I don't quite have so much about my trip.
You know, just kind of...
Nine!
Well, isn't that quite mysterious?
let's see guys let's see let's see where do we want to go
today I have to unlock some of these harder ones rake oh oh
I can unlock it wait click to unlock oh be the beginner map
oh Haunted!
Looking forward to the concert during AX.
I tried to buy the VIP tickets, but they sold out so fast.
You girls are so popular.
It's crazy.
Good luck.
Thank you!
Oh, thank you for reminding me all that I have to respond to
something.
Looks great!
So cute.
They were showing me some of the stuff for the t-shirts.
The Among Us Toa got ejected for being sus.
Someone went welcome to membo ship, but then they
disappeared.
Was it you, Kenny?
I started my Metal Gear experience with Phantom Pain.
We've done dying from an aneurysm yet, because I lied.
I started with the original on the aneurysm.
I'm old as hell.
Younger than Mata, though.
She's so old.
It was...
No.
Huh, Kenny, huh?
Well, you were gotten something big happened in my life.
A dog I used to watch named DuckDuck was given up by his
mother.
He and I now live together full-time and watch you together.
DuckDuck!
That was a dog's name, DuckDuck.
So, Sophia, thank you so much for the 20 gifted.
Thank you!
I've got an interview for MGS Con 2 staff in like seven
minutes.
Let's go road!
You're gonna staff?
Speaking of Metal Gear.
Oh my god!
I ordered the um...
Dell, thank you for that tiny gift.
Thank you!
Freaky ghost sofa.
Metal Gear.
Let's do Haunted, even though it's a harder map.
We'll do it on medium.
Oh, wait, hold on you guys, hold on before we talk about
Metal Gear.
Look, I have...
Oh, you can't see.
There we go.
I have so much money I can buy a hero.
I was trying the new hero.
Where is she?
Oh, Rosalia.
She's so cute!
Doing subsistence for MGS3.
I don't know yet.
I haven't decided.
We're going to start Metal Gear next week, so.
Iron Fall!
Thanks for the 20 gift, and thank you.
end did i say thank you down already did i thank you thank
you so much thank you for the 10 gift
commencing virtuous mention
thank you so much oh my god oh my god thank you for the
birthday captain thank you guys oh my gosh thank you for the
five thank you guys thank you thank you thank you thank you
so Thank you!
Oh my gosh.
Welcome back, Minto.
Could I get a happy birthday?
It was cursed as you wanna sing it.
It was on June the 2nd.
Happy birthday, Washa.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, happy birthday, happy birthday to you.
I had to do it fast because it's quite past your birthday.
Sorry.
Oh my gosh.
Why are there so many gifted?
Take up.
Thank you.
Thank you for the 10.
Kyle.
Best of fresh Kyle.
Thank you for the 50.
Thank you guys.
Thank you.
Valentine.
Thank you for the 50.
Oh my gosh.
Big Anatomy.
Thank you for the five.
Okuro.
Murphy thinks we're the 10.
Oh my gosh, wait, you gave X for the 20.
Oh my gosh.
Gabo thinks we're the 5.
I can't keep up.
Wait, it's like delayed, though.
It's like delayed.
Stop!
So many gifted.
You'll get us up.
It's too fast.
Stop.
I can't get up.
Oh my god.
KZRaptor, thanks for the five.
Superliminal, thank you for the 20.
Detective Jones, welcome to my blue ship.
Thank you, Joseph.
Thank you for the 20.
C2, thanks for the 10.
KBorn, thanks for the 10.
Rockwell, Roper, thanks for the 10.
Raymack, thanks for the 5.
I cry, but I fart.
Thanks for the 20.
And Drago's thanks for that dying.
Weeping, welcome back.
Well, this truck, thanks for the 5.
J.R., welcome back.
KZR, thanks for the 5.
Roku Yon, thanks for the 5.
I think I'm repeating people.
Niel's, thank you for that 5.
Oh my gosh, you guys, please.
Can you make it for the gifted?
Good playlist, make it for the 10.
You guys are trying to talk.
There we start, thanks for the five.
Joseph, welcome back.
You guys are trying to talk.
Should we buy a new hero is what I'm trying to ask the hero.
Make it back.
Thanks for the five.
See you don't chat.
Invisible Moose.
Thanks for the 10.
Prince of Denmark.
Thanks for the 20.
But let's fix for the 10.
Speak then.
Stofin.
Thanks for the 10.
Should we get a new...
One.
Thank you.
Thank you for the movie.
Lost in the story.
Thanks for the 10.
Kenny, thank you for the...
What?
I saw it.
I saw it before it disappeared.
Cody, thank you for the time.
Which monkey in the is the Nacho Libre monkey?
I don't know.
I don't think he's in this movie.
Buy the coolest one.
No, because he thinks we're the far.
Get him over.
Which is the coolest one?
We have 5,000 monkey bucks.
We could literally... Oh, I was going to say we could
literally buy any of them but we can't buy Geraldo or COVID
virus.
Setsuna, thanks for that, Carol.
Citizen Phoenix, thanks for the time.
Sauta?
She seems pretty cool.
Can pop camo?
Is she good?
Hmm.
I can't believe skins are so expensive too.
Oh.
Quincy.
Those scrolls lead to a quest for the heroes.
Yeah, but you don't get the heroes.
You just get rewards for them.
I'm drunk!
Thanks for the time!
Saurah is the best.
Saurah can solo chumps time.
Really?
Fat, I mean, fat fusty.
It's that creator of XLR20!
Just passed my interview to become a full-time cardiologist
at a hospital.
Let's go, Ashwin!
Wow.
You're smart.
You're a doctor.
You're a real doctor.
So should we get Sada?
Is she pretty good?
It's kind of sad.
Maybe I should save up for the haunted man.
Look, it kind of looks like you a little bit.
Kind of looks like a wisp.
Oh!
I'm going to grab that tooth.
Let's go!
Corvus.
Going on a trip to New York in late August.
Can you recommend some places to see?
I'd love to see Federal Hall for MGS too.
I don't know many places in New York though Something I
think Iran Thanks man You're pretty cool yourself What is
something to do in New York?
Federal Hall I want to go stand where Solidus died You can
catch me on the back of the statue Just like peace sign with
oh my gosh I want to go see where the president died
I'm not I don't plan on going to animate MYC though I
thought maybe to go for the Hollow Life concert but I think
I am too booked up in July and in August so it's kind of
hard over half an hour are we up Oopsie.
Glad to have you back, Mint.
I was happy I got to say hi to you at Afkai.
Catch Mint jumping on the random cargo ships off the
Brooklyn Bridge.
Maya!
I'm so happy to see you back, Mito-Chem.
I'm glad we could see each other at Afkai.
I hope you're feeling okay.
But I didn't get sick at Afkai.
I got sick because of Matara.
fault it's not me tb table tray thanks for the 10 gift thank
you so much i blame the roach as you should should i get
sada because she's cool actually i really want this skin
maybe i'll get her and then save up for this look how cool
she looks actually i've been wanting this the this skin for
a long time The Ryden skin kills me every time.
Hmm.
Shang-Chi skin is so good.
It really is.
It's really cute.
Sada is really good.
All in favor of buying Sada, say I.
Thanks for the Super Chat, too, guys.
Xbox Showcase showed MGS Delta outside my own freakout.
I was wondering.
Oh, boy.
I wonder how Mint is going to react to you.
Got the collected edition and backpack ordered.
I got the, I didn't get the...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, okay, that's
fire!
I didn't get the, I got the, the...
My blade's legendary!
Oh, my blade's legendary!
I didn't get the, I got the other tactical backpack before
they announced the camo one.
But I, I liked mine, I like mine more than the tactical one,
so it's, or the camo one, I mean, so.
Leah's birthday is this week, and I want to surprise her
with a happy birthday from you.
Would you sing her a ghosty happy birthday?
Thank you.
Bia, your friend Leah.
Leah, happy birthday!
I've been asked to sing a happy ghosty.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, dear Leon Happy birthday to you Happy
birthday!
Okay, let's try.
Let's go to Haunted.
Medium is premium.
What is this mean?
Oh, you can't see it because I'm a big head.
Hold on.
I'm gonna scoot down a little bit.
What does...
What does this mean?
I don't know, I've never seen it before.
Are you guys still gifting?
Thank you so much.
Oh my gosh, Joseph, Duffy, I don't even know how many you
gifted, I'm just...
Say your name!
You have an upgrade.
Oh...
You can unlock their final form.
Oh, is that what that means?
Ah!
Wait, like this?
Oh, no I can't.
No I can't.
Morning, two, thanks for the ten.
Hi, Mint.
Hello.
Hello, Mr. Fish.
It's for a challenge.
Ah!
Okay, okay.
Hmm.
Let's try her out.
I'm just gonna put her...
Where should I put her?
Let's make some ribbons.
Some what?
J-May, these are the 10 gifts in.
Thank you.
Oh!
Oh shoot, they come from this way too!
Uh oh.
She was almost on beat for a second.
Mr. Minto!
Oh!
Can you please say, lol, weep, and get wrecked.
Lol, weep, and get wrecked.
I discovered you through Henya.
Are you became easily one of my favorite streamers to watch?
Keep up the dope work, dude.
Thanks, DJ!
Thank you, DJ!
Oh.
the other day sometimes i'm like yeah i'm indie but i can't
i want to like i should behave better sometimes you know i
uh i almost tweeted i almost just tweeted sarah's fauna just
cause i really like her but i'm glad i did it because the
other day she followed me back
I was like I was so happy Real though right She's just so
cute I just kind of like her a normal amount Look at her go
I'm saving up because I want to buy This boat Real tweet it
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Hmm.
Everyone's gonna say bad placement.
Oh!
Normal amount.
Uh-huh.
Thank you, Kaboosh Kaboosh.
Thank you for the gifted.
It's not showing me gifted.
Are these old ones or...
It's not showing me.
It's just showing the people who were gifted.
Oh, I'm Let me move myself somewhere else, sweet.
Where should I go?
I'm kind of just peeking out like a weirdo.
Hmm.
Um.
What if I go here instead?
What if I'm upside down?
What if I...
Hmm.
There's no balloons up here.
Right?
Australian stream now.
She goes so hard.
I'm gonna put another one.
Preemptive.
Preemptive sub.
Detective Jones!
Thanks for the gift!
This is hush money.
Not to wish weep and a happy birthday for the next 10
months.
Him suffering is really funny.
Oh!
Is this hush money to not win?
What's wrong with...
Hey Minto, can we get a tiny Minto in every corner?
Fine, thanks for the 10 gifted, thank you!
Minto finally came to Australia, yubi!
Stinky!
I don't want to be here next to you guys anymore.
This area smells!
Where should I go?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'll just be like a big body here.
Um, I don't know what else to do.
Wait, I'm kind of crooked.
Is this crooked or not?
I feel crooked no matter what I'm at.
Oh, that was better.
That was better.
Okay, I'll just stand here.
Don't touch me.
Don't point fingers at me.
Don't poke me.
Don't.
You're not allowed.
Normal day I've been to her front yard.
What?
You can remove these!
That's me in the window.
Right there, you know.
It's normal things.
Stop!
Stop pointing at me!
Stepping on the balloons.
Yeah.
With my high heels.
Polk the Minto.
Stop it!
I wonder where I should have put her instead.
Did you say hi?
Okay.
Even better!
Are we breaking cafe rules?
Yeah, actually.
Made cafe rules?
You're not supposed to touch the maze.
Full of jelly.
I actually am.
Whoa!
Thanks, Kinky!
Heals.
Yeah, I had so much jelly.
I had so many vitamin jellies.
Oh, I have a jelly right here!
Hold on.
Actually, I can barely taste it.
So sad, but I lost most of my taste, you guys.
I'm having like the full COVID experience.
It sucks.
I can't can I smell it yeah I can smell it
mmm mmm I can taste it cognac grape jelly oh sorry jelly
grape
mmm it's funny because when we when Matara and I were eating
out of place she was we were we went to a cooler sushi
and she was like God the sushi here is so bad the sushi here
sucks this just has no flavor this was before we knew she
was she was just like later on even after she even after she
like knew that she had COVID she was just like, all my food
here has, like, usually I never have, um, usually I never
have bad food experiences in Japan, but this time
everything's been mid.
I'm like, girl, are you?
I was like, Matara, think for two seconds why that would be
in our current situation.
will join the diamond dogs mgscoin volunteers now see you
there yuppie congrats like think for two seconds why you may
not be smelling or tasting stuff well
so silly
look i've been working on my upgrades and stuff i'm kind of
in the way sorry but I will almost have enough for to unlock
this whole thing whoa what's this whoa I don't know what
just happened but nice did she figure it out yeah eventually
you know my boy Darcy is always fighting with this Elizabeth
chick and everybody thinks they hate each other but I could
can see sparks whenever he with her should i tell her to
just confess to her what are what are you cupid over here if
it goes south they're gonna blame you man do you want that
blood on your hands
someone say my name welcome back me though thank you chill
for ice monkey what if we did only ice monkey i don't have
enough for ice monkey I'm... I have to save up for Ice
Monkey.
I'm
gonna put an Ice Monkey in the corner.
Nobody puts Baby in the corner.
I'm gonna put him right next to me.
Hey Ice Monkey!
Look at him, juggle.
Oh my god, the monkey's juggling above my head.
There goes my little balloons.
useless monkey oh my god he has so much xp from doing
nothing
boss focus i i absolutely am i think we'll do this one as
the heats and this one is the twin the twin guns
i love when he spins really fast when he juggles really fast
it's so funny i clapped when i saw ice monkey
They showed MGS Delta Trailer, I thought I was Ace
Comforter.
They showed the planes.
I'm sorry.
That scene is so iconic, though.
Had to have been Delta.
Oh, yeah, Metal Gear!
It's so weird because usually I wake up.
I wake up, right?
And I see, I see, like, news about idols or something.
But this time it was the complete opposite.
I woke up and I saw news about Metal Gear, so...
It was kind of a...
A strange situation.
Where I'm like, wow.
It's like very opposite.
Um...
Dang, she's slicing and dicing.
I like that she gets camo balloons too, it's great.
Um...
But oh, I'm so...
I'm so sad.
I got the deluxe edition.
Wait a second.
How are they hitting balloons over here when they're faced
this way?
Why are the... Why is there stuff flying around?
What is going on?
Did you get the Terrarium?
No, I got... That's the... I got the deluxe one, which was
the one for the UK.
Oh, it tracks.
The darts are homing?
They are?
No way.
But yeah, since they released the collector's edition at
like 4 a.m., I was asleep.
I did not get it, unfortunately.
I'm so, so sad.
But I think they'll re-release more.
I just have to be vigilant for whenever that comes out, you
know.
But it was so unlucky.
So is the collection actually sold out?
For now, yeah.
But like I said, I think they'll...
Hopefully that's not just Copium.
But I truly think they'll release more.
You can click Spacebar to do the next round.
Oh my gosh, you're right!
Wow!
I didn't know you could click Spacebar to do the next round.
Thanks!
just have all your friends ping you on discord when they
restock it i don't think anyone is uh
um i think i i think you guys ping me more on twitter than
on than my friends would ping me
i think you guys ping me more on twitter than anyone else
let's see let's i like getting this guy in i'm gonna I'm
gonna put him over here.
And we'll start getting in this because I really like this
one.
What's the second upgrade?
Oh, gains 10% attack speed for 1% life.
I wasn't watching the stream, but I got gifted a
notification.
Oh, notification of a gifted member.
Big thanks for that.
Aww.
Well, thanks for dropping by.
Thanks for the super tight.
I didn't have to do that.
Thank you, though.
Thank you.
How you doing up there, Ice Monkey?
Can you give us a juggle?
Give us a little wave.
Yippee!
Bring me more.
I accidentally woke up my boyfriend because you kept making
me laugh out loud, Iro.
Oh my gosh, stop lulling.
Stop ruffling at my jokes.
Stop lulling so much.
Lull, lull, lull.
Raffle, raffle, raffle, raffle, raffle, raffle.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, no, I didn't mean to put him there!
Oh, that was close.
let's do it
why didn't they why didn't they get those those those ones
though I know I can they not get the oh maybe they don't oh
maybe I didn't do the what's the words on them the camel
boop boop boop I hope you were able to receive my gift the
um a figure i have to check from afkai they haven't they
haven't sent the stuff yet they said that they'll let us
know when they sent it from afkai but they haven't um
shipped them to us yet so just started ba haven't made a
mistake what like the game blue archive yuppie oh no i love
blue archive i'm gonna plant a tree oh wait i'm gonna plant
it right behind him put in your radius get ready oh but
i was really bad about keeping up while i was gone that was
a volume by the way guys is it too loud just let me know in
fact i'm I'm going to turn down just a tad.
Handle it.
Oh, I thought we almost sliced.
I thought we almost...
Okay, there we go.
Hmm, louder.
Was that it?
Um, where should we...
Hmm.
I gotta maybe get rid of these trees.
For $500.
Craziness.
Let's make some more money.
Oh yeah.
Let's do that too.
No jacket?
It was a limited jacket made by Alpha Industries for the
club.
Oh, no way, really?
That's so awesome.
$500 monkey bucks.
I love sniper monkey.
Me too.
I love Sniper Monkey.
Gifted 10.
Thank you, Peculiar!
Thank you so much!
Tuck, tuck, tuck, tuck, tuck, tuck, tuck, tuck, tuck, tuck.
Oh, okay, now we have lots of money.
Look at them, guys!
We're doing a little bit of lawn maintenance, you know, on
my mid-cafe.
In good news, I got my Mintara Mondays goods and bad news.
My desk chair broke.
No!
Sorry, did you Japan trip?
was a bust.
Hope you feel better soon.
Thanks, Merlin.
Thank you.
Thanks for the peek.
I'm sorry your
chair broke, though.
Okay, now we can do sniper monkey because he can see
everywhere.
I'm gonna line him up all here.
A line of sniper monkeys.
Oh, that's not a sniper monkey.
Well, it'll be nice to get this guy.
Maybe I put him like I wish I could put them at the end, you
know?
We'll put one sniper monkey there, one sniper monkey there.
And you're gonna be our fast sniper monkey, and you're gonna
be our...
Full metal sniper monkey.
Sniper monkey!
And we'll have even more sniper monkeys.
So many sniper monkeys.
Thought it would have been best on a corner.
Yeah, I didn't...
realize how this map worked, but that's okay.
You know what?
I was gonna say live and learn, but I'm dead, so I just
don't learn.
I never learned.
Woo!
What's this one?
I never leveled up to this one before.
Super fast monkey.
Get ready!
Moab!
We are...
Actually, maybe I want to...
Let's click this and upgrade you.
There we go.
And you.
Perfect.
Big sub.
Is it a big old sub-burean?
This one?
Oh, wait.
I should add more subs then, shouldn't I?
Because it gives more...
Let's add another little guy here.
Maybe I should add...
do this one then i'll go this route but i can't oh i can
almost unlock it i might be able to unlock it soon
yo welcome back thank you full sub squad well this guy is
not a sub he's an alpha
moeb what's she say oh my gosh I'm being covered by
notifications.
I'm also stepping on the banks.
I like that banks.
Yeah, how were you guys while I was gone?
What happened?
Did you...
Did you miss me?
What'd you do?
Did anything interesting happen?
Saw this Korean, I think.
Oh, really?
Okay.
Hmm.
Trying to decide what I want to upgrade.
If I want to upgrade any sniper monkeys or if I want to
upgrade.
Let's do this one.
I do.
Oh my god, it's so full.
Look at these guys go.
They're so cute.
I graduated school.
Let's go!
I got a 3D printer.
What are you planning on doing with that?
Watched game trailers.
There's a lot of great games coming out.
I mean, with Delta and Metal...
I mean, Metal Gear... Metal Gear is Delta.
With Delta and the Indiana Jones game.
I can't wait for that, too.
I'm so excited.
I believe my Ace Combat 7 save replayed the entire game.
You got this.
Wait, you finished it today?
Never mind.
You did got it.
You got you.
All I did was sit in a room, staring at the all.
Metal gear.
Also metal gear.
There's so much metal gear.
I got the vinyl records this morning.
I'm very excited about those.
Oh my goodness.
I've been kind of wanting to get into like video game
vinyls.
This is the perfect opportunity to start, baby.
So, uh...
Oh, yippee!
Wall.
Nah, you said all.
Started my internship while you were gone.
Wow.
Look at you.
You're being productive in society and stuff.
Oh, what's this?
What's this?
Whoa!
My truck broke down.
I spent two days in a rest area in the mountains in the
middle of nowhere.
What the?
Are you okay?
Got my associate's...
Wait, associates.
Is that associates?
A degree.
After a decade of putting it... Is that an associate's
right?
Congratulations!
I got a degree!
I did this run after I came back from off-clay.
You're so fast.
Sounds like an I survive story.
For real, right?
Are you actually okay?
Oh, I forgot to collect my money.
Um, but yeah, oh, let's see.
What should we upgrade to this one too?
Oh, I can't upgrade!
Oh, dang it.
No, just kidding.
I'm 31.
You know what?
I am gonna try this one.
Go down.
But what's the point of getting these?
If it doesn't shoot while it's submerged, right?
Hmm.
Um, but now that I'm back, uh, um, let's see.
Oh, nice, I can unlock this one.
Which I have all...
Whoa!
The more blooms there are, the more damage it does.
Um, that sounds pretty good for...
Oh, MonkeyNomics!
I can finally unlock that!
Um, oh gosh.
Now that I'm back...
I'll be honest, there's, like, been things that I've been,
like, trying to handle.
But, um...
Things have been kind of...
It's been not so...
I don't want to say not so great.
Just a lot of things where, like, things that I'm hoping
will be done by a certain time.
And I don't think they will be.
So...
a process.
I mean, this is what happens when you're indie, you know?
Uh.
It's been a learning process for sure.
I'll say that.
It's been a learning process.
Find a decent turntable in the 200, 300, 400 range.
I saw um...
I saw an audio technical one that I was looking at.
Would you recommend?
Hold on.
Let me see it if I still have it pulled up.
There was a Audio Technica...
It was in purple, because I kind of liked it.
A lilac.
A-T-L-P-60X-B-T.
Maybe.
I like Audio Technica in general, so...
I figured maybe going with them would be a good choice,
right?
Perhaps, maybe.
Those are a safe bet.
Let me guess a little overwhelming.
Well, basically I was trying to like get a somewhat of a
merch launch.
Not launch.
A merch lineup for my anniversary.
Um.
but one thing that I was like most excited about the person
that I am working with they came back just a couple days ago
and they were like a lot of factories didn't want to work
with us because of a certain thing so but I finally found a
factory I'll get back to you in in 30 days and I was like
days so uh yeah
if i dropped one can on a commission then my artist just
ghosted me no file a dispute with your bank if that happens
what's this oh we can make them raise up wait so submersed
to detect camo, pop balloons, and reju...
Wait, how is it popping balloons if it's submerged?
I'm confused.
Since you asked, I passed my exam yesterday.
Let's go!
Wait, can anybody help me with this one?
Oh, radiation.
Oh, there are.
Oh.
I say, I say.
Reduces ability, cool down.
Is everybody worth 20%.
Naruto.
Yay!
Maybe I shouldn't have upgraded these monkeys the exact
same, but it's fine.
I just realized my mistake, but it's okay.
This one.
Come on, come on, there we go.
Whisp Sweatshop to produce merch soon.
I'm just hoping that, like, you know, that, um, like, you
guys aren't going to be, like, disappointed by a lack of
stuff.
Like, you're just, I hope that you guys won't be, like, man,
is Mint doing anything at all?
She hasn't put out this or that or this.
I'm just a little worried about it, is all.
Aria Technica is a good brand.
A model you mentioned looks okay.
the belt drive on it though what will that like kill my
records
wow we're like killing it aren't we
does she having fun is good enough for us i don't know I
still want you guys to like you know be like oh mint does
such cool things it's just been a little slow
that's all relax if you need to no you can always offer free
orders Yeah, I was thinking of that.
Well, I mean, they'd have to probably be pre-orders anyway.
But I kind of have to solidify what I'm doing at all.
I have to solidify anything at this rate.
But you know, I'm doing my best.
I want to get this one.
The spirit of the forest.
Don't jump to the worst conclusions.
What do you mean by that?
Oh,
look at this guy.
Look at this guy over here.
No, he's like...
He's so fast.
What else should I build?
Oh my gosh, thank you for that.
Good super.
It appears we meet again.
Mint Monkey.
Nice to see my boy hiding in the corner, clutching the game.
How much experience do you think he has?
Four.
thousand by doing absolutely nothing what a champ what a
champ my guy is
click on the sub upgrades again I have ever oh I was gonna
say I have ever everything one million what is this
unfathomable range power and synergies with other monkey
towers and heroes puts all bloons under assault.
Four, four, four, hundred.
What is this?
I've never seen this before.
Nautic Siege Corps.
What?
Thank you, Red.
Thanks for two months.
One million XP.
Hold on, I'm gonna eat some of my...
Ooh, I'm starting to feel a little bit dizzy.
Ooh, hold on.
I don't get nausea.
My friend, when she got COVID, she said she was really
nauseous.
I don't get nausea, but I get lightheaded a little bit.
Don't be afraid to ask her friends for help or advice.
Yeah.
Um.
I think for me, it's like, there are things that I want to
do, but I can't figure out a way how to get them made.
to like contact a place directly and get it custom but also
it's me being like i want to do something cool but my
limitations are low right now or or my limit yeah my
limitations are are restrict i have i have limitations
we're here for you anything else is just a cherry on top
don't sweat it Wow!
Moab!
Hot the dog.
Hot the dogs!
Money.
Oh yeah, let's up- 100!
What do you mean by that?
Why is it so expensive?
I've never seen that much monkey money before ever!
I told Darcy to confess to Elizabeth.
She rebuked.
Get the F out of him.
See, I told you.
I told you!
Oh, dang, that was fast.
I got sick even before I went to Off-Kai.
Oh, my gosh.
Everybody feel better.
Belt drive won't damage your records.
Just try not to touch the record while it's spinning or
you'll wear the belt out.
Ah, okay, okay.
Direct drive doesn't have that problem.
I see, I see, I see.
Oh, my gosh.
Thank you, guys, for all this.
Stay cute!
Will flavor a block game you'd play with Bessie Bird?
I don't know.
She and I should talk about it now that I'm back.
Mm-mm.
Hope you're getting over the crud quickly.
I think I would say I'm on the recovery end.
I would say that I didn't feel so bad for a very long time.
Especially once I started taking medicine, I was like, oh
yeah!
Ah, yeah!
It feels so good!
mostly it was my head hurting my head was like oh it was
like so oh it was so bad but now i feel my head hasn't hurt
at all
that's a word that's a word i see i want this guy real bad
how do i what's the best way to make money you guys.
What's the best way to make a monkey box?
I don't want to take out a loan.
I don't want to be in debt to anybody.
Maybe I should build another bank.
Payments missed you.
I missed you guys!
Banks?
Okay, let's make a bank.
I'm going to put it right.
Is it still in range of him?
I think so.
Maybe technically.
See, this one I don't want to go.
Wait.
Earned heaps of money each round.
What's a merchant man?
Hopes of monkeys trail.
Huh.
Which is the best path to go?
Rob a monkey bank.
Ah!
Which is the best path, you think?
Sorry, MGS.
Because if you just beat MGS 2 and loving it, I'm a Steam
Achievements fan, though, getting big boss code name took
years oh i'm sorry viz it's not even something i'll do
reminds me of a silly anime girl on the internet quote no
expectations yeah bottom path seriously you like the bottom
path but it halves your value
we'll try it
so it just collects in there?
Or something?
We missed we're working on our aim.
Yeah, what's that supposed to mean?
What's that supposed to mean?
It's nice to meet you!
Thank you for being part of the experience that helped me
check something off my server list soon.
Thank you!
Also, Joe Mama.
Shut the hell up.
I'd rather fight 100 duck-sized lions or the sun.
That's how this question goes.
100 duck-sized lions.
Those are just cats, are they not?
Those are just normal cats.
Right?
If you think about it.
Yo, we are, like, killing it right now.
Maybe I should take out a loan for real.
place.
Generates money, Ishma.
Oh.
Whoa, look at it!
Go!
Oh, sorry.
Whoa, let's do it the more valuable.
Oh, ZOMG!
That was easy.
Duck-sized cats.
That's like the same thing.
That's like the same exact thing.
Oh my gosh, wait, I can almost get him.
So close.
I'm taking out alone.
Just kidding.
I'm gonna be able to summon two phoenixes.
I'm taking out alone!
Ew!
Yes!
Now they start.
Yes, they start growing.
They start growing!
Collect that money.
Look at it go!
How are the kitties?
They are so good!
I...
Um...
My roommate had to take Butaro to the vet.
shaped cats.
No!
Then they're just dogs right away.
A manga cat.
Thank you so much.
And turns out he has maybe acid reflux, and that's why he
throws up all the time.
So he has to...
I had to change his diet entirely again.
I was like ordering food for him in Japan.
My stupid sensitive cat.
Okay.
Okay, maybe I can get this one now.
I like how we just like...
Oh!
Scary, scary, scary.
DDT, I don't know if we're still ready for it.
Poor old man.
I know, my stinky cat.
It's such an old man.
Hmm.
Uh oh.
I'm as sharp as I can.
Should I try this?
I guess I tried it.
Um.
Maybe I should have invested in something else.
Oh well.
Oh yeah, other than that.
No!
I think I would have lost that anyway though.
I think I would have lost that anyway.
My cat throws up sometimes, but now I know that happens when
he overeats.
That could happen.
Sometimes, sometimes my cat eats too fast.
But hey!
Insta monkey!
Yubby!
Our first money on an intermediate map.
Oh, monkeys.
Oh, no.
Monkeys play.
That was a good one.
That was a good round, everybody.
We can still do carve.
That one's spookiaso.
Be the beginner map for the first time.
Oh, we got to get...
Yeah, yeah, let's go do...
Let's keep...
You know what?
Let's just keep going through these.
We'll do this one.
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
Hmm, hmm.
When I see a monkey, I think of Johnny Bravo.
Do the monkey with me.
Wait, how does this go?
They just go straight across?
Huh?
Did they go down?
Where should I put her here?
Resort mode is really easy for Sada.
Oh, it circles three times.
Oh yeah.
They loop around a few times.
This is the easiest map in the game, don't worry.
Maybe I should have let it see how it went before I even...
Wait, can I put monkeys on these chairs?
Oh, in the square!
I'll put her there instead.
I'll put her there.
Oh, yes I can!
See?
That's where Ice Monkey will be.
Ice Monkey is going to be...
It's going to be...
Louncing.
Yeah, Ice Monkey will be lounging in the chair.
Ice Monkey is really good in this map.
For lounging!
Evan, what is that?
What?
What is that?
Are you okay?
That tickles.
Look at him!
Oh, he's lounging!
He's just chilling little guy!
My potus.
We can have two ice monkeys on a date.
yeah but like ice monkey is kind of selective he doesn't
just go out with any ice monkey Sada looks like a like a
private chef for ice monkey right now you know how they like
sit in their little booths and stuff she looks like a
private chef slicing and dicing she's doing hibachi table
for ice monkey ice monkey and fire monkey forbidden romance.
There is no fire monkey.
There's alchemist monkey.
Two ice monkeys is just getting crazy.
Some would say it's a waste of my monkey bucks, but um...
They might be correct.
I know who I want on the other table.
Me.
It's me, I'm lounging with Ice Monkey.
You guys can't stop me.
She blew in my tower to lie defense.
She left you defenseless, man.
Someone come into the stream and say, Where's Mito?
Little does Ice Monkey know.
There's a poison in that drink.
It's a matter of time before he croaks.
Or not croaks.
Before he...
Oh, ha ha ha!
Yes.
Let's see.
What else can I do here?
Is there any magical things going on?
Any, let's put a...
Let's put a...
Let's put a boat monkey.
I don't think it's Jan did it.
Wait, if I do that, you can totally...
Oh my gosh, I'm just standing in the middle of the room.
I'm just standing here.
So awkward.
Okay, click the base of the parasol.
Oh!
Oh, that's so cute!
Okay, I'm gonna go back to my normal spot.
I feel uncomfortable.
There we go.
We'll put another ice monkey there.
Some may say that's a waste of my monkey books, but...
Ice monkey doesn't know MGS lore.
He just explained it to him.
Click the coconut tree.
Was that a coconut crab?
Oh my god, good thing I got out of here.
That thing was gonna eat me.
Oh my gosh, I was about to get Amelia Earharted.
Thank god I got out of there.
Yeesh.
No monkey, no monkey.
No monkey, no monkey, no monkey.
But down here on these three, we're gonna put sniper
monkeys.
Sniper monkey.
Right here.
lounging sniper monkeys.
Everybody's on vacation today.
We can eat, we can do each route with each monkey.
You here.
And you here.
Perfect.
It's a fabled beach episode.
Is that what happened to her?
That's what was the theory for a while actually.
Was that she got coconut crabbed.
You just got coconut crap!
You're getting eaten alive.
Have you ever tried mortar monkeys?
Is that this one?
I'm not.
You know what?
Today's the day we mortar monkey.
Which sounds dangerously close to murder monkey.
Look, I like how each of them have a different hat on and
everything.
So cute.
So how do I use this guy?
I'm gonna put him right in front of their salad.
I just set a target, right?
Target.
Kill monkey!
Kill ice monkey!
Third wheel.
I lost a bet to Cole at Offcutt.
Why?
What?
What happened?
Picker blast.
What's the best route for our murder monkey?
How could you, Minto?
Hold on, I gotta remember which monkey is going with which
direction, you know?
This guy's...
Okay.
Deed.
Two.
Zero five two.
Okay.
I guess I should actually put him to work then.
We'll just put him right there.
Dear Christ, welcome to membership, thank you.
We were going to get lunch and I bet in one super chat that
the people behind us would go to Curry Hugo and then they
didn't.
I had that one day at the convention.
It was pickup.
Someone picked it up.
I think someone from staff picked it up from me.
So what did you have to do?
You lost the bet?
What do you do now?
I never...
It was pretty good.
I actually didn't get to finish it, though, because I was...
Basically, I took it back to my room.
I took it back to my room because we got it while...
we were signing the postcards for the Patreon and I forgot a
spoon and I just never went back for a spoon and so you know
it's kind of hard to eat curry without a spoon oh I had to
give you money
yippee appreciate it zero two five is probably the best
route always it okay well we're still we're still early
gathering you know so i lost a bet once my name was never
the same yeah your name changes all the time well
don't eat curry with a fork what do you eat sure well no not
typically i usually use it with spoon but i didn't have
anything i didn't even have chopsticks i have a fork i
didn't have a spoon I had my hands and that's a little...
Like that was a little...
I don't think...
That was a little...
New fan who got interested in here.
Thanks to all the cool off-kind merchant cosplay.
No way!
Sawyer, what order you should play MGS short.
And I have to say, I started with MGS.
Some phantom pride.
I guess I'll just pass away again, I suppose.
Look at back, me, thank you!
And there's a pocket utensil for Marie.
Oh, you're so right.
Because that also kept happening at the hotel in Japan.
Basically, we had a 7-Eleven by our hotel.
And it was like, I would ask them to heat stuff up.
up for me and they're like no it's self it's self-serve so I
was like and so I would be like oh well I'll just use the
microwave wait I was like I'll just use the microwave at the
hotel but then I would forget because the forks and the
chopsticks and all that fun stuff was all next to the
microwave at the 7-Eleven, so I would forget it.
I maybe should get an actual like travel spoon set.
Wait, they wouldn't eat your food?
No!
They told me to go use the self-serve thing.
Burny stuff.
Whoa, they're all on fire!
Nice.
Yeah, it's actually some messed up.
Poke it to utensil.
Mentor, you okay?
I've never been okay.
It was so sad for me, you guys don't understand.
Start my Metal Gear journey with the NES port of the first
game.
Bounced off of it because I was a silly kid who thought it'd
be like Contra.
Understandable, though, I guess, I suppose, you know.
I get it.
Oh!
Moeb!
Nice.
Gosh, we're so good at this game.
I've been working on setting up what's called an uncapping
tube.
Save more wax.
Oh my gosh, for candles.
You and your candles.
So that's why Makise Kiritu wanted her own for me.
I started with survive.
Base.
Everybody knows you should start with Metal Gear Survive.
I'm going to put the Gatlin Gunner.
We're going to put him down here.
And we're going to do our...
ray of doom.
It's like so.
There we go.
What do you think of people whose first Metal Gear saw was
acid?
I don't really have an opinion, I say.
I think that's an interesting choice.
I think mostly the reason why... I understand why so many
people have started with five.
Um...
but um the reason why I'm just like don't do it don't start
with five is because you just don't understand what's going
on you know you're gonna be so confused okay good now we can
use I'll just do this we'll just get night vision for all of
them the NVGs I started with two see that's so confusing um
it's kind of it kind of reminds me of how i start or my
first final fantasy was final fantasy 10 2.
not final fantasy 10 oh no no i had to go in with the 10 2
and guess what i was so confused you'll be confused no
matter where you start i suppose that's kind of true too
though
Get ready!
Moab!
Why don't they juggle at the same time?
These stupid...
Stupid monkeys.
What can I do for you?
The idle one.
Yeah, I kind of loved it, though.
It was what my friend gifted me for my birthday, so I was
like...
Yeah, I want...
I'm going to play that one.
So, uh...
It's a clean cut and still cuts a tomato.
Um, but I...
Did you at least play 10 after that?
Uh, eventually.
Would you be surprised if I told you a lot of people start
with Revengeance and end up very confused?
See, even though I start with Revengeance, I wouldn't say
that I was super confused.
Wait, what does this do?
Oh, drops a crate full of cat.
Oh, there it is.
I wouldn't say I mean I was confused but I was like I I
think I think revenge since as a starting point is less
confusing than starting at five how to start Metal Gear as a
kid with the NES game not the NES I have fond memories of
playing pretend with my brother and our next-door friends
we'd sneak around.
Our house is like Snake.
Oh, you were normal.
I played Pretend as Blue Eyes White Dragon.
I was like, yeah, I'm Blue Eyes White Dragon.
I'm just a dragon.
Why couldn't I play Pretend?
Why didn't I pretend to be Yu-Gi-Oh?
Why didn't I pretend to be like a human character?
I have no idea.
Instead, I was like, I'm Blue Eyes White Dragon.
It's better that way.
And then sometimes we would be the harpy sisters or
something like that, me and my friends.
I was going through my little brain.
Look, our little mortar, murder monkeys getting good.
He's getting all this XP.
Oh, it shatters the things.
Nice.
And then I can't get this one.
Even faster reload.
Okay, we can almost get it, though.
Maybe now?
No.
But several people gifted a...
There was like a Yu-Gi-Oh...
What's the word?
A Yu-Gi-Oh Sanrio collab with McDonald's.
That is like the...
Okay, that is...
Now that I think about it.
so convoluted but some people gifted me at afkai they gifted
me the cinnamarol blue eyes white dragon which is just the
most absolute perfect thing for me ever in the world but you
guys i feel like kaushi henning recently have you guys seen
the hanumaru han Hanamaru obake um sunreal character
recently i've been really obsessed with him okay we need a
game where you play a senator What do you do?
You sign bills.
It's actually like a senator simulator.
Yu-Gi-Oh!
Sanrio McDonald's.
Yeah, it's all three together.
It's just...
It feels a little much, right?
Maybe.
Yippee!
Free play.
Is this destined to be a Dragon VTuber fighting?
fate to be a ghost maid instead I've thought about like if I
were to you know if I were how do I say able to change my
image you know because I mean I was dead several years ago
um to But I don't think there would be much that I would
change if I had the option to.
Wait.
Oh my goodness, all the donuts are so backed up.
Glad you're back.
Thanks, Joshua.
Want to help me select the next movie I watch based on the
title again?
Wait, isn't Steam...
Steam Boy's an anime, isn't it?
Dual Blood Rain.
become a dragon.
I don't think I would want to be a dragon.
I don't think so.
I think there's a lot of dragon vtubers.
But now there's also like a lot of ghost vtubers.
When I first came around, there weren't so many, I think.
But now there's so many, I feel.
So many.
Actually, I should probably put in a this guy so he slows
him down right and then when this guy booms him up there are
a lot of youtubers yeah I guess that's true too there
definitely are a lot of youtubers everybody rebrands the
dragons hi Hanna I think Dragons are just cool, so I
understand, you know, if people, you know, if someone wants
to be a dragon.
And maids.
Yeah!
There's a lot of maids now, too.
But maids are, you know, maids are a staple, so.
That I can't be upset about.
They all died.
And two.
But, uh, you know, I guess it is what it is.
It is what it is.
A snake.
I've seen, like, Lami YouTubers before.
So cool.
I want to get to the ray of doom, but it's so expensive.
What else can we...
Let's aim for this one next.
Oh, let's get some more money, too.
Money, money.
La mia.
There we go.
So now it's making its own...
Now I don't...
Yeah, it's just generating its own cash, right?
Yeah, okay.
Oh.
The more slack of Kinky Kitab for sewer beat them.
for the smh if you if you could like create if you like
could have your fate like your your ideal vtuber debut
tomorrow what what would you want them to be in what what
kind of vtuber would you be like oh my gosh this is hitting
every every little check mark that i have oh baby
Pirate warlord.
Oh, that sounds fun.
A bear.
There's plenty of bears, I think.
A detective.
And I'm not asking this to get ideas or anything.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not going to be like, So my next outfit should be a
bear.
Witch with a big hat.
There's always more necessity for big hats.
Chew!
I'm gonna put in a...
Oh, we're so close!
How do I get the money from here?
It just generates on its own, I guess.
There we go.
Kaiju VTuber?
My model is a sea angel.
Like an...
A blonde fairy?
a bad taste an alien I've seen those before
but you can't name 100 VTubers um VTuber 1 VTuber 2 VTuber 3
VTuber 4 VTuber 5 VTuber 6 VTuber 7 VTuber 8 VTuber 9 VTuber
10 Hydro VTuber with different personalities for each head.
That would be insane.
That sounds so fun.
Actually.
I guess that's what's so great about VTubers.
Is you can have so much.
So many different kinds of.
Of creatures and critters and everything.
A scuba diver.
Would give what you want them to do actual scuba diving?
Um, actual scuba diving streams.
That would be awesome.
I would love to do a scuba diving stream.
Thank you.
Thank you, money.
Let's see.
Oh my gosh, I was about to click on Ice Monkey.
32, 14.
Okay, we can almost...
Maybe soon.
There we go.
Nice.
Curling you with the ghost tractor.
You can try.
Why are you guys always trying to destroy me, huh?
I say some stuff sometimes, and you guys will not get my
hands on you.
What's wrong with you?
Dave the Diver VTuber.
Metal Slime VTuber.
I diagnose you with Goofy.
Thanks for the pink cubic.
I'd be living on our, I'd be a living rocket with a
look-like classic animation.
Butch Hartman hips for sure.
Butch Hartman is the guy that does the art for fairly odd
parents, right?
Does he have hips?
Like, does he have hips?
Jar VTuber.
What's wrong with you?
Stop it!
Common Rider?
Yeah, someone said Tokusatsu earlier.
I find it hard to believe that there's...
I mean, there's definitely a Tokusatsu Vtuber out there.
I actually feel like I could name 100 VTubers.
That sounds like very easy, actually.
Naming 100.
He makes women with hips.
Wow.
Let me...
Ooh.
voice crack do
it then if you can name hololive it's like 70 already that's
what I'm saying I feel like a hundred is like people are
just like do it then but you can't but it's actually like a
hundred doesn't a hundred is not even that much right you
might need more monkeys I need a vacation I'm just gonna put
in super monkey.
Just kidding.
I'm gonna put him
hmm.
Name a monkey.
We need more ice monkeys.
More monkeys you have all of chat.
Wow.
why is my drum set so what it's angel the type of deep sea
slug they're cute oh cute I mean another ice zero zero ice
monkey in the near the table oh the butler monkey butler ice
monkey he's oh actually this is ice monkey over here who
catches this is ice monkey catching his ice monkey cheating
on him oh my This is the ice monkey who's just like, That's
my lover over there in that seat, holding hands with that
other ice monkey.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, scandalous.
Drama.
Absolute drama.
Let's put, let's put.
Air carrier.
Aircraft carrier.
Monkey.
Okay.
Deploy the mini planes!
Super Monkey is a hero.
Are you a hero?
Have you been- Have you been a hero recently?
When's the last time you were a hero?
I offered a seat to an old lady.
I'm a hero.
I didn't expect money out of it either.
Though it would have been nice.
It would have been cool if she had been like, Here's 10,000,
or not 10,000, here's 1,000 yen.
That would have been so grand.
Oh my god, she's so crazy.
Sometimes they do that, though.
Sometimes, I was told once before that sometimes if you
offer a seat to a grandma on a train, sometimes they'll give
you money.
And ever since then, I've never expected it, but I'm kind of
just like, What if it happens to me one day?
I mean...
What if it happens to me one day?
I'm just saying.
Yippee!
Are you Himmel?
Himmel, the hero, would never hold the seat, expecting for a
thousand yen.
But would be great.
if he got the thousand.
Yeah, I'm just saying.
I see the operasita batara.
It was so funny.
When I was on the plane back, I was just like, I was like, I
didn't get the, I didn't get the, um, the rest of the
clothes that I wanted to get.
And so I was like frantically trying to order them on, like
on the flight as it was taking off.
Look at this.
He covers the entire map.
He's so awesome!
What a great passive.
So good.
Wait.
What can you upgrade?
Da-da-da!
Carrier flagship!
Okay, that's not so bad.
We can upgrade that soon.
Pre-paying a forward for that hero who gives up his seat for
Mint Ba-chan.
There was a time when When Mitara and I went...
I just literally said Mintara so funny.
Oh, those were DDTs!
When she and I were sitting and...
But we were separated and then somebody gave up their seat
so we could sit next to each other.
But that's like different, right?
They didn't think... Oh my god, it takes up the entire
thing!
That's so crazy!
That's like different though.
Oh, I should probably start.
Let's also get this bottom pathway.
Twin guns.
Long distance.
Mintara.
It's because of the Mintara Mondays.
Oh, I got rid of it.
Stage of the carrier.
Carrier flagship.
Oh, this is round 93.
Oh, my gosh.
Wow, we went through 93.
So easy.
We might actually get to pass 100.
Nice.
Nice, nice, nice.
Oh, we shall see.
Trying to get...
Let's see.
Maybe I'll...
Maybe I'll get this guy, too.
Yeah.
Let's do it.
Dun, dun, dun, dun.
Dun, dun.
Hey.
How much?
We have like no experience on this guy.
That's okay though.
Seeing a huge lack of farming.
Chill out.
We're getting there.
Gosh Gosh
Wasn't this one really expensive?
Yeah, maybe Hmm I'm trying to save up for this one Maybe we
should just
Moab Supply Drop
A little late for farming now What are you talking about?
It's never too late!
It's only round 96!
What are you talking about?
We're going to...
We're...
Gone, baby!
We're going, going, gone, baby!
Oh, I keep forgetting to upgrade this guy.
My bad.
Oh, I didn't even have time to click the thing.
Your farming is at 43.5% of efficiency.
Bit too, why do you not farm?
Because, um...
You know, I like doing things natural.
Oh, natural, baby.
I do...
Okay, supply.
Upgrade.
Oh, I didn't even need it.
Oh, my gosh.
I didn't even need her.
99, baby.
I can't upgrade too much.
I think we're good.
Wow!
Oh, I thought I said...
Oh, does this thing need to be close to her?
Uh-oh.
Attack!
Oh.
Oh my god.
Are you aware?
Are you aware of the carrier's abilities?
No.
Let's see.
Does extra damage can place other monkeys on the upper deck?
Of the ship and increase the attack speed of all...
Wait a second!
Oh my god!
I can put little monkeys up here!
That's wild!
That's so crazy.
This map is so easy though because they loop so many times.
What should we put up there?
I'm gonna put a helicopter.
I'm gonna put I should put I should I feel like I should at
least have the helicopter out here though right like I can't
believe as many times as I've used the helicopter I don't
have everything unlocked
put ice monkeys on top for decorative ice monkeys
oh an alchemist okay we'll put one of monkey and one
alchemist oh wait maybe i should have switched those
oh wait does he will he reach all three of these guys hmm
how many monkeys do you think i can squish up here
Apache is OP.
Yeah, I wanted...
I've been...
I actually...
Oh, I didn't realize I could...
Actually, unlock it now.
So we'll do that.
Okay, hold on.
Let me get my...
Let me get my helicopter, guys.
Let me get my helicopter first.
Okay.
Go.
That was it?
No way.
That was so short.
Wrong monkey.
What are you talking about?
Oh, the wizard.
Oh, wait, no.
Alchemist.
Right, monkey.
Right here.
Is that M-M on the carrier or E-E?
That's E-E!
That's E!
Simba, welcome to Rambusha, very cool!
But wait, if I put Alchemist Monkey here, will he reach all
three of them?
Here, he'll only reach two of them, right?
Wait, does he have... What's his... What's his...
Larger... Oh, larger area!
It doesn't even matter where I put him.
Maybe I should put him here, or here then, because he'll
reach over here as well then.
Okay, we're going to put him on the bottom.
like that wait what's his radius oh what happened to the
larger radius you know it's fine
who cares about ddt i guess dang i thought i would have
enough money come on guys nice nice and nice and nice It was
larger potions, not radius.
Will that acid pool do anything if I already have this on
the ground?
I'll just put a second one.
It's fine, you guys.
There we go.
They're buddies.
Screw the ice monkeys.
We already have two of them over there.
Alchemist, yaoi, you said it, not me.
You said it, not me.
Those were your words.
I chose to read them aloud, but those were your words.
Just stop it fast throwing.
Yeah.
I think it would be better to throw faster, too.
Okay, we'll just stop it then.
We don't have to do all the upgrades, I suppose.
Um, 32.
Where was...
Oh, no.
There was another one that I was gonna upgrade.
I know I need to do that one, too.
Huh.
I can't remember.
Hmm.
Hello.
Myoshi's a gamer.
Yeah, basically.
These poor monkeys, it's like...
Look, this factory is literally cutting into his bed.
this kind of sucks for him so sorry for you
let's get in super monkey too and we'll get him buffed as
well which is the best route for the super monkey because I
started on both of these I think I was going for the sun one
and then I was like I'm gonna go for a robo monkey good to
see you back home again hope you have a great dream Thank
you!
Thank you, thank you!
Okay, I'm a monkey.
Oh, that was so fast.
I think we'll do the triple Moab.
Oh wait, I was gonna go for this one.
There it is.
Welcome back, Minto.
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you.
Hmm.
Okay.
Next round.
107.
Money, money.
Top of a Batman is fun.
The power of the sun is unstoppable.
Okay, then I'll save up.
I'll save up for it.
This one.
Holy moly.
Wait, how much is...
500,000!
I think I need more trees.
think I need more farms.
I think I'm slacking a little bit.
I think I'm slacking a little bit in, um, in the amount of
money I could be making at this moment.
I just realized I could taste my coffee.
Yippee!
It's weird the things that I can taste and the things I
can't taste.
Because, um, I can taste salt and, um,
I can taste...
I could taste the grape jelly.
Maybe my taste is coming back more than I thought it would
be.
More than I thought it has.
Your health is going up!
Going up, baby.
No monkey village.
Where should I put it though?
Where do I even need to put it?
Oh my gosh, I forgot this ice monkey was here.
Wait!
This guy is killing balloons!
We can't have an ice monkey that is doing something.
We have to have only useless ice monkeys.
I first realized the location of that guy.
He was killing things.
He was helping out.
He gads.
Dang, it pushes it back so well.
It's crazy.
Holy moly.
We have...
Have you guys seen how many lives?
We have 560.
the extra what salt
is taste is tongue versus a lot of what we normally taste
and food is from the smell well I can actually smell I never
like I could actually at some point smell better than I
could taste he was carrying we're gonna lose now we're gonna
lose okay all my these guys down here max very Very good.
514 extra lives.
How is that possible?
He just wanted to help.
No, Ice Monkeys are not allowed to help.
They're only allowed to be little cute goofy guys that
juggle.
Okay?
We'll have to understand.
They're sensitive.
Maybe I should do...
Which would be the good one...
Epic range maybe.
Simba!
Thank you for the...
We gifted.
Thank you so much.
Twin ice monkeys.
Ice monkey deserves to be pampered.
Exactly, exactly, exactly.
This is, I don't, I don't, I know people will say that this
is, my map is not optimized, but this is peak monkey
optimization right here, actually.
This is what they don't want, don't tell you.
Okay.
Third ice monkey.
Ice monkeys clap when they attack those.
Aw, that's pretty cute.
Oh, my YouTube is breaking.
Dying.
You know what, maybe...
Hold on.
This is just long range.
This is...
You know what?
Since I'm saving up, I'm just gonna go like this.
Whoa!
The DDT has always freaked me out.
I don't actually, this might be my longest game I've ever
done ever, you guys.
This might be the longest I've ever gone in a game, I think.
Do I sound congested?
Do him, yeah, oh, do a village right here so he can hit all
types.
So true, so true.
In fact, I'm going to do it right in between.
It's even going to get Ice Monkey.
there we go only a little bit that's good I guess is it
because I usually sound nasally are you saying I usually
sound nasally fortified DDTs might be the end of you hey
shun the non-believers
I thought that was the end of me I thought that was the end
of me.
I need more experience.
He earns heaps of money.
I need heaps of money.
I need it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Just kidding.
Six of...
This is...
I'm a ghost.
This is not a spooky number.
This is the spookiest number.
Number of lives.
Oh my god, it's this thing again.
Oh my god, there's two of them.
Wait a second.
Uh-oh.
Am I in trouble?
Oh, there's three!
Oh, there's three of them!
Am I in trouble?
Um, oh.
Maybe not.
Maybe I'm okay.
Hey!
Yeah!
Yippee!
Get it off the screen is haunted!
It's gone now.
You're all safe.
The forbidden number.
You're all safe here.
I protected you.
I am your savior.
I want to get to the 60,000.
Or what else can we do?
by almost everything's maxed it's crazy what level is she at
she's the max too everybody's so many people are maxed we're
gonna reach 60k in no time with this 120 holy cow you guys
this is might be the furthest i've ever gotten ever it looks
like it's fanning my butt i think this is the furthest Tom!
Welcome to Membo's ship!
What else should I... should I add to the playing field?
What's another monkey, everybody?
Name a monkey, name a monkey.
I wish I could upgrade to the Sun Temple, but it says it
sacrifices someone, right?
It's kind of... Who am I sacrificing?
Yuppie!
So close.
For the Super Storm.
Ah!
Oh!
Super Storm!
I want to see what happens.
What does it do?
Storm blasts all balloon types for massive damage.
Blows them away from the exit.
Let's go.
Ice Monkey!
Ninja Monkey.
Could add a Ninja Monkey.
You know why not?
Get a Ninja Monkey in there.
Why not?
Guys, I didn't even like get past our...
the front.
Oh my gosh.
Upgrade!
I...
I don't think I will.
I don't think I will now.
Please more karaoke stuff like break stuff when you better.
Okay.
Nah, I've said it before.
While I wouldn't mind, I'm actually going to put a Gatlin
Monkey on this end too.
And this guy will face this way.
Exactly like that.
And then we'll go, we'll upgrade his laser.
And then eventually we can upgrade this guy.
But I don't think I will anyway.
And are you the same person?
Wait, can someone check?
Was Anna the Ice Monkey person before too?
Anna, are you...
Are you saying Anna of Ice Monkey fame?
I want to... Actually, not fame.
Infamy.
Why aren't you upgrading the monkey on the right?
Because we're gonna get to him.
We need 80,000.
I upgraded him first and now we're gonna upgrade him.
Don't worry about it.
Hold on.
If YouTube wasn't so slow...
oh my gosh oh oh my gosh youtube is so slow youtube is the
worst ever please hold on i have to restart my youtube
okay there we go youtube ram usage is really bad for real i
know right Okay, we're getting to 80,000 you guys and then
we'll upgrade.
Don't worry, it's gonna happen.
I believe, I believe, I believe.
And then we can upgrade that one.
Can you downgrade Ice Monkey Streamer?
Ice Monkey's already 0, 0, 0 everybody.
That is the most, it's the least I can do.
People, this game is no monkey business.
This game is actually all only Monkey Business.
This game is all Monkey Business.
This game can't be anything but Monkey Business.
This game is a business.
I'm losing stock right now.
They said if you don't upgrade Laser, my stocks are
crashing.
The Monkey Market is going to be in shambles.
Please, you don't understand.
The Monkey Market right now depends on it.
Sell him to downgrade.
I like how...
I was gonna say Sada doesn't even talk anymore.
DDT, handle it.
I miss him.
The monkey recession!
Oh god!
Upgrade this maid.
Am I not already?
Am I not already peak?
She is not peak, Your Honor.
What if your next outfit was an ice monkey made?
I think that's a waste of money.
That is a waste of my money.
Look how much he is doing.
He is blowing these guys back.
He's blowing them.
He's blowing them hard.
sounds like an investment to me would then i be peak would
then i be peak if i were ice monkey and then i could sit
there and juggle that would be the whole stream i would just
sit in a little lawn chair and i would juggle sometimes i
wouldn't even juggle all the time i would only juggle
sometimes holy moly these guys are ass okay it seems we're
already at 50 out of 80.
52 out of 80.
I'm nerf.
Okay, there we go.
It
was just 11,000.
We could take the risk.
Maybe I should build another farm.
I wish I could upgrade these ones.
What's this one?
Whoa!
money but um it was worth it okay what if you arrange that
letter to spell out big m they they hit absolutely nothing
they just go
never hitting it shush shush we're hitting 80k we're hitting
80k don't worry about it what's this do
Oh, monkey call the arms, monkey arms.
Oh, monkey arms, monkey arms.
What are those ice monkeys doing?
Yeah, they're just lounging.
They're hanging out.
And they're juggling sometimes.
Oh, hold on.
They'll definitely juggle next time.
Look at that go!
You have to be really fast, though.
They scratch their butt a little bit.
They're peak monkey farm.
And you guys, these guys are lounging down here as well.
Everybody this is just the most relaxing game ever.
Actually I'm quite impressed at how far we've gotten.
I'm actually super duper impressed right now.
I'm like damn.
Maybe I'm good at this game.
You know?
I can upgrade this one though.
You got, no.
I'm gonna get the 80.
We're almost at 60.
What are we saving for?
This guy right here.
He's 80,000.
Ray of Doom.
He's expensive.
Damn, she's good.
I thought of that.
I mean, do you guys know that camp rock clip where the girl
is just like, she's like doing things with her arms.
She's like on the keyboard and it's like...
And they're like, she's pretty good.
That's me right now.
These DDTs, more like...
DDD don'ts.
Why do people always spam monkeys?
I'm not even reading it.
Too much.
Mucho Texto!
Sorry.
Mucho Texto.
Um, anyway.
Because it's fun seeing your reaction.
I don't think so.
I don't think they do it.
Well, maybe they do it for my reaction.
Maybe they're just like, the streamer noticed me.
But I just, Mucho Texto, do not read.
I have my limits.
Oh, we're only, okay, that one.
I have my, even I have my limits.
Why are you not efficient, VTuber?
Ah.
Efficiency?
Because I can't be peak and efficient.
Oh!
Ta-da!
Whoa!
Let's, um...
Unlock this and this.
Nice.
Holy moly.
Okay, this one will upgrade next, which we'll get in no
time.
As we set an off guy.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, am I
in trouble?
Nah, we're fine.
By accepting this money, you must play this game exactly.
the way I want despite the fact that I am perfectly capable
of playing it myself.
We will be reaching 200 at this rate, Minto.
No, don't say that!
You're gonna jinx it!
Supply drop!
You're gonna die at 150.
Will I die this next round?
140?
Hiya!
I guess we'll see.
Oh, it's fast!
Uh-oh.
Am I in trouble?
Am I in trouble for real?
Uh-oh.
Rock roll.
Oh no!
There's a second one!
Uh-oh.
Yeah-oh.
Oh.
Oh, that was close.
Oh, they stopped it.
Woo!
We were almost in trouble there.
The bitrate is dying.
Oh, no!
Does it actually die?
Uh-oh, I didn't even think about that.
Maybe I should get more of these first strike guys, though.
I was thinking, because they're pretty, you know, they're
pretty good.
They're pretty good to have on in.
You're very crunchy.
No!
I'm supposed to be goopy.
Like, ectoplasm.
One ice monkey took you to a hundred.
And two ice monkeys are taking you above that.
Three ice monkeys.
Even further beyond.
Mmm.
We're turning the loopy sections.
Okay, like here.
Oh!
Sorry, that scared me so much.
Oh,
here we go.
I think everything, every monkey we have has a...
As is as upgraded as it possibly can be.
That's crazy.
This monkey...
Where even is the monkey?
Yeah, we have a thousand lives even.
We're crazy.
DDT jump scare.
Okay.
We can't die now.
Not yet.
Oh, this one.
What does this do, though?
Automatically triggers a powerful missile attack whenever
Moab quest, balloon spawn.
Ah, neat.
Minto was also meeting you on Offkay.
Thanks, Tiara!
I know what I'm looking at, but I'd still choose to believe
it's a nice monkey.
It is a nice monkey carry.
You're not choosing that.
That is the absolute truth of the matter.
Whoa.
Ta-da!
Mm-hmm.
I hate having to circle over this, though.
I wish it was an easy collect.
What else should I add now, though?
What should I... Oh, we can add one of these, God.
We can add probably a wizard monkey.
We can add both wizard monkeys.
We can add a necromancer.
And we can add a phoenix.
Kiwawa.
Let's go with kiwawa now.
We'll add kiwawa right here.
Um...
Oh, wait.
I didn't need that one.
well okay now we'll upgrade max efficiency
oh my god you're back can't you be funny like like the
person that always was begging for ice monkey instead of an
annoying spam can't you have funny spam instead Oh,
thanks, Mon.
Can I get a happy birthday from my Oishi?
Also, which Hero Monkey do you want to unlock next?
Etchanane is my favorite.
I don't know that one.
Happy birthday, people!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, dear people!
birthday to a you.
Woo!
Happy birthday!
Yeah, why can't you guys entertain me instead of me
entertaining you?
You guys are supposed to be the funny ones, huh?
Still cuts a tomato.
A tomato.
And look, while the, like, everything is blowing, like, this
guy blows them back.
It's such a good setup.
I think this is the ideal setup.
Don't copy and paste them.
I will have you timed out.
And that's not a good...
Oh, whoops.
Oh, I don't think I pressed it.
Okay, good.
That's not a good timeout.
Timeout of shame.
Dang it.
Do they have a wizard monkey?
I have a wizard monkey.
I'm going to put a second Wizard Monkey.
Well, a second Wizard Monkey will go...
Wait, no, I want a second Wizard Monkey to get the...
Here.
This is...
Necromancy.
Oh!
Okay, we're already necromancing.
Holy cow.
Okay.
Never mind.
Uh...
Wall of Fire right there as well.
Oh my god!
There they go!
I know we've spent a lot of money to get him, but like, he
could just...
skull immediately like you know two men were robbing a
liquor store and the first one says this is whiskey his
partner shrugs and says yeah but not as whiskey as robbing
of this is whiskey Damon still takes for the 50k
This is whiskey.
Hello, kitten.
Could you please answer the phone right now?
It's...
No, I'm still calling.
Hello, kitten.
It's pretty whiskey that you're not answering right now.
But I would...
Think that you would pick up the phone.
In about...
Five seconds.
Or else, I'm going to get very angry.
How's the bit rate, everybody?
Am I crunchy?
How's the bit rate?
Nice.
I'm putting you in the contraption.
Very crunchy.
Still strong, actually.
Didn't go to Off-Kai, so here's a regular streamer tax.
Ah, thank you!
Very crunchy ectoplasm.
We're halfway there to full Phoenix.
Lord Phoenix, I'm so sorry.
We should start calling Kiara that Lord Phoenix.
Look at, you see the DDTs like come up and stop.
It's crazy.
Wow.
Who said no?
that level 150 was gonna kill me.
You didn't die at 150.
Yeah.
I didn't.
Ooh, it's coming in hot.
I
think that move is not so great.
It's better if like, there's a lot of balloons everywhere.
She's gotta clean up, you know?
Money?
go for 200 oh shoot oh you guys were in trouble we're in
trouble we're in trouble oh I just realized how far that got
yo we were so in trouble but we were fine we were in trouble
but we're fine
hmm oh
no hmm
hmm I already got all these guys
um we could get this guy or a bomb blitz
would a bomb blitz be worth it hmm I don't have so many um
there's also this guy but the juggernaut i forgot wait isn't
he really good maybe i think i should get him though right
this guy will have stuff sending all over the place right
oh it's not that great oh not really oh
oh i guess it does says only fortified lead boom it doesn't
even like yeah oh god What else can I get?
Um...
We need a million XP.
Pirate monkey.
Oh wait.
Oh, what?
Why does it keep...
Pirate monkey?
Plan monkey?
Do you have a middle path gatling gun?
Um...
on it mmm hmm no maybe I can have him up here and firing
down or here and firing down maybe they can they can but I
have a lot to go until 60,000 to unlock that enough.
Middle path boat.
Middle path boat instakills the OMGs.
Yeah, yeah, I have.
I've been using that one.
I already have it.
The preemptive strike and stuff.
What if our lasers charged?
Woo!
Oh, the bow.
Oh, bow.
Oh.
I keep showing by this show.
This one, the pirate lord.
Oh, okay, let's go for it.
It's gonna take a while, y'all.
But we can...
We'll put him in here.
Sign him up.
And we're also trying to get the 50,000.
Oh my god!
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
50, oh wait, wait, 50,000, please!
50,000, please!
Please!
Why don't I have enough money yet?
One pirate ship can eat three moabs.
Dang, okay.
Good to know for this to go through, to go down this way
then.
I do like this one.
Really improve power and can shoot three grappling hooks at
once.
Plundering extra cash from each moa.
Okay.
All right.
Let's hope that we can get the money.
Here we go.
Duh!
I don't know what I just did, but...
Oh, we have super crazy birds flying around now.
Oh, nice.
I think we're good.
And we should probably increase this as well.
so that we can get pops by 100% for, yes.
Okay, nice.
So this is our next thing, 40,000.
Oh.
Uh-oh.
Oh, please, please.
Ah!
Oh, wait.
It does another loop?
No way.
Ah!
just kidding dang we were not we were not up to stuff rip
erroney everybody all of our lives that we saved up that we
accumulated take my first time ever giving money to a
streamer no thank you weird ghost that for some reason uses
real currency hey the afterlife is just like real life i
think GG everybody.
That was an amazing run though.
That was the furthest I've ever been ever!
Oh, go away.
Cancel.
That was the furthest I've ever been ever.
So I'm pretty proud of ourselves.
Have 1,000 lives in a single- We did that!
We did that!
GG.
Pretty good for someone, not even level 50.
That's what I'm saying!
saying yeah you can make it to 200 someday I believe I told
you guys not to jinx it gosh gosh well now I don't have to
stand I can be big I can be big big toe big Minto.
Bigger Minto.
Yay!
Yippee!
Big toe.
Big Minto.
Big.
Minto.
Big toe.
I looked away for one minute, VTuber.
What did you do?
I didn't delete Ice Monkey.
I promise.
Clearly you needed more corn soup than helicopter Clearly
Well guys that was good GG That I mean I know that was like
one of the easier maps But That was a good taste of how
crazy it can get Right Big mean toll Big mean toe resort
is classified as the easiest yeah it is pretty easy I think
it is the easiest I like I can agree with the classification
please stop talking about toes sorry dog strings thanks for
the five gifted thank you is this why mean toes only nine
toes and then I'm the tenth nine toes and then a standing
I'm standing tall is the 10th toe.
You mean you mean toe?
Resort Cubism and logs.
Logs.
Hold on.
Let's see.
Cubism.
Oh, I was thinking of tree stump instead of logs.
Oh, this one.
And log...
Oh, I'm blocking logs.
Logs.
Logs looks pretty easy, too.
But things when they, like, overlap a lot is...
Yeah, I can see it.
Expert.
Oh, darkest dungeon.
My sanctuary.
Hashtag ouch.
What does that mean?
Oh.
Oh, I can unlock some of these, though.
It's kind of fun.
Off the coast.
High finance.
Cornfield!
Just got my bachelor's in computer engineering.
And moved into a new apartment a few days ago.
Let's go, Leopster!
Corn.
Corn, corn, corn, corn, corn.
I love corn soup.
Actually, I just love corn.
I took a Matara to Pepper Lunch for the first time.
And she was like, the corn was a good idea.
I was like, corn is always a good idea.
Corn is always the best.
Yeah, it is.
So, um...
I don't really have a schedule since I didn't expect to be
home a little early.
but I'll be streaming tomorrow as well.
Don't know what yet.
We'll figure something out.
And...
Yeah.
So, I'm not quite sure what.
Same time tomorrow?
Same time.
Same place.
Same minty.
a fresh channel.
Mm-mm.
Balloon same time tomorrow.
Imagine.
No.
No, I'm not gonna do balloons today, I don't know.
That would be crazy talk.
But...
No.
Don't even tempt me.
You temptress.
Stop being such a temptress.
Stop being so seductive right now, okay?
As an expert at this game, I'd like to offer you my
recommendations.
The secret to winning is to buy monkeys and place them to
pop blues.
Riveting.
Advice.
I wasn't doing that before, so I'll try that next time.
Thank you.
Sorry, can't help it.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Blowns.
I hope you feel butter soon.
Thank you.
I'm already feeling butter.
Like I've congested, but I even feel like, hold on, I'm
gonna drink some of this green tea.
I hope I can taste it.
Yum, yum, yum, yum.
I couldn't, I actually couldn't taste it earlier, but now I
can even a little.
Bloons is the cure!
I'm diseased and bloons is the cure, everybody!
Bloons!
So you'll let me play Bloons tomorrow?
No, I'm not going to play Bloons tomorrow.
Don't worry, don't worry.
We found the cure.
I'm just going to play more of it tonight.
Immoral Plane, thanks for the 20 gifted and Johnny!
Thanks for the 5 gifted.
Thank you.
Edward, thank you for two months.
There were so many, I think, notifications were really
backed up.
So there's a lot of donos that didn't show up.
So, David Titanium, thank you.
I got my Tetrio sprint.
That's what we'll do tomorrow.
We'll play Tetrio.
Actually, I thought about it for today, but I was like, my
brain's going to be too small.
Too smart.
No, too slow.
Tomorrow we'll play Tetrio.
So you can all thank David Titanium.
titanium for that.
I got my Tetrio sprint record down to 50 seconds.
Glad you're back.
I can't stop playing that game.
I haven't played Tetrio in a long time, so it'll be a great
Zatsudan game, right?
Well, a great yapping game.
Timo, thank you.
Cool things Mint does.
Be Mint.
Stream, be Mint.
Tweet, be Mint.
Thanks.
Did you know I've been in number for two months?
Yeah, please.
Thank you.
I'm glad to hear you're doing better, Min-tao!
Rest up some more so we can get...
Do more big brain blues!
Thank you, Servo!
Wrong for Robin, thank you!
Wow, this deck, thank you!
Seymour, thank you!
I found out my Waka vendor listed a Metal Gear Arc game
machine.
Interested?
yes yes I'm interested in the Metal Gear arcade machine I'm
interested I'm interested please please give me their
contact information blah blah
blah blah blah thank you for good all thank you heard you
held hands with the vampire what me and Maria yeah we might
have held hands um actually i think i was the one who like
grabbed her hat
i think i went in first not thanks for the vibe but thank
you eventual ghosts that's that sounds about right hope you
feel better thank you so much so forward
it's because you know off kai gave me so much energy so i
felt like a little I was like a kind of I felt um what's the
word corporal when corporeal when I can manifest physically
I was absorbing so much life energy that I was maybe I can't
be why everybody got sick right corporeal corporeal
corporeal first off Kai was really fun for me too thank you
I hope...
Wait, no.
I'm glad you had fun.
Or plural.
Golden Foxy, thank you!
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, Golden Foxy!
Travis, thank you!
And I think that's all of them that didn't make it through.
So thank you guys for the donos as well.
Sorry that they got all blocked up by...
They got all blocked by the gifted donos.
But yes, I still see you.
I see you.
Thank you.
The gift wall remains strong.
Yes, it dies.
I'll, it's funny because I'll like leave OBS open after I,
after I stream and eventually I'll hear a
I miss you a bunch.
Thank you.
I miss you guys too, but I'm back now.
Um, at least until AX and then I'll be performing there.
Uh, performing at the concert, not at AX.
You don't need an AX
But, uh...
Um...
Oh!
Wait!
Maybe I should add Toot Toot Toot Toot Toot to my list,
shouldn't I?
Um...
My rain just had a pavloat in response to the Toot Toot
Toot.
Sorry, sorry.
Maybe I should add one.
I'll think about it.
all right i should go uh it is a cute sound and i love
stein's gate so don't miss a fiction show um where you guys
have made to me oh there's a story that only the maid cafe
knows at afkai um after after the maid cafe closed they did
a special it was so funny they like opened it especially
just for like Matara and I and um and I was uh I was like
hanging out with some friends and Matara like called me and
she's like where are you you said you were gonna come to the
mid cafe and I was like ah I gotta drop some stuff off in my
room and I'll come back and um I went and did that and I was
she was like how long do you think it'll be and I was like
five minutes and so I ran to my room and I put my stuff away
and then I ran to the maid cafe.
when I opened up the door, they were all lined up.
Even Mataro, she was lined up with the maids.
And they welcomed me home.
And I was like, it was.
It was a dream come true.
I was like, except Mataro, she kind of ruined it.
But I was like, oh my god, are all lined up oh my gosh so
and something really silly i danced for the maids even i
danced a little bit our group had the maid cafe time slot
right before you were there ah man next time maybe but uh i
danced for the maids and um I taught them how to do some
otage.
They were so cute.
And they served me a sandwich, but they said that it was
really nasty.
And I was like, no, I'll eat it anyway.
And it was really nasty.
I couldn't finish.
They were like, um, should we get you something else,
Ojo-sama?
But I'm not used to being called Ojo-sama.
I was like, no, I'll eat it for you guys.
And it was so bad.
It was so gross.
But, um, yeah, I said something silly there that it's only
the maids and the maids, no.
Oopsie.
We had made Minto Sonia's mermaid, so it was fun.
Yeah!
I got to meet her!
She was so cute!
Her cosplay was so- oh my gosh, I can't believe there were
mint guys players at off-campus.
I can't believe I got to see them it was so awesome oh my
gosh I can't believe it I can't believe it that's crazy hmm
what was wrong with the sandwich I don't know it was like a
it was like their gluten-free option or maybe maybe their
vegan option I'm not sure but there was like a a hummus and
an avocado spread inside that just tasted so awful did you
see the bunny i saw pictures of the bunny girl but i never
got to see who i'm so sad i only got to see pictures so sad
here's some singles for the maids i've never been to a maid
cafe but i assume you throw money at them like you do at the
club you don't do that but at my maid cafe you can throw the
money at me
okay get out
But yeah, throws quarters out.
Oh, it's getting in my eye.
Oh god.
So awesome saying, made mint sunny at the maid cafe.
It was so awesome saying you were fine.
What the hell?
Wait, what about me?
What about me, huh?
Theocrats, thanks for the thank you.
Thank you for that.
Oh, oh.
Thank you guys, thank you, thank you.
The money, no.
Made Sonny and Rubey were so cute.
Yeah, they were so cute.
Here you go, boss.
Okay.
You guys waited for this, it feels like.
Oh my gosh, thank you guys.
Thank you.
Gonna head out now, fun streaming.
Thank you, I'm also gonna head out.
I'm gonna head out too because, oh, I should get some rest.
But tomorrow we'll play Tetrio together, so we'll all be
able to play games together!
Yuppie!
How many people can be in a Tetrio room at once?
I don't know.
99?
100?
Hmm.
I'm not sure.
Otomito!
Thank you guys for the warm welcome back!
I'm so happy to be home.
I'm so happy to be streaming.
And next time I go to Japan, I won't make the same mistake
of getting the bad hotel and The next time I go someplace,
I'll stream.
Oh.
I'll make sure of it.
Sorry for... sorry for being gone for so long.
And having nothing to show for.
Oh, I'm so...
But, um...
Sorry.
That's all I can do.
can say, I just feel so bad that I was gone and have nothing
to show for it.
Except my cough.
Except my baby cough.
But yeah.
Okay.
Thank you guys.
And enjoy the rest of your night and I'll see you tomorrow.
And... Oh!
Hold on.
Since we have time.
We have time.
We have time, we have time, we have time.
Wait, hold on, do I get an ad?
Will I get an ad?
Oh, no, I won't.
Yeah!
There's something strange,
Let me tell you something.
If there's something weird, slip it in your bag.
Ow!
Let me tell you something.
Yeah!
Bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin,
bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin, bustin,
bustin, bustin, bustin!
I'm seeing things sleeping in your bed.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
An invisible man sleeping in your bed.
Oh!
That is busting, busting, busting, busting, busting,
busting, busting, busting, busting, busting, busting,
busting, makes me feel Feel good, feel good.
I didn't cough as much as I thought I would this stream.
And I haven't even taken that much medicine today.
I think I'm feeling better!
I'm gonna test again tomorrow.
See how I'm... how I'm... how I'm progressing.
Feel good, feel good, feel good.
Beep, beep, beep!
Mmm!
Freaky ghost made!
freaky ghost man Freaky man baby Ow ow ow what if my name
wasn't made mint what if my name was freaky man
Let me tell you something sleeping makes me feel good
I'm afraid of no sleep.
I'm afraid of no bed an invisible bed oh freaky ghost bed oh
my book glasses my face is a little crooked don't worry
about it don't worry about it there we go busting busting
makes me feel good feel good feel good feel good feel good
you know what if some artist is listening and if you're
bored one day you ever want to make me some some some new
glasses that I can wear on stream that and one one lens says
like freak and then the other glasses say oh wait how can I
say freak phantom maybe in both lenses and the other one
says nothing the other one says why freaky master minto and
then i can say do you like my glasses feel good freaks and
friends feel good good night freaks and friends thank you
see you tomorrow bye bye thank you