Oh, wait.
Go back to the main menu.
Go back to the main menu!
What?
There we go.
Kept you waiting, huh?
Howdy, Minto.
Hi, Minto.
Welcome back to Metal Gear Solid 2!
Yippee!
Yippee, Yippee, Yippee!
Yippee, yippee!
Good morning, Minto.
Even though it's afternoon, good morning, Minto.
What took you so long, Minto?
Um.
I don't know.
I think...
I was distracted on TikTok.
But yes, welcome back.
And everything.
best to get through as much of the game as possible today
but no pressure if i don't finish or do finish or whatever
it's the vinyl guy from the con i hope you enjoy it also
your q a was fun we hope to see you back in texas again
thank you bruce oh my gosh i can't wait oh my gosh the vinyl
i'm so thank you can we have a quick recap from the previous
two episodes of course paul that's a great that's a great
idea so um for those who are familiar with the game we are
right about to um to uh disable the bombs and then uh uh no
that that is not solid snake but if you oh my gosh thank you
for holding the super chance oh my gosh hold on give me a
second and then i'll read them um um let me do the recap
first uh And, um, I'm trying not to, like, spoil.
So, basically, from the very beginning, two years ago, on,
um, in, in New York, um, the Hudson River, two years ago,
um, Solid Snake dies!
Solid Snake dies on the tanker after he fought Olga, and
after, um, Aselai stole the Metal Gear.
He double-crossed Grilukovic and killed Grilukovic, the
Russian side and everything.
And he stole Metal Gear Ray from the military.
And he was just like, ha, ha, ha, this is mine, ha, ha, ha.
And then Solid Snake dies.
So sad, so, so sad.
But then we move two years later on to the big show.
the big shell incident where a group of terrorists called
dead cell have taken hold of the president oh my god not the
president and um they're but but they're led by their leader
solid snake oh my gosh not solid snake but he died on the
tanker two years ago what and um so we are riding and we've
disabled bombs we well the guy who taught taught us how to
disable bombs also blew up so we fought a fat man we um uh
we met fortune and she's really sexy yeah we met a bisexual
um that was vamp um we met pliskin who uh we've never met
that guy before ever before and uh Yeah, now we're trying to
get to the president.
But first, we must cross a field of bombs that we must
disable.
Blow up.
We must shoot the bombs.
Iroquois Pliskin.
Maximilian, thank you.
First time being able to catch a Metal Gear stream live.
So it's lovely to see you in real time.
I hope you're taking care of yourself and that you have a
fantastic day.
Thank you.
Yoshi, welcome back for two months.
Awesome to be here.
Love you guys.
Thank you.
Football!
Oh.
Today is not my birthday, but it was on Thursday.
I kept missing your streams because of work.
Can I get a happy birthday, please?
Of course!
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, dear football.
Happy birthday.
I think I got everything.
Did I cover everything?
Was that everything?
We saw some sexy ladies in lockers, some sexy ladies in the
bathroom.
Schrödinger's snake.
He's simultaneously dead and not dead.
There was a parrot.
Yeah, we saw a parrot.
Oh, Rose.
Nothing of Rose.
Oh, and Olga.
Yes.
Well, sorry.
I said Gurluka-Vich.
I forgot to mention his daughter, Olga.
We fought her on the tanker as Snake, and now she's still
working with Ocelot and not Solid Snake.
And, of course, Raiden has his lovely, lovely, lovely
partner of Lifetime Partner who he'll never abandon, who
he'll never ever take for granted, who she is loyal and will
never leave him either.
They're going to grow happy and old and die together.
And that's Rose.
And they never have any problems.
They're the healthiest relationship ever.
What did I ask?
Because I asked this to get different views.
What motivates you to keep going in life?
When things get stressful, what do you do to keep yourself
from worrying about things?
Oh, that's a deep question, Yoshi.
Thanks for the super chat.
Um, what keeps me going in my afterlife is the ability to
see my oshi if i could see my oshi then there's something
worth staying dead for and i always worry sorry i don't stop
worrying i don't know how to do that yet oh hiya minto oh
hiyao wish me luck i have multiple drama interviews next
subplots good luck with your interviews oh my gosh good luck
good luck good luck But yeah, now I think I got everything.
So yeah, we're about to disable some bombs.
And yeah.
We'll see how far I get today.
I'm thinking.
I don't know.
And Draco is next to the 20 gift day.
Thank you.
Load.
How did we get to 2099?
Huh?
Wait.
How did we get to...
Ha!
Poor MGS2.
My brain is still comprehending Hideo Kojima's tweets about
Deadpool Wolverine.
Yes.
I love Hideo Kojima's tweets about the new Deadpool
Wolverine movie and how he was just like, it's so awesome
seeing Wolverine so ripped and so muscular and I'm like,
what do you mean by that?
Oshi Love is strong for real for real Hi Mint by Oshi Hello
Wow it's been 99 years What does he mean?
I don't He means what he said That guy always means what he
says right?
Oh Alright let me get used to the game once again So, am I
going to get a call from Colonel if I get too close?
Oh, oh.
Ryden, you haven't destroyed all the control units yet.
Use the first person view or the sniper scope to look
around.
How's the audio, by the way?
Let me know.
The Otaku Tan 2024 schedule was uploaded on Guidebook.
Looks like your meet and greet autograph is Friday, day one,
evening.
Hoping there will be space in line if I light up five hours.
Oh my gosh, ghost of mid, please.
You don't have to...
I have several meet and greets.
For Otaku-tan this coming weekend, I have several
meet-and-greet, so please don't feel like you have to line
up so early, okay?
Please don't live.
Please.
Just another day for riding, aka Agent Lovely Hips.
Best answer.
Now it's time to eat chicken.
Yippee!
Yes, and I do have...
Let's see.
Let me get all my ducks in a row.
in this is how i'm oh gosh don't go overboard riding all
right let's we have a sniper where is our sniper oh here it
is we have look at that we have the psg1t tranquilize
tranquil tranquil tranquil tranquilize rifle trank rifle
yeah and we but we're gonna use this one
How do I zoom in on this thing?
Zoom with O.
Fire with square.
Sons of libera.
I'm gonna get that bird.
Hold on.
I'm gonna...
Stop riding!
Stop!
He's like, don't...
Oh!
Rising.
I think I got it.
Does it not shoot through the...
Does it not shoot through the thing?
Does it not shoot through the flag?
Silence out of...
Oh!
Oops, I pressed the wrong button.
Oh gosh, I don't want to run out of bullets.
You'll hear it if you get it.
I think I need to take some Pizzizamine.
Or is my Pizzamine?
Or...
Wait a second.
Ryden has cigarettes!
Oh, I have 10 of them.
Perfect.
There we go.
Okay.
I think I'll get it.
What the heck?
Okay, let's get the other stuff first.
Let's get the other things first.
Oh!
Move, birds!
Move!
Oh, oh, oh.
Okay, that's one.
I don't know, actually, how many there are.
Move, birds!
Move!
I don't think I killed him.
Oh.
There's two?
I don't know how many there are.
Wait, why are those still blinking though?
Also, I don't...
Oh!
There it is.
Alright.
Wind!
Oh!
Oh, I got it.
Nice.
How did you guys...
I can't hear it.
Am I deaf?
Oh.
How many are left?
Ryden, you didn't get all the control units.
You weren't thorough enough.
I'm not dying!
Take a good look at the airborne cipher.
You can see the control unit for the IR sensor.
Huh?
The control unit is right above cipher's...
camera avoid shooting the camera at all costs looks like if
a cipher is shut down the resulting signal will trigger an
explosion the whole bridge would oh target only the control
unit on the upper part of the cipher aim for the blinking
light blinking light okay i wasn't let me finish my art i
know there's a cipher oh here oh a blinking light okay i got
you Oh You sent the blinking light What the hell happened?
Right
Snake Snake You sent the blinking light Snake Oh gosh
You sent the blinking light I mean, Pliskin.
I swear that guy, like, just gets me every time.
Thanks for making Ava some fun experience.
I already bragged about meeting you.
It's the second most famous person to my friends.
I'm not even.
Thanks to your brainwrap panel, I now learn MGS is really
about butts.
Yeah!
Thank you for coming to meet me.
Thank you so much.
Yeah, Freudian slip.
Freudian slip.
Same voice actor.
I don't think even...
I think they sound really different, actually.
I don't even think it's the same voice actor.
I think it's just, you know...
Okay.
Did I misunderstand what you said, Pliskin?
Pliskin, oh Pliskin.
Alright, alright, come on, come on, riding.
Come on, riding, riding, riding, shaking hands, riding.
Riding.
Stop shaking your... There we go.
Stop shaking your hands right now, Riding.
actually that managed to hit i'll be honest because that
didn't seem like it should have hit because i was low can i
go down now because oh i deactivated it right right but i
deactivated them okay that's a no this is this is this is
what's gonna take the longest and In today's stream.
Just trying to...
Okay, well now I know.
Okay.
And one more over here.
No, we're not finishing.
Shut up!
This part?
Yeah, we're not finishing this part today.
Yeah, guys.
Sorry.
Dang it.
Ryden, Ryden, Ryden.
Ow!
Ryden!
Oh my god.
This is the mod, watch it, this is the whole stream.
He didn't, Colonel didn't even sound, actually was that
Colonel?
He didn't even sound like he was, like, sad about me dying.
He sounded, like, so disappointed.
He was like, Ryden, what are you doing, Ryden?
Okay, I'll take the I was trying to do it without the
pizzazzamine, but I'll do it with it.
Okay.
Okay, guys, we Don't blow up this time.
This is the run.
Can I still get it?
Even when it's behind the flag.
I never actually knew if I could.
Oh yeah, I did.
Okay, nice.
Then there's the one.
What's the blinking light?
Oh, at the very, very top?
Maybe?
What's the blinking light?
Pull it through flag.
was still there.
Oh, oh, say.
Uh.
This isn't mean.
Green light.
Did I not get the green?
Gosh, this part's so silly.
Pliskin.
I thought I got the blinking light.
Okay, I'm gonna aim for the tippy tippy top.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
Yippee!
Okay, and oh, I remember this one.
Is that all of them?
Oh, gosh.
I don't remember what other ones there are.
Was there any that I need to lay down for?
Because, well, they tell you when we're good, so they tell
you when we're good.
I need laying down ones.
I don't know why I'm...
What?
A mustache man!
Why?
Thank you for the welcome to my vlog.
Looking forward to more episodes of everyone's favorite
telenovela.
Reglaas de la naturaliza.
What?
Oh!
I see it.
Oh, yes!
That's...
Duh!
The one that I got before.
This one.
This is a mean, this is a mean, this is a mean.
Uh...
Zoom in.
Enhance.
Sorry, birds.
I'm gonna destroy this party.
Why can't I move just slightly?
Oh.
There we go.
Yay!
I don't think I hit one.
Did I?
I don't think so.
Alright!
Okay, are you guys ready?
Wait.
I have a grenade launcher.
I don't have a stinger.
Do I get it here?
I sure hope so.
Let's go!
The Tossy one?
Okay.
I found us a ride.
I'm all ears.
One of the enemy's Kasatka's.
Is it in good shape?
Full tank.
I'm heading for Shell 1 now.
What about that Harrier?
It's not on the heliport here.
I'll set this one down there.
How would every loving heck do you play this game without
the pressure-sensitive buttons?
They're being held on level B1 in the core.
It's...
Yeah.
Pliskin, you didn't happen to find any other places where
hostages were being held, did you?
No.
Nothing like that.
Okay.
How many hostages are there?
There's a few short of 30.
One dead and several wounded.
The Kasaka's cargo area will hold 13, max.
What about the other Kasaka?
Kasaka.
I sabotaged it.
us if it can't get off the ground no we'll have to make two
trips right can you fly a Kasatka I have a pilot who's flown
the civilian model the Ka-62 and VR there's not a whole lot
of difference between the military Ka-60 and the civilian
model oh for takeoff right let me introduce you to my
partner Otakon Otakon hey Ryden nice to meet you I'll talk
to you later oh my god it's I'm the worst.
Colonel, I need some answers from you.
Who exactly is Pliskin and his partner?
I know what you're thinking.
It keeps coming back to Shadow Moses.
And now this Otacon...
AKA Hal Emmerich PhD, a Shadow Moses survivor.
Rose?
Rouse?
Snake and Otacon both became fugitives after Shadow Moses
wanted for acts of terrorism.
An anti-metal gear organization.
Yeah.
They sabotaged and destroyed countless Metal Gear units.
throughout the world oh my god responsible for the incident
two years ago that necessitated the construction of the big
shell oh snake and his partner aren't terrorists wait why do
you mean snake and his partner I look back on what I've done
here so far and things like training and sense of duty alone
won't get you it's right it's spoiling Jack are you okay you
need you okay higher I can't think of the right word but it
has to be pure will backed up by by courage or He's starting
to believe.
He's starting to believe.
I've saved my life on it.
The solid snake that saved Shadow Moses couldn't turn into a
terrorist.
Maybe that's true.
But they went down with that tanker two years ago.
We even recovered Snake's body.
And the DNA test results on the body say it's him.
It's him.
Jack, I know what you're saying, but Snake is dead.
He can't be here.
Not even as this Dr. Hal Emmerich.
But that also means that he can't be the terrorist leader
behind this thing.
Yeah, he died!
He died!
No more solid snake.
Whoa.
Uh-oh.
A Harrier?
No.
I love that guy.
I love that guy!
No Harrier.
We're good to go, guys.
A trash bag!
I've been waiting for you.
A messenger from the Patriots.
So you're the boss around here?
No, not just around here.
I'm the boss to surpass Big Boss himself.
Oh, solid snake.
No, that is not solid snake.
Yeah!
Not solid snake!
Brother.
Save it.
Don't say you've forgotten me.
Oh my god, the...
Snake!
That was snake?
No.
Who was you?
Solid snake, too.
Snake?
Take cover.
Ah!
Whoa.
Oh my god, you're gonna blow up the whole bridge!
Oh my god, he's so awesome.
Stop impersonating him.
Identity theft is real.
Brother, I'm a whole different game from Liquid.
Hehehehe.
Nano machines.
Oh my god.
I cry.
Wow!
Um, hi!
There's someone else on the bridge here, please.
Oh my god.
Oof!
The voice acting is so low compared to like the sound
effects and the audio and everything.
Ah!
No, complain.
There it is.
There's the Harrier.
It's the Harrier.
He's getting...
Just shave him!
Wax him!
If he's Harrier!
Oh.
He's a shrinking baby.
How can a play like that be sneaky?
The world needs only one big boss.
Oh my god, Top Gun moment.
I drown you fools for interfering.
Ah!
Oh,
my ears, please.
Yippee!
The Kasaka can't stand up to the Harrier.
Why not?
You have to shoot the Harrier down.
Oh, okay.
It's happening in the bay right now.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, this is a little far out.
But we do eventually get to the bay.
I thought you meant like this is happening in the bay right
now of New York.
Okay, I'm going downstairs.
Okay.
How do I remember to do this?
Oh!
Oh my gosh, Pliskit!
Why are you sending it to me from up there?
Where is it?
Oh, Stinger.
Oh my god.
Blah, blah, blah!
Oh my goodness!
Oh gosh, I have to remember how to do this fight.
Where is he anyway?
Oh, he's on this side.
Beep, beep, beep, beep.
Where are you?
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
I think he's upstairs?
Oh yeah, there he is.
Ah!
Oh, I think I ran into the wall.
Everybody.
Classic Minto move.
Oh, get out of the way, Pliskin!
She's scaring me.
Oh my god, there he is.
Shoot the copter.
Take cover!
Take cover?
I think.
Is this when he starts doing everything?
Where is he, anyway?
Oh my god, she's so fast.
Yeah, it'd be great if I...
Game!
Bozo!
What are you gonna take...
What are you gonna take care of, huh?
Oh my god.
Well, if you would just give me a chance, I'm just standing
here.
Let me in!
Mom said it's my turn!
This thing is so fast.
Oh my god.
This is when he starts blowing everything up.
Oh, go in, go in, go in for the kill!
I would have just hit the wall.
Am I going to even get a shot at getting this guy?
Where is he?
Where'd he go?
Oh, there he is.
Come on!
Oh my god.
Oh,
okay.
Whoa.
And I wait.
Grisket go upstairs.
Why do I need to go upstairs?
I'm cozy down here.
You're
all...
You have not hit...
You have not hit me once!
Come on!
This is not the best you can do!
I'm literally standing still!
Solid dust?
Best you can do, my butt.
Where are you?
Oh my god.
Oh, there he is!
Ah!
I always loved how when you shoot a Semtex, the whole bridge
blows up, but when these two...
I know, right?
It's so unfair.
I don't know.
Where?
Oh.
Oh no!
Ah!
Okay.
Oh!
Oh my god, he did hit me.
Oh god, he did get me.
Okay, I'm good now.
You know, just got hit by a missile, no biggie.
Nice!
Hit you?
There we go.
Did I get him?
I don't think I did.
Shoot.
No, I don't think I got him!
Wait, can I get him here?
Come on.
Oh, I don't think I will.
I think I'm gonna blow myself up if I try.
Ah!
Oh no!
Can you get up, Rylan?
Oh, is he gonna get me?
I think I should.
Behind me.
Yeah, I know.
I was totally looking the wrong way.
Where has he come from?
He like comes usually from like this.
Where is he?
Ah!
Oh, you're bleeding again.
This guy is so... all over the place.
Ah!
Get his butt!
Just take the shot!
There we go.
These camera angles crack me up.
I'll shred you to pieces!
Oof.
Gosh, he's got so much health.
What are you taking care of anyway?
What are you doing?
His butt is so prominent.
I swear, in the HD collection, I think they nerfed Raiden
because he looks good in this game.
He looks good, good in this game.
I know I'm like going the super...
Oh, that is not!
Oh my gosh.
You!
Oof.
My man just says oof.
So funny.
Oof.
What is this?
You're tougher than I thought.
sitting down here, dude.
I'll let you go out in style.
Did I get him?
Nice.
Oh, but not like...
Not super...
It's not a super good shot.
Nice.
Still got him, though.
It's hard finding him sometimes.
Ah!
Oh!
Take the shot!
Oh, I didn't get him.
Bit by bit.
Yeah, bit by bit.
Oh, gosh.
He's out here somewhere.
We'll get him.
Oh, there he is.
Run!
Nice.
We get that nice, good old head-on collision.
Did I get him?
I can't tell sometimes if I get him or not.
Damn.
One tough walkway.
Okay.
I'm let you take care of...
Oh.
See on the other side?
Where is he?
Oh, sure.
Dude.
Okay.
Oh, this side.
Oh, he's doing his, like, far away thing, right?
There he is.
There he is!
Got a lot of smoke coming off of you, buddy.
You're not looking so good, man.
This thing is just indestructible.
Yeah!
Oh, my God.
That was, like, the small...
Oh!
It's like the smallest amount.
of damage ever.
How much, how many bullets?
Oh, I still have a lot of bullets, but I don't know if I'm
gonna be able to get him in time, to be honest.
There he is.
Oh, maybe I can, maybe I will.
We'll see.
Die!
Oh, dang it!
Oh my gosh.
Can I get him from here?
Okay, let me try again.
It's the little...
Oh, oh, nice, nice, nice, nice.
Okay, good, good, good, good.
What is that the best you can do?
Okay, he's back on that side.
Shoot!
I didn't, I didn't get him.
Oh, thank you!
Where?
Wait, oh, up there.
You're gonna make me run for it?
Come on.
Right down.
I'll let you guard in style.
Woo-ha!
Usually.
like to get him that during that part but hey let you go out
it's time
bye solid it oh we got his eye
into the ocean oh there's something coming up it's my throw
up
Wow!
Alright.
So dramatic.
That's Metal Gear!
It's already active!
Oh my gosh, it catches it in his mouth.
Look how cute!
Ray is just like a little puppy dog!
How can you not think Ray is the cutest thing ever?
He catches the whole plane in his mouth!
He is so cute!
Oh my god, what a show.
You got this Ryden!
Level 2 grip!
Yeah, if we hadn't had the level 2 grip, we would have
fallen into the ocean.
True facts.
Oof.
You might want to get like a iPad or something for that.
Who are you telling that to?
Vamp?
Does he care?
They got my eye.
Me eye!
Vamp, go!
Where is he going?
He's like, he jumps into the water and swims away?
Like, where is he going?
Oh my gosh, please, Pliskin!
He's just...
Oh my gosh, he's watching the show.
Oh my god.
He's like, ah.
When I see some buns, I get hungry.
Oh, there he goes.
What a freak, this guy.
Hey, what's that?
It's running on water.
It's...
He doesn't even call Vampy like a person.
Vamp is an it.
Oh my god.
Vamp, the true strongest character in the series.
Ryden doesn't know what to think about any of that.
Ryden, you all right?
Yeah, how about you guys?
Yeah, you have some explaining to do.
The chopper?
We need some time for repairs.
The chopper.
The president's all yours.
Okay.
Can I ask you something?
Are you the snake?
They said you were dead.
Big shout's only like three inches deep.
There are still too many things I need to do.
Oh my god!
Snake, you're a legend, and that's why I need to ask you
this.
Legend.
A legend is nothing but fiction.
Someone tells it, someone else remembers, everybody passes
it on.
I'm here because I was assigned to this mission.
Not because I want to.
The snake.
I'd be out of here in a second.
Snake after all!
How could you come back to all this?
Why keep fighting?
There's something my best friend said to me once.
What?
We're not tools of the government or anyone else.
Fighting was the only thing I was good at, but...
At least I always fought for what I believed in.
What about...
What about the DNA results from that body?
That was Liquid's body.
He and Snake are identical on the genetic level.
Liquid?
A deception?
For our own protection.
We stole his frozen body from some organization.
That's crazy.
though that's all there is to it we just took his body an
NGO insofar as we're a nonprofit organization of civilians
advocating a cause yes the cause happens to be the
eradication of metal gear yes we work on our own but it's a
cause worth fighting for why would you stick your neck out
for something this risky that's the way I used to look at it
four years ago I was holed up in the middle of nowhere in
Alaska drinking too much we have a responsibility to the
coming What are you talking about?
What responsibility?
Keep track of the mistakes we've made as a species.
Crazy how Pliskin disappears and Snake shows up.
I know.
To fight for change.
And that's what keeps me alive.
History says we're facing things.
You think you could change the future?
I'm not as arrogant as that.
What you do isn't grassroots activism.
It's more like terrorism.
No, it's not.
I mean, maybe it is.
Philanthropy received some information.
A new Metal Gear prototype was being developed here.
And terrorists were planning to raid facility the
information came from a very reliable source so you're here
too we're here to stop all that very reliable i also have a
personal motive looks like the terrorists have his sister in
the big shell oh my god we're here on our own not under
anyone's orders we have our own battles no this is a
military mission so okay jack are you all right just barely
you almost gave me a here you go again who wasn't
intentional i know that and i know i need to stay stronger
say a prayer for me rose so i can come back you will make it
back i'm with you all the way remember that means a lot to
me you know i'm going to save the data okay jack yes thank
you all right now we're about halfway through right so good
stuff 29 to 9.
he's to our So insufferable.
What?
They're the best ever!
Colonel, Metal Gear's already gone active.
It's not too late.
You can still prevent a nuclear strike by securing the
president and preventing password confirmation from taking
place.
Get to the president.
He's in the core section of Shell 2.
I'm checking the satellite images.
Looks like you can get to the core from the other side of
Strut L.
Oh, boy.
The core hasn't gone under yet from what we can tell.
Follow the railings down, then jump onto the pipes.
The only viable strut in the outer perimeter is the L.
The L.
That attack just now doesn't make any sense.
It's like they have no more use for this place.
Colonel, you were monitoring the codec calls.
That man was the real snake all along.
Maybe.
Don't let your guard down with him.
Why do you say that?
Because they were never a part of the simulation.
They're an unknown factor.
Maybe.
You can take your simulation and...
Yeah.
We're out here.
We bleed.
I'll say it for you, right?
and shove it up your ass.
I suggest that you do, Raiden.
Shove it!
Even if that is Snake, that has no bearing on your mission.
Colonel, you and Snake used to be on the same side.
Oh.
I don't understand.
I read about you and Snake in the darkness of Shadow Moses.
I don't give a damn what that piece of trash said.
Do you get me?
You've changed, Colonel.
This guy, Colonel in this game is so So, so, he's so mean.
He's so mean in this game.
Why are you going to be so mean?
Oh, wait.
The coolant is this one, right?
Here it is.
Snake broke his heart.
Okay.
Now I won't accidentally burn myself.
What?
Oh.
Wait, wasn't there a ration in there?
Oh, man.
So much for that ration.
Puskin, can you send me another, please?
No!
I forgot that it was gonna fall.
No.
No!
I just cartwheel over.
Wait.
I don't do it.
I don't remember actually.
Do I just cartwheel over?
Oh!
Gosh.
Oh my gosh.
Oh on the other side.
The one with the bird poop?
The side that's actually trying to kill me?
It's a leap of faith.
What's going on?
Answer me!
Jack?
Jack!
This Jack right there floating, never learning how to swim.
No fade.
Wait!
We can get the ration now.
Maybe.
Hold on.
Okay, I'm not gonna...
I'm listening to Mei Ling.
I'm not gonna be so stupid to always try.
For the...
You know?
I don't have to, you know?
But what if I just...
Run down?
Grab it, run up.
Ooh, what a gamer.
Yeah!
Okay.
Alright, I have to...
Oh gosh.
He'll grab onto this, right?
Mealing is right.
You're just that good.
You missed the boat.
Here we...
Lean onto the railing.
No, this isn't happening.
Jack, you have to answer me.
Jack!
Nice one, gamer.
Thank you.
Oh, someone's calling me.
Wait, my cell phone's going off.
Hello?
Use the cool it spread- God damn it!
I know!
What do you think I've been doing?
God, how'd you get this number?
How'd you get this number?
Happy April 30th!
Please remember to Lolliloo Live, Laugh, Love, in these
drawing times.
Thank you.
Backseating.
I don't remember how to do it.
Like, I remember having to go to that pipe over there and be
careful of the bird poop and everything.
I just don't remember how to get over there.
Live, laugh, grow fat.
Flip over the railing after pressing on it.
Oh, thank you.
You think this is a good spot?
Over a little bit.
Level two grip, baby.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, riding, riding, riding.
You're scaring me, Raiden.
Okay.
Crawl, crawl, crawl, crawl.
Crawl, crawl.
I hate this part.
This is even how speedrunners do it.
They're too scared.
They're too scared of this part.
They crawl too.
Everybody crawl.
Oh my god.
Jump.
Yippee!
Okay.
We're all good.
Oh, nope.
Almost.
Almost there.
Grab it.
Grab.
Raiden.
Grab the... grab right and go... lift up.
Lift.
Can't go that way unless you carwheel.
No way!
Oh well.
Remember the basics of skateboarding.
Oh, it's on fire now!
Wait!
Was it always on fire?
Did that just happen?
Run!
There are guys here, aren't there?
I don't have a nerd.
Aren't there guys here though?
Where do they come out?
Scoot scoot scoot Yeah
No, sir.
Oh my gosh I have to get them to move closer.
Perfect.
Nobody else, right?
Nothing here.
Oh no.
Oh.
Uh.
Here.
Dangling.
Dingling.
Oh.
Dangle, dangle, dangle.
Dangle, dangle.
Isn't this where the AK-74 suppressor is?
Wait, really?
Oh, hi, Mint.
Hello.
Wait, is it actually?
Are those guys still asleep, or...
Who am I hearing?
Who am I hearing right now?
Oh, oh, this is where they're...
This is the windows.
I remember this part.
Oh, gosh.
I wonder how far can I get from Dingle dangling Oh my god
You encounter DM You encounter nothing
Gosh he saw me so fast Uh Just a box
They won't be able to see me Oh my god Just a box Just a...
Just a box!
Do you think he can tell?
Those other guys are still asleep.
Maybe I'm okay.
Maybe I can go.
Bam, bam, bam.
I don't think I can crawl here because I'm pretty sure at
some point the...
From what I remember...
Oh my gosh, I can't use it here.
Oh my god.
Oh god.
Oh no, that's not what I meant to do.
Oh my god.
But don't the floors give out though in some point?
Go up, go up.
when do we get beat on
I'm scared soon those guys still asleep over here no way oh
gosh I wish I could take them out again there's too many
guys go away you know what screw it let's just crawl for now
I can't see where they are
Okay, but this is...
Maybe okay.
Now I can at least see where he is.
You know?
Oh, all right, nice.
Level two, grab baby!
Bye!
Bye, losers!
Bye, idiot!
Oh.
Oh wait.
Don't say, oh god, it looks like always he's looking
directly at me, right?
Oh, freaks me out.
Okay.
Now, oh, okay.
Careful.
Can I...
Wait, how do I get past that part?
Wait, can I just walk past it?
Wait.
You can crouch, mid-press.
Duck.
Okay.
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
Yeah.
In fact, we'll just do that the whole way, baby.
Wait.
I think.
Oh, look at that.
This is such a nice view.
I think this is where we get peed on.
Oh!
I'm going to go in my pants.
Nobody's looking right.
This is for you guys.
Wow, what a, what a, wow, he's just going everywhere.
Wow.
Okay.
Thanks, Kojima.
Oh my god, there's so many of them.
Oh, the codec, you're right, thank you.
I hope I didn't miss it.
Codec while P. Jack, do you need to save?
Wait.
See ya.
Did I miss it?
again is he still going no i think i missed the codec
the enemy has already entered the nuclear he doesn't care
secure the president before they can confirm and finalize
the code input the president is on the first floor of shell
two's i guess rose doesn't care if i get peed on or not does
he do it again we'll wait oh i'm going to go in my pants
you're really excited about getting peed on
No, I was excited for you guys.
Call him again.
Cardo!
Right, my sympathies.
Sneaking missions are called wet words for a reason after
all.
Don't worry about it, Jack.
It's okay.
That is, as long as you take a shower, the second you get
back.
Do we have a deal?
I look so...
I got so caught up in this, I forgot.
Skirt check!
Skirt!
Today, I have a skirt on.
Skirt check.
Skirt, skirt, skirt, skirt.
Certified Freak Phantom Moment.
I did not put that in the game.
Okay?
I did not decide that that should be a mechanic, you know?
I think I can take it out from here.
Oh, dang it, wrong part.
I always forget it's the bottom part.
Oh, and it's gone.
Okay.
Am I good to just...
I want to take it out before I run over there, you know?
Let's see.
Come back!
At least it wasn't Johnny.
Sorted!
Welcome to Mambo Chef!
Thank you!
Will we get him?
You know what?
Let's just go.
Oh!
I'm off wall!
Wow.
Just kinda... Okay.
I'm gaming.
When you developed this game, how many people tried to stop
you from adding this?
It was definitely a...
A divisive decision.
You know?
Oh my god.
Hey.
What if I take out?
Like, what if I...
What if I...
Like...
Ah!
I'm just gonna run for it.
Why are you giving me so much stuff?
Brr.
Oh no, it's broken.
We gotta go into the core.
Okay, now I can take it out, probably.
What the?
There we go.
Where's the other ones?
Oh, there.
Dang it.
These things are so...
Ah!
Yeah!
These things are so particular.
I think if I...
Nice.
Okay.
And now you.
Nice.
They're so particular.
I think we got all of them.
Nope.
I hear one more.
Oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
Ah!
Oh, God.
Do I think I can hit it from here?
There I can hit it.
Or if I had good aim.
Second R2, man.
Okay.
Okay, sorry.
I just like to be safe.
I don't want anybody to catch me.
Anything like that.
Where am I going?
Kareem is just like mine for real for you really good there
should be a way to cross over from your present location on
the KL connecting bridge to the core of shell 2 get to the
core of shell 2 the core of shell 2 before the enemy can use
him to reconfirm the nuclear launch code okay so it's not
this one what's over here anyway I
can't go in here yeah
Shell too, baby.
Is that guy still up there?
Where does he go?
Okay.
All right.
Are you guys ready to believe?
Oh.
That was just a test.
Do you guys still believe in me, right?
Oh, my God.
Oh my god, why can't you walk in a straight line, buddy,
pal, friend of mine?
Oh, gosh.
If I were a bird, I would not be hanging around this place
any longer.
Okay, okay.
You can do it.
I wonder if I...
Yeah.
Oh!
Oh gosh.
I believe I have trauma from this area.
Gamer.
Well, Olga!
My father had some unfinished business with him.
Olga, calm yourself.
Your personal feelings.
Then screw your plan.
I've been waiting for this day for two years.
And I will send him to the bottom of the ocean, right next
to my old man.
She's not going to see you.
The launch comes first.
Very convincing.
I don't trust him.
Don't talk that way about one of your own.
He's not one of my own.
He left my father to die.
Olga, we'll talk later.
We need to get started on the final checks for the unit.
All right.
i'm headed back there okay the upper connecting bridge to
shell one is down what about the chopper the cam off is out
of action get the oil fence from strut elm okay i'll tell my
men to start pulling out not yet their retrieval comes last
there's nothing funny in this scene right it's just them
right snake snake what about the other man oh oh my god luck
on his side certainly
explosion snick listen olga the court confirmation is in one
hour keep the president alive until then okay easy i know no
one gets in here keep them alive keep them alive of course
keep them at oh the currents what does that mean oh oh oh oh
the door stays shut unless the president manages to take out
that circuit panel from inside the room i could do it and
it's no job for bare hands i would win with my bare hands i
almost said i could do it with my bare hands we leave for
russia when this business is done i want half the money for
that of course that was part of the agreement my bare hands
we start living for ourselves after this if there's anyone
who wants to stay here i want you to take good
are the cream of the crop it's time they went free are they
what happened to rebuilding mother russia cream of the crop
is dead the world is a different place now cream of the crop
just as a reminder i'm going to say this again one last time
don't try anything on us they just built this room with high
voltage floors with the contractor i know right oh man I'm
in front of the room where they're keeping the president
everything all right no sign of flooding but I can't get
close to the door the floor is electrified don't test it
you'll be baking any suggestions remember the shadow Moses
VR training take out the circuit panel right when did I do
this in shadow Moses try ventilation ducks yeah I think I
see one oh boy look for a remote control into the room oh
wait i did do this target the circuit panel got it right the
president the president is wired with nano machines if we
know the frequency is one of my favorite series i love
solidus me too but there's no response it looks like the
walls have a built-in radio shield so that's why i was
thinking with the with the ducks with the ducks to confirm
his position you know i was like i never launched a missile
through ducks a remote control missile launcher first.
Ducks.
Ducks?
Oh, God.
Oh, this is where I was hiding.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
I see this.
I see this hallway and I want to start crying every time.
Mr. President.
Can you hear me?
I have a like a I think this is why I'm a ghost honestly I
have a trauma from from just this room from just oh hello
what is this oh I gotta get the Nikita first thank you
I remember there not being any guys around here yet Can't
get it.
Oh yeah, my rations are...
Oh, this one?
Has a bunch of things in here.
Anyone else?
That's it though, right?
Anybody?
Oh.
Anyone else?
I don't see anyone.
Oh!
I thought it was the actual thing!
I'm so stupid.
What's that?
There's no...
Nothing here.
Chaff.
Yeah, it's just the ammo.
I thought it was the actual thing.
I forgot.
And this...
Why would there be...
Oh, here's the nerd.
Why would there be security cameras in the...
In the break room.
Mr. President!
He's close to the wall.
Oh my god, it's just like an MDS-1 when do you see Otakon!
Who's there?
Come here, come here.
Come here.
Who's there?
Is that a Metal Gear Solid reference?
Who's that?
Knock it off!
I don't remember the music being so loud in this game, where
the voice acting is not so loud, you know what I mean?
I don't remember.
Where do I get?
The Nikita missile.
Where do I get it?
Carnal!
The only way to the president is past this electrified
floor.
Yeah.
Use the remote-controlled missile.
to destroy the power source that will cut off the high
voltage current to the floor locate a remote controlled
missile turning it down might know where to find them he did
sweep shell as long as you guys think the audio is okay
though oh snake do you guys think the audio is okay if you
can hear all right i don't want it to be too low i feel like
this is one of those games where like the audio should be as
loud as me sounds good okay what can i do for you jack i
want to You gotta need drama for me, Rose.
Rose, oh Rose, my beloved.
Stillbindos.
Oh, 10 hours, exactly.
Jack, have you remembered what day it is tomorrow?
No.
I see.
Give it up, all right.
You said you had something you wanted to talk to me about?
What was it?
Give it up, all right.
We'll talk about it tomorrow.
You!
Why does it have to be tomorrow?
Yeah.
So I can build up enough courage first.
you won't run away i would never do something like that liar
every time i want to talk about something you suddenly
remember that you have some work you have to do or you get a
stomach ache oh my god that's not you know it's true what
are you so afraid of again not afraid of anything and i
won't try to run away you are such a liar right then well
then we'll talk tomorrow yeah so tell me you have to come
back okay tell me sorry rose we can't do anything tonight i
got a headache you know he's still here what give it up he's
he's like this wall what's up with this wall oh let me call
snake that's right oh my god it even says snake now binary
thank you for a mic do you know where i can find some remote
controlled missiles remote controlled missiles i saw
something on b1 in the core of shell 2 but be careful out of
the tanks thanks to that explosion oh god we gotta swim we
gotta swim oh we gotta swim oh ping pong
mr president was there was there ding dong ditch time to
avoid drowning yes but also no Yes, but not, not yet.
Yes, but soon.
I hope there's no bugs down here.
I hate those.
I don't see a way to make the music, you know, back in the
day, they didn't really have options like that to increase
the music and also like, you know, or turn down the music,
things like that.
Alright.
I'm new here.
Get ready for peak gameplay.
Oh gosh, I forgot how to swim.
Colonel teach me how to swim.
Colonel!
I forgot how to swim.
When you're on the surface, you can swim in corresponding
directions using the up, down, left, and right movement of
the left analog stick.
Thank you.
Push the punch button to dive down from the surface.
okay okay now look at the cans now where what okay I keep
thinking that the blue parts are um oh god ah what are you
why are you calling me underwater Colonel B-1 is completely
flooded how right are you a mermaid what I'm fine with
swimming stroke the water and move forward by pushing the
punch button okay push it in rapid stroking to swim faster
okay change your heading with the left analog stick looks at
the cans we'll take yeah you down you're talking about left
and right to face those directions the o2 gauge will appear
under your life gauge while you're flooded the gauge
corresponds to the amount of air you can hold from a single
deep breath once the o2 gauge falls to zero the life gauge
will start the kernel I'm gonna drown to be aware of Colonel
Colonel I'm gonna drown Colonel Oh,
oh, gosh, oh, gosh, oh, gosh, oh, gosh, oh, gosh, oh, gosh,
oh, gosh, oh, gosh, oh, I'm going to drown.
Okay, okay.
There was something down there, wasn't there?
I don't, you know what, let's just explore, because I truly
don't remember where to get it.
Oh, this is a dead end, isn't it?
Wow, good job.
Idiot.
Yeah, we'll just...
Oh, wait.
Yeah, there we go.
Yeah, we're just gonna go on an adventure!
You...
A little adventure.
You know what?
Game has really traumatized me with, um...
With, uh...
Oh, there was something in that room, wasn't there?
Ooh, la la la!
looks like a certain traitor.
Kingdom Hearts 2.
That game...
Hold on, I want to go check this room again.
I'm pretty sure there was something in here.
That game has the worst swimming... Oh!
Night vision goggles!
There we go.
You're welcome, everybody.
You don't even have to tell me.
Kingdom Hearts 2 had the swimming mechanics ever so bad oh
wait was it two or one maybe it was one kingdom arts 2 had
the rhythm game yeah yeah yeah kingdom arts 1 was the really
bad one kingdom arts 2 had the rhythm games yeah yeah yeah
who the heck swims like that I don't I think at by this
point we know Ryden is not okay.
Ryden's a bit of a freaky guy, you know?
Oh my god, Ryden!
Ryden...
Rubber Duckie!
I'll be honest, I thought the mines showed up in the second
part, I'll be honest.
That's my bad.
For not remembering.
There it is.
You have the remote controlled missile.
Good job.
Now head for the first floor of the Shell 2 core.
Take out the power source and make contact with the
president before the launch code can be reconfirmed.
Okay.
Don't rush me.
I'm already drowning in here.
I'm drowning in time.
Oh gosh.
Is there a...
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up,
up, up, oh god, oh god, oh god, I'm really not okay.
We're fine.
I'm just bleeding out a little bit.
I have some bandages.
Don't worry about it, everybody.
There we go.
Was there anything in here?
This is where we go to later.
So we have to go find the president first.
Okay.
I'm glad I went down here, though, and now I remember.
What is that right there, floating?
Is there anything over here?
Oh, gosh.
Raiden?
I forgot your thing goes down faster because you have less
health.
Go up.
It's the Raven figurine?
Wait, actually!
Are you a mint enough maid to rescue the president?
Of course I am!
I won't let anything happen to the president.
Don't worry.
Scouts honor.
Oh, I'm running into a wall.
No, that probably didn't spark confidence in you.
Scouts honor, nothing will happen to the president.
Ah.
No mysterious heart attacks?
No.
None of that nonsense.
What is this?
Shadow Moses?
No, this is the big shell.
We don't have stinking heart.
attacks here except for aims but that guy already had a
heart problem i think so you know he doesn't count
riding looks so stupid on the stairs i love him i know right
okay mr president
watch this
idiot knock it off The president!
The president's dub!
Um...
I wish I could get that other ration.
The one that I didn't need earlier.
Gosh, I ate two...
I ate two!
Dang!
Uh, mines in the water and, like, destroyed all my health.
Are these still down?
Yeah.
You're such a prankster.
I know!
I'm just a prankin' guy.
Oh, here we go.
Swimming builds an appetite.
I know, when I was a kid, every time I would go swimming, my
mom would make me peanut butter crackers.
So I think about that.
Oh!
Press square to aim in first person.
My best!
I really got childbearing hips from this angle.
Look at that indent.
The sneaking suit lifts and separates the cheeks to prevent
them from clapping.
I know, look at that.
They are spread open.
Oh, my riding!
Wow!
Godly.
Ride in.
Spread over, look at them!
Are they not?
Alright.
Don't worry about it, President.
Don't worry about it, Mr. President.
Oh my god, they're so fast.
This way.
Watch out, Mr. President!
What is it?
What's up Mr. President?
Stop it!
Mr. President!
Trying to...
Oh my... Wait!
I guess I can't get other stuff in there, can I?
Not yet.
Stop it!
Stop!
Stop sending that missile to me!
Stop it!
Stop... Stop launching missiles at me!
What's wrong?
Let's chop it.
This is not funny.
There we go.
Okay, time for funny cutscene.
Mr. President!
President Johnson.
Happy birthday to you.
So you're finally here.
You've been expecting me?
Happy birthday to you.
Your equipment.
That skull suit isn't exactly standard military issue.
Mr. President.
Are you alright, sir?
is this some kind of sick joke I thought you came to kill me
happy birthday I'm prepared to face the consequences of my
betrayal what you're you're a man I know you can't tell by
the cheeks but Foxhound sir Foxhound Raiden's totally
unfazed I see now things are starting to make a little sense
He was reminded of a previous life Well grabby switch over
to nano communication so nobody can listen in my god mr.
President my hog Yes,
surprise prostate check.
I don't think that's where your prostate is Have managed to
input the code sequence necessary for launching a nuclear
strike I don't think that's where that is I punched the
sequence in my cell You're working for them?
If you asked me two hours ago, my answer would have been
yes.
Right now.
They're keeping me alive until my vital signs are
reconfirmed.
They betrayed you?
I wouldn't quite put it that way.
I wanted power.
They sought destruction.
But why stoop to terrorism?
I wanted absolute power.
Oh my god.
But you're the president.
You have power.
No.
I'm just a figurehead.
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't have any control.
is in the Patriots hands.
Oh, Lord dump time.
Here we go.
The truth behind this country.
I don't know anything.
I'm not surprised you've never heard of them.
Very few are aware of their existence, even among those with
code word clearance.
Huh?
Politics, the military, the economy.
They control it all.
They even choose who becomes president.
Putting it simply, the Patriots rule this country.
It's a Patriot.
Now.
It's hard to believe, isn't it?
That is the truth.
The space defense, income tax reduction, and national
missile defense programs, every policy that's been credited
to me was actually done according to their instructions.
Space defense was initiated by Congress.
That's what the patriots want the country to believe.
It's all a show.
Democracy is just a filler for textbooks.
Think about it.
Do you actually believe that public opinion influences the
government?
This country is shaped and controlled as the Patriots see
fit.
The people are shown what they want to believe.
What you call government is actually a well-staged
production aimed at satisfying the public.
Huh?
Don't you know me like that.
I'm legally sane, you know.
It's not your sanity that worries me.
Huh?
The Patriots.
Even I don't know who the actual members are.
Are they financial, political, or military leaders?
No one knows who the Patriots really are even my
instructions come from a cutout Oh all I've been told is
that every key decision is made by a group of 12 men known
as the wise men's committee wise guy office the White House
merely puppets pawns in a game by pledging my loyalty an
insignificant son of a senator was awarded the presidency
hmm of course that wasn't The only price I had to pay.
That guy's mean.
What do you mean?
Even if a pawn becomes a queen, it is still just a playing
piece.
I wanted to leave my own mark in history, but my ambitions
were...
The guy in the bottom right looks like Van Gogh.
You'll understand someday.
I wish to be a member of the Patriot.
I wanted to wield the power of a king instead of being an
expendable pawn.
of the Patriots.
And that justifies acts of terrorism?
I'd intended to use the new Metal Gear as a bargaining chip.
Bargaining chip?
But I underestimated Solidus.
He actually wants to challenge the Patriots, even if it
means the destruction of the world.
What are you saying?
Whether you believe it or not, the balance of power rests in
the hands of the Patriots.
Cloud strife.
They regulate the country's various interests through
controlled presentation.
Cloud strife.
Staging a drama that is palatable to the Jedi.
masses.
Can you imagine what would happen if they ceased to
function?
The crowd strike was actually the solidest.
Getting rid of the Patriots.
A space that every power monger will try to fill for their
own greedy ends.
And talking about an unregulated power struggle, panic,
civil war, chaos.
Like it or not, the Patriots is an organization that must
continue to exist.
No they don't!
So you changed your mind because you wanted to avoid global
chaos global chaos when I told solidus that I wish to
prevent disaster he replied that pawns can never become
players and who is this solidus do you don't recognize your
president my predecessor George Sears president Sears that
was the name the public came to know him by I knew him by
his code name solidus why does nobody recognize the third
snake preceded by solid and liquid, a survivor of the Les
Alphons Terribles project.
Les Alphons Terribles?
Neither solid nor liquid.
It was a well-balanced masterpiece that the Patriots saw fit
to a trusted presidency.
However, he fell out of grace with the organization four
years ago.
When acting on his own, he started an incident.
Four years ago.
Oh, I didn't go for him.
That's right.
At the time, the DARPA chief, Donald Anderson, together with
certain influential parties, initiated the development of
Metal Gear Rex and an advanced nuclear warhead.
However, this did not fall in line with the Patriots' plans.
What's more, Solidus decided on his own to send his most
trusted man, Osala, to provoke Liquid Snake, bringing about
the said incident.
As a result, he succeeded in obtaining Rex and the data on
the warhead.
But in doing so, he ended up revealing the existence of both
Rex and the Genome Army.
a blunder that earned him the wrath of the patron that
sounds like an awesome game name the wrath of the patriots
no that is not solid nor liquid snake i thought he resigned
that's the story given to the general public following his
resignation the patriots selected me their new porn but that
would mean their new presidential race was that was quite a
show wasn't it it was a stage by the Patriots for the
benefit of the public.
Even the Democrats and Republicans were dancing to the
Patriots' tomb.
It's the diaper chaff.
Everything went according to plan, but for one exception.
Following his resignation, Solidus' health was scheduled to
fail him, bringing about his untimely death.
Capt?
Correct.
But before the Patriots could execute their plot, Solidus
went underground with the help of Ocelot.
As he avoided pursuit, Solidus gained control of Dead Cell!
Winning over Colonel Golukovic's outfit.
From there he bided his time, knowing that his opportunity
would soon arrive.
What opportunity?
The completion of the new Metal Gear Project, an opportunity
that would even his odds against the Patriots.
By stealing the Patriots' most valued project, he would be
able to place them in a very uncomfortable position.
It's the only chance he has for survival.
Once he has the new Metal Gear, he'll declare war.
against the Patriots.
Yeah!
No!
Metal Gear is already operational.
He's jealous of the other two and big boss.
Bravo can you move on.
What you saw was Metal Gear Ray.
Hijacked two years ago from the Marines by Ocelot.
That was not the new Metal Gear.
Show me the Wikipedia article.
Metal Gear.
Right here.
What?
Huh?
You're standing in it.
To be more precise, this entire big shell facility is the
new Metal Gear.
What'd you say?
No.
I'm quite sorry.
you say the upper structure that you've seen is coming right
designed to represent an offshore cleanup facility the main
structure extends from the foundation all the way down to
the ocean floor the connecting elevator is located on the b2
floor of the shell one core arsenal gear that's the code
name arsenal gear arsenal nobody gives love to arsenal gear
that's right he's a big old turtle carrying a load of over a
couple of thousand missiles including nuclear warheads all
protected by a horde of mass-produced metal gear ray units
mass produced the ray unit was originally designed for the
Marines to be used as a countermeasure against the metal
gear variations throughout the world the Patriots had ray
redesigned to protect the new arsenal gear so now anti-metal
gears are guarding a metal gear ironic isn't it that's not
all Arsenal Gear has full access to the military's tactical
network, giving it the ability to exercise absolute control
over our nation's armed forces.
Not to mention our nuclear armament.
But we like kind of destroyed most of it.
Arsenal was created to be the core of our country.
What kind of idiotic weapon?
No.
You're not seeing the full picture.
Arsenal Gear is more than just a military tool.
It is a means to preserve the world as it is.
it will establish a new form of control the Patriots will
use it to keep their place as the country's true rulers
right by what they fear an overabundance of digital
information the world will drown in the coming flood of
information and they along with it we got a lot we got yeah
we got too much information too much digital information
making it possible to shape the truth for their own purposes
in short the arsenal system is the key to their supremacy
the key yes the GW is the Patriots trump card Arsenal gear
will be fully operational when GW is successfully integrated
once operational it will be a completely new form of power
for the Patriots to wield right and is just like what are
you talking about from them so that I would be in a strong
bargaining position hope to trade my way into their ranks
the solidus preferred rebellion i love solidus his plan to
unleash a nuclear his only crime was gunpowder to break the
patriots control of the business community is also a key
factor in his offensive effort outer heaven listen there
isn't much time the football served as the key president is
talking about memes again i've already input the necessary
code sequence it won't be long before gw begins to establish
connections with other external systems and Arsenal gear
becomes fully operational stop them before that happens that
is your role okay roll you've got to find Emma Emmerich well
she's the only one who can stop that thing once it's been
activated what are you talking about she's the system
programmer everything is going over Ryder's head right now
level B1 in the core of this building I thought the levels
below us were flooded I'm sure they won't let her die just
yet as she's the only remaining programmer for this no it's
flooded according to Ocelot she was being held in a locker
room located in the northwest part of level b1 what do you
mean they're just not gonna let her die but it's flooded
they're gonna what stop the ocean they can do like this is
card four it'll give you access all the way to Emma's
location yippee give this tour when you find What is it?
A program for disrupting the control functions between GW
and Arsenal here.
Take Emma to the computer room on level B2 Shell one core.
She'll know how to load the program into the main system a
virus.
That's right modeled after Fox die Fox die design to
selectively eliminate personnel with a specific genetic
code, but why do you have it the Patriots had it engineered
as a failsafe And Ocelot forgot to search.
He's the president.
Why wouldn't he have it?
That disc is the only way you're going to stop arsenal okay
do you feel ibs do you feel a little funny well i've told
you everything you need to know yeah okay bye there's only
one thing that remains to be done what's that
get you out of here president we're gonna save you right now
come with me
There's no time to argue.
Oh my god!
The final shot for my vital ID will start any second.
If you kill me now, you'll at least prevent the nuclear
strike.
Cut it out.
Do it!
That's her role.
That's not my role!
Ah!
It wasn't me.
I didn't pull the trigger!
It wasn't me!
I didn't do it!
That's abusing your right to free speech, Mr. President.
Ex-president The president why did you alas my finger must
have slipped I'll see you around Carrier boy.
Carrier boy.
Oh my god.
Forget him.
He did us a favor Without free will I would do that between
submission.
Carrier boy My only real choice is to put an end to this
charade let me at least have the freedom to end it myself
always question Ocelot's motives okay stop arsenal this is
my last order as your commander-in-chief I'm counting on you
Oh, no.
Mr. President.
Mr. President, I'll take you somewhere nice.
Come here.
Come here, Mr. President.
Rest.
Rest there, Mr. President.
Rest well, Mr. President.
Oh, my God.
Oh, oh, seven for Mr. President.
Nice, more bullets.
Um, um.
Colonel, we have a problem.
No response!
What else could you be doing?
Snake?
No response!
What else could you guys be doing?
Oh, wait.
Okay, I have one last person.
He'll always pick up.
No!
The room is jammed.
Then why do I still have my map?
Wait, hold on.
We got goodies to get.
We got goodies to get, everybody.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun.
What else is in here?
Oh, am I stuck?
Oh.
There.
I can't go any further?
No way.
That's it?
That's it for me?
Oh, why?
How?
How am I stuck, though?
I can't believe...
doesn't seem like the type of game that would do an
invisible wall you know metal gear never seems like the type
of game that does an invisible wall what is this guy the
president is dead I see I'm sorry to hear that where do we
go from here your mission was to rescue the president and
eliminate the terrorist threat however given the recent turn
of events we will honor the president's directive you must
put a stop to Arsenal gear once and for all yes do you
actually think there's any truth to his story about this big
shell facility being a front for Arsenal gear I don't have
the security clearance necessary to verify the facts however
he was the president I'm sure he was talking about aren't
you forgetting that he was part of the terrorist plot all
the more reason why I believe his information is reliable
huh we're talking about a man who chose to die rather Thanks
to his sacrifice.
The Nuclear Launch Authority has shifted to the Vice
President, effectively eliminating the terrorist threat.
Oh.
Colonel, when you put it like that, it almost sounds like I
should have assassinated the President to eliminate the
threat.
That was not my intention.
I was trying to point out that there is certainly some
credibility to the words of a man who chose death to protect
the innocent.
The Colonel has a point, Jack.
What about the information he gave me on the Patriots?
Yeah.
That's a new one on me.
out riding we're running out of time find Emma she's
supposed to be located on level B1 in the core of that
building you're in yep right you've got to find her before
Arsenal becomes fully operational okay hurry Jack it's up to
you to make sure that the president didn't sacrifice his
life in vain okay understood riding out when do you ever say
what's your status riding snake the president What?
There was nothing I could do.
What about the nuclear strike code sequence?
He died before his vital ID could be reconfirmed.
When does he ever say that?
But that Ocelot guy obviously killed the president on
purpose.
Why?
It doesn't make any sense.
They had to know that they couldn't launch the nuke if they
killed the president.
Maybe there's a way to launch without reconfirming the vital
ID.
Or maybe they found a more effective weapon within Arsenal
Gear.
You knew about Arsenal Gear?
Yeah.
Why didn't you tell me about it?
You never asked.
Am I correct in assuming you also know that the big shell is
a front for the project?
You mean did I know that the big shell, a fully functional
environmental cleanup facility, was designed to camouflage
Arsenal gear?
Yeah, I did.
It's exactly what the president and Ames described, a
massive cover story.
Oh my gosh, so good.
The good news is that it hasn't really done much in terms of
cleaning up the environment, so we won't have to worry about
any toxic gas being released if we have to blow the house
down.
Okay.
When did you find out about all of this?
It took a while, but we uncovered the info around the time
you took out that mad bomber.
What a troll.
I know.
There's no doubt that Arsenal Gear is being built here.
And it was all set up two years ago.
On that day, all of it.
Two years ago, what really happened here?
Two years ago, Hudson River.
I took these photos two years ago.
Oh my god!
I know these pictures.
They were on the news on several websites.
If I remember right, the news, the website.
the tanker that's right oticon me we were used we'd hope
that by going public terrorist action water though that was
the plan at the time can i go i want to see opinions i've
gone through vr training of the tanker mission before yeah
well i doubt it accurately simulates the events that mission
serious environmental disaster i'd infiltrated the dummy
tanker to obtain proof that a metal gear was under
development I did that.
Shortly after I made it aboard, an armed group led by
Colonel Gelukovic raided the ship and gained control.
Oh my god.
Olga and Ocelot were among the raiding party.
The world.
Yeah, and him.
Who are you talking about?
A man that was supposed to be dead.
Their target was also Metal Gear Ray.
But Ocelot eliminated Colonel Gelukovic and Marine Commander
Scott Dolph, and he hijacked Ray.
Oh, Reparone.
Yeah.
I don't know what kind of deal was going down.
That's what Ocelot said at the time.
Something like, I'm taking it back.
Ooh.
Ocelot then sank the tanker, along with the soldiers of the
Marine Corps.
This is a great summary.
Best character, Dikido.
Dikido.
Odecon managed to have a small boat ready for me.
Yay, small boat!
That was the easy part.
The tough part was not getting dragged down with a sinking
tanker.
Small miracle when you think about it.
It turned out that the whole thing was a setup to lure us.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Oh.
Photos of Snake, taken by the cipher, were released to the
public.
Oh.
In turn, we became the world's most wanted environmental
terrorists.
Yeah!
It was definitely a move aimed at putting a stop to our
anti-metal gear activities.
But why did they choose Snake?
Because he's sexy.
Since the Shadow Moses incident, Snake became sort of a
hero.
Oh my god.
Everybody saw him naked?
When did that happen?
Yes, to a certain degree.
Oh, that's... I did all of that.
Actually, this is real footage.
Look how cool I look.
They didn't choose Snake to be a hero.
So they decided to do a spear campaign.
This is all real footage that I did.
I wanted to make an example of him.
So everybody would think twice before a...
God's family has a history of small food.
They set all this up just to nail you guys.
No, there's more to it than that.
The Marines' Metal Gear Ray project headed by Commander
Dolph was carried out in opposition.
to the Navy's Arsenal Gear project.
I know.
To be more precise, the Patriots considered Metal Gear Ray
to be a thorn in their side.
Hence they attacked the dummy tanker and stole Ray.
I remember when he was doing this.
They followed this up with a perfect plan.
They immediately sent a fully loaded tanker to the same
location and sank it.
Then set up the facility to camouflage the development of
Arsenal Gear.
it two more puppets in their show a lot of this stuff is
from cut content yeah i remember he had like a titanic-esque
like both fell victim to osilat where you had to run out
with all the water behind all this excuse osilat to get hold
of ray huh no he was underground keeping a low profile at
the time then it must be the patriots if that's the case
what's osilat doing alongside solidus
Quadruple crosser.
Doing what he knows best.
We can figure this out later.
The nuclear strike's been prevented.
But Arsenal still has a massive payload of missiles to deal
with.
If the opposition gets control of those missiles.
Ryden, you've got to find Emma.
Wait a second.
Isn't Emma Emric?
My sister.
What's she doing here?
You got me.
She's a computer whiz who specializes in neural AI and
ultra-variable volume data analysis using complex...
logic how she got involved in weapons development is beyond
me hmm whatever her reasons we need her in order to stop
Arsenal Raiden find her I'm on my way okay time for what I
know you want to go on the Niro sama Niro sama I
love being able to freely wander this area I'm treasuring it
I'm not taking it for granted it at all.
Pew!
Pewing!
Guys, I will need to go to the little ghosties room probably
before we go into the next fight.
Um...
Wait, did I get everything?
Yeah, okay.
Coming!
So we'll need to go to the little...
I
had...
But we remember where to go.
We go to that one room and we go...
Xew!
With the handle.
good no bugs here I hope the lower level doesn't have any
bugs that would be awful you guys oh my gosh you guys can
listen to this ambiance oh my gosh it's kind of relaxing
here this is so nice you can just listen to the water
flowing this actually sounds so
this is really nice actually It's like the sound of the
electronic, like the whir of the machines and I need to pee
now.
Okay, potty break for everybody.
Potty break for everybody.
Can we listen to Bryden talking to himself?
Wait, what do you mean?
How could he talk to himself?
I am going to save real quick, though.
See if Rose got anything to say.
What can I do for you, Jack?
You can give us some the sweet, sweet tea, my dear Rose.
Jack, what is it?
I've always been alone.
I'm so lonely.
Lonely?
Rose, we've always...
Rose!
Not always.
What do you mean?
You've never slept beside me.
What are you talking about?
I...
After we've been together in my room, you stay awake all
night, or you head for the door.
Is this really the time to bring this up?
jack why listen rose i'm right in the middle of a mission
and i why why can't you relax when you're with me look the
mission i why don't you open up to me rose i i just can't
all i ever wanted was to share your dreams to spend a
meaningful evening with you girl i'm about to go drown you
by my side when i woke up is that asking too much i just
wanted to save the game i'm scared of the night scared of
the night scared of the night what's that supposed to mean i
can't relax when i'm with some baby jack you wouldn't even
let me in your room i need privacy i just can't be bothered
don't go into my room wrong word what i wanted to say was
bother there are certain things that i have to keep to
myself oh my god do you remember that time i forced my way
into your room oh no we'd known each other no no and you
blew up yeah he didn't it was the first time you ever raised
your hand against me I was so worried about you look I'm
sorry it wasn't your violent nature that scared me it was
your room it was your room stop it there wasn't anything in
your room only a bed and a small desk it looked like a
prison cell Rose no television set no family pictures not
even a poster.
Rose, I only use that room for sleeping.
A lifeless room.
Almost like your empty heart.
I don't know.
That's why I tried to keep you out.
I thought I was beginning to understand you.
Until I saw that room.
I didn't expect to get this.
Would you have been happier if I had a picture of you
hanging on the wall?
Oh my god!
That's not what I was trying to say.
Enough, Rose.
We'll talk about this later.
Oh!
After the mission.
Right.
Oh my god.
I understand.
I didn't expect to get this Kodak just now.
Why are they together?
It was...
It wasn't you that scared me.
It was your room.
There was nothing in there, bro.
Why are you living in a prison cell?
I literally said no furniture.
The military dude spying on them must be friends.
Oh my gosh.
Let's see what Snake has to say real quick.
Oh god.
Emma's probably being kept in filter chamber number two on
4B1 of Shell 2's core.
Go around from the south and you should be able to reach
her.
Start out by swimming south.
Oh goodness.
I'm so glad we're not.
Oh gosh, I'm so glad we got that Kodak.
Okay.
You just hang out with Raiden real quick.
I'm going to go fishing.
You guys, hang out.
I'll be really fast.
I just got a peep.
I'm going to be like that Garlukovic soldier.
I'm going to do it off my balcony in honor of him.
I hope nobody's standing below.
You don't understand, Rose.
There are certain things I have to keep to myself.
Slyly brushes his BL manga into the midway.
Jack and Rose have a relationship as loving as it is
unhealthy.
So good.
Okay, VRB.
VRB.
Gonna go do it off my balcony.
I'm back, but I want more tea, so I'm gonna go get more.
So I'm gonna be just a little second more.
Shout out to everyone playing Blue Archive who decorates
their cafe like riding.
Oh my god.
Shout outs to you, Oimo.
Bear me, again.
But I'll be fast.
I hope there were no weird messages.
While I was gone.
I hope there was nothing strange.
Give him a shower.
I did get a snack, though.
I got watermelon.
The perfect summer snack.
Not me.
Nothing in my bed.
What would be in your bed?
Oh, definitely not riding.
I love watermelon.
That was fun meeting you this weekend, Mint.
Can't wait for the Atarashi Gakko Show.
Oh my gosh, yes!
Have so much fun.
Do you salt watermelon?
sometimes, but I'm not really a salty fan.
Oh, God.
We ready to go?
Let's go.
Oh, my God, my eyes.
Okay.
Ikimasu.
I think I can make it this way.
Since we have high health, we've got high health.
Oh, hello?
Ryden, are you reading me?
This is Otakon.
What's your situation?
Otakon!
Wet and miserable.
This place is flooded.
The seawater that's been pumped up is pouring into the
building.
I see.
Listen.
something I have to tell you about EE don't worry about her
I'll get her out she's afraid of water what what yeah when
she was six years old she almost drowned with my father in
our swimming pool she can't swim well yes and no we used to
swim a lot together when we were kids in fact she swam like
a fish until that day when she almost drowned when the
accident happened I was in my room I learned later that EE
was calling me for help she didn't doubt for a be there you
could see the pool from my room but I didn't realize at the
time that she needed my help what were you doing oof I was I
was I was gonna survive the ordeal yeah but my father didn't
so you blamed yourself and left your yeah sorry he seems to
believe that was the case the fact is I betrayed her and you
think she can't swim because of the traumatic experience I
haven't seen since that day but yes i think so i got a
letter from julie her mother after they moved back to
england in her letter she mentioned that ee couldn't swim
anymore that she refused to even wear a bathing suit damn if
she still can't swim we're in trouble level b1 in the core
is pretty much flooded i didn't do it maybe you can help her
overcome the trauma you want me to help her get over it it's
still gonna take some time to repair the camov sorry kid
emma's rescue is up to you thanks an underwater mission well
this is a first look I'll see what I can do I suggest that
you drum the map of the building into your head because you
won't have time to look at it when you try to bring Emma out
yeah I'm counting on you riding I covered most of the core
when I had to take out the C4s if there's anything you need
to ask me call me on the codec I'll do that can I ask you
snake why are we here
Hi!
B1C.
Okay, back.
There we go.
Just to suffer?
Just to suffer.
Okay.
Alright, Ryden.
Okay, good.
They didn't have time to reset up the mines.
I think we're...
Oh wait, oh, oh.
Hold on.
This way.
I think we're good.
Oh!
Oh my god!
But they had time to set up rations!
Let's go!
What is that?
Wow.
I'm glad the posters are surviving.
What's that?
Oh, thankful.
Ah!
Okay.
It's this one.
But what's this one go to, anyway?
Can we even open it?
Oh.
Oh, it won't even let us, okay.
Here?
Wait.
What button am I supposed to press here?
Oh, there we go.
I was trying the action button, but it was being weird.
Oh.
No surprises.
Ah!
No surprises, please.
Still there!
Oh, he's a still man now.
Oh, my goodness gracious.
Um, hold on.
Uh, is he still there?
Oh!
Uh, oh.
Uh.
You're my boy.
Snake, I found him.
Probably being kept in filter chamber number two on floor B1
of Shell 2's core.
Wait!
I found him.
I think he's a crab.
Emma's probably being kept in filter chamber number two on
floor B1 of Shell 2's core.
Swim as far west as you can.
Then head north and you should reach filter chamber number
two.
Oh, what?
I know, wait!
I found him!
Emma's probably being...
Maybe Colonel?
Colonel, I found him!
When you're on the surface, you can swim in corresponding
direct...
I give up.
This poor guy...
They're like, we don't have time.
to worry about a dead man he's already dead oh gosh uh up
okay how do i get through here again over and under around
uh this way right under under yeah and over and uh oh shoot
uh around that's a wall Oh god, I'm gonna end up like
Stillman.
Under, under, under, under.
Oh, what's that?
Grab it.
Ryden?
Ryden, turn around.
Okay, just go up.
Okay.
Maybe you have to stare at him and then call.
Oh, maybe.
Laugh and grow fast.
Come on, grab it!
Yay!
There you go, buddy.
Am I going the right way?
Gosh.
Up.
Nope.
No.
Go down.
And here.
And then go up.
Here.
Oh, not high enough.
There we go.
Nice, nice, nice.
Stinger bullets.
You know what I mean.
What's here?
Okay.
Cool.
Let's get our breath.
Wow, that's a huge ration.
And let's avoid some mines, I believe.
Or, oh wait, maybe in the next section?
Okay, I sure hope I'm not ambushed here.
Soggy ration.
That's how I like them.
I don't want to see any bisexuals.
I'll cry.
No!
Still ticking, huh?
Unfortunately, hell had no vacancies.
No!
Also, I love Ryden's response to seeing a man who he
literally shot point blank in the head.
Still alive.
Human muscles are quite elegant.
They speak out clearly what a person's next move will be.
They even tell me which way a gun is going to be pointed
before the trigger is pulled.
But your muscles, they're different.
Oh my gosh, it's really surreal.
I met like so many of these voice actors.
Now that I think about it.
I met Phil Lamar.
Like a week ago.
That's crazy!
You knew I was coming?
a nuisance.
I can't let you interfere with Arsenal gear.
So cool.
I know, right?
Okay.
She is of no use to us now.
What the?
But she served us well as the live bait for the big catch.
Crazy Ivan sometimes speaks the truth.
Are you calling me a catch?
Emma's alive?
She was some time ago.
become quite serious i wouldn't be surprised if she's a
mermaid now did you really think killing the president would
prevent a nuclear strike think again i didn't do it our
voices every one and everything you probably voices the
purified hydrogen bomb purified hydrogen bomb purified
hydrogen bomb why is it when snake repeats everything it
sounds good but when ryden does it just makes him sound like
an idiot heavy hydrogen nuclear fusion using lasers and
magnetic generate heat insulated compression it was a top
secret project initiated by the current president and
solidus has no idea of its existence the clean thermonuclear
bomb is at an experimental stage and is handled differently
specifically it becomes launch capable when arsenal is
activated I don't want to say spy sexual stop looking in the
mirror six months ago we lost everything we believed fall in
their cover-up we were labeled as killers responsible for
the mass murder of civilians as well as our own allies I
can't tell what's going on in this picture believed every
word turning a deaf ear to whatever we had that fat man and
then vamp our only goal is to wipe them from the face of the
earth and destroy this world of deceit they have created
along with them you're insane insane we might be the only
ones telling the Vamp is cradling someone's head.
Oh.
It's Raiden's inherent talent.
Kind of like how when you say things, they sound cute.
Final check for activating Arsenal has been completed.
All Arsenal personnel report to your station.
Who is this guy?
Well, it sounds like Arsenal's ready to go into operation.
Damn it.
You're still hoping that the girl can install that virus
you're carrying around.
How do you know that?
You know?
It's a shame you're not going to be around long enough to
hand her the program.
That isn't seawater, you know.
It's a byproduct of the microbes contained in the pool.
Buoyancy is practically non-existent thanks to the high
oxygen content.
I've heard about that kind of water, literally recently.
Take a good look at your grave.
Like I saw kind of a video about it.
Ta-da!
Oh my god!
We have to fight Vap!
Okay, let's kick his butt.
Oh, gosh.
I don't remember how to do this fight.
The car.
Can I take him out here?
Or does he...
Oh, gosh.
Ah!
There you go.
Okay.
All right, I'm just going to take care of these real quick.
Shia!
Okay, nice, nice, nice.
Oh, okay.
There he is.
Can't you, like, shoot him in here?
Oh, God.
Where is he?
Oh, oh, uh...
Can't do it while...
I can't do it.
Not while he's being a ballerina.
Woo!
Yes, ma'am!
Yes!
Oh, oh, oh!
Yep, oh!
Oh, can I...
Jerk.
I
don't remember how to do this fight.
Sorry, guys.
If you're just like, this?
Oh yeah, Stinger in the water does work too, that's right.
That's like how you cheese it, isn't it?
Doesn't it work?
Stinger in the water, where is he?
Hey buddy, where are you at?
Is it a cheese?
I think it's technically like, well I mean, I say
technically as if like there's a right way and a wrong way.
Stop being so fancy with me.
Stop.
Sorry, I'm not using the trank.
I just really...
You know what?
I don't want to use it on him.
Oh.
Whoa, he's over there.
I know if I fade him.
And then...
Oh!
No!
I missed my chest.
He's like...
He's like good to...
Good for like two seconds.
Oh my gosh.
Oh.
Oh, he scared me.
Okay, so after he throws...
Oh, he's...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, right now, right now.
Ah, shoot.
Okay, I'm remembering a little bit.
I'm going to just be slow, you know.
Oh, not Nikita.
Just kidding.
I'm just kidding.
There we go.
Where are you at?
It's like so...
Such a little amount of...
Whatever works.
You know?
Oh my gosh.
Are you stupid?
You didn't even hit me once!
You aimed at the entirely wrong direction!
I should have gotten a better shot, though.
It's my bad.
Oh, it takes out, like, his stamina.
Maybe it's not Good to do it then.
We'll just wait until he comes back up.
Just wants to show off.
Yeah.
I kind of want to swim in there, though.
Oops.
That was too slow.
Maybe?
I think actually I can...
Yeah, yeah.
That's right.
I can punch him.
Just a little bit.
Every little bit helps.
I cross-chugger.
Everybody's actual skills.
What do you mean by that?
Gosh, I'm so slow with aiming.
Oh, maybe I should just go for his stamina.
You know what?
One or the other.
Maybe I should just go for his stamina then, you know?
Never realized the melee works on him.
Oh, shoot.
I forgot that.
Ow!
This first hit on me.
Hey, come here.
Oh my god, he's getting really aggressive with me!
Yo, get up right then.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, oh, phase, phase two?
Phase two, I think?
Ah!
Oh, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Oh my god.
Suddenly I started sucking.
I don't think...
I got him though.
What the?
Oh my gosh.
You sucker.
Like it.
Why aren't you able to get me so well?
Oh my god.
What?
Be do.
Don't choke.
I'm trying.
He stopped being able to attack
my...
How do I shoot him now?
Wait.
Oh, I'm about...
Oh, oh.
Uh, you can use a big guns.
Singer him?
Okay.
Yeah, let's just go back to that strat, right?
Oh, that was so close.
Holy cow.
That was close.
Yeah, try and get me as I run away.
I'm a coward.
I
like how he falls back into the water.
Tactical retreat.
So true.
That's right.
Yeah.
Actually, I don't care if you're okay.
I can't wait for your very timely death.
Back into the sea with Yeet!
He avoided it.
Oh my gosh.
He's so fast.
Go back into the sea!
Stop!
Stop it!
You're so fast!
You're being too fast!
Oh my gosh.
You're being too ridiculous right now, Vam.
You're being ridiculous right now, Vam.
And you're not gonna go back into the sea?
Yeah.
Phase 3.
Shoot!
I know he's...
You can get him after he has launched the 3.
It's just hard to tell when he's gonna do it.
Sometimes he jumps around.
Sometimes...
Okay.
Let's see.
He's got the zoomies.
Which would have been better.
more bullets for the M4.
How?
Guys, I have a question.
How do I auto-aim?
How do I turn it on?
How do I turn on?
Auto-aim.
Hey, look!
Uh, no!
Oh, shoot.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
I'm too slow though.
Okay.
Oh my
gosh!
I'm so bad.
Yeah.
Throw your thingies!
Oh my god, it's a freaking wall!
Oh my god.
Throw him!
Oh my god!
Take any damage, please.
Where is he?
This is getting stupid, vamp.
This is getting stupid.
This is, look at, look at everything is littered with your,
with your little things.
Oh my god.
Ah!
It was pretty funny, I'm not gonna lie!
It's okay.
Come on.
Ah!
You were fighting!
How?
How do I?
Yeah.
He spins.
He does his little...
Oh my god.
Bleeding out again.
Maybe I need to hit him and then shoot.
Can't remember this.
Breaking pie at all.
Ouch.
Yes.
Okay, let's see what else I got.
This is stupid.
Will he be able to dodge this?
Please, ma'am.
Please.
Ah, bubble!
Why?
Why have you tried shooting?
I did.
Is it...
Can I shoot in first person in this?
I have no idea.
I'm not auto-aiming!
I'm not auto-aiming.
If you are just like, you can't auto-aim, I'm not doing it.
Oh my god.
Just come down here!
You, you, peace!
Please!
Ah!
Finally.
I never want to see your stupid face again, Vap.
Drown in that water.
Drown, drown, drown in it.
God.
So dramatic.
Colonel, they've apparently completed the final check
procedure for Arsenal Gear.
Sorry.
Sorry that last part was so annoying.
You got to get her to install the virus program that the
president gave you.
When you find her.
Take her to the computer room on level B2 in the...
core of shell one snake did you catch all that I didn't make
it on time Arsenal's going active you killed him but now
he's dead you're gonna have to wait I'm going after Emma
literally like two-thirds of that fight was me running
around a circle can't your partner do it I would if I could
but the security for this system is no joke next is the easy
part of the game understood I'll make sure you have your
family reunion uh what's up a lot of years have passed
between ee and me then you should see her right i don't have
the right to see her we can talk about this later riden i
think you'd better get moving emma's in the locker room to
the north right i'm on it
okay um i'm out of con yay we lost a couple of rations
though But, you know, we'll get them.
Ah, we'll get them back.
Thanks, Gain.
Okay, watch out.
Watch out!
Go down?
Go up?
Somewhere?
Oh my gosh, I'm in the...
Riden, Riden, I didn't...
It just...
It just threw me into that room.
Riden, why are you so thick, man?
Wait, this is the same room!
Riden, go this way!
Oh my god.
He is so thick.
Thick.
Down.
Ah!
Body armor!
Yeah!
Oh, we're gonna need that later, for sure.
We're gonna need that.
Oh my god.
Ah, turn around, Ryden!
It's not worth it!
Oh gosh, go up, go up.
Um...
Is there anything in that room?
I can't remember.
Down, down, down.
Oh, wait.
I wasn't, you guys, I swear, I swear to you.
I was not, I was, I didn't even press circle.
I swear to you.
Brighton's bleeding out.
I got a bandage.
Where is my bandage?
I'm lost.
I think I do have to go into that really cursed room.
Did I go all the way back to the beginning?
Where am I?
Stick drip, the ping!
Yeah, exactly, exactly.
Oh no, wait, it's this one.
We're here, right?
Wait, this is...
No, yeah, it's this one.
Go, Ryan.
Okay.
Wish I had a node right now, node right now, node right now.
Oh, possess a mean.
Book!
C4.
Get bullied, nerd.
I wonder how much she's like her brother.
We all know they have one thing in common.
Here's the one thing in common.
Are you alright?
There it is.
Raiden, I'm getting you out of here.
Get me out.
You're lying.
Where are you taking me this time?
The best escort mission of all time.
I'm here to help.
This is my redemption arc.
Here, I'll prove it.
This is my redemption.
Do you have nanos?
This is my redemption arc.
This is...
Do you?
This is my redemption arc.
Everybody on this project has them.
Okay, good.
Let's try.
Beep, beep.
Can you hear me now?
Nanocommunication?
That's right.
I have nanomachines too.
Her little hairs are so cute.
And you're not one of them.
That's what I've been trying to tell you.
One sticking up.
Oh, cute.
Actually, I need your help to stop Arsenal.
I understand you're the only one who might be able to do it.
And who told you that?
The president.
Really?
I need you to come with me to Shell One.
Your brother's waiting for you there.
My brother?
Bull.
Uh-oh, come on.
We have to get moving.
This place will be flooded soon Come on E-A Oh my god, take
his hand take the pretty boy's hand Oh my god, she's just
like this is just like my Japanese anime's This is just like
my otomi games.
Oh my gosh Be shonen
What Why'd you...
We better move.
Yeah!
I can't swim.
At least she'll get to wash her pants.
You can swim.
You used to love it.
How do you know?
Your brother told me.
He's really here?
That's right.
He's here to rescue you.
I don't believe you.
He would never come for me.
And I'm telling you he's here, waiting for us at Shell One.
No!
He left me.
My mother...
When we needed him the most...
when my father died all he could think about was himself
Emma we can go over all that later but first we have to get
out of here no I hate water it's hopeless I can't swim I
hate water it's wet it's coarse it gets in my pants swim you
can do it I can't oh my god come on deep down inside you
know you can swim I can't keep my eyes open in the water
endless blue the water he wants me it won't let me go all
right then close your eyes i'll guide you i i was injected
with something my legs i have trouble moving them listen
emma just hold your breath she has so many excuses i could
never tell if that was actually true i mean the way she
walks like it does seem like she had something injected but
like she just seems so you know she just seems like she has
all sorts of excuses that's right yeah how long just a
little while are you sure of course i'm sure that's how i
got here i don't think i can do it i'm not good at holding
my breath look amma i have an idea i'm not good at holding
my breath put your ear against my chest and listen to my
heartbeat your heartbeat count the beats don't think about
anything else when you reach 100 open your eyes by that time
we'll be on the other side Give me a signal if you think
you're running out of breath.
What will you do then?
Hold on.
I'll say it after this.
I'll swim faster I'll swim faster Oh my god.
Oh my god.
Fry then you have a girlfriend.
Hang on tight
She's so small.
She's so cute.
I'm closing my eyes Take some deep breaths deep breaths a
one and a two and a three wait what is it let me take off my
glasses you know you should wear contacts there's nothing
wrong with my eyes you should wear contacts I wear ugly with
your glasses trying to be different from the other girls no
it's not like that I like glasses and there's this guy I
liked who used to wear them your first boyfriend your first
boyfriend no somebody more important anyway they bring me
luck yeah I see that's why why'd you take them off then okay
let's go Emma no Emma no a three okay this
one she has small breath she has small breath capacity okay
What I was gonna say is, um, there used, there was like a,
there was like a, I don't know, not a rumor, but it like
went around, right?
How they were just like, if you use the Pazesamine, if you
use this, then it'll slow your heartbeat and she'll be able
to hold her breath longer.
but it's not true but then also it's kind of misleading
because they give you this right before you see her so it
kind of it feels like it would be true you know so a room a
rumor wait yeah I guess so right
that does sound true for this game I know right it sounds
like it really would work right especially because he then
also says listen to the sound of my heartbeat and then this
is supposed to like well I don't know if it actually stops
if it makes your heartbeat slow down or whatever but old
gaming magazine said the same thing yeah it was always not
real misleading what can I do for you Jack I got I got a I
got a cute babe on my back how do you feel about that Rose
about trying to break into your room Oh.
Rose, just forget about it.
No, listen to me.
I said I did it because I was worried about you, but it
wasn't just that.
What?
I was suspicious.
I thought there might be someone else.
Someone else?
Another woman.
Oh, Rose.
In my room?
I really thought so, because sometimes you're so horribly
cold.
We watched...
We watched King Kong together.
I'm serious.
Sometimes I feel like you're pushing me away.
So I...
Did you get in?
Yeah.
Are you satisfied now?
There wasn't anyone there, was there?
No.
No, there was no one there.
You really selfish.
There was absolutely no one in your room.
Not another woman.
Not me.
Not even you.
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to apologize.
I wanted to apologize and then insult you.
I wanted to apologize and then, you know.
Hey, Jack.
Why do we keep going back between 2000 and 2099?
What's happening?
I think my PS2 is broken.
Let's see.
See?
Take care, Jack.
Wait, she doesn't care about the girl in the back.
Maybe in the next rooms.
Okay, hold on.
We just came from that way.
Did we go this way?
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah, yeah.
What's in that other way, though?
What is in the other...
Did I get everything in the other place?
You know what?
Maybe it's fine.
Okay.
Good job.
Emma!
Put Emma down first.
Okay, let's go back.
I'm gonna make sure I got everything.
Sorry guys.
Loot goblin time.
Gotta gobble.
Nope, turn around, turn around.
Turn, turn, turn, turn, turn.
Oh, my O2 though is gonna be kind of not so great because...
Oh, also, let's put on the ration first.
Oh gosh.
Oh, I did get everything here.
This is where I accidentally blew up.
But this room had, like, two bombs in it.
I don't know if it has anything else worth it.
Okay, you know what?
Never mind.
Let's just leave.
Okay, okay, I got it.
Sorry.
I like to double, triple, triple, triple check everything.
Okay, guys.
That's fine.
It takes me no time to get there and back.
See, I'm fast.
I'm speedy.
Speed, speed, speed, speed, speed.
Okay, now we can take her hand.
Look at her.
She's sitting there.
She's waiting for me.
You okay?
You traumatized?
Let me rest.
Just for a second.
Me too.
Oh, I'm regaining life.
I didn't realize that I was bleeding out.
What did she think of this?
Ha ha!
I am so tired.
Okay.
Alright, complainy pants.
What do you think of?
This!
Oh gosh.
You actually lose so much health.
I'm so tired.
I'm tired.
Jack in the box.
Okay.
Alright, let's go.
Come on.
Get up.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Come on!
I don't remember how I, uh...
How I take her hand.
Come here.
Oh!
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Sorry, come on.
Hold on.
Let me grab your hand.
Grab her hand.
Oh, sorry.
Grab your hand.
Um...
Oh, triangle.
Thanks.
I was trying to grab her hand.
hand I'm awkward okay gosh I have no furniture in my room
don't blame me just
gonna chill here you did good you did go it's coming I
concentrated on your heartbeat it's coming it reminded me of
when I was a kid my brother had a heartbeat So did my dad.
I remember my brother giving me a piggyback ride.
I was sleeping with my ear against his back.
I could hear his heartbeat.
Sounds like you were close.
We were.
Back then.
We were stepchildren in our parents' second marriages.
She looks so much like Paz.
Wherever my brother went, I used to tag along.
So cute.
My brother didn't have any close friends.
It's Huey.
It doesn't matter.
We both wanted to be loved so much.
So much that we used to pretend.
Pretend?
Yeah, we used to play house.
My brother was the husband and I was the wife.
But it was always just make-believe.
We were only kids.
Just make-believe.
You know what I mean.
I never had a family.
Oh.
But I think I know what you mean.
Okay, a way to bring it, make it weird, right?
And here it is!
Here it is!
Briden, what's your status?
Colonel, I've got Emma Emmerich here.
We managed to avoid drowning.
Good job!
Get her over to Shell 1 as soon as you can.
That's going to be hard with the connecting bridge on the
upper level destroyed.
Didn't Oda say something about taking the oil fence at the
bottom of Strut L?
Yeah, I remember that.
You should be able to go down by way of Strut L.
He said the thing!
We've managed to avoid drowning!
She's been injected with something and she can't walk
without any help.
The worst part about being socially awkward is when you try
to hold a girl's hand, you end up breaking her neck.
Oh, you could have told me that sooner.
Take your finger off the action button.
Emma can sit and wait until you help her back up.
Colonel!
You won't be able to use any weapons while you're leading
her.
Now head for Strut L.
Yeah.
We're on our way!
We've infiltrated the computer room.
What's your situation?
Emma's safe.
We're heading your way.
Good job.
Shell One's deserted.
Looks like everybody's aboard Arsenal.
I had a look at the system, but there's nothing I can do.
Eee's our only hope.
Right.
I'll put her on then.
Eee?
What?
How?
I'll use my Kodak as a relay.
Ahem.
Here she is.
How?
Eee.
Is that you?
How?
Eee.
Stop calling me.
calling her that why are you involved with metal gear huh
you knew our family's dark history and still got involved
what's wrong with you i should have known answer me why are
you repeating the she has no thoughts i can't i wanted to
hurt you i can't r1 and r2 her you abandoned me no that's
not what happened all right that's enough who are you i'm a
friend of otakon's amma otakon enough with rivalry that's
not what this is we haven't got time for this right now I I
got you snake I'll head over there with Emma most of the
enemies aboard Arsenal but I suggest you be careful make
sure Emma gets here in one piece ridden take care of my
sister don't worry I'll get her there yep most the enemies
should be all all of them should be on an Arsenal Alright!
Oh!
Wait, what was that?
Oh, just kidding.
My cell phone's going off!
Hello!
Be careful!
Claymore mines are set there!
Huh?
There are!
Wait, actually!
Also, how'd you know where I was?
You freak?
Where's my mind detector?
Sorry, I don't remember where a lot of stuff is.
Oh, mind detector, there it is.
Wow!
They just set these here!
Like crazy!
Why are they there?
That's so funny.
Come on, E-E.
Let's go.
Okay, oh my heart.
Oh my heart, oh my heart, oh my heart to troll you.
Well, who would go the long way?
I guess me.
Oh gosh, oh gosh.
I've never walked that direction.
I don't think I remember that either.
Snake and Hal are waiting for us in Shell One's computer
room.
I've got this disc that the president gave me.
This disc is supposed to contain a virus that can corrupt
Arsenal Gear's operating system.
We need you to this is this is my program What what why did
the president give it to you oh Did something happen to the
president no?
No
Dramatic flashback it's dead it wasn't me though you
actually wrote this virus.
It's not really a virus It's more like a worm cluster.
It's actually a delayed effect autonomous program that's
designed to invade GW's cerebrum and render its nerve
connections useless.
You know what GW is?
Of course.
I created it.
Huh?
You look surprised.
Uh, well...
Cat got your tongue?
I'm sorry.
I...
How about the Patriots?
Ever heard of them?
Yes.
But I only know what I've been told.
How is Emma told so much at her?
Like, she's like, so young.
But it's hard to put into words.
Thank you for the 10 gifted.
Thank you.
Are you reading me, Emma?
Yes, loud and clear.
The president said that Arsenal Gear was the Patriot's key
to supremacy.
That's as good a description as any.
What exactly is it?
It's a massive data processing system capable of controlling
information on a global scale.
scale a data processing system that's right the system's a
social device for maintaining the Patriots control actually
reads her well in this day and age information emerges from
every direction and is freely distributed a variety of
information gathered by servers employing the latest in
high-speed communication networks and P to P technology is
rapidly circulated to individuals in fact the speed of this
circulation process is accelerating on almost daily basis
the Patriots seem to be afraid of this development.
Apparently, they believe that their role will shift from
dominant to dominated.
Whoa.
Let me give you an example.
You're aware of Solid Snake's anti-metal gear activities,
aren't you?
Yeah.
Yeah, I know a little about it.
Well, that's just a small sample of uncontrolled
information.
I can guarantee you the Patriots did not want Solid Snake's
name publicized.
Now, look at it like this.
Political scandal, corporate corruption.
Up until now, the Patriots have managed to keep a lid on
these and other.
other self-serving events, but with their existing data
processing system, they're no longer able to effectively
control the flow of information generated at the individual
level.
With the new created system, they can fully regulate digital
information.
The high-level information can be categorized in stages,
given clearance levels, and deleted as necessary.
Where do I know this voice from?
It's Jennifer Hale.
By the public.
By deleting such information, the Patriots can shape the
course of history as they see fit.
Somebody's bound to catch on.
No, the memory not to mention the lifespan of the average
individual is extremely limited on the other hand digital
information lasts virtually forever it doesn't deteriorate
so the alphabet 26 letters right it could have been 30
letters what if the four deleted letters were controlled by
a program impossible my brain not in fact something similar
is my brain here is just whole do you know how many genes
exist in an individual about 30 to 40 thousand right that's
what was actually a hundred thousand according to the
original theory advanced by the scientific community.
Information regarding the remaining 60,000 was suppressed by
the Patriots.
Why?
How would you know?
Do you know what a gene looks like?
Did you count them yourself?
There are research organizations.
Of course!
And their reports have already been subtly altered.
They're even beginning to believe the doctored reports.
GW is a system that allows the Patriots to decide what will
be recorded in tomorrow's history.
So what we're talking about is one huge censorship system
for deleting information which might be inconvenient to the
Patriots.
Bum, bum, bum.
The actual physical core for handling the task, GW, is
installed in Arsenal.
It's the only system in the world with an optic neural AI
that has a parallel processing capacity of 980 trillion
hammets.
I suppose that being a specialist in neural AI and complex
logic role in your association with the Metal Gear project.
That's not the only reason.
What do you mean?
I guess there are plenty of other reasons.
Yes, there are.
I understand.
Do you?
So Arsenal Gear was actually designed to protect the GW
system, wasn't it?
Yes, it's armed with everything, including nuclear weapons.
Why did you create something like this, Emma?
What the hell?
What is the AI?
actually capable of controlling everything no gw is only the
system's core it's only for deciding what data is stored or
deleted the actual subsystem for executing the task exists
within our social structure what you freak do you remember
the panic that gripped the computer industry prior to the
end of the century you mean the y2k that's exactly yeah y2k
our government supplied the world with the countermeasure
program using the internet at full capacity y2k cloud strike
organization every key facility throughout the world in
addition the same program was included in an os application
for distribution among the public definitely making out the
y2k countermeasure contained a program designed by the
patriots yes and everything supplied from that day onward
contains the same program impossible do you know how a
computer operates do you really know the basic principles on
how data is exchanged well nobody's aware of it but there's
a subsystem previous prompt it's about to be activated is
that why solidus wants to burn out every electrical circuit
in manhattan with a nuclear blast no probably but the
overall system isn't actually complete what it still lacks
the necessary factors for judging situations i heard they
were planning a major experiment in the next few days to
provide complex data for gw to study and suddenly all this
happens sounds cute emma it's not your fault if it wasn't
for the terrorists yeah you're right i'm i mean well i think
that's about all i know but you still right i'm thanks but i
think you still my bird in the computer room is he safe your
bird that noisy overgrown parakeet excuse me he's a And he's
very cute.
Well, the bird's okay.
Did you know that in the old days, miners used to take a
canary into the mine shafts to detect toxic gas?
Yeah.
That's what he's for?
No.
I really needed someone to talk to.
Why did you bring that up then?
Right.
I think we'd better get moving.
Look at that guy.
He's so cute.
We've got a little longer to cover than the last time.
I'll give it my best.
Yeah.
Whatever you do, don't open your eyes.
Why not?
There's a dead guy.
Why do they have to do it again?
Who put more mines there?
Who did that?
Okay.
What are those sticks in your head?
Decoration?
They're lacquered chopsticks.
They hold your hair in place.
Did you know that they're pretty popular in Europe and South
America?
What are those sticks in your head?
You're not only cute, but smart too.
Oh, I'm much more than cute.
She's so cute!
Okay, let's go.
Raiden, you have a girlfriend.
How did they let her keep a pet in the workplace?
They didn't even let her have her- her pet is in a
completely different area.
Hey, Rose.
How do you like it now?
Jack, is that you?
Yeah.
You like her on my back?
You like this?
You like what you see?
Well, Jack, it sounds like you and Miss Emma are getting
along just fine.
I've been monitoring your every move in conversation.
I can't say it's been fun.
Give me a break.
I'm only trying to keep her spirits up.
Is that right?
Absolutely.
My mission is to get her to the computer room.
That's all?
Yeah.
You're lying.
You're attracted to her, aren't you?
I'll admit she's cute.
Oh, my God.
Rose, you're beautiful.
You know how I feel about you.
Have you remembered yet you mean 30th?
Yes.
It's your birthday, isn't it wrong?
You're not even warm.
What is it then?
Forget it.
You don't even know her birthday.
I am just a little a little jealous Rose she better get
moving good luck She doesn't even know her birthday.
He's like it's your birthday, isn't it?
This guy take Emma and go to strut L Okay, there's a ladder
down onto the oil fence on the ocean surface from that strut
wait tell me more the most toxic relationship let me talk to
Emma oh okay one condition no arguing no problem put her on
Eee is that you yes what do you want why did you get
involved in weapons development a lot of people will get
hurt even more will die I'm talking about the destruction of
homes and cities radioactive contamination for years to come
you of all people should know the horror of nuclear weapons
you know about our family's dark history yeah why EE why you
left me no fighting made my life a living hell no fighting I
didn't have a choice don't lie to me the pool you could
never look me in the eye after the accident you took the
easy way out so you wouldn't have to face me oh that way you
could avoid responsibility every day the girls are fighting
you ran you ran No, that's not why I left.
You left me and took the easy way out.
That's not true.
I left the house because...
You're a criminal, just like me.
A criminal?
I know what you did.
You manipulated our account on the network.
But...
Look at what you're doing now.
You're nothing but a cracker.
No, I'm just applying my knowledge for the cause.
The cause?
What cause?
Justice?
For peace, E.B.
I'm not like Snake.
I can't carry a gun and face the enemy.
That's why I do what I do best.
Oh, right.
Nice justification, Hal.
Forget about being a criminal.
You'd make a great lawyer.
Maybe she met Hacker.
All right, already.
That's enough.
Mr. No Nonsense coming in to stop them from...
Emma.
What's up, Raiden?
Out of my way.
Let me talk.
You want to talk to Otacon?
Yes.
Oh, put him on.
Yeah?
What is it?
it up to now scientists have continued to be active
participants in war what's your opinion what's your oh the
way she leans there's been an ideal event that fuels the
progress of science but therein lies the trap we scientists
must establish some form of work ethic it's a tragedy that
both the government and the military act as sponsors to
modern science what are you talking about the atom and
hydrogen bombs were born from laboratories owned and
operated by universities Los Alamos and the Lawrence
Livermore Labs were run by universities.
There's something strange about that.
Weapons development and universities.
This may come as a surprise, but science requires that
information be exchanged freely.
You're referring to the will of Professor Oppenheimer,
aren't you?
See, I told you it was hacker.
Science and weapons always existed at different levels.
I never thought that my research results would bring about
misfortune to others.
That was until the Shadow Moses incident.
I have no regrets.
hell we scientists know the dangers oh my god emma it's up
to us to protect the people she's like i like nuclear
weapons or their politics man and nuclear weapons cannot
coexist mere mortals were never meant to handle nuclear
fusion watching the brother and sister nerd rage my
government respects me can you tell me what's wrong with
that can you okay that's enough oh my god oh my god well
let's see if there's one more okay i had a Huge crush on
Emma.
I don't blame you.
Oh, Snake.
Let me talk to him.
Oh, yeah.
Otacon's busy right now.
You'll have to settle for me.
What?
Okay.
Right.
Now, what do you want?
I was wrong.
Science doesn't exist to benefit the world.
Rage!
Science is for the individual!
For me, it's a way to realize my dreams.
Nerd rage!
Sounds pretty greedy.
You can't realize your dreams without greed.
And what's your dream?
revenge on how to beat him in his own game nerd fight i am
gonna make him regret the day he left me yeah i am gonna
make him realize he was wrong of all the idiotic i think
that's enough idiotic it's my goal my reason for being alive
how is wrong he's only being used by his country he's
pitiful even you guys are using him oh i'm using science to
achieve my own dream real bright lady That's exactly the
line that scientists are never meant to cross.
Oh my god.
I sold my soul for revenge.
I will never forgive him.
Yeah!
Don't pretend this conversation never happened.
No, you tell my brother exactly what I said.
Emma.
What?
You're speaking your mind, not your heart.
Whoa.
Just leave it at that.
Uh, okay.
Oh, awkward!
Should I check one more time?
It's so entertaining to listen to them go off.
The rumors about Big Shell being a big cover-up are all
true.
It seems like I just took a leap, huge leap here.
Sure, there are some facilities to clean up the pollution,
but they're not running at full capacity.
Don't you think it's funny that even though two years have
gone by since the incident, they haven't managed to clean up
all the crude oil?
Of course, the media doesn't report that kind of thing.
I think they're having fresh shipments of crude oil brought
in to replace the stuff they've cleaned up.
I'm sure you were told about toxic chemicals being released
if the plant were blown up also seems pretty fishy.
I don't think it's actually true.
Information is being suppressed on a human scale.
Get me out!
The new Metal Gear is worth all the effort and money they're
spending on it.
So I've been lied to all along.
Yeah, man.
Oh, no.
I think even your CO didn't know what was going on.
And that's probably what he's been telling you.
I didn't mean by the Colonel.
I meant by you.
Huh?
Huh.
We never lied to you.
We just didn't tell you everything.
That's all.
Lying by omission!
You know, you're a pretty interesting guy.
You're just like Snake said.
What did he say?
That you're a weak, simple-minded, stubborn fool?
A weak, simple-minded...
Ah, don't worry.
He didn't mean anything bad by it.
Nothing bad.
What could possibly be worse than that?
That lying, useless, backstabbing, mincing, son of a...
I'm his friend.
I know him better than anyone else.
I know he's not that he's raging.
Yeah, so what?
And by the way, there's one more thing you should probably
know about Snake.
He's bisexual.
He's right here.
Ah!
Next to you?
Yep.
Did he hear every word?
I'm... I'm just gonna get back to the mission now.
Oopsie!
Oh my gosh.
Oh, I thought that was a mine.
Oh, my God.
I thought that was a mine.
Oh, my gosh.
I was so scared for a second.
I was my whole body flinched.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, my gosh.
I thought it was a mine.
Cheese, Louise.
Cheese, cheese, cheese, cheese.
Oh, my gosh.
Okay.
This way.
Down, down, down, by the river.
There are no mines in this room, though, right?
Close your eyes.
Emma, Emma, Emma, Emma, sorry.
Sorry, I'm bad at direction.
Close your eyes.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Ooh, the heck is Louise.
My favorite part of these games so far is how many small
details there are.
So many interactions and conversations I didn't see when I
played it.
I know, right?
They're so fun.
Snake!
You've got rations.
Rations are...
Okay, I think I'm good.
What is it?
Oh, I prefer rations over Rose's home cooking.
That bad, huh?
Sorry, I thought that maybe I would get something while
looking at him.
While zooming in on him.
He looks pretty bad shape.
Not gonna lie.
Sorry, I didn't mean to skip the cutscene.
Okay.
Alright, there's bombs down here!
There's bombs!
I saw them.
Okay.
They replaced them maybe.
Oh, rush.
Oh, hold on.
Wait.
Oh gosh, I'm going the wrong way.
Wait, was that something there?
Oh, God.
Sorry, Emma.
Oh, my gosh.
But there's a rash in there.
I have to go that way anyway.
Okay.
Okay, your solid two.
Ryden, please dump your girlfriend already.
No!
Stay with her forever.
I love the excitement.
Oh, my God.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh my god, Emma!
Emma!
That was crazy, wasn't it?
That was wild, Emma, wasn't it?
Yeah!
Look at the water, it's disgusting.
Why is it...
Why is the water making noise?
Ew.
Okay, here we go!
She'll be fine.
She'll...
She's fine!
Okay.
Alrighty.
We're here.
Don't worry.
See?
And no bugs inside.
No bugs.
Oh!
Shoo!
Shoo, shoo!
Come on, Emma.
It's okay.
Bugs!
I hate bugs!
Come on, come on.
You look so sad.
Come on.
Bugs!
I hate bugs!
I'll freeze them for you, girly.
Yeah!
Just a little bit more.
Where'd they come from?
Nasty.
Bugs!
I hate bugs!
Yeah, me too.
Especially pink ones.
This does a really great job.
This is every exterminator's dream.
Okay, Emma.
Don't look so sad.
My goodness.
Oh.
Oh, they're hidden in there.
Let's just go.
Come on.
Mata in shambles?
Good.
Trank her and carry her over the bugs.
Maybe we could do that.
Oh god, you guys.
Oh, my stomach's starting to hurt.
No, no.
No, no, no, no.
My tummy's starting to hurt at this part.
You guys, I have a bit of a trauma here in this area.
If you know, you know.
But I have a bit of a trauma in this area.
Don't sit down!
Oh my god.
Oh, what the?
Did he...
Did he disappear out of existence?
What is he doing?
Oh my gosh.
Okay.
I'm gonna take her this way.
I'm gonna have her hide.
Oh my gosh.
Oh god.
Oh god, oh god, oh god.
I don't think you guys understand.
The emotions I'm feeling right now.
Oh god.
God, oh god, oh god, oh god, oh god, oh god.
Oh guys, you guys don't...
What happens here?
Oh shoot.
Oh my god.
There's somebody there.
Just a box.
No, no, no, no.
Go, go, go, go, get out.
Oh my god, my cat.
Oh my god.
Wait, Paz.
Paz, stop!
Stop climbing my chair!
Okay, I'll let you out.
Hold on.
Paz, please, Paz.
Paz, Paz, Paz.
Paz, please.
Oh my god.
Hold on.
I gotta let my cat in my room.
Paz, I'm sorry.
Okay, just one second.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh gosh, oh gosh, oh gosh.
Oh gosh, oh gosh.
I'm wondering if I should just kill him.
Sorry, buddy.
Oh, wow.
You're a tough guy.
How?
Okay, there we go.
Don't worry.
I'm going to handle this room first.
Emma!
You guys, I can't have him waking up, okay?
It's too scary here, okay?
You have to understand.
Who doesn't understand?
Doesn't he come out of that hallway on the right?
Okay, let's just go get Emma.
Come on.
Let's go.
Well, you can wait in the...
You can wait in the waiting room.
In the...
In the lounge.
Here, here, in the pool.
break room.
There you go.
Take a... Actually, there... Oh, I was going to say, there's
no couches in here.
There he is.
What's his route?
Let's see what he does.
Get her a cola too.
Now, does he look up?
Because if not, I can just stand and, you know, then grab
him.
Which way does he turn?
Oh, oh, oh.
Okay, we can just stand over here and wait for him.
perfect i'm feeling oh god i'm i'm feeling it mr crabs i'm
feeling it mr crabs i'm feeling it mr crabs i'm
sorry i'm really sorry man is there something else here oh
this is for my own good this is for this is for me sorry i
have to do it i have to do it to you i have i have to i have
you guys it's for my own please
it's for my own well-being
this is the part i've been dreading the entire game please
understand all right come on yeah emma don't look close your
eyes close your eyes okay come on i'm gonna put you in that
hallway okay
yeah i'm gonna put you in here don't look at the blood is
fine don't look at it don't even notice it
oh that's me this is this is me right now i'm a tired i'm a
tired okay okay okay can i just leave okay okay okay i know
i seem dramatic right now but i don't i don't know if you
understand i don't know if you could You might understand.
I don't know.
Turn around!
Can't I peek up over ledges?
I can't remember.
A sesame fall!
Oh my god, that was close.
How do I peek up over ledges?
L2, R2, and first person away.
Oh!
And
down!
Increase to maximum security!
Send a replacement guard for the area.
Emma.
Emma, it's over.
Emma, it's over for us.
Emma.
Emma, it's over.
What are they gonna do to her, actually?
I'm curious.
Ah!
So anyway, I started blasting!
Yeah!
Oh shoot, where'd you come from?
Emma!
Emma, we can't leave this place.
Emma, Emma, we're in trouble.
Emma, we're in trouble.
Emma, this is a bad run, Emma!
Emma, the run is over, Emma!
Emma!
I can't save this, Emma!
Jack please answer me Jack Oh gosh You can actually kill so
many guards They stop coming I don't believe that I don't
believe that to be true at all
You okay?
That was all just a bad Bad dream That actually went Um
Worse than how I first Have done it
That was actually worse than before That's so funny Funny
how that is Funny That bastard
Oh god Oh wait He didn't notice that did he?
Nah he was too busy sleeping Too busy being a sleepy guy
Come on Oh hello?
Come on girl We gotta run We gotta go I'm gonna put you over
here again Don't worry Gonna put you over here.
Yeah.
And I'm also gonna put both bodies over here too.
Gonna put both bodies over here too.
Oh
no, wait, that was my...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh my god, wait.
Open.
Now fall asleep.
There we go.
Okay.
Let's get his butt.
Alright.
You come here.
Come here, come here.
Come here, come...
Oh.
Come here, come here.
Come on, come on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Eternal sleep for you.
A nice eternal slumber for you.
Emma, don't look.
Close your ears.
Hey, give me something before you go.
Really?
cheap cheap
this guy there we go all right come on Emma yeah he is
stingy okay all right one guy you know what let's actually
move him a little bit inward so nobody can see him either
right yeah then we'll put your friend right on top of you
come on Renta's so brutal?
I don't want them waking up!
They wake up and they'll be like, Oh, oh, we got an intruder
guy.
Uh-oh.
Better, I guess I better attack everything and, you know,
call for backup and do everything terrible.
Okay.
They won't wake up.
They do!
Don't they?
They'll wake up eventually.
takes forever yeah and i take forever to to get through this
part okay so we're even
it's fine
actually when does this guy come through the elevator is it
timed or
good night this is the only time when murder is okay Okay.
I'll leave you.
Well, this is not a safe spot either.
Hold on.
Let's wait for the other guy to leave.
I don't know how much he can see.
Let's turn around.
I don't want him to see me walk in front of the stairs.
He will see me walk in front of the stairs.
We know you enjoy the killing in this area!
Yeah, I do.
And I'm not afraid to admit it.
I enjoy the killing in this area.
I will kill for sport.
Okay, lay down.
Let's see.
Oh, wait.
I think I'm too low.
I'm too low.
Wait, maybe if I do this, maybe I can get him from far away.
There we go.
I can't see him.
he's gone.
Oh wait.
Oh gosh.
Oh please put me out of my misery.
Uh oh the misery.
Oh my heart is going like a bajillion miles per hour.
Oh my god please.
Oh where are you?
Ryden why are you so short?
I'm tempted.
No it's fine.
It's fine.
No I won't do it.
I won't do it.
I'm I'm just gonna steal your stuff.
Oh wow, wow, you got the big, you got the big guns, okay.
I don't remember where to do this, how to do.
Oh gosh, I'm too short.
Oh, I can get him.
But I think someone will wake him up.
I think I should have waited.
I think someone comes around.
Let me see if someone comes.
Oh god.
Oh my hands are so sweaty.
Oh my god.
My hands are so sweaty.
Oh god.
Everything is gripping.
I'm gripping.
Can you please turn?
I see.
Oh there we go.
There we go.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay,
okay, okay, okay, okay, let's go.
Lolly, lolly, lolly, get your adverbs here.
Okay, I'm gonna leave you right here, okay?
Okay, don't do anything stupid.
Oh, gosh.
There's that guy up there.
What does he do?
What do you do?
Is there another guy?
Is there anyone else?
Is it just him?
He's asleep.
Oh!
Please go back to sleep!
Please, please, please, please, please, please Please,
please, please.
Oh god, oh god, okay.
Go back to your spot.
He went back to your spot.
He went back.
He actually did it.
He actually...
Oh, you, you.
Please go back to your spot.
Please, please, please, please, please, please, please,
please.
Please, please, please, please, please, please.
Get up.
Take my hand.
No.
What can I do for you, Jack?
Oh, God, Rose.
I did it.
Oh, my God.
Jack, how far do you think the Patriots' digital control
extends?
I don't really know, but it probably influences a lot of
what goes on and how every day lives even mundane things
like which movies and songs will come a hit and what kind of
happiness and taste would be the easiest thing to manipulate
i mean think about the kinds of film and bands everyone
wants to go to see it's whatever's at the top of the charts
what are you talking about charts are made up exactly but
you can't really control individual taste it's too closely
tied to personality thank you i don't know about that trends
have always been about following the
No.
You're awesome.
So is the idea of word-of-mouth communication.
Rose, you have any friends you've met online?
Hmm?
Yeah, I do.
How many?
Well, if you count only the ones I talk to a lot, I'd say
about 20.
20 people!
One or two tops?
Rose, you have 20 friends on the internet!
That's how it is for everyone, I guess.
Oh my god!
And even if your online buddies had fake identities and were
circulating false information, That's an insane amount of
friends online.
And there'd be no way for you to know for sure.
Well, what about people who do meet face to face then?
Like us.
Oh my gosh.
Have you ever really shown me the real me?
Why was that so easy?
I wouldn't even know the real me myself.
But you're being honest with yourself now.
Oh, that's how I see it.
Well, how am I being honest?
I've never seen you show so much feeling.
Fear, anger, even a kind of giddiness.
thing to say but you're living out loud for the first time
that i've seen i'm just trying to get the job done this is
war you know this is war you know okay back to the game
everybody you're different from your usual restrained self
what about you then i always want to be open with you as
much as i can about what the heck are you talking about did
i get all of them which one which stress okay All right, now
that I've...
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, I feel so much relief.
Take Emma and head for Strut L.
Oh, my God.
Strut L is on the south end of that KL connecting bridge.
Okay.
Snake, are you online?
Raiden, I may have to sign off for a while.
Anything wrong?
Just a small errand.
Don't worry about it.
What's it about?
Here goes.
I'm going offline.
No!
He is offline!
Okay, str- Oh gosh, this part's kind of annoying too though.
Come on.
Oh, the anxiety was the real enemy all along.
Yep.
Oh, PSG.
Chaff.
Oh, my bad, sorry.
Here we go.
La, la, la.
Walking along.
Oh, be careful.
Oh, la-la-la.
Here we go.
Snake hates us, you guys.
He hates.
Guys, it's so...
Wait, he can't see me.
Idiot.
Is there anybody else?
Just him?
Where'd you come from?
You must have come up the stairs.
Ah.
Sometimes their vision is like...
Sometimes I feel like they actually have 180 IQ.
And sometimes they're just dumb, dumb little guys.
We can't see two feet in front of them.
Alright, let's go, Emma.
Come on.
Oh, wait, I have to get the coolant, don't I?
Don't catch on fire.
Emma, Emma.
Emma, stand back.
Watch as a pro.
Takes the reins.
Oh, oh, sorry.
It's still on fire.
Okay, don't go, Emma!
Emma, it's still on fire!
Emma, let's go now.
No, these guys aren't genome soldiers.
I just like to say that they all have 180 IQ.
Okay, I hate this part.
Oh no!
We don't have a card!
Beep beep!
What's wrong?
This door is security level 5.
I don't have card 5.
No, I don't have card five.
He's such a baby.
Giving up already.
He's such a whiny baby.
I don't have card five.
Ta-da.
What the?
In European Extreme, they are like insects directly
telepathic ping.
Your location.
You should have told me you had it.
Gosh.
The truth is, I just remembered it myself.
Why are you so mean?
Who cares if it...
You didn't need it earlier.
Why are you such a jerk, Raiden?
Gosh.
Must have 195 IQ.
Yeah, pretty much.
Alright, let's save.
I know.
I just... I save so often in this one...
Jack, is that you?
Because I love the drama.
He has card five cheeks, though.
How could he be so mean to Rose...
To Rose, to Emma.
Talk to you soon, Jack.
Oh.
Okay, she's got nothing to say to me.
Alright, Colonel.
Riding, there should be a ladder down to the water somewhere
near your present location on Strut L.
Okay.
Take Emma to the ladder.
I hope she's good with heights.
Okay, we don't have a nerd in this area.
But I hear them.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait.
Where is that guy?
It's just the one guy, I believe, right?
Did I just say nerd?
Oh, sorry, node.
Where is he?
Doesn't he?
Doesn't he come over here?
Am I crazy?
Hey, guy.
Huh?
Where is that guy?
Where is he?
I'm scared.
I'm gonna...
Good.
I'm so not cool it
we'll get him when he walks over there no worries oh okay
hold on oh shoot oh there's two guys there are two guys
there's two guys I believe I believe there's two guys I
think there's two guys I think there's two guys you guys
there's two guys.
There's two guys.
Okay, now let me take him.
Now he's down.
Now get your brother.
What are you talking about?
Your friend just passed out!
Emma?
Emma, I might have... Emma, don't just sit there, Emma.
I might have made a mistake, Emma.
Emma, I think I think I made a mistake, Emma.
Emma.
Emma?
I think I made a mistake.
Emma, I made a little whoopsie.
Emma, don't be mad at me.
Emma, why don't you look at me anymore, Emma?
I thought he would have...
I thought he was gonna go get his friend waking up.
Oh, she needs a box too.
Are they gonna come over here or...
I sure hope not.
You know what?
Maybe...
Why am I even wishing for that?
Emma!
Emma, just stay put, okay?
Just you stay there.
Do they think about your actions, Missy?
In the timeout corner over there.
We're just waiting for the caution to run out, okay, Emma?
Don't worry about it, Emma.
All personnel, return to your stations.
Shoot.
She can't hear you.
She has her iPod's in.
Cool.
All right, let's try that again.
Let's try that again without messing up this time.
Okay, Ryden.
Now, what we need to do is not mess it up.
Some instincts as a gamer.
Oh, gosh.
Can this guy see me?
Okay, now investigate your friend.
Your friend just fell asleep.
Are you gonna not notice him or...
Okay.
Oh, oh, he did.
He just kicked him awake.
Oh, shoot.
Okay.
Do you have any stun grenades?
I think I do.
But Emma will also be stunned.
Will she not?
Oh, he's gonna walk over.
Okay, let me see if I can get him now.
Oh, there we go.
There we go.
Okay.
Come on, Emma.
We just needed him in position.
Oh, oh, oh, okay, we're good.
Let's go.
They're asleep.
Sleepy fellas.
Such sleepy fellas right there.
Get drag her by the legs.
But if you drag her by the legs, she will...
You can't go through doors, I'm pretty sure.
I don't think you could take her through doors if you drag
her.
Come on, in through here, and down the hatch.
Big shells, ebious soldiers.
Alrighty!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Are you afraid of heights, Emma?
Are you okay?
You're good with heights too?
It's crazy how much and how little of the game we have left,
isn't we?
What a three.
I have a question.
for you what is it how do you feel about heights I can't say
I like heights the waters higher on my phobia list I'm so
centered well we have to go down the ladder how far down
just a little bit why do I feel like we've had this
conversation before how little is little about 130 feet huh
you can do it would you take no for an answer how are your
legs better the numbness is gone I can cute when the
numbness is gone.
Okay, follow me.
So cute when her numbness is all better.
She's got little legs at work.
Here we go.
Sweat.
This is, it's about to be one of my favorite, like, vistas
of the game.
Don't look up her skirt riding!
Oh, she's wearing shorts.
Okay, never mind.
What a thrill.
With darkness and silence through the night.
Make sure to have the D-mic ready.
Oh, you know it.
Right.
The sunset.
It's beautiful.
Here.
If we don't hurry, it'll be the last we see.
This whole area is like my favorite.
Oh, here, here, here, there.
This is my favorite scene in the game.
Or like view in the game.
It's so...
pretty it's so nice it's so cute oh okay I'm ready enemy
soldiers gun ciphers I don't think we're gonna be able to
slip past all that poopy man looks like it can barely
support one person how much do you weigh Emma are you gonna
ask me how old I am next Wow if you go alone I think you can
make it across so beautiful
This is Ryden.
Do you read me?
Ryden's out.
We've made it to the lower part of Strut L.
We'll have to cross the water from here.
Can Emma walk?
Yeah, she's okay.
The pontoon bridge doesn't look too sturdy.
Emma's going to have to cross it alone.
Right.
The oil fence.
There are ciphers and several guards.
Ryden, you're carrying a PSG-1, aren't you?
It's as pretty as me, though.
It's time to play sniper.
Not bad.
This spot gives me a good vision.
of the targets you're going to have to cover Emma until she
crosses to strut E I'll get there and provide some support
of my own yeah you can handle it I can I know the drill I
know the drill I faced a similar situation in advanced mode
level 4 VR training with the PSG 1 advanced mode level 4 VR
yes it's better than nothing make sure you don't hit Emma no
promises right now with Arsenal's boarding in progress
security should be at a minimum that doesn't mean it's going
to be easy given the situation they probably got claymores
in place to make up for the security shortage make sure you
use your thermal goggles I have the thermal goggles I'm
heading for strike when snake tells me to use thermal
goggles I don't mind so much I'm gonna clear a path for you
from here how sniper fire you're kidding trust me what if I
fall into the sea I can't swim you were loud and clear what
that's supposed to mean no no get going you'll be fine okay
what's that supposed to mean time to blind yourself true oh
golly all right here she goes and here we go let's grab some
ammo and let's get into position
That's right.
Oh, okay, everybody.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, possess a means, too.
Where is it?
Sorry.
I can never find everything.
Okay.
Thermal goggles, a go.
All right.
You good?
We're good.
Look at her.
Let's get this guy.
Let's take this guy out.
Nice.
And the ciphers.
taking those out.
Oh, dang it.
It was the Pazazamines fault, everybody.
Wasn't me.
It wasn't me.
I know I don't need it for this part, but...
Oh, my God.
There we go.
Okay.
Oki-dokie!
And, uh...
Take this guy out.
Oh, what?
Where?
It's over here, right?
There's more.
Look at her go.
Ah, there's another man!
Oh, are you kidding me?
Are you kidding me right now?
Are you?
Sleep!
Oh my god, there's another guy.
All is well.
Where are the other ones?
Oh, let's take this out.
Um, can I zoom with this?
Zoom in with, oh.
Am I just not looking in the right places?
Oh, that's a guy.
That's a man.
There were other mines though, aren't there?
Let's take this guy out.
Um.
I think I got him.
Shoot.
I think he'll fall asleep.
Yeah.
Mine's on the third bridge.
Oh, oh.
I'm just taking stuff out while we wait.
You good?
Everybody's sleepy, sleepy, sleepy, sleepy.
Everybody's sleepy.
Nobody's awake.
Don't do it, Raiden.
Oh, you're shaking heads.
Oh, Raiden.
Raiden.
Nice.
I don't need no sesame...
Oh, directional mic.
Oh my god, that's a man.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Wait, sorry, I need this first.
Oh, that's a bird.
Scared me for a second.
Where's the directional mic is with the mic?
Where is she?
There she is.
Go, Emma, go!
Go Emma, go!
Do they stay asleep?
Or do they wake back up?
Oh shoot, oh shoot, oh shoot, oh shoot Oh shoot Um, I think
I should be good Good Emma, don't worry about it, girl Lee,
don't worry, I got you Ah!
Don't worry, Emma!
Emma, I got you Emma, I got you Emma, don't worry, don't
worry Don't worry
This is Snake.
Can you hear me?
Yeah, loud and clear.
Oh, nice and clear.
I've reached my sniping position on Struck E.
I'll provide support fire from here.
Do me a favor and take out whatever I miss.
Just call me when you want me to shoot.
Oh, okay.
Alright.
Oh, my bad, sorry.
She's gonna...
This is where the D-mic is most important.
But also, we can D-mic.
Okay.
Over here...
Where is he?
Where is that guy?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, someone's talking to himself.
Ah, where is he?
Oh, oh my god, sorry.
I'm so sorry Emma.
Emma, I'm so sorry girl.
I'm so...
Don't worry.
Don't worry!
You're safe!
Oh, gosh, there's another guy here.
Oh, my God.
Wait.
Oh, your friend is...
Oh, my God.
There's multiple of them.
Alright, there's so many of you guys.
I don't think I hit a single...
I don't think I hit a single shot.
Hey, can you, like, all fall asleep so I can do the fun,
funny stuff?
Where is she?
Uh-oh.
Wait, where'd she go?
Where?
Oh, there she is.
She is, okay.
There we go.
I got you in my sights.
Snake can help.
I know.
Okay, there we go.
All right.
All clear probably.
Yeah, I'll call Snake to do the rest.
Thanks Snake!
Damn, I don't think I can do this.
Snake, take over for me.
Take over me.
I'll take care of it then.
Oh, you can zoom in with the mic.
Oh.
I'm going to show you how sniping should be handled.
Take a good look.
Okay, thank you.
Take out the mines.
My sniping field will be limited to the area you're watching
through your PSG-1 scope.
Keep a good lookout on Emma's surroundings even while I'm
shooting, alright?
Okay.
D-mic time.
Hold in first person, move with left analog stick.
How did all this happen?
This poor girl.
You okay?
Just step over.
Why am I doing here?
Just step over them.
It's fine.
How did all this happen?
Can you take out this one?
Snake!
Take out this one!
Nice.
Any...
Any mines down there?
Take out that one.
Take out...
Nice.
Good job, Snake.
There he is.
You horn dog, you.
How...
Did all this happen?
Oh my god, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait.
Nice.
Okay.
Now we can do the D-Mike.
Wait, did you just kill that guy?
Oh, no.
He's still, he's still, he's still kicking.
Freeze!
Oh, here it is.
A girl.
What are you doing here?
It's not my choice, thank you very much.
Oh.
You're not gonna shoot me.
No, why not stay away from good-looking women when you're
fighting otherwise you'll get hit with diarrhea One of the
few things I learned from Shadow Moses.
What are you talking about?
What are you talking about history?
Don't worry about it.
I have no idea what you're talking about, but does this mean
you're letting me go?
Well, you could have found a nicer way to say that.
Oh, sure better hurry Don't mention it just run like hell.
Oh God.
Oh no.
Oh no This place is about to sink.
Just get out fast, okay?
Johnny!
What?
What's your name?
Don't have one.
Huh?
Okay, fine.
It's Johnny.
Hey, if we run into each other again...
What a weird guy.
Okay, now we have to be serious.
Okay, there's a lot going on around here.
okay let's here let's uh take this i'm gonna try and oh
shoot this guy oh okay or snake you can do that too okay you
can do that
oh my god snake you said he would do it that was me oh my
god here i'll take out this one there we go that was me Oh,
that was Snake.
Snake, what are you doing?
There she goes.
Snake, you have any words?
Snake, you got any words for Emma?
Are there any claymores?
I think I got all of them, but let's just check.
Let's check.
Oh, wait, what's that?
That's a bird.
Okay.
Yeah, we're good.
She'll make it in one piece.
She'll be totally fine.
Oh, the sun is so bright.
Snake, you got any words?
Not bad at all.
What do you mean by that?
Uh-oh.
Snake!
We both can't aim.
Snake, our aim is both bad!
Wish they'd give me more medicine.
Oh, you got it.
You good.
You got it.
Phew.
Alright.
We got this.
Just a little more.
Not bad.
talking about me snake right where's pliskin so sorry to
tell you this but so sorry to tell you this but all right
all right yay we did it doesn't he have a really gross line
about he does he has like a line where he's just like ah i i
date her or something oh my god no oh my god no No, please!
No, why are you back?
Don't shake, don't shake, don't shake.
Just shoot!
You have him!
You have him in your crosshair!
Yay, Vamp!
Send no one ever?
Wait.
Hold on!
She's like...
She's like joking.
I'm like, hold on!
One second!
Oh, did I hit?
Oh my god, please, controller.
Bye, forever, vamp!
Never want to see your ass again, please.
Emma, you good, girl?
You okay?
No, Emma, Emma, Emma, Emma!
Emma!
It wasn't me!
I didn't shoot her, I didn't...
I didn't shoot her.
No I didn't shoot her, I didn't...
Where was this aim?
Where was this aim before?
No, I didn't shoot her!
No!
It wasn't me!
Oh god, oh god, oh god, oh god, oh god.
Bandage.
It'll fix everything.
Stop the bleeding!
Pressure!
Something!
Don't pull out the bullet that I didn't shoot.
Raiden, you want to get over there or something?
Raiden, you want to make your way that direction?
Raiden, you want to...
Let's just codec the situation.
Raiden, Emma's been stabbed.
Oh, stabbed!
How bad is it?
She's conscious, but the bleeding's bad.
I'm bringing her over there right now.
Riden, get that disc over here as soon as possible.
I'm afraid her time's running out.
I'll be there.
These other guys can take missiles to the face.
But...
But one little stabby stabby stab, and that's it for her.
What's up with that?
Big stabbed hurts.
That hurts.
Emma took like 10 bullets.
I know.
Oh gosh, oh gosh, oh gosh.
Oh wait, isn't there a timer?
Wait.
Oh shoot, I forgot about this part.
Snake, what's your situation over there?
Emma seems to be doing something to GW's defensive
capabilities.
All we need now is your disc.
Okay, I'm on the way.
You better hurry.
I don't think she's gonna make it.
How's the bleeding?
But there's like guys I have to worry about too, isn't
there?
Oh shoot.
You'll find the coast is clear with everybody aboard Arsenal
right now.
Understood.
Oh, the coast is clear?
Wait, uh, uh, Snake, I see, I see someone moving.
The coast does not appear to be clear.
I repeat.
I repeat, the coast does not appear to be clear.
Oh, it's this guy.
He's listening to his music.
Timer.
My bad.
Sorry.
Okay.
Where am I going?
Snake, where am I going?
Sorry.
Right.
We're in the computing.
room on b2 of shell 1's core emma's not doing so well get
over here as beautiful girl from korea i think we might be
sold stop b2 of shell 1 now where we're we're wait oh oh b
oh oh no oh no oh no oh no wait oh wait where's this is f
where's B.
Oh, B2 of Shell 1.
Okay, B2 of Shell 1.
Okay, sorry, my bad.
Hold on.
I think this guy is right here.
We have to wait for him to leave.
Okay.
He's jamming out.
Sorry.
Sorry, man.
Okay.
Sorry.
It's this way, right?
Oh, my goodness.
Raiden, can you not get caught on everything?
I'll send you an invite to our wedding.
Okay, I'm looking forward to it.
Ooh, we'll take that.
All right, bye.
Bye-bye.
Wrong way?
Arsenal's launch has initiated a security lockout.
Autocons managed to override anything that leads to the
computing room.
This is no time to get sidetracked.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Wait, wait, wait.
Nice.
Box number five!
Is it this way?
Okay.
I've never seen that code before.
Because I'm stupid.
Oh my god, please.
Oh, I had it, but the controller pressure...
There we go.
Oh my god, oh my god.
Got it.
Um, anything else that I should be worried about?
Oh shoot, I have to go back through this thing.
Uh, okay.
Ha!
La la la, la, level two grip strength.
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
la la.
Nah, the coast has never been clearer.
B2, we gotta go see your little bird.
Yeah, I don't know why.
I think if he had said, he did say the computer room, right?
My brain is just a little silly.
I was like, where is that?
Okay.
Alright.
And it's clear in here, right?
Oh my god, my eyes.
My eyes.
Oh, my eyes.
Get it together, Raiden!
How could you not have seen those?
Can you imagine if it did the whole cutscene with the
thermal goggles on?
Oh no.
Punished for getting sidetracked.
This game is such a troll.
Gosh, Raiden, your hips are whack in this game.
How's Emma?
I think he got some internal organs.
I can't stop the bleeding.
Help.
I'm here.
Got the disc.
He's trying to be quiet, like, be respectful.
Emma set everything up.
Apparently all you have to do is pop in the disc.
Otakon, stop loving women.
Okay.
uh that should insert the virus into the ai is it working
just leave it to emma uh-oh uh-oh an antibody agent wow this
is damn the connection has been cut is the virus upload
complete i don't think so the count stopped at 90 percent
auto con i don't think emma's made any mistakes but a
portion of the worm cluster might have been altered after
the disc Emma's hands by the Patriots will the virus still
work I have no idea shadow clone how is is everything all
right oh it's all right snake is so sweet good least I won't
be adding another page to our family's dark history yeah
that's right what if the virus doesn't work I should destroy
that thing or take out solidus and his men how do we get on
board don't be so loud right I don't think we can unless
somebody inside gives us a hand the bird how
I...
I always...
What is it?
Hated your glasses.
Wanted to see you again.
Oh, music, there we go.
You don't hate me?
Never.
I never wanted to get in your way.
I wanted to hurt you.
That with Arsenal, if I followed in your footsteps, I could
be closer.
I just wanted you to look at me.
Look at me as...
As a woman.
I could never do that.
Don't be so honest.
Can I...
Can I ask you the best way?
Sure.
Oh god.
What?
Why?
Call me Emma.
Why is that such a weird request, Hal?
Otacon, please.
Oh god.
I'm already in pain.
What's wrong with EE?
Otacon, you!
Emma?
Emma, Emma, answer me.
Bro, oh god, it's just so painful.
He doesn't like to watch Otacon cry.
Every woman in this game series must suffer because of
Otacon.
Oh, God.
I didn't.
I didn't leave you.
Because of the accident.
I had...
I had a relationship with your mother.
She seduced me.
What's wrong with the dying girl?
My father's death It was no accident.
Good.
He took his own life.
Coward.
It was my fault.
All my fault.
Forgive me, Emma.
The world doesn't need Huey.
The world doesn't need your father.
Father's a poopy dookie head.
Oh, God.
Ah, not the bird.
Oh, it's the wind.
Oh, it's the bird that makes me cry.
Love me some Huey hate.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Oh, the bird.
Help.
I miss you.
Attention.
Arsenal gear is ready for launch.
I got to raise the upper levels immediately.
Sounds like they're cutting this area loose.
What do you mean?
It means we're going to sink.
We have to get the hostages out.
And what about the camo repairs?
We won't be able to get everybody aboard.
We'll just have to take as many as we can.
My sister...
won't be able to come with us.
We will be commencing the countdown shortly.
Personnel in the upper levels, head for the evacuation area
immediately.
That sound, I know it's a wolf, but it gets me every time.
I'm always the survivor.
Oh, God, Honokon.
Why, Wolf?
Oh,
my God.
Make me cry every time.
It's okay.
Otacon, take care of the hostages.
What about you guys?
We got other arrangements.
There's our ride out of here.
Anyway, we're going to have to sink that thing if the virus
doesn't work.
Yeah.
I should be going with you.
You've got your job.
We've got ours.
You mean...
I'd only get in your way.
No!
Wrong.
Only you can save those hostages.
Right?
Right!
Listen, the two of you won't be able to destroy that thing.
Eliminate the enemy.
That's your only option.
Please!
Yeah!
Uh, yeah!
Oh my god.
As long as that bird stays quiet, we aren't good.
Oh.
E-E?
Damn!
Otacon, try to get as many hostages out as you can.
It's a short flight to the shore, so don't worry about
overloading the cam off.
Oh.
He needs support, Snake.
He needs...
He needs support.
Yeah!
Ah!
I remain fresh now.
Wealing, Raiden.
Get out of here.
Oh my god.
Oh.
The bird is a paid actor.
I miss you.
You said other things.
You said other things earlier.
I heard them.
This part is so goofy.
It's so sad and so goofy.
Where he's like, I'm out of here.
You and me, we're the same.
I'm getting emotional whiplash here.
I know.
Both you and I.
You are.
We were always alone.
That is Otacon.
He's a simp.
Really appreciate how much snake killed.
There's Radicon.
We were always waiting.
He dies.
Snakes are a really good person.
Waiting for somebody.
Somebody who would love us.
But we were wrong.
You can't wait to be loved.
You have to go out and find it.
Go out and find it.
Four years ago, I realized that you can't just wish for a
happy family.
You have to make it happen.
Now you have one.
I only wish I knew that sooner.
Now you have a happy family!
I learned that I could love.
As you probably did.
Emma.
Emotional damage break.
I'm loving your playthrough of the MGS franchise.
Only one I've never played is four.
You think he's gonna be okay?
You can watch us play for them!
He's tougher than he looks.
Consider it done.
Now, how do we open this thing?
You can come out now.
Huh?
Oh my god!
A ninja!
Ninja!
What the- A ninja?
Arsenal's going to take off.
We still need you to take care of a few things.
Oh my god!
This time, someone fail us.
No!
Snake, what's this all about?
Time to go night night.
Bedtime riding.
How do you do that?
Nighty night riding.
You changing sides now?
Change sides?
I don't recall saying I was- on yours damn it snake who's
the ninja who's the ninja gray fox
oh god girl look over here
she's been working with snake the whole time
gray fox sea woman
We get quite a few cutscenes here now, if I remember
correctly.
Oh!
Titanic Reel!
Good job, Otakon, good job.
He did his job well.
Mm-hmm.
Jack, are you reading me?
Do you want to save your mission data up to this point?
I do.
Thank you, Rose.
But it's...
It's writing.
Oh.
Are you saved Merrill, not AutoCAD and MGS1?
How is he alive?
Your mission data's been saved.
You know, he got out.
This is...
Is he still alive?
He was when Ogden brought him in.
This is just like MGS1!
I'm just a guy!
Check my bloodstream.
It's got gunpowder in it.
He's a non-existent operative from a non-existent
organization.
I suspect it is much.
However, I know this man.
You know me?
Wake him up.
Ow!
I thought he was gonna slap me.
the parallels I know right a lot of things have been quite
similar to MGS1 it's kind of crazy solid ice it's been a
while hasn't it
huh okay you know this fellow fellow you remember me don't
you you've grown
By concentration of cerebral implants, have they altered
your memory too?
It's time for Jack to let her rip.
Look at the eight pack he's got going on.
This is my son.
Huh?
I taught him everything.
This is my son?
oh my god the eye patch solidus jack i never thought i'd see
you again you know me you don't remember oh my god your name
your skills everything you know you learn from me
and you were one of the best among the child soldiers that
fought in that conflict oh my god right in the child soldier
when you were barely ten years old you became the platoon
leader of the small boy unit at the time your outstanding
kill record earned you several nicknames including white
devil and Jack the Ripper oh white Mamba I was your
godfather I named you little baby when the war ended you
disappeared from the relief center I wondered what happened
to you I should have known they would recruit you
It's an interesting coincidence if he's a lackey for the
Patriots.
I doubt he knows anything of interest What should we do with
him strip him down?
We'll use him like you suggested.
Oh What about dead cell?
Ignore them He's dead.
Oh, oh my god Dead cell is basically dead.
All that's left is fortune.
Could it be that he's here too?
Liquid.
He's already stripped down.
In another hour, we demonstrate the power of Arsenal Gear.
Oh my god.
Attack with standard weapons, of course.
Yes, proceed as planned.
At last report, all is well with GW.
Hmm.
How about the troops?
Arsenal, it looks like he's skimming something.
You're the spitting image of big boss.
Solidus was doing all this while Venom was building a zoo.
Yeah, I guess you're...
Is that so?
Perhaps I should be grateful to this kid for that.
I guess so.
It's funny because Solidus is the youngest sibling.
And we know how old Eli is.
This situation...
find it very nostalgic where am i why inside arsenal gear of
course this time he had to take his pants off though
actually we're also inside the memory of shadow moses oh
what do you mean by that i'll take this back no you don't
need this anymore do you dang it awesome lot like riding oh
god she'll get us out she doesn't want to look at her wind
is blowing we shall speak again a foul wind is blowing sorry
yeah it's johnny don't move stay as you are okay we're being
monitored by a camera okay what are you up to i'm switching
over to nano communication okay
mr x ninja correct it's me what i thought you were the
leader of the russian troops no That was just a smokescreen.
He says it about Olga too.
This guy just to provide you support This guy says it about
any of the lady the Colonel no the Patriots what I I
deceived my troops betrayed them Oh my god, but why my child
is being held hostage by the Patriots It all started two
years ago when I lost my father during the tanker incident
my men and I had nowhere to go legal Russian organization
the Russian mafia something like that actually I learned
much later that it was a subordinate organization of the
Patriots I was expecting at the time when I gave birth to my
child it turned out I was in a hospital run by the Patriots
no my child was gone my baby is being kept somewhere in this
country have you ever met your child that's not fair once a
me a photo of my child be a network I've never even held the
child in my own arms I see given your situation nobody can
blame you for what you did that's your opinion I thought you
were enemies he wasn't responsible for my father's death
whoa actually we owe him our lives oh two years ago they
were responsible for getting us out of the sinking tanker
alive that's me that's me oh that did not happen that's from
the trailer so you were partners since the incident no i
only found out the truth shortly before this huh when i
confronted him here you fought with snake when two years ago
well it was around the time you were holding hands with that
girl oh snake Oop.
Holding hands with that girl.
So you joined hands with him to pay back a debt.
No, mutual gain.
Mutual gain.
My job was to assist you.
If Solidus gets away with Arsenal, your mission is a
failure.
True?
The Patriots would judge that as failure on my part and
terminate my child.
Putting it simply, my child's life depends.
on your success so you did it all for your child but why
would the patriots want to help me are they hoping i'll take
solidus out no you're just like me we're just pawns no we're
not pawns for what purpose we're not pawns in the government
plan huh you'll figure it out sooner or later but i wonder
if you'll handle it true listen when someone's talking to
you listen i don't know if i've ever heard that one before
he's got to be stopped what about the virus no I'm not sure
Olga doesn't see the picture they took.
I think the Patriots have tampered with the program.
Will it work?
I don't know.
Get me out of this thing.
That's not fair.
I'll release your restraints after I leave this room.
Oh, okay.
Snake's got everything.
I couldn't bring it here.
Oh my god.
And where do I find Snake?
It's chilly!
It's too cold!
Olga!
I've never heard that.
I don't think I have either.
I don't have it.
The passageway ahead leads to a hangar.
He'll be waiting there.
I still haven't gotten my favorite, Rose.
one though it's the egotistical woman one arsenal gear oh
god here it comes it's impossible to completely destroy this
thing the only option is these guys if there are people here
who have never seen metal gear solid two before please no
spoil i still can't afford to be discovered please no spoil
the line is you're a real egotistical woman yeah i love that
one oh god you can't keep this up they're bound to find you
listen i'll free you in a little while brace yourself i
can't even move my head anymore she hit me where'd she hit
me yet
hello hello
oh hello hello oh the stomach jack are you all right you
can't change the camera view yet i don't believe jack is it
true you have to wait until after your first release it's
unbelievable drafting small children sending them to war
it's not allowed under international conventions icc rules
don't mean a lot in war someone told me that there are over
300 000 children in combat right now i was just one of them
so you remember i thought your memory had No.
Manipulated by them.
It was.
But I have nightmares every day.
Pieces of the past.
I can't put together.
Oh my god.
Why didn't you tell me?
You couldn't begin to understand.
You wouldn't know that until you try me.
No.
I didn't want you to get hurt.
Ah.
There was never a real reason for me to fight.
Except that someone put a gun in my hand.
And that someone...
was him him it wasn't your fault if I survived the day's
fight I was praised fed and had a bed to sleep in I think I
was only six when I held my first AK but I'm not even sure
of that Jack I'm not like snake I never questioned why we
fought you were like you were like ten years old they give
you a gun you ask how many to kill if you didn't you were
the one they shot instead it's okay Hey, no one is blaming
you.
I'm blaming you.
We were shown Hollywood action films every day.
The kind with macho guys and big guns.
They call it image training.
That's crazy.
He had to watch movies.
They built us from the ground up into killing machines.
We were fed once a day.
I can still taste the gunpowder they mixed into the food.
Gunpowder in the food?
Yeah, gunpowder!
Giving it hallucinogenic properties.
It kept us drugged.
Oh my god
Rosa's reaction there is like the most believable thing
those of us who survived were taken in by NGOs Her cheeks
are the bomb.
I gave me a new life in the States.
I can't complain But nothing's changed the only people who
have no problem with my past have secrets and agendas of
their own Terrible nightmares every night.
I can never forget I'm afraid of the night.
That's why I don't sleep next to you.
You should have told me.
Told you what?
That I'm a killer?
And always have been?
No.
What I hate more than anything else in the world is my own
past.
I didn't want you or anyone to know about it.
Oh, God.
Now I know why I was chosen for this mission.
No one can take him on.
Take him down, except me.
I've been kept alive this long for this.
I knew as soon as I saw Solidus.
Jack, I love you the way you are now.
You have to believe me.
I didn't know anything about you.
I admit that.
So dramatic.
Where you were born, how you grew up.
Pass the popcorn place.
But I know that now.
And I know that what I feel for you can only get better.
And I'll share in your past if that's the price.
It doesn't work that way.
No one can share the burden of what I've done.
It's not one of those warm and fuzzy things couples share.
No.
I accept the good and the bad, Jack.
That's what you do for someone you love.
I don't want to share my past with anyone.
I just want to forget about it.
Jack, I haven't told you, you know, about what I've done.
Oh, uh-oh.
She got secrets.
The last two years with you, it's been more than I've ever
hoped for.
Jack.
Jack, oh, Jack.
But I can't go any farther.
I'm breaking up with you.
I know you want to get married.
Oh, I...
But I can't.
Imagine getting broken up over Kodak.
There's no way to erase my childhood.
It's all right, Jack.
Please, don't say any more.
Ah, we're free.
Took her long enough.
Gosh, oh, oh my god.
Get back in.
Thank you, thank you.
So this is the cosplayer you saw at MGSCon, minus the towel.
Luckily!
Light.
Wow!
Oh my...
Oh god!
Oh my god!
I really swear you could see...
See...
I swear you could see something when he lays down.
Oh my god.
Thank goodness.
We don't want to catch a cold now.
I don't want to catch a cold now.
Beep, beep.
Which way does this go anyway?
It doesn't even have a number.
Double cheeked on a Sunday afternoon.
Hallelujah.
Pause mid-flip.
Oh, that was actually...
That was actually pretty good.
I remember this scene like it was yesterday.
truly touching he's a candle he's just a candle there's
nothing there oh god here we go colonel I'm naked and cold
and the clap of my glutes is alerting the guards I'm gonna
need to get food soonish kind of I'm starting to get hungry
get your equipment back first or you won't be able to do
much good.
I'm naked.
Right.
Rendezvous with that man.
Go through the northeastern door and head north.
Not when I'm naked, please.
Not when I'm naked.
Don't say it like that.
Jack, I guess you need to save.
I guess so.
Try getting an alert and going back.
I'm pretty sure I have.
It's clock keep changing between 2099 and 2000.
Hang in there.
Time to rendezvous with that man.
Oh gosh.
This part you actually have to be sneaky.
What was the best way to go?
I think I remember.
Okay.
It's time.
Ryden, do you copy?
You must continue your mission.
I've lost all my gear.
I need to locate Snake.
He was never factored into the simulation.
Leave him out of this.
I can't do much naked, especially in this temperature.
That's cold!
That's true.
You won't be able to attack or enter the hanging mode
either.
I think Snake has my gear.
Ryden, take out Solidus and his men.
You must recover Arsenal intact.
Colonel, are you...
under orders from the patriots your role that is mission is
to infiltrate the structure and disarm the terrorists my
role why do you keep saying that why not this is a type of
role-playing game the point is that you play out your part
and I expect you to turn in a perfect performance Colonel I
just remembered something yeah what that I've never met you
in person not once hmm complete the simulation colonel who
are you no more questions we have rosemary what do you mean
by that over and out ride in out i
like this area because all the little rays you can see him
here music here is so crazy oh my gosh you can see my breath
oh Oh, the floor is so cool, too.
Everything about this part is so cool.
Oh!
Ryden, turn the game console off right now.
What did you say?
The mission is a failure.
Cut the power right now.
What's wrong with you?
Don't worry.
It's a game.
It's a game just like usual.
Great timing.
You're wearing your eyes plain so close to the TV.
What?
What are you talking about?
Ryden, something happened to me last Thursday when I was
driving.
home I had a couple of miles to go I looked up and saw a
glowing orange object in the sky to the east it was moving
very irregularly suddenly there was intense light all around
me and when I came to I was home what do you think happened
to me aliens fine forget it oh my god I love this so much
Ah!
Outer heaven.
Oh my god.
Destroy the final weapon.
Metal Gear.
Cochina.
Big Bus.
No.
Oh my god.
Wait, I can't...
Yeah, he's right there.
Oh gosh.
How do I get past this guy?
Hold on.
I'm waiting for him to leave.
I think they're ma...
Oh my god, sorry, I took too long.
Honestly, though, you have played the game for a long time.
I have.
Don't you have anything else to do with your time?
Rude!
Oh, yeah, there's a box over here, actually, though, isn't
there?
Yeah.
Nice.
Okay, I remembered.
Yay, we finally got our zone in the ender box!
Yay!
Okay.
we just wait for this guy to go past oh uh oh
can i not right now oh my gosh i can't hang oh shoot what's
that nothing
actually there is something i have been meaning to tell you
but i just couldn't what's that i think you should know
though what's that on saturday morning last week i saw a guy
leaving rosemary's room how should i put it It was like they
were...
Intimate.
I'm sorry.
What's that supposed to be?
Sorry to bring this up during the mission, but...
Yeah.
Hmm.
Yeah, just...
Exactly.
I can't...
Oh, wait.
I think I can go right here.
Oh, no!
Just a box.
Oh, shit.
Um...
Eee!
Just a box.
I thought I was close enough to the edge.
Oh shit.
I lost my box.
And I lost everything.
Everybody?
I lost it.
This is it.
This is over.
It's over for me.
I don't remember how to get to the stairs now.
There's even cameras.
It's so over.
Can I go underneath here?
No,
but where's the stairs?
Even my patience has its limits.
I just can't leave this thing up to you any longer.
I'll do the fighting.
You can just go home.
Okay.
Sounds good to me, man.
Luke, go ahead.
You do the fighting.
You do the cooking.
You do
the...
Who's there?
Hmm.
Exactly.
No one.
Oh, shoot.
Oh, I'm so...
This is it.
It's over for me.
I don't have a box!
An anemone or Clamatus plant's juice can cause a rash.
When pruning them, it's a good idea to wear gloves.
Oh, shoot.
Um...
Uh...
Variety level 13.
Oh, the giant!
Rescue Merrill.
The return of Gnola!
The giant Gnome soldiers.
Look at that.
Wow!
We are missions!
Yeah?
Granola.
I hear it's amazing when the famous purple stuffed worm in
flapjaw space with the tuning fork does a raw blink on Harry
Carey Rob I need scissors 61 I need scissors 61 when I met
Paul Iding he wrote that on my he wrote that on my thing
without me even asking I was so excited on my poster that I
had him signed president Baker should be somewhere to the
south of where you blasted through the wall there's some
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I do remember.
I had to run into Aria and just got back.
Oh, there she is!
I think I missed something.
Um.
I need scissors.
I was a North American fall webworm in my past life.
That's what I do.
I webworm on the internet.
I'm a webworm.
Oh, yeah, let's stay still.
Let's see if we get the code again your mission is to
infiltrate the fortress Gallowade rescue the hostages and
neutralize metal gear assembly is complete this part is so
awesome this part is so awesome man you got a PSG one you
can use that against sniper wolf sniper wolf and save
Merrill what's going on oh my god it's so creepy great
Crazy!
Actually, I'm in really bad shape financially.
I pay money to my ex-wife as part of our divorce settlement,
among other bills.
I just had no choice but to make you pay for lunch the other
day.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay, Colonel.
It's okay.
Who was he?
Who programmed that?
Who put that in to the system?
Honestly, though.
You have played the game for a long time.
Oh, we got this one before.
Don't you have anything else to do with your time?
No.
Your mission is to infiltrate the fortress Galuade.
Rescue the hostages and neutralize Metal Gear before its
assembly is complete.
No.
I think we've gotten all of them now, right?
Oh, I missed it.
Oh!
Even my patience has its limits.
I just can't leave this thing up to you any longer.
I'll do the fighting.
You can just go home.
I'm in really bad shape financially.
I keep super chatting, me too, for Slay Metal Gear.
I hear it's amazing when the famous purple stuffed worm in
flat jaw space...
It's okay, I like this one.
Okay, I think we got all of them.
I think we got all of them.
I need scissors.
61.
So awesome.
Okay.
We can start ignoring the kernel now.
Hey, babe.
Hello.
Colonel.
Oh!
Ah, Beelink!
Remember what the Gaul said.
No!
She's so...
The graveyards are full of indispensable men.
Beelink!
She's so cute!
You're all alone and surrounded by bad guys.
Try to be careful and avoid getting into a fight whenever
you can.
I actually don't remember when we- when he comes to here.
Jack, it's me.
Oh!
Hi Rose!
Jack, I owe you an apology.
If it's about that conversation just now, I know.
She's so cute.
No, it's something else.
What is it?
That day at Federal Hall two years ago.
Here it is.
It wasn't a coincidence.
I was ordered to keep an eye on you.
Keep an eye on me?
Yes, by the Patriots.
You're a spy?
I suppose, yes.
It's an ugly word.
Are you still there?
Was sleeping with me a part of the job?
I fell in love with you.
How could anyone?
I can't explain Excuse what I did.
I've reported every detail of your personal life to them
these two years.
What you did, said, everything.
Must have been fun.
But some things I didn't tell anyone.
Oh.
Like what I felt for you.
So that's why you were involved in this mission.
I should have known.
Why else would they toss an analyst into the mix at the last
minute?
I'm sorry.
I know what I did was wrong.
I feel like I'm playing with dolls.
No matter where I go, I get used.
myself to suit your tastes hairstyle clothes the way I move
things I talked about you say you love the color of my hair
my eyes they're not even real you must have gone over my
psych profile with a fine-tooth comb how do you change my
job great performance had me completely fooled what I really
wanted was for you to see the real me it hurt to play out
this this artificial romance it was worse to lie to myself
than to you the more love you made the more it hurt contacts
I guess I guess that makes sense to it so it was artificial
on my end too oh it was just a game not the real thing oh
check oh check I feel better knowing that what I was in love
or thought I was with someone who didn't exist.
I was trying to be someone I wasn't by loving what wasn't
real.
I don't know who you really are.
The person I knew isn't real.
She's not the woman I'm talking to right now.
In a sense, the deception was my own, not theirs.
Jack, I thought I was acting because that was my job.
I thought I was acting.
But I did fall in love with you.
That wasn't an act.
I mean, you were acting.
You don't believe that?
You thought you were acting.
acting you had your reasons right hey i understand but i
have nothing left to jack what what i'm i'm carrying i'm
pregnant joe whoa my baby what's going on she's also bad
she's a pregnant oh my god amazing how you walk around like
that Snake!
Been waiting long.
He's so cool!
I love MG!
Phew!
Where's my gear?
Right over there.
There he is.
Yeah!
That's more like it.
Everything you had when you were captured is still there.
Nice.
Oh?
Nano.
Ass shot.
They can't just do that, you know?
Brian coming to terms with his parasocial religion.
Sorry about earlier.
I had to use you as bait to gain access to Arsenal.
It worked.
Why didn't you tell me about Olga?
You didn't ask.
Not happy about that?
Get over it.
Any effects of the virus yet?
Still waiting on that.
So, it was rigged by the Patriots?
Looks like it.
From what I can tell, Arsenal is headed for Manhattan.
I don't know what Solidus is planning, but we'll have to
deal with it one way or another.
There's also a troop of production model rays ahead.
How many units?
25, according to Olga.
Hey, come on.
25!
Can't say I've faced that many Metal Gears before, but I
think we can deal.
Uh, you're gonna be the one...
You're the one who's gonna be facing it, right?
Because we have no other choice.
Right, Snake?
You're the one who's gonna be facing him.
How?
I've stocked up on Stinger missiles.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
Olga left this for you.
20 or the 20 or 20 or the 24.
25.
What's the...
Oh, thanks Olga.
Thanks.
Olga asked me to give it to you.
Besides, I'm not a big fan of blades.
Ask about the bandana, Wyden.
Ask about the bandana.
Jack is back, baby!
Move the right analog stick up and down to make a vertical
slice, and left and right to slice parallel to the ground.
Oh god, oh.
Move the stick in a circle to do a rotating cut.
Oh god.
Push it forward to lunge and strike.
So jank.
You can guard with your blade if you have the L1 button
pressed down.
Okay, L1, L1, L1.
You should be able to deflect a bullet or two.
Okay.
Up, down, up, down, up.
He's gonna stand there or...
Oops, sorry, stay.
God.
Don't be so dramatic about it.
He watched anime?
Yeah.
No, no, no, hold on.
Don't turn and look at me, please.
I'm embarrassed.
Okay.
And then when I run, too, Can I deflect bullets when I run
or is that just...
Killsake.
Oh my goodness.
Oh, uh, wait.
It was, uh...
Oh, that's the jab.
Jab, jab, jab.
Uh-oh.
Wow, thank you!
This was the day Saucy Binto was bored.
Thank you, Alfred.
Thank you.
Also, Yenwei, thank you.
Rose acts weird and needy and possessive.
Rose is also trying to play the role of Jack's ideal girl.
I guess he's into deeply problematic women.
I guess so.
Oh, sorry.
Let's just want to...
Oh, my God.
Whoa, he's breathing in my...
We're so close, I can...
He's fogging up my glasses.
No way.
Wow, we...
you look so cool snake I love the floor in this area so
awesome oh I guess that's it hi come on time to go you weeb
oh if you run out of ammo you can have mine he's got enough
absolutely infinite ammo wait up snake I I love that.
I love that line so much.
Infinite ammo.
Snake, have you ever enjoyed killing someone?
What are you talking about?
I'm not sure.
Me too.
Sometimes it's hard to tell the difference between reality
and a game.
Diminish sense of reality, huh?
VR training will do that.
Do you guys mind if I get food before we continue?
It was field training when I was a kid.
I lied, Snake.
We only have a little bit left of the game.
I have more field experience than I can remember.
this to me riding we don't carry guns to take people down
we're not here to help some politician either you can say
that because you're a legend a hero I'm Jack the Ripper a
dirty reminder a terrible mistake legends don't mean a lot I
was just a name to exploit just like you people will
remember only the good part the right part of what you did
there's no right part at murder not ever and we're Not in
this to make a name for ourselves.
And what are you and Otakon fighting for?
A future?
You can stop being part of a mistake.
Starting now.
Sorry, serious conversation.
What am I supposed to do?
Just change.
Just be a better guy.
Have some of your ammo.
Find something to believe in and find it for yourself.
And when you do, pass it on to the future.
Believe in what?
That's your problem.
Come on.
They're gonna put us mid-fight, aren't they?
I'm just gonna have to pause it and go get food.
Oh.
Maybe?
Snake!
Riding!
Yeah?
You alright?
Yeah.
So we're all the hostages.
That's good news!
How's everything on your end?
All right, for now.
But there is something.
It's quiet.
What?
The Colonel's last transmission.
Transmissions?
Just strange.
No idea.
Interference?
I don't know.
Find a new V2.
Where is this Colonel?
I don't know.
I've never met the man, actually.
I'll dig around.
Thanks.
I owe you one.
Yeah.
If there's anything else, call me on the codec.
I might be able to help.
The frequency is 141.12.
141.12!
Potatoes ready on my desk?
Uh-oh.
Uh-oh!
Lido!
Ninja cyborg.
Ah!
Um, yeah, about that.
Uh, I'm gonna go get food real quick.
I'll be, you guys can listen to this.
I'll turn it down a little bit.
Um, I have some food ready.
Um, so I'm just gonna grab a plate and I'm gonna, um, uh,
eat, eat for a second.
We can, it's a little snack time for a second.
I'm sorry to get really hungry and I don't want to do the
fights while I'm on an empty stomach and I gotta get some
more water so I'll be like right back I'll be right back
I'll be right back thanks guys be our way
your mission is to destroy the shagohan eat some tasty
animals like the purple stuffed worm variety level 16 tasty
thanks colonel
Okay, here we go.
Sorry for the wait.
So sorry.
I'm back.
I've got spaghetti.
I'm gonna like turn down the music just a little bit so
we're not like, so we're not eating in like, um, you know,
battle music and stuff.
Mmm.
Nah, you were the gifted!
That's one, thank you!
That was starting to get so hungry, though.
Good spot to...
Maybe, well, not the best spot, but...
A decent...
Well, we only have this area.
We don't have so much left, honestly.
Just a few more battle sequences, and...
That's it.
You deserve it?
Thank you.
Yeah, I think we'll be able to...
I think we'll be able to...
Finish today, tonight.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, then movie time.
So true.
Though I'm worried about the Metal Gear fight.
Hmm.
A little worried about Metal Gear fight.
But I'll do my my Minto best.
A few more big fights and about an hour of Brain Rock
cutscenes.
Spaghetti!
Yeah!
I wish I could eat this while they were doing the cutscene.
But, you know, that's fine.
We're on normal difficulty.
I don't exactly remember how many.
Minto best?
Yeah, she is.
I think it's a...
I think it was eight.
Right?
I thought it was eight.
Seven or eight.
Yeah.
I think it's eight of them.
So for anybody curious, I remember how they meant it.
mentioned the 25 Metal Gears?
Well, in the harder difficulties, you'd have to fight all
25.
and I believe Kojima probably wanted that to be the case
across the board.
But in the lesser ones, it's only...
It's only...
It's only eight, I believe.
Hmm.
But the timing for it is pretty difficult for me, so...
You do it on hard?
No!
Golly, no.
No, no, no.
You picked up the body armor.
I did!
I did get the body armor!
You're right.
And that's huge for that fight.
Leg then face.
Your reflexes have gotten so much better for this game.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
We've been powering through.
Oh, it's only six?
Ha, thad!
No peak wide to help you.
I miss that guy so much.
Metal Gear Solid 5, I wait for you.
Just for P-Quad.
Do you ever wonder if Raiden was given BB cells?
Like the genome soldiers that Liquid talked about.
I don't think he was, though.
Because their whole thing was trying to raise a soldier like
Big Boss?
Without it being him.
Like...
They wanted to see if a person raised on a battlefield would
turn out like big boss.
Is that spoilers?
We already know that he was raised as a child soldier.
EXP boost the children.
My new kitten likes watching your streams.
Ignore the blue soup.
No, I won't ignore.
Um...
But yeah.
Install mods for MGS5.
I plan on it actually.
I'll be playing on the PC this time.
But I think...
Okay.
Don't judge me for some of these.
I don't know.
Because I've played through the game before.
I might install some like quality of life things.
I don't know.
Maybe like the ones where you know you don't have to wait
for items to be developed and also like the one where if you
grab a soldier, he's already like S++ tier.
Just stuff like that.
It's not cheating.
I already beat the game.
Hmm.
But also, if you guys have any interesting mods,
remove the grind.
Yeah, that's basically the biggest...
issue with it you know i
like the gotcha yeah but don't you you need the only thing
is like to unlock certain things you need like a certain
level don't you with the soldiers so it's kind of like oh
well to unlock it i just need an s soldier not
a deeply unserious mods oh my god i want those oh yeah the
music tape I wonder what song we should put as our as
Pequod.
Sorry, I'm almost done with my food.
Oh, yes, the mod that...
Wait, yes, I've seen...
Or I know about the mod that replaces D-Dog with Ocelot.
Or was it Kaz?
Get the mod that replaces Diamond Dog with Ocelot.
I've never seen it, so don't, like, tag me in it or
anything.
But I've heard about it.
People have told me to get it.
They were like, you should have that one.
I don't even know what Metal Gear is.
Um, I hope you're enjoying the stream.
Um.
Planning on streaming the other MGS?
Yeah.
Between some games, I might take a break.
Just so I can tackle some other game series.
that I want to do.
Like maybe after three or four?
Might take a small break.
Maybe after four.
Because that kind of completes the timeline.
I think after three I'll immediately want to go into four.
So probably after four is when I'll take a break.
No, my...
My breadstick got kind of hard.
Sorry, Ryden.
I must be in peak spaghetti condition.
Mint.
That's me!
Mentally!
Play Metal Gear Rising again?
Of course!
That's the one I have to play the most.
Because now I'll understand it.
For context, I played Metal Gear Rising first.
And, uh, I was like, what's going on?
Who are these people?
Now, I'll understand who these people are, kind of, mostly.
Most of them.
Well, some of them.
Not very many, not very many people that, uh, reoccurring
from the original series.
Oh my god you guys, I got to hear Rules of Nature live at
MGSCon.
And Sam's theme.
What's it called?
Oh gosh, I can't remember.
I just remembered.
There will be blood!
Blood!
Chen!
It was so awesome!
I was head banging and I was like, yeah!
It was so awesome.
The only thing I know for real.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, I'm so sorry, you guys.
I'm so sorry.
I've taken a long time to eat.
Jason Charles Miller looks like a video game character.
He looks so awesome.
He looks like my uncle.
Well, my uncle was in a biker game.
They made us watch VTubers.
The kind's with maids and karaoke.
I still remember the taste of mint they mixed into the food.
Yes.
Nom, nom.
It's cute hearing the plate and the stuff talking.
Stop!
Oh gosh, my desk is covered in postcards, so I don't have a
place to put my plate.
I don't think a cat followed me in, so I'm just going to put
it on the ground.
Okay.
Oh, memories broken.
The truth goes, I've spoken.
I can't even remember my name.
Okay, she lives like this.
I have so many postcards.
So many, so many.
I have like...
Almost 5,000 postcards to sign.
And then I have the last month's...
Or the...
Like, I've ordered almost all of them.
month so yeah is
that for one month no no no that's for five months mm-hmm
well it would have been less it would have been just 4,000
but uh Matara and I this is for the podcast patreon by the
way for anyone wondering um one of the tiers is we send an
autographed, a hand-signed postcard.
And, um, is this the original PS2 version?
Yes, this is the original PS2 version.
Um, but, uh, we have been really bad about sending them out.
Because it's hard for us to meet up and sign them.
So, uh, I've been signing some, and then I'm going to give
them to Matara Atakutan.
And then I'm going to, um, some more and bring them with me
to Japan and then probably mail her the rest of them but uh
but um what was I saying oh yeah we decided the first batch
of postcards of course they got sent and they were like had
this horrible mark on it this scuff mark on it so we decided
that we wanted to reprint them and read or resend them out
so so that's why it ended up being another like a thousand
of them
too scared to say skin marks yeah yeah yeah yeah okay are we
ready
okay l1 block r r3 stabby stab circle circle stab Left,
left, left, right, sideways stab.
Up down, upy stab.
Variety level 7.
Shoot down the space invaders.
Training will have to be postponed if we are invaded by
UFOs.
She's still freaky.
What if we call Otacon?
Now we have this thing.
There's a door at the north end of that coroner.
Okay.
The solidus should be somewhere on the other side.
Stay with Snake and keep north.
Alright, Snake.
Are you here, Snake?
This guy is UFOs.
There's a door at the north end of this corridor.
The enemy's on the other side.
We'll rush it.
Okay.
Here we go!
Wow!
Uh, block.
Unblock.
Oh, wait.
My gun, not gun.
We're...
We're blade time!
Blade mode!
Wow!
Oh, shoot.
Ah!
Stop!
Oh, sorry.
Oh my gosh.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
My Russians?
Oh my gosh.
Oh, hi!
Don't punch me.
What the hell?
Thanks, Snake.
Um...
Run
like this then?
Okay, so I do have to run like that.
I thought it was just running normal.
Huh?
Oh!
Yeah, I'm okay.
I'm okay!
Oh my god, all the blood.
Oh!
Oh, Snake!
Watch out!
Watch out, Snake!
Oh my god.
I'm going, I'm going!
I got this!
Ah!
Is there any more, um...
Oh, um...
Good job, Snake!
I'm just gonna regain my life real quick.
Are you okay, Snake?
Okay.
I'm coming!
I'm coming, Snake!
yourself.
Ah!
Stabby!
Stop!
Come on, this is so...
Oh, okay, good job.
Oh, there's an invisible wall.
Is there anything?
Oh, wait.
We can see them here.
Right!
Metal Gear...
Look at them!
Look at all the metal gear.
Metal Gear Ray!
So much blood.
It's not my blood though.
Look at them!
Oh!
Little baby!
Metal Gear Ray!
Alright, let's do it all over again.
Snake, do you have any rations or...
Otacon, you got any more rations?
Anybody?
Otacon, do your job.
There's a door at the north end of that corridor.
Yeah, solidus should be okay.
I already did that.
Okay.
Oh Oh, oh, I didn't mean to call him again my bad.
There's a if okay there we go Okay
Hello About this kernel of yours.
I found out where he is where here inside arsenal.
I've checked out all the possibilities But I keep coming
back to arsenal.
It isn't a relay point.
It's the origin of the signal The music's so creepy.
The encryption protocol it uses is exactly the same as that
of Arsenal's AI.
The so-called GW.
What the hell does this mean?
I think it means you've been talking to an AI.
That's impossible.
The kernel probably isn't GW per se.
GW was most likely stimulating the protocol activity in the
dormant part of your brain.
Check his fingers!
The kernel is, in part, your own nanomachines.
The kernel is, in part, your own creation.
Cobbled together from expectations and experience.
That's crazy.
He has 11.
But it's probably the truth.
The virus may be starting to affect GW.
What?
Wow.
It was all an illusion?
Everything I've done so far?
Oh, Bryden.
Snake, what's happening around here?
He sounds like he's gonna cry.
What I do know is that you're standing right here in front
of me.
Not an illusion.
Flesh and blood.
Oh, Bryden.
It's your call.
You can drop this if you want.
I can't do that.
Let's go.
Be strong.
See if the hair blends into a shirt collar.
Yeah, yeah.
We're in the colon.
Ryden, they've got Rose.
What?
Rose is being held in the holds.
It's a trap.
How?
Rose!
Why are you still believing him?
But Snake, it's a trap.
Since the Colonel doesn't...
There's no way he can take Rose hostage.
Yeah.
You're right.
I am right.
Yeah.
Okay.
Does Rose exist?
Don't be weird.
What if I've never really met her?
If the Colonel is something that I partly dreamt of, then
everything I remember about her could be...
Don't jump to conclusions.
Wouldn't it be a crazy twist of Snake and Otacon were the
real gas letters?
Ryan!
Is this what Olga was talking about?
Nice.
Don't watch where you're pointing that thing.
Here we go.
Oh.
Oh, wait.
I just remembered something.
Here we go.
Ah!
Oh,
dropping like monkeys!
Maybe I...
You know what?
I don't know why I'm using my gun.
Oh my gosh, I saw this in the...
I'm just gonna use my gun.
Oh, yeah, I can use it on some of them.
Ayy!
Anyway, so I started blasting.
Yeah.
Yeah, take him out, take him out.
Okay.
We get him eventually.
Yeah, out of way, baby.
The sword is overrated.
The sword is overrated, everyone.
Oh, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Ah!
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Ah.
Fish and mailed!
Uh-oh, we're almost out.
Oh.
Ouch, ouch.
Time to change.
To this guy.
You got him.
Oh my god.
I need to heal, but...
Again?
You can't do this to me twice!
Oh my gosh.
My little bandage.
I can't see.
Kojima, please.
Is that a band- a bandage?
I don't have- oh, I never got a cold.
Fishing mailed!
Yeah, that's right.
Oh, that's you, Snake.
Oh my gosh.
Dang, Snake is so fast.
Thank you!
Can you give me your ration?
Give me health, please!
What are you giving me?
More ammo!
Okay.
Uh...
Snake is...
Oh, I got it.
Body armor?
Oh, you're right.
Just eat the bullets.
Fortune!
Oh, she's been...
She's...
She's a...
She's been a long wait, solid snake.
She's seen better days.
Of all my sorrows.
Two years ago you killed my father.
That was the beginning of hell for us.
Everyone I love has been taken from me one by one.
And no matter how hard I try, I can't follow them.
An endless nightmare.
The only thing we live for is to see it end.
Our weight is almost over.
You can't be serious about firing the nuke.
Since no one can kill me, I may as well kill everyone I can.
Damn.
I'm starting.
You suck.
Ah!
Looks like I'm today's pick.
You go on ahead.
Wait!
Isn't two better than one?
Ow, the edge.
Snake!
No, Snake!
You want eternal rest?
I've got him right here.
Say hello to my eternal rest.
What are you going to do?
do bullets can't get near her i'll think of something
there's no such thing as a witch you think you could kill me
she's been why are you been crying but let's get one thing
clear i didn't kill your father do you think anyone believes
your lies right get out of here why don't you tell her who
it was you literally saw it
oh my god snake don't die What a thrill.
Going to go fight the hot girl alone.
Now go.
Here we are, everybody.
Arsenal gear rectum.
Jack, I've been watching how you fight.
It says it on the floor!
It looks like you've remembered the way you used it.
or is it one of the s3 plans proud achievements what are you
talking about what are you talking about it came as a
complete surprise when oselot discovered the s3 data from gw
not a bad idea though using fire to fight fire creating the
perfect assassin to retire solid snakes brother
solid snake simulation it's a development program to
artificially reproduce solid snake the perfect warrior the
result is a foxhound commando when foxhound no longer exists
a simulated solid snake shaped by vr regimen sound like
someone you know jack i'm sorry to see you reduce to one of
the patriots puppets but i've made use of you and their too
solid snakes sudden appearance your arrival it was obvious
the Patriots were among my ranks I had to smoke out the
agent before the mission entered the final phase you came in
handy sorry I doubt you Jack those days during the Civil War
were as real as they come every day was absolute split
between life and death yeah you ran from it and now you've
been led back to war by something less than real look at the
way he rides
sorry silenus no more games jack at least you know there's
no reason to keep you alive now no Papa!
Please, Papa!
I've given you a worthy opponent at least.
But now, you should die as the little Jackie boy I want.
Jackie boy.
Oh!
Come on, come on, Raiden.
You have so many other better weapons.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Um, hold on.
I'm going to use this ration.
body armor.
What is BDU?
Oh, that's the uniform.
The Gurlukovic.
Okay.
Then, we're gonna grab Stinger Missile.
And we're gonna...
Okay, remember how to do this fight.
Ouch!
Remember how to do this fight.
Okay, I remember.
We'll just focus on this guy real quick.
No, I need to get him before...
Oh shoot, I missed my chance.
Oh shoot.
Ouch, ouch.
Get up.
Get up, Rylin, please.
Oh my gosh, I keep missing my chances.
I know I have to hit him in the mouth, but I have to hit
him.
Can I chaff in this part?
Does chaffing work?
I can't remember.
Oh shit.
Oh, I don't think I hit him.
No!
Oh my god.
It does help.
There we go.
Woo!
Holy moly.
Can't get too close.
Stop sending missiles at me!
There we go.
Nice.
So...
I
don't remember this part.
Wait, I don't remember this phase!
I don't remember this phase!
Oh shoot, I don't...
Hold on.
Snake!
Oh wait, no, I should have caught an Otakon.
Oh, sorry.
Otakon!
Otakon, help, help me.
Right.
Aim for Ray's head section with the Stinger missiles.
That's it!
Call the colonel.
CURNON!
The mass production Metal Gear is unmanned.
It's probably under the control of GW, the Arsenal Gear AI.
A chaff attack should cause electronic interference and
confuse Ray for a moment.
Use the opportunity to fire a Stinger into it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
I had I'm so mad because I had the
Guys, I don't think this is the run I'm just saying I don't
think this is the run But
Yeah, he's leaving Oh, that's so unfair That's so unfair,
man Oh, gosh Oh my god, please I just stood up This is so
unfair!
Ah!
You son of a bear!
That was so mean!
I adjusted him!
Where was my... where was my iframes?
Hmm...
Fishing my own...
If only...
Alright.
Um...
Chop.
Ration.
armor.
Chaff!
Oh, chaff!
Oh, that's a magazine!
Oh my god.
Oh my god, oh my god.
What the!
Oh my god.
What are you doing?
I'm so, so... That was really embarrassing.
Okay.
Chaff?
I think the chaffs last a little longer.
Oh, okay.
Oh, shoot.
I just realized.
Um, I did not...
Oh, I didn't I didn't... I didn't...
Oh!
It still works!
Yeah, let's go!
Nice.
Yeah!
Will it work?
Nice!
Okay, bye!
So unfair!
I have no more bandages either.
Oh gosh.
This thing is such a pain in the butt.
Oh my god.
I need the chaff again.
My vision.
Chaff!
Okay.
Now's time to sting on myself.
Hold
on.
I think I need to get that.
Oh gosh.
Chaff again.
Cha!
There.
Those are stupid, silly.
And take him out!
Nice sir!
Okay, I'm gonna grab this.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Next!
Next, please!
Ow!
Oh my god.
No!
That's my waste!
You're such a jerk!
Oh, I don't think that works.
Oh, it did!
It did!
Okay.
And chaff.
Stinger!
Oh, I think I missed.
Oh, never mind.
Ha!
Chaff!
Soon.
Soonish chaff.
Oh, chaff now.
I think I can get, like, two in while...
Okay.
Okay, there we go.
Stinger!
You're close.
You're really close.
Run away, run away, run away.
You're too close, you're too close.
Oh, so unfair, so unfair.
How am I supposed to know which one comes out?
Beep, beep, beep, beep.
Oh, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Ah!
There we go.
Not the great timing, not the best timing, but you know.
Oh, that's the wrong guy.
That's...
Can you give me more traps?
Oh, shit!
Oh, my God.
Nice dodge.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Right where it hurts and right in the kisser.
Nice-oo.
Oh, he's like immune for a second.
Oh, okay.
I think he's better.
There we go.
Okay.
Right in the kisser.
Oh gosh.
Once I'm out of Chaffs, what do I do?
Oh, whoops, I didn't mean to kid that guy.
Oh, shoot.
Run!
Nice.
And kiss him.
Oh, Chaffs, Chaffs, Chaffs, Chaffs.
What am I?
Once I'm out of Chaffs, what do I do?
Wait, oh, he's not done.
Oh, my God.
I came running in thinking he was still over.
Oh, my gosh.
That's so...
Ah!
Um, right there.
Now he's done.
What's him out of chance?
What do I do?
Ouch, ouch.
That's nice, I guess.
Body armor.
Oh, gosh, oh, gosh, oh, gosh, oh, gosh.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, shit.
I was trying to...
I pressed X.
I swear I did.
Oh gosh, okay.
Two more chaps.
Oh,
there we go.
Stinger missile.
Okay, I have a lot.
Okay, okay.
Ray, did I say Rose on accident?
My bad.
Okay, get him, get him, get him.
Oh gosh, though, for real, once I'm out of chaps, what do I
do?
This has been my whole thing!
I'm so bound!
Half
is unnecessary, but it makes it way easier!
It makes it way easier to avoid the beep, beep, beep, beep,
beep, beep, it's one, you know?
Oh, I just shot that into the ether.
There we go.
Oh!
Oh, geochie, geochie, geochie!
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Sorry, I've been, like, staring at the computer screen so
much.
My contacts are drying out.
Get up, Brandon!
Oh, shit.
Oh, my god.
Oh, my god, oh my god.
That's it.
This is it for it.
It's over.
It's so over.
It's so joe over.
Oh, shit.
No.
No!
Can't even aim!
Oh my gosh, wait, we're on Rose!
Oh god, oh god.
Everybody's shooting at me!
Calm down!
Oh, ouchy, ouchy, ouchy.
Oh gosh, but we got him, we got him.
Oh, hello, hello.
Oh, how many more?
How many more?
That was cruel.
So crass!
How many more do I have?
Lose and more samurai!
Just go
quick.
Jack be quick!
Jack be- I have one ration.
Oh, Jesus God.
It's so over.
No, it's so over.
We were doing great boss only because I had the trap
grenades.
Now I don't have the trap grenades anymore.
Oh, gosh, you saved just like a few...
Oh, my God.
I pressed X, but not soon enough, I guess.
What's the point of...
What's the point of even running?
What's the point?
Oh my god!
Oh shit!
Okay, please.
I'm bleeding out!
This is it you guys.
Oh, I don't want to have to do all of it over.
Oh shit!
Riding!
Come in!
Right?
Riding?
How many did I get through?
Like three or four?
I think three or four of them I got through.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, four.
Oh.
You were on the last one?
No, I wasn't.
Oh, God.
Five out of six.
Okay.
One thing I know now is they always come in from the right
side so I need to not a baby actually I don't know I feel
like if I'm on the left side they're gonna hop on top of me
right there oh my tummy hurts okay why
didn't I pick up more chaff grenades can
you get more chaff
nope if
you get the second stinger shot a little faster you avoid
the missiles I I should start shooting the guys in the back
too because they also I don't know I would have to be very
strategic about it because they also like I want to avoid
their missiles as well they're the the beep beep beep beep
missiles are the ones that are really hard to avoid like
they're the ones that make it difficult I think well for me
at least you were doing good until the ray utilized jump
scare tactics
Oh shoot, oh shoot, oh shoot, oh shoot, oh shoot, please!
Oh my god, I'm forgetting controls.
I'm forgetting controls!
Why am I forgetting controls?
Worst time to forget controls!
Oh, it's these.
It's these.
Riden, are you alright?
Yeah, I dodged into it.
It's okay.
That one doesn't count.
Oh my god.
Oh, I missed it.
I missed my opportunity.
I missed my window.
I missed my window of opportunity.
I missed my...
They don't stop coming.
They don't...
Two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
they don't stop coming they don't stop see this is why I'm
just like I can't I can't get a shot in
right what's wrong riding right in
maybe if I do get closer but then they all start blasting at
me are
you gonna come up are you coming up now are you hopping up
No?
Okay.
You're not hopping up.
Look at them.
Look at them staring at me.
Stop looking at me, you!
Stop watching.
Yay!
Oh my god.
Even dodging it does nothing.
Ryan, get up.
Get up, Ryan!
What the?
Why did you duck?
Why did you do that?
Ray down.
Oh my god, no, wait.
Wrong!
He's the guy that's coming next, though, right?
You're coming, yeah.
You're hopping up next.
I know.
I know, I know.
I know your game now.
Oh.
Wait.
I missed it somehow.
Next guy comes walking.
on in.
Oh, I see.
Ah!
Um.
Right.
Come in.
Riding.
What the hell is that?
Oh.
He's so fast when he's here.
You're not coming up yet.
No, no, no.
Yeah.
Now he's coming up.
Oh my god.
Where are my rations?
Oh my god, Brandon, please.
This is so funny.
Why don't I get invincibility?
Just kill me.
What?
I was standing right there!
Riden, come in.
Riden, Riden?
Oh,
ow!
Oh, shoot.
Oh, shit.
Ah, ah.
I forgot to do my Riden.
Oh, my body armor.
Oh, my God.
Please, Riden, move.
Keep going, Riden.
Just get out of here.
Oh, no.
Okay.
Oh, oh, I missed my chance.
And I also...
I also just...
Guys, oh god.
I...
I don't believe.
Why is your eight?
Why are you...
Oh my god, run, run, run!
Run, run!
Oh, thank god.
Ah!
That's one down.
Oh, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
Come on up.
Even with body armor.
Even with body armor, they hit so hard.
Oh my god.
Stop shooting at me!
Okay, oh shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot.
Here it goes!
Riding, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up!
Okay, now it's time to chuff, chuff, chuff, chuff, chuff.
Jeff?
Where's my...
Guys...
Guys, I'm not...
I'm not feeling so good.
Guys, I'm not feeling so good.
While I wait, I should really take out like some other...
I should really do some other things.
Oh, he's leaving.
Oh, shoot.
I missed my opportunity.
I didn't notice.
Ah!
I didn't notice that he was down!
I missed my window of opportunity!
Oh my god, both of you guys.
Ouch!
Why is... Why am I... What's the point of dodging?
If it's... If... Even when I'm in midair, nothing happens.
What's the point of dodging?
Don't fall off.
Don't fall off, Raiden.
you take them out i'm just getting their legs so that they
well hopefully i just realized also i need to jump did i did
i no i didn't there we go okay okay oh gosh
because if they're like you know if they're down then
they're less like even though i'm not They're less likely to
shoot out, you know?
Oh, well that was...
Why do you have so much ammo?
Oh, okay, here.
Okay.
Little waves.
It's fine though, it's fine.
Oh my god!
Oh, shit.
Oh, I still got it.
My ration!
This is three.
Oh shit.
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run.
Run, run.
There's another ration over here.
I wonder if I can get it.
Wait.
Oh, no, that's not a ration.
Oh, Stinger Rocket Bowl.
There's something over here.
Oh, more bullets.
No chap.
Shit.
I have come.
I have you guys.
I've lost it, I've lost...
I've lost everything, I've lost all control.
I give up, I don't want to play anymore.
Ah!
Why don't you run?!
I don't want to play...
I don't want to play anymore!
Oh god, that was so close.
Holy shit.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, get the ration.
No!
I'm sick of this game!
This is a game sucks!
Oh, why did I...
Why did I...
Why?
Oh, I got him still.
Nice.
Take him out at least.
Come on, come on up!
Number four!
Number five!
What's the point?
Okay.
Stinger!
Why am I doing this?
It's all just some simulation!
It's just a simulation!
Oh my god, they gave me another... they gave me another
ration though.
Please.
No!
I missed it!
I missed off!
I messed up, I messed up, I messed up!
Run him in between his legs!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Run him between his legs.
I'm gonna use it now.
Where's my...
Where'd my...
A body armor...
Why are we here?
Just to suffer!
Stinger, stinger, stinger!
Okay, nice to loot!
In the kisser!
Oh, I hope I hit!
I did!
Okay, your turn!
Your turn!
Yep.
In the kisser!
Oh my god, Raiden, Raiden, please.
I hate that mechanic more than anything, I think.
Oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit.
Just stay on the chat.
Okay, there we go.
Tactical, tactical, okay.
Hey,
you, hey you, hey you.
Oh, thank you.
Oh
Which one's next?
Oh, I think I went the trap grenade too early, but that's
okay Stinger Stinger Stinger Stinger.
Oh, uh Stinger.
Oh Stinger Stinger Stinger
Get the, get you, get you, get you, get you, get you, get
you, get you, get you, get you, get you, get you, get you,
get you, get you, get you, get you, get you, get you, get
you, get you, get you, get you,
you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you,
you, you, you, you, you,
Oh, ouchy ouch.
ouchy out.
Come on, come on.
Maybe two more!
Oh, shit.
I actually don't know anymore.
Ciao!
Okay, more.
I thought that was the last one.
I'm not gonna lie.
I thought the other one was the last one.
I'm out of traps.
Of course I am.
Of course I'm out of traps.
Why wouldn't I be out of traps?
That'd be ridiculous otherwise.
Okay, recover, recover, recover.
There we go.
Nice.
Why do you get invincibility and I get nothing jack poopy?
I know I don't need chaps, but I like to have them.
They make it really easy.
They make it so much easier.
Oh!
Oh, I'm so sweaty.
Pyrohawk, thank you.
Or that, not that game.
This fight makes me go bonkers for real.
Feels like I'm just in hell, you know, just never running
hell.
The same thing.
Over and over again.
Olga, don't do this.
They'll know.
Olga!
I hold them off.
Give your time to get away.
What about you?
You did amazing.
Well done.
Thank you.
Thanks for the tangy up there.
Oh, my hands are shaking so much.
Sorry.
Sorry I got a little extra during that fight, you guys.
I'm okay.
I have to, like, talk my...
through those kinds of fights sometimes, you know?
I have to be like, okay, unequip, equip, unequip, equip.
I have to like talk myself.
I have to be like, jump, hi, blah, blah, blah, blah.
It's how I focus.
Oh god!
Don't do it.
Don't do it!
Live!
I think we could have done a second take on that one.
Oh, God.
Oh, gosh, her death is so...
I feel so icky.
Enjoy the show, Jack.
Let's pick up where we left off.
Oh, something's wrong with them.
What's going on?
What's wrong with it?
AI, GW, it's out of control.
Oh!
Ooh, the way they shake is so creepy.
Ew!
So creepy.
I love it.
Oh, God.
They're possessed.
A ghost in the machine.
GW.
Metal ray freaky.
I'm reading an abnormal impulse cascade throughout the
neural network.
I want some chocolate.
What happened?
Maybe some kind of virus.
The Patriots?
I don't know.
Ocelot, what have you been up to?
It's too late.
Arsenal's system control is going haywire.
It's out of an emergency center.
GW equals ghost wife?
The virus.
Oh my god, he's turned superhero.
GW means goat?
George Washington?
No, no, no.
Ghost what?
Ghost woman.
That's mean.
yes how it is why does his gun work on it but not mine
actually I don't know does the gun work on it I imagine not
Otakon told me to use the sting or missiles damn the
patriots damn the patriots
that's all it is even having his little the little snake
hair tuft is just so Amazing.
You still have some use.
What?
Snake!
Snake, I just had to fight off like six...
Metal gears.
All by myself.
I might be better than you at this point.
You had a hindee.
I had a harrier.
I had to fight.
Oh, yeah, it was safe.
Snake spilled his spaghetti.
You lack his charisma.
You know what?
You're so right.
Are you awake yet, Jack?
GW, the arsenal AI is corrupted beyond repair.
I admit that I underestimated you.
The moon.
Oh.
Snake!
I'll squeeze the answers out of you instead, my son.
Oh, oh!
Wait, why isn't it...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, okay.
Oh my god.
If you stop, it'll really go...
Okay, I was like, why is it still going down?
Oh my god.
Is that all it is?
Okay.
Ah!
What do you hope to hear?
be solid but handcuffed by fortune it's not him i want the
answers from i'm gonna look at snake for oh i was gonna say
for for more oh i'm handcuffed what do you mean that's not
your business oh really it so happens i have some business
of my own to attend i like that fortune's the only the only
dead cell left you know you were going to screw me over
weren't you Who talked?
Ocelot?
Not exactly.
I was the one who used Ocelot to suggest the idea to you in
the first place.
What?
I was planning to give you Arsenal to begin with.
Oh, okay.
Why the uncharacteristic generosity?
But it's fine.
I'm no philanthropist.
Arsenal is far from intractable.
It needs other Metal Kieres as guards.
A huge payload of warheads.
And full air, sea and land support to function efficiently.
a large attack force without support arsenal is nothing more
than a gigantic coffin seizing arsenal gear was never the
real objective what what was your objective why does
everybody just create things a list of names of the patriots
oh the patriots they were planning to extend their control
to digital information flow with gw and arsenal that means
the information that they want to filter out is contained in
GW.
Including that list of the highest 12 members of the
Patriots' Wiseman's Committee.
I kinda wanna go get my cake.
And once you knew who they were, you would cross out their
names one by one.
While we, with our useless arsenal, drew their fire.
I gotta finish it sooner, I'll go bad, I think.
You were using us all along.
Oh my God.
Were you any different?
Everybody uses everybody.
But your plans hit a snag with GW destroyed, hasn't it?
Everybody double crosses, everybody triple crosses,
everybody, everybody is just in it for themselves.
No, there is another way.
Really?
But we have our own plans to carry out.
I love fortunes.
We'll take the arsenal since you don't care for it anyway.
The purified hydrogen bomb is ready to go.
A nuclear strike won't stop them.
It will damage their power source.
How is it possible to get so...
So...
First things first.
Attach to characters.
In just a single video game that was what you wanted Even
Batman you see him once good luck and I love him so much
quite enough of that
Oh boy Good riding What exactly do you find so funny Shere
age usually are humorous I played you I played you he's
pointing at everybody played you played you But we're
running a little short on time.
What are you talking about?
I played you.
Everything you've done here has been scripted.
A little exercise set up by us.
Oh, my God.
The S3 plan was conceived as a means to produce soldiers on
Paul with Solid Snake.
Yeah.
That's what I told you.
Otakon and Fortune fell in love.
But the VR training the boy was put through is not the meat
of the project.
I think you think this little terrorist incident is your own
doing solidus This is the s3 training colonel he looks so
mad orchestrated recreation of shadow moses what Ames and
the president's deaths you thought before was the recreation
no no no A computer virus that mimics fox died this whole
game has been the recreation of shadow moses Incidents.
Ames' own nanomachines were used to shut down his pacemaker.
Ah-ha-ha!
I arranged for the appearance of the ninja as well.
Thanks, Peter.
As for the president, although Johnson realized what was
going on, he played out his allotted part.
As for the computer virus, it's a digital game.
counterpart of Fox tie it was also designed to eliminate
every scrap of information regarding the Patriots from GW
your plan was invalid even before execution so yes birds
were paid actors too fat man was a different story he's one
of our own people a sort of examiner we hired to test the
boys progress before letting him tackle the exercise proper.
We had to arrange for Stillman's presence to coax the maniac
and to agree.
Oh.
If the boy had allowed the big shell to be destroyed, this
exercise would have ended there.
Fat man just being his own thing is just so fitting for him.
Fat man is just his own guy.
Given the right situation, the right story, anyone can be
shaped into snake.
even rookies can fight like men of experience even me i can
become like snake an instant creation of genius fiddle and
this training kernel will provide more than enough data to
formulate such a program you dead cell olga you're all
nothing but pawns pawns to create the Also, I've never met
someone that he couldn't double cry.
You and the boy were selected because your relationship
resembles the one between Snake and Big Boss.
Fortune, you and the rest of Dead Cell stand in for the
Foxhound squad that Snake took on in Shadow Moses.
You're the most impressive collection of freaks outside of
Foxhound.
All right, they never met Freaky Phantom.
We've gone to a lot of trouble to set you up against the
boy.
story about purified hydrogen the boy is just the tip of the
iceberg i'm a freak too when i sunk that tanker along with
your old man two years ago throwing your husband in the brig
was a part of it too oh you were told it the eradication of
death cell six months ago was an act of the patriots uh-oh
we provoked and encouraged your hatred never go against a
woman's sword and you opted for we planned just as we
planned orchestrated except for the appearance of the real
solid snake oh he's just he looks like he's like who's it
for you all in our misfortune was just a part of their
project but you can't hit her
Oh, how could...
You're no, Lady Luck.
You have nothing that we didn't give you.
Oh, fortune!
What?
Do you know why no bullet could hit you?
It wasn't magic.
Or some new age mumbo jumbo?
wasn't your psychic talents it was all staged by the
Patriots what can they not do you were being shielded by the
electromagnetic weapons technology that the Patriots
developed oh my your dead cell comrades loved your father
and husband we needed a pathetic wretch like you to keep
them focused you've been our puppet all along just like olga
oh my god no the patriots are just the patriots this
patriots that you were hamming it up as the tragic heroine
thanks to the script that the patriots wrote for you well
what about free will exist indulgence absorbed in your own
misfortune you couldn't get enough of the drama bro he's so
mean i could have died whenever i wanted to Yeah, I guess
so.
Thought I got her in the heart.
Oh, my God.
He's Lady Luck.
Thanks, Raiden.
Now I remember your heart's on the right.
A waste of metal, my dear.
raised was your luck's run out this is the little gizmo
there's no such thing as miracles or the supernatural only
cutting-edge technology wait then how did she didn't oh my
god my ears she didn't have that on did she
can't prevent me from descending what's with the hackathon
oh no the Patriots!
Happy 4th of July!
Time to fight!
25 more rays!
Yippee!
Here's the real boss fight.
Remember the alamo.
Now that I have enough data, all I have to do is retrieve
Arsenal.
And clean up the refuse from the exercise.
Look out, look at his tail.
Ray is just so cute.
Yeah!
Oh, nice.
Good job.
Rules of danger.
That's how we learned it.
Wow.
How's this then?
I love Solidus's outfit.
It's so awesome.
Oh, Fortune!
She stands.
She's still standing.
You're an idiot.
Get the hell away from there.
I told you, your luck's run out.
Take your reward.
It's all the payload Ray has.
Die.
oh my god
100 ray size arsenals or one arsenal size
she's so awesome she is lady look i
love her so much she's so awesome she is lady luck my third
my name is helena doth jackson the daughter of a proud and
noble soldier
i can see my family again
so awesome damn damn So awesome.
Try this instead.
Try this on for size.
Uh-oh.
Oh.
Oh, that's pesky hand of his.
No!
No, not now!
This game just never stops delivering.
It's one thing after another.
It truly is.
Brothers!
Liquid!
I've been waiting for this!
It can't be!
Liquid!
Brothers!
I've been inside this arm all along waiting for the right
time to awaken I love this game so You were inside Ocelot
Yes, a sleeper in the arm of a Patriot spy.
Oh, it was you two years ago exactly.
I was control.
I guess we know who tops Imagine doing an alpha strike on a
one HP and it was like all your information about Ocelot to
your partner and got you out here what you're the only one
that can free me after all after all dramatic pause uh
dramatic pause i'm off to bury the patriots for good you're
drowning in time brother how why do you think i chose oselot
as my host that guy's crazy before i go i have a family
matter to settle with both of you there's room for only one
Snake and one big boss.
Grrr!
Oh, missed every single one.
Good job, Solidus.
Time to say goodbye!
Front bell!
Damn!
The greatest David Hater noise in the entire franchise is
coming I'm excited.
Deep inside.
Edward, stop this thing!
Hey Snake, you coming?
Weeeee!
Yeah!
Like, wait, stop this thing.
Snake was on something this dark.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
We're going to crash right into the city.
Arsenal.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, wow.
False alarm.
Guys, like a glove.
That was so clean.
Oh, now we're here.
Are you guys ready for even more info dump?
Let's go.
I have to go to this place.
Oh, I'm so happy we're at the end.
Oh my gosh, I love the ending of this game so much.
much hit me with it federal hall yeah federal hall
what are you laughing at do you know what day it is today
april 30th april 30th uh actually july 20th
George Washington took office as the first president of the
United States of America 200 years ago today.
And it happened right here.
We were going to declare another independence, the dawn of a
new nation, here.
The end of the Patriots' secret rule, liberation of this
country.
This was where it was supposed to begin.
This is where freedom could have been born.
yep yep all you want is power at any cost sorry I was
checking a text it's not power I want what I wanted to take
back from the patriots of things like freedom civil rights
opportunities the founding principles of this country
everything that's about to be wiped out by their digital
censorship Jack listen to me we're all born with an
expiration date no one lasts forever life is nothing but a
grace period for turning the best of our genetic material
into the next generation yeah the data of life is
transferred from parent to child what is that water that's
how it works but we have no ears no legacy no we brothers
are called les enfants terrible very clone from our father
with the ability to reproduce conveniently engineered out
what is our legacy if we cannot pass the torch your legacy
is a mark of some sort is what you do with your time here
you don't need to have children it's okay when the torch is
passed on from parent to child it is extends beyond dna
information is imparted as well spade or neuter your snakes
they have wait all i want is to be remembered by other
people by history he was a kendall patriots are trying to
protect their power their own interests by controlling the
digital flow of information i want my memory my existence to
remain unlike an intron of history i will be remembered as
an exon that will be my legacy my mark in history okay crazy
pants but the patriots would deny us even that i will
triumph over the yeah he did get rose pregnant and liberate
us and we will become the sons of liberty yeah title drop
baby Are you receiving?
We're still here.
I don't want to talk to you, creepy colonel.
The AI was destroyed.
Who are you?
To begin with, we're not what you'd call human.
Over the past 200 years, a kind of consciousness formed
layer by layer in the crucible of the White House.
It's not unlike the way life started in the oceans four
million years ago.
The White House was our primordial soup.
We are the very discipline and morality that Americans
invoke so often.
How can anyone hope to eliminate us?
As long as this nation exists.
So will we.
Cut the crap!
If you're immortal, why would you take away individual
freedoms and censor the net?
The net!
Jack.
Don't be serious.
Don't you know that our friends have your interests, not
ours in mind?
What?
Huh?
Listen carefully.
Like a good boy.
Rose?
The mapping of the human genome was completed early this
century.
As a result, the evolutionary laws of the human race lay
open to us.
We started with genetic engineering.
Override previous commands.
Generate cute maid.
But there are things not covered by genetic information.
What do you mean?
Human memories, ideas, culture, history.
Genes don't contain.
any record of human history they don't is it something that
should not be passed on should that information be left at
the mercy of nature we've always kept records of our lives
through words pictures symbols from tablets to books but not
all the information was inherited by later generations a
small percentage of the whole was selected and processed
then my books not unlike genes really uh-oh that's what
history is jack but in the current digitized I'm gonna see
all my books.
Trivial information is accumulating every second.
Preserved in all its triteness.
Never fading.
Always accessible.
Rumors about petty issues, misinterpretations.
Slander!
Wait, what about libel?
Preserved in an unfiltered state.
The Count?
It will only slow down social progress.
Reduce the rate of evolution.
Right.
You seem to think that our plan is one of censorship.
Are you telling me it's not?
You're being silly.
What we propose to do is not to control content, but to
create context.
Create context.
The digital society furthers human flaws and selectively
rewards development of convenient half-truths.
Just look at the strange juxtapositions of morality around
you.
The music is crazy.
In order to humanely murder other humans.
Rights of criminals are given more respect than the privacy
of their victims.
Although there are people suffering in poverty, huge
donations are made to protect endangered species.
Everyone grows up being told the same thing.
Be nice to other people.
But beat out the competition.
You're special.
Believe in yourself and you will succeed.
But it's obvious from the start that only a few can succeed.
You exercise your right to freedom, and this is the result.
All rhetoric, to avoid conflict and protect each other from
hurt.
the untested truths spun by different interests continue to
churn and accumulate in the sandbox of political correctness
and value systems everyone withdraws into their own small
gated community afraid of a larger forum they stay inside
their little ponds leaking whatever truth suits them into
the growing cesspool of society at large the different
cardinal truths neither clash nor mesh no one is invalidated
but nobody is right Not even natural selection can take
place here.
The world is being engulfed in truth.
And this is the way the world ends.
Not with a bang, but a whimper.
We're trying to stop that from happening.
It's our responsibility as rulers.
Just as in genetics, unnecessary information and memory must
be filtered out to stimulate the evolution of the species.
This game is too crazy.
And you think you're qualified to decide what's necessary
and not?
They're aware of Twitter.
The Patriots go on Twitter.com.
Who else could wait for you to see of garbage you people
produce, retrieve valuable truths, and even interpret their
meaning for later generations?
That's what it means to create context.
I'll decide for myself what to believe and what to pass on.
But is that even your own idea?
Or something Snake told you.
That's the proof of your incompetence right there.
You lack the qualifications to exercise free will.
so quickly right does something like a self exist inside of
you that which you call self serves as nothing more than a
mess he just gave up come on right of ready-made truths self
is just something used to preserve those positive emotions
that you occasionally feel another possibility is that self
is a concept you conveniently borrowed under the logic that
would endow you with some sense
that someone else tell you all right then explain it to him
Jack you're simply the best and you got there all by
yourself what happened do you feel lost why not try a bit of
soul searching maybe don't think you'll find anything though
I run that all those self is something that you yourself
fashion every time something goes wrong you turn around and
place the blame on something else it's not my fault it's not
your fault in denial you simply resort to looking for
another more convenient truth in order to make yourself feel
better leaving behind in an instant the so-called truth you
once embraced should someone like that be able to decide
what is truth should someone like you even have the right to
decide God you've done nothing but abuse your freedom you
don't deserve to be free we're not the ones smothering the
world you are it's on you right individual is supposed to be
weak but far from powerless a single person has the
potential to ruin the world in the age of digitized
communication has given even more power to the individual
too much power for an immature species building a legacy
involves figuring out what is wanted and what needs to be
done for that goal all this you use to struggle with now we
think for you we are your guardians after all sounds kind of
nice you want to control human thought human behavior of
course anything can be quantified nowadays that's what this
exercise was designed to prove you fell in love with me just
as you were meant to after all isn't that right jack oseline
was not told the whole truth to say the least we rule an
entire nation of what interest would a single soldier no
matter how able be to us the s3 plan does not stand for
solid snake simulation what it does stand for is selection
for societal sanity
my sanity is gone controlling human will and consciousness
what ai summarizer says for the stream is i agree what the
What just happened?
Sold are trained in the image of solid snake.
Whoa, it scared me for a second.
It is a method, a protocol that created the circumstance
that made you what you are.
So you see we're the S3.
Not you.
The game is screwing with you.
For real, that was getting too meta, too meta.
That's crazy.
You heard what President Johnson said.
This GW system is the key to their supremacy.
The objective of this exercise was to establish such a
method.
The difference between submission and rebellion.
I wonder if you would have preferred a fantasy setting.
Ooh, with elf girls.
We chose that back thought because of its extreme
circumstances.
Sorry that.
It was an optimal test for S3's crisis management capacity.
With the mind, trigger, control, and solve this, it would be
ready for any contingency.
Snake is so awesome.
And now, we have our proof.
I did all that.
Fantasy Metal Gear would just literally be Bloodborne.
There are also reasons behind your selection.
Solidus raised plenty of other child soldiers.
Do you know why we chose you over them?
It was because you were the only one who refused to
acknowledge the past all the others remember what they were
and pay for it daily but you turn your back on everything
you don't like you do whatever you like see only the things
you like and for yourself alone what's wrong with that rose
can attest if i don't like it why do i have to deal with it
to see me for what i was i lied to you but i wanted to be
caught you pretended to be understanding to be a gentleman
You never made a conscious attempt to reach out to me.
The only time you did was when I gave you no choice but to
do so.
I was just trying not to.
What?
Trying not to hurt me?
Dear, the one you were trying not to hurt was yourself.
Avoiding the truth under the guise of kindness is all that
you did.
It occurred to you to do nothing but look out for yourself.
Even if you claim that it was for my sake, that feeling was
nowhere to be seen.
In the end, everything was for your sake.
in are you okay exactly why is the ai laughing it's creepy
you're a perfect representative of the masses we need to
protect why is the ai laughing why does it have emotion like
that provided obeyed our orders and did everything you were
told to me the exercise is a resounding success the snake
actually ever there in the oil did you tell me the gw was
still incomplete but not anymore thanks to you emma your
persona Experiences, triumphs, and defeats are nothing but
byproducts.
The real objective was ensuring that we could generate and
manipulate them.
It's taken a lot of time and money, but it was well worth it
considering the results.
I think that's enough talk.
It's time for the final exercise.
Oh, yeah.
Brighton, take Solidus down.
Wait!
Think again.
I'm through doing what I'm told.
Oh, really?
something um if you die yeah i was gonna say olga's baby the
ai talk using the ai voice not to mention the death of rose
she's wired the same way what rose does she actually exist
of course i do jack you have to believe me belive me solidus
at least once you dead we will collect the necessary data
Leave me.
Then we'll consider the exercise closed.
So, Jack the Ripper?
Jack the Ripper?
Will it be Solidus, the Patriots' creation?
Or you, Solidus' creation?
Our beloved monsters, enjoy yourselves.
Oh, God!
Chills!
Oh, the last line is just so...
Oh!
My God!
My son.
my clone brothers and I are called monsters replicates of
evil genes you are one of a kind but still a monster shaped
by a dark and secret history we need to decide which
monstrosity will have the privilege of survival by the way
Jack this part is so funny I was the one who killed your
parents By the way, man.
I claimed you for my own and raised you as a soldier in the
army of the devil.
I am your foster father and your worst enemy.
The timing is crazy.
Because I needed to know whether we were really someone
else's creation.
We're repeating history, Jack.
Liquid and solid hunted down, big boss, trying to sever the
tie that bound them to him.
Unless you kill me and face your past, Jack.
You will never escape.
You'll stay in the endless loop.
Your own double helix.
Little baby.
It looks just like paws.
It's time we were both free.
Oh!
My hands!
Are free!
Here we go, everybody.
Final boss fight.
Let's do this.
No guns.
I have other reasons for wanting you.
Actually, I don't remember.
I don't think I can use guns in this.
The clues to the Patriots inside GW have been erased.
But there are other traces.
Ooh.
Inside you.
What?
The information is being carried by the nanomachines in your
cerebral cortex.
And throughout the neural network they've formed.
I forgot about it.
What?
That's crazy.
Why do you get two swords?
Here we go.
I don't
remember how to fight.
Oh.
Oh shoot.
Oh my god.
Okay, I have body armor.
What else do I have?
Nothing.
Okay.
I have my dog tags and one ration and I can become a
Grulukovic soldier.
Why did they give me that of all things?
Ah!
That's how I fight.
That's right.
I remember now.
Stabby!
Stop!
Whoa!
I'm on fire!
There's an additional ration.
Oh, there is?
On the edge?
Oh, I see it.
What's wrong with you?
Oh my god.
I don't remember how...
I think I beat this last time in one try.
I don't remember how the hell I did that.
Come on, get up!
Get up,
Ryan!
Probably by hitting him.
Probably.
Yeah.
Oh shoot.
Oh my god.
Oh I can't.
I hurt him.
I'm dumb.
That's why.
I'm dumb, Dad.
You gave me gunpowder!
Why can't I get a hit in ever?
Oh my god.
Or it can block.
Like that.
Oh.
Get up.
Nice.
Oh!
Is that the best you can do?
Hee!
Oh my god.
It's so...
janky oh my god this sword is so janky oh my god sweep
sweep i'm trying to get his right side since that's where he
has the the eye oh oh my goodness
you have to keep it tight i'm trying It's funny to hear him
laugh at me, though.
What can I say?
I'm not a weeb, like everybody else.
I think I got the most hits by...
Oh, oh shit.
Forgot to do L1.
Oh, nice.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, shoot.
Okay.
There we go.
Yeah, who, ha, he's...
No!
What the hell?
Oh, that's right.
I can hold...
I can hold L1, right?
Oh my god.
I just end up turning around.
It's so funny.
Shoot.
Oh shoot.
I missed my chance again.
Oh!
I got him.
Yeah, I'm the one who hitting you.
Woo!
Why?
The sword is... Oh my god.
Oh.
Ah!
Never mind, L1 doesn't do anything there, you guys.
I lied.
L1 doesn't do anything there.
L1 doesn't do anything.
After this, you'll be ready for Dark Souls.
Oh my god.
No, no, no.
How did I beat this first try before?
What's...
That was built different back in the past.
Oh, ouch.
Oh my god, I'm on fire again.
I think I just gotta...
Oh my gosh.
I think I just gotta avoid them.
I think you have more rations.
Uh, that might be the case.
Okay.
Oh, it wasn't interesting before.
Oh, yeah!
I'm working on it!
Why are you calling me?
Some simulation game, you know.
Yes, you are.
You're nothing but mere weapons.
No difference from fighter jets or tanks.
He had that grandpa angle when grandpa facetimes you Both of
these are the same as the code names used by the US Armed
Forces to refer to Japanese warplanes during World War II
Your code name Ryden 2 comes from the Japanese Navy's name
for one of its interceptors stop it.
I'm not a weapon Oh, really?
Do you know the code name?
Why are you guys so quiet?
For the Japanese fighter Ryden it was Jack Both of you are
just weapons to be used and thrown away.
He looks so defeated.
Don't cry.
Oh, I see a tear.
Oh, don't cry, Ryden.
And the weapon has no right to think for itself.
Don't cry!
Now, it's time to fulfill your purpose.
I'm working on it!
Now I'm out of the groove!
Oh my god.
Oh, ouchy, ouchy, ouchy.
Oh, I was holding L1, though.
I was holding L1.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
Hold on.
Guys.
Oh, my God.
Ah!
I don't think this is it.
I don't have any more health.
I didn't see.
Unless they give you more rations.
Do they give you more rations?
And part...
Ha, riding.
Call Aticon?
Okay.
Let's call him now.
What is he?
gotta say.
Brighton, you don't have a lot going for you with just your
bare hands.
You have your own blade.
Use it.
Okay.
What an asshole.
You know what, Hanukkah?
Wow.
Brighton, take Solomus down.
Think about Olga's child and your Rosemary.
You must win.
Nice angle, Grandpa.
Okay.
Oh, shoot.
What the?
What's wrong with you?
Ah!
Wait, I was...
I couldn't move!
Oh my god.
What the hell?
Oh, there we go.
Oh my god.
I'm, like, pressing X.
And he's lying down.
What are you doing?
Oh my god, these things again.
Oh, oh!
You guys, I think I'm in trouble.
I need more rations.
I don't have enough.
I'm not good at sword fight, you guys!
This is so janky!
Oh my god.
Okay.
Thank you.
How
can you still do fire also?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, that was weird.
Sorry, my...
It wasn't attacking anymore.
Oh, my God.
Thank goodness you approved your group strength.
Does that really make a difference?
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna fucking lose my brain cells with this guy.
Maybe stab.
Just remember the basics of CQC.
Yeah, totally.
applicable in this fight totally applicable L1 doesn't do
shit this fucking game, I swear to God I
did when I press X I really need you to, I really need you
to cart wheel away, okay buddy I really need you to do it,
please I just really need you, oh God oh my god oh my god
oh, oh oops, there we go Please!
He sounds like an actual snake when he goes
I hate the sword!
Oh my god, I hate the sword!
Oh my god.
Oh my god, no!
I sometimes you stab and sometimes you jump, right and right
away!
Oh god!
Ride it.
Ready to give up, Jack.
Yeah.
Can you give me another ration, please?
Something.
Oh, my God.
So, I have a question.
If I do left on the joystick, am I...
Oh, right.
Shut up, Colonel.
Am I swinging to the left or am I swinging to the right?
Hold on.
Because people are, like, go towards...
See, I'm...
I can't tell.
That was...
The first one was...
What?
Okay, hold on.
Okay, so if I go right, I swing from the right.
There we go.
Like that.
Okay, okay.
But it doesn't really do much.
And also, sometimes it inputs us up, up, and I don't know
why.
Ow, child.
Nice.
Oh!
Ow, child.
Okay.
If you ask me too, I would...
I got nowhere else to go.
It was either that or the...
Why do you have missiles?
Why can't you... Why do you have missiles?
Hold on, I'll just start over.
Yeah, I'm already gonna go out.
I hate Colonel.
He's pissing me off.
Oh my god.
Why sometimes?
I can do it from the right, and it seriously, the input
says...
What's wrong with my controller?
What's wrong with this game?
Wait!
Why if I swipe right, it says I'm doing up!
Oh my god.
I can't.
Come here.
Oh my god.
Okay.
I'm so tired, you guys.
I'm so tired.
I'm standing up.
Oh, you were doing...
You were doing less damage to me as I was laying on the
ground like a fucking potato than me actually moving.
Are
you gonna launch missiles at me?
Side!
Rice, why have I done like no damage?
You're mad.
This is so stinky.
What's wrong with you?
The left side.
Right side.
That's me and you.
Hey.
Okay.
Let's go.
All right.
I don't know.
How?
How did I do this?
First time last time.
I must have been.
I must have been an absolute like.
Oh my god.
But the Nirvana.
I don't
like doing the the pierce because it takes too long to to
recover from it
nice R2 wait there's R2 ah oh my god oh shit I'm dying oh
my god
Why is he have such a big health bar, too?
So unfair.
Oh my god, please.
Every time I try to grab your eyes.
That move is so OP.
You already have my oxygen.
Why do I have to also...
do i also have to be slammed on the ground oh my god i can't
see it when i'm i'm stabbing him but like i'm getting the
angle wrong obviously but i'm like how how am i supposed to
the camera angle is just so funky oh my god why did why do
you turn around oh like i'm not even moving
oh i almost ran into that this is so messed up this is so
messed Stokes, all it is.
I wasn't worried about this fight, but now I am.
Oh my god.
Can we not have the camera angle change while I'm running?
And while he decides to do that?
Hey, but like, I've tried blocking stuff and it wasn't
working, so I don't know.
Okay.
I really, though, you guys don't need you guys to be like,
oh, do this, do this.
You know?
It's okay though.
Oh my god.
Oh!
Yippee!
Why
are you still going?
I'm dead!
Gosh.
This
is so stupid.
So when he goes above, I wonder if he goes above, I wonder
if he goes above.
I wonder if I can block that or if it's just two.
I'm on fire.
Oh, and not.
How am I alive?
We die.
Thanks for the gift, dude.
Why do you sometimes do more than what?
Sometimes you do.
Oh my god.
I can't read them at all.
What?
What's wrong with you?
And one hit!
Oh,
it's so strong.
I just gotta do a little frustration cry.
I was like, I'm not worried at all about this fight.
I did it in one shot before.
I think I'm just tired.
Since I've had a long week.
Sorry.
Need food?
No, I'm good.
I already ate.
I ate earlier.
Liquid had some sense of honor and fair play to face off
compared to Solidus, right?
Well, kind of.
I mean, Liquid still went into the Metal Gear against a
singular man.
But it was more even in the car fight.
One singular man.
I'm gonna go get some water.
I'll be right back.
Okie dokie.
I got some honey water.
I don't want to drink tea because it's kind of late.
No.
Yummy.
Yummy,
yummy.
Okie dokie.
I'll try to block more.
And...
Um...
I'll try to beat him.
Skill issue, something, something.
Get behind them.
Yeah, I've been trying.
He's a slippery snake.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Great start, Ryden.
Oh, see, like, that?
When I try to...
Okay, when he does...
When he revs up for that...
Oh, see, I will...
Okay, I was holding L1 there.
Oh wood, I promise.
Oh, it does work.
That works.
Okay, let's see what...
Let's see what he can block.
Okay.
Oh, okay.
Oh, oh, what the lag?
Okay.
Oh, shoot!
I turned!
Ah!
Wait, where's that ration?
There it is.
Okay, the angle of the block has to be extremely specific
then.
Oh, come on.
I'm blocking!
Oh, that didn't work.
I'm on fire.
No, I'm not.
I'm blocking!
Oh!
Okay, so I cannot block the over overhead one.
That's good to know.
Oh, shoot.
Wow.
I'm blocking.
Oh, ah!
Sorry, I just realized which one it was.
I'm blocking.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
What's that?
Yeah, you scared of my...
Don't laugh at me.
Don't laugh at me, solidus.
I'm blocking.
What the?
Why do you block back?
I'm on fire.
I'm blocking.
Oh.
I'll never learn my lesson.
Yeah, you afraid of my sword?
Why do you look so tiny in that thing?
Why is he look...
Is he really that small?
Is Raiden really that tall?
I can't.
I can't tell.
Oh my god.
Okay, if it's the other side, He's gonna sweep me.
But if it's the left side, he's gonna...
Oh, like that!
Oh, see, see, see, see, see, see, see, see, okay, okay.
I'm just testing how to get used to...
Okay, okay.
Okay.
I'm blocking.
Hang in there, Minto.
Thank you.
Oh.
I guess I'm...
I should probably like yeah triple oh I can't see myself oh
my god can't block those what's wrong with you solidus
is 511 according to Google what he's not tall but he look
how tall is right in then I'm blocking I'm blocking I'm
blocking and you're blocking too and i'm blocking and you're
blocking and i'm blocking and you're blocking and i'm
blocking and you're blocking and i'm blocking and i've got
you in a corner oh shoot you swept me you side swept me oh
and i'm blocking and you're blocking and i'm blocking hey no
offense oh
i'm blocking and you're blocking Oh, and I'm blocking!
And you're blocking!
Oh my god.
Oh, I'm blocking, and you're blocking, and I'm blocking.
Yeah, I'm blocking, and you're blocking, and I'm blocking.
And now you're blocking, and then I block, and then you
block.
Ah!
Nice!
I probably shouldn't stand so close to the guy.
I'm blocking and then you're blocking and how could you even
triangulate like how can you maybe if I oh shoot I'm
blocking oh no die oh I'd never learn my lesson oh it's
so unfair oh there we are I'm just chipping away I'm just
chipping away I'm gonna block, I'm blocking.
Yeah.
What?
Oh!
Nice.
I'm blocking and you're blocking.
I'm blocking.
Yeah, maybe we could do that the entire rest of the...
Oh, shit.
Oh, you missed.
And I'm...
Oh, shit!
I missed too!
Oh.
God,
I can't, I can't see.
Oh, God.
Oh, oh, how did I make it?
How did I live?
I'm blocking and you're blocking.
Oh, nice.
Do
I have any rations left?
No.
The game says, get good.
Get good, lady.
Oh, one more!
Nice!
blocking when you're running away
yep oh we're standing here
oh wait face two face two standing here i realize that i
don't like to play Resorbs.
Oh, where was I?
Oh my god.
Oh.
Uh-oh.
No, no.
Please, Solidus.
I don't have any more.
I don't have any more rashes.
I'm gonna bleed out.
Solidus.
I'm gonna bleed out!
Oh, God, I've gotta bleed out.
Solitus, I'm gonna bleed out!
I'm gonna bleed out, Solidus!
Solidus, I'm gonna bleed out!
Ouch, oh God, Solidus, I'm gonna bleed out!
1 HP and a tree!
Yeah!
I would like to thank Honeywater.
You are lost.
Thank you, Irvin.
Thank you.
Okay, someone should really get right in some bandages.
You got animated.
It's only when we're backed into our toughest corners.
What does he say there?
I think he says, it's the crazy frog.
Honey water.
Bleeds out mid cutscene
Oh seven
Oh so good You know how to make a boss battle exciting Yeah
I totally Totally was on purpose David thank you for the
five gifted Thank you
I want to go there and I want to Lay where Saul had just
died Great job boss thank you Andrigus Thank you!
Yay, we beat it today, you guys!
Yippee!
Oh man, struggled quite a bit in the last two moments, but
that's okay.
Last two fights rather.
Yippee!
Code name boomers.
Who am I really?
No one quite knows who or what they are.
Oh, snake!
The memories you have.
This ending is so trippy.
Our burdens you had to carry.
It doesn't matter if they were real or not.
That's never the point.
It is rude.
the world as absolute reality most of what they call real is
actually fiction huh what you think you see is only as real
as your brain tells you it is then what am I supposed to
believe in hmm whatever you want to believe in believe in
whatever you want to believe in tell other people about
having faith what we had faith in.
What we found important enough to fight for.
It's not whether you were right or wrong, but how much faith
you were willing to have that decided the future.
The Patriots are a kind of ongoing fiction too, come to
think of it.
Make the victory all more rewarding.
Congrats, Pinto.
Thank you.
It didn't feel like I was going to win because I kept saying
I'm going to bleed out, saw it is.
Decide for myself.
you choose will be you i don't know if i can i know you
didn't have much in terms of choices this time but
everything you felt thought about during this mission is
yours and what you decide to do with them is your choice so
what did ryden do in between being a child soldier and this
a new name new memories choose your own legacy it's for you
to decide cap of what happened sure I could try it's a
little funky you know by the way what is that oh my dog tag
dog tags that's my birthday anyone you know Yeah, it's me.
No, I've never heard the name before.
What?
Ryzen!
I'll pick my own name and my own life.
I'll find something worth passing off.
I'll pick my own name continues being Ryzen.
They taught me some good things too.
I'm getting freaked out seeing my name and the tags after
forever got married.
We've inherited freedom from all those who fought for it.
We all have the freedom to spread the word.
Even me.
Snake, what about Olga's child?
Don't worry.
I'll find it.
I count on it as long as you keep yourself alive He's safe
Do you know where liquid went?
I put a transmitter on his red.
I don't think snake knew the gender of the kid, right?
But I have a feeling they gave us a lot of bogus location to
begin with you know Cheer up we have a better lead This
contains the list of all the Patriots what?
But Ocelot took it.
The one we gave you wasn't the real thing.
I'm just gonna hold it up in public, you know?
This virus is coded to destroy only a specific part of GW,
namely the information about the Patriots' identity.
Which means that there's a parameter coded in here that
defines what that information is.
I get it.
Analyze the code, and you can probably find out where they
operate.
Count me in.
No, you have things to do first.
You have a lady to please.
And people you need to talk to.
And a lady to talk to.
Okay, everybody just go about your business.
Don't worry about the dead president behind the statue.
Rose!
We're just gonna...
She's like, howdy!
You've got furniture to buy.
Rose.
His skull suit in this part looks so...
It looks so much like the sneaking suit in three.
Her bird!
What's wrong?
A lot of things, actually.
She isn't an AI.
No, she's real.
who am i really I wouldn't know but we're going to find out
together aren't we it's better for your circulation yeah
smusher see me for what I am okay a dummy I know what are
you an idiot sandwich oh my the baby there's
still more cutscene and then one of the credits play do you
remember this place oh god of course this is where we first
met I remember now I remember now today is the day I met you
that's it how could you forget
happy April 30th everybody Oh,
happy birthday to my favorite idiot guy, my favorite idiot
couple.
I think I found something to pass along to the future.
I mean, you're having a baby.
You're passing along...
You're passing along plenty.
Are you talking about the baby?
Yeah.
But genes aren't the only thing you pass on.
There are too many things that aren't written into our DNA.
Rose, I...
It's up to us.
I made history.
I killed the president.
An ex-president.
What kind of things?
About the environment.
Our ideas, our culture, poetry, compassion, sorrow, joy.
Oh, sorrow and joy.
We'll tell them everything together.
Is that a proposal?
Oh, this is for your ears only.
Yay!
Rizden.
Oh, my gosh.
Don't worry, there's still more to go.
There's still more talking.
Oh wait, it's after the credits.
Just kidding.
Um...
Yippee!
And think...
What am I made of?
Am I full of sorrow?
Am I hurt?
pain or am I filled with love yeah Kojima and Tomokazu
Fukushima yeah Tomokazu Fukushima
yeah Fukushima Sun thank you for thank you for guiding
Kojima Love watching your playthroughs every time.
Thank you!
Okay, after the credits, after we get back to the main...
The main menu, I'll explain for people who are like, I don't
know what's happening.
I'm so confused.
Kill the ex-president, was assaulted by the current
president.
Who can top that?
M was there for the current president's death, too!
What a grim reaper.
Thanks for playing one of the best Metal Gear games.
I wonder where that Pliskin fellow went.
I miss him too.
Yeah, me too.
Inner peace, not war.
The dreams that I let slip away.
I will find the joyfulness I'm looking for.
Out of the MGS game song Where would you rate this one?
Better than the best is yet to come?
Hmm.
They each make me feel something different, you know?
I love this one because I just really love jazz.
But it also just makes me...
I don't know.
Each game's theme song makes me feel something different.
This song in the feels.
I know.
But I really do love this one a lot.
I
put it above Heaven's Divide, but not calling to the night.
I really do like calling to the night.
A lot, a lot.
I think like one and two's themes.
I don't want to say themes, like their songs.
Really make me feel like this nostalgia.
Are free.
Little sounds of laughter.
A smile, a kiss from you to me.
Ah.
Love, love, love, love.
Again, they all make me feel something different.
Love, love.
Me by...
This day...
For a while...
Chris Zimmerman!
Yeah!
Voice over director Chris Zimmerman!
She is such a genius at directing, my god.
Say goodbye to yesterday, my friend.
Yippee!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Chris the goat.
And her husband is Acelot.
Yeah,
yeah.
Patrick Zimmerman.
Revolver.
Power couple.
Oh, ex-husband.
So, I'm so sorry.
My bad.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Anyway.
day.
Double crossed again.
No, no, no.
Planning, game design.
Hideo Kojima.
Yoji Shinkawa.
Yeah.
Tomokazu Fukushima.
Look at all those people in the script.
Crazy.
Crazy, crazy.
And what a crazy script it is.
What a crazy script it is.
It is.
So crazy.
Nakagawa Shoko.
Not like Shoko-tan, right?
No.
Right?
Skateboarding theme!
Wait.
Wait, is it actually Shoko-tan?
I don't think so.
Oh, what?
Wait, you're...
Ghost Babel.
Wait, I don't remember seeing a Ghost Babel's poster.
Oh, wait.
Was it in the...
The...
Yeah, she would have been really young.
Yeah.
Because she's in, like, her mid-30s now, I believe.
This game came out, what, 2001?
Yeah.
I think she would have been too young.
That's a funny...
A funny, uh...
Quinky thing, though.
Congrats, Minto!
Seven hours of grinding.
There's some struggles he pushed your way through
frustration to finish it today.
Yippee!
Thanks for another awesome MGO stream.
Thank you!
Okay.
Let's finish it up.
Ah, the song is so good.
Riden is... Rose is real and Riden had a girlfriend.
It's the most unbelievable part.
I mean, he's, he's a good looking guy.
He's just got to work on his personality.
We can leave behind much more than just DNA.
Through speech, music, literature, and movies, what we've
seen, heard, felt, anger, joy, and sorrow.
These are the things I will pass on.
Yeah.
That's what I live for.
Snake, you're so awesome.
We need to pass the torch.
And let our children read our messy and sad history by its
light.
We have all the magic of the digital age to do that with.
The human race will probably come to an end sometime, and
new species may rule over this planet.
Earth may not be forever.
But we still have the responsibility to leave what traces of
life we can.
Oh.
Building the future and keeping the past alive are one and
the same thing.
He's so awesome.
He's so wise.
Snake, solid snake.
The squirrels will rule.
This is implying the squirrels will inherit the earth.
Yay!
One second.
Oh.
Snake, you there?
It's me.
I've finished going over that disc.
did you find the Patriots list of course it contains the
personal data of 12 people oh there was a name on it snake
it was one of our biggest contributors oh what's going on
around here I don't know anyway where are they well we were
right about them being on Manhattan but but what they're
already dead all 12 of them what did it happen well about a
hundred years ago What the hell?
Oh my god.
Whoa!
Yay!
Wow, I saved and continued the same amount of times.
I killed 72 persons!
Oops.
But I only alerted 16 times.
It's not so bad.
I'm an elephant!
Oh, sorry.
I'm reading some of these codes.
I'm an elephant.
Yuppie!
I think I always get elephant.
Fucky-wookie.
Zool.
Yubay.
Nice.
What'd I get?
Yay, I got the camera.
you way
and now the screen changes to rider oh god this music this
this title Music is so, oh, it sets the tone of the game so
well.
It's, oh my God.
I love MGS2 so much.
I'm going to press the start button though, so we don't loop
through the.
Oh my gosh, Ray.
I never noticed him there.
Unless he wasn't there before.
I don't know.
Um, such a good game.
Oh, so good.
Freaky elephant sounds like an MGSV code name for a random
guy or a group.
Truly.
So yeah.
The end of the game is pretty wacky, huh?
There were some people maybe who...
Sorry it took so long.
The ending cutscenes are so, so long.
Some people who are just like watching for the first time
and are just like, I'm so confused.
So basically, from what we learned in this game, Solidus had
this thing.
called the S3 plan in which he was training child soldiers
to try and become like solid like to become like a solid
snake right they want to see if people can become like oh
wait what yeah mini snakes they all wanted little or the
Patriots sorry I'm a well solid okay hold on sorry Sorry, my
brain is so mush right now.
Okay, so, hold on.
Because there were multiple S3 plans, you know?
There were multiple S3 plans.
Everybody had their own, basically.
Everybody had their own S3 plan, you guys.
Because they all talked about it.
Ocelot had one, Solidus had one, and the Patriots had one.
So, that's why it's kind of weird.
And...
Do you have one?
Hmm, what would my S3 plan be?
Hmm...
Does Olga's baby have one?
Yeah.
Olga's baby had one.
I think everybody should have an S3 plan.
Everybody, start feeding your children gunpowder, okay?
Super sexy stakes.
yeah basically but anyway solidus was raising his little
children's child soldiers to become uh you know powerful and
if they could become you know if they're raised in a certain
condition if they can become like snake and um then ocelot
was just like actually i double crossed you uh and um and uh
Solidus's thing was just like, yeah, yeah, they raise in
certain conditions.
And Ocelot was like, actually, I double crossed you.
This whole video game was my S3 plan.
And actually, the whole big shell was the S3 plan because it
was exactly like Shadow Moses.
And then the Patriots' S3 plan is just like, what?
the sanity thing.
I don't even know how to describe it.
Where does the White House soup come in?
The primordial soup.
Yeah, nature versus nurtured, then mind control.
Their sanity plan.
But we find out that basically...
Colonel the whole time was part of this program called G2.
w which is part of the patriots and um is this ai that the
patriots are like this overseeing ai or group of people that
um that are able to control everything i guess in the world
and what they really want is because the digital age is
rising they want to control digital media before they were
able to control stuff.
But now that digital stuff is becoming more prominent, they
were like, we must control the digital media as well.
I don't think Mint knows what she's saying.
What?
What are you talking about?
I know what I'm talking about.
They want to moderate Twitter.
Yes, they want to moderate Twitter.
And, uh...
and um so ridden from just being a little baby he was always
basically just he never was able to make his own decisions
and he thought that falling in love with rose was his own
decision and no she was a plant um and she does actually
exist but um the rose at the very end when she's like
talking going back and forth with the kernel that's ai rose
she's not real but Up until then, she's real, you know.
But he can do flips.
Um, wasn't Rose AI the whole time?
No, I don't think so.
I thought she was only AI at the very end.
I mean, if so, they gave...
They trained that AI so well.
They made that AI insufferable.
Yeah, real Rose is cut off.
after she says she's pregnant.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
She's real up until that point.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And so, um, yeah.
Um, that's basically it.
That's really it.
Solidus was just like, no.
I want to, I want to be remembered.
Meh, meh, meh.
So he didn't want to be erased by the Patriots, essentially,
I guess.
I don't know.
So he was like, down with the Patriots.
And, um, am I real?
Does GW win?
I mean, at the end of this, kind of, yeah.
GW does kind of win at the end of this.
The Patriots got what they wanted because they wanted
Solidus dead and they got it.
they had the virus in them so you know they have the virus
was kind of like sleeping through them so yeah but there's
other Patriots so they prove the s3 plan could work I know
we're all just we're all just pawns and the Patriots plan so
if anything bad bad ever happens to you don't blame yourself
blame the Patriots blame the Patriots for it's their fault I
don't understand but pog what how I don't know how much easy
how much more easily I can explain it to be honest why did
they say that the Patriots died a hundred years ago though
well we'll have to play the other games to find out it's a
mystery Yeah.
Yeah.
This is why we need the MJS podcast?
Oh.
Explain in the form of a caffeinated karaoke stream.
I need...
Actually, I don't need any caffeine right now.
I'm ready.
I'm like, my eyes are droopy.
Patriots are basically the physical embodiment of the memes.
That's what they meant by.
They are American culture.
They're the memes.
Yeah.
Was the Colonel at any point part of the Patriots?
Like, the Colonel, the A- the Colonel in this game?
The Colonel in this game the entire time was GW.
Are you playing MGS3 on PS2?
Yeah, oh yes, I am actually.
I will be playing Subsistence.
You are.
So, we'll get that hidden cutscene that happens in MGS3.
The game within a game.
Something I really love about this game is how the theme of
censorship and controlling information is exactly what they
did with Ryden and hiding his existence from all commercials
and from...
Whoa!
Yeah, you're right!
So meta.
Patriots stressed out and overworked by Oshi.
Unforgivable.
But yeah, I'll be playing...
I'll be playing the PS2 version.
It's funny because I was just like, oh, if I'm going to be
gone in Japan for a whole month and I won't have my PS2 or
anything like that, what if I played the 3DS version?
But the 3DS version of Metal Gear Solid 3, but I was like, I
don't think I want to put myself through the torture,
probably.
Even though Patriot's AI speech is relevant today, I'd say
Snake's final speeches are also very important to learn and
use in our lives.
It's so true.
Snake is so wise.
He's so awesome.
I love Snake.
Oh, my PS2 clock battery.
Oh, you're right.
I don't think it's dead.
I think I'm just going to probably put it on like a random
date and see what happens.
I think it's getting mixed up because it's going back and
forth between 1999 and 1999 and...
2000 it's kind of weird
snake is very philosophical i know solid snake is like
really he's such a good person i love that guy um but uh
oh i'm so tired oh i was so tired yeah we did it we did it
we'd be a metal gear solid too I was wondering if I'd be
able to do it today, but I was like, I don't know.
There's really not that much left of the game after from
where we were at, you know?
So, hmm.
This weekend is Otaku-thon, so I will be there.
So, a bit of a shorter streaming week.
I'm so sorry.
My streams are all...
Everything is so whack lately.
And then as soon as I get back from Otaku-thon, I am going
straight to Japan.
So it's kind of, but I will be bringing all my stuff.
And I will be streaming in Japan.
And I have checked, I've double, triple checked my hotels.
I will be able to stream there.
So, yes, yes, yes.
It's gonna be my first con ever.
Oh my gosh, so exciting.
Thank you.
Thanks for going.
Congrats with you, with finishing one of my favorite MGS
games.
I can still remember screaming like a monkey when Raiden got
the sword.
I wish the sword never happened.
It's so...
It's so icky.
It's the hottest summer in recent years in Japan.
Good luck.
It's okay.
I'll deal.
I actually don't know if I'll be going out that much, so...
It's okay though.
Thank you!
Happy to see one of my all-time favorite games completed!
The sword is cool, controlling it.
Yeah.
I love hack and slash.
Once I just started blocking though it was great.
I would block and then he would block and then I would block
and then he would block.
And then I would block and then he would block.
Until MGS4 came out, my friends had a theory that everything
after Ryden got knocked out was a fever dream.
It held for seven years.
That would then be such a stinky ending, though, right?
It was all just a dream.
Oh, that's the biggest cop-out.
This is the part where I plugged the MGS2 analysis driving
off the map.
It really made me appreciate the game.
design choices and the writer later got to work on MTS4
among some other Metal Gear.
Oh, thank y'all, I'll get to it.
A VR simulation.
A VR sim...
What if we're all just...
This is the Matrix.
Kojima watched the Matrix and was like, Hmm, yeah.
How about like that?
Oh, man.
I think we can canonize I'm bleeding out solidus as a code
word.
A code word for what?
Ryden didn't avoid drowning in time.
We're trying to enter the big shell.
Oh, my gosh.
That's real.
That's some real conspiracy theory.
I'm bleeding out solidus.
I'm bleeding out for perseverance.
Anytime you guys are feeling like you're about to...
You don't think you can make it.
I'm bleeding out, Solidus.
Woo-ha!
So, for this is the run.
Watching you play this game after having played it myself
just barely February this year.
Made me go like...
Oh, from like...
from wait like to love because of all the stuff you freak
out about it's so easy to freak out about this game it's so
great oh i wish we could have gotten more jack and rose
drama so blows my mind how much kojima predicted regarding
ai i know right censorship so on in the finale yeah i mean
yeah it's pretty crazy i guess uh back then With the
internet being so new, you could probably look at it and be
like, well, what if this happened, you know, like, what
if...
What if people start using the internet in this way?
Hmm.
Freaky.
What rank did Minto get?
I got... I got elephant.
As I... as expected.
I got elephant.
I only had 16 alerts!
I think that's not so bad.
Patriots, thank you for your service and perfecting the
sword blocking simulation.
Thanks, Avril.
Okay.
Well, guys, it's been eight and a half hours.
Thank you for this fun little endurance stream.
I'm gonna go now and sign more postcards.
I'm going to go sign more postcards and I will catch you
guys.
We'll probably make a schedule for this week.
I will try to make one.
I will try to make a schedule while I'm gone as well.
Maybe not with specific games, but at least with times and
things like that.
So that we can have some semblance of normalcy.
I think next week might have to be mostly...
no streams mostly I will try once I'm in Japan and stuff but
there's also VX V Expo so and I'm the concert with Doki so
it's it'll be more outside events than streams I believe
yeah I will be attending the conventions from Japan so you
might get a really sleepy Minto.
Nah, I'm so hyped.
I'm super excited.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But once things calm down, like I said, August is pretty
really crazy.
But starting September, things seem to slow down a bit.
I have a few more events that I have planned.
some outside of the USA and
but I shouldn't be traveling for them so I should still be
able to like be around and such sorry that I overbooked
myself my math teacher always said in order to catch an
elephant you gotta dig a hole fill it with wood wait a hole
what burn the wood and put peanuts around the hole then when
the elephant goes to pick up a peanut you kick it in the in
the ash hole does this work what is this what is this joke
just hope you get enough rest yeah yeah I will
well the podcast MGS episode happened after the series is
done for bug mom well I don't think she's gonna finish it in
time she's gonna finish it in time She hasn't even touched
it.
So, I don't know.
But it'll still happen.
Yeah.
It'll still happen.
I think we're just going to talk about kind of...
I think I'm mostly going to kind of remind her what she's
been through so far and maybe her theories about future
games.
I'm going to make it...
I mean, it'll be spoilers for just MGS 1 and 2.
and then the beginning of three, since that's all she's
played.
So, yeah, I'll have to censor myself a lot.
But we'll hear what her theories are and things like that.
We can talk about the culture and the experience.
Yeah, talk about, like, you know, what she's looking forward
to.
And things like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Alrighty guys, I'm gonna go Thank you guys Love to hear your
MGS Con review Yes, yes, yes Of course I'm gonna go Otomito
everybody, thank you so much for For cheering me on And
pushing me To finish it through And everything, I really
appreciate it I'll see you guys tomorrow If I see you and if
not, I'll catch you When I catch you Yeah!
Otsumita!
Thank you!
Get some rest.
Thank you so much for watching.
I really, really, really appreciate it!
And I'll see you guys next time!
Ita-nashai-shai!
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye!
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye!