Why does it seem so quiet?
I don't know why the music seems so different than before.
Hello everybody, I'm Mint, welcome.
Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello.
Minty first being a member again.
Thank you.
Thank you guys.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Hello, hello, hello.
Good morning, Minta!
Good morning!
Hello, hello.
Why is it so low?
If I turn it up, I don't remember it being that high.
I don't know.
I have no idea.
I didn't adjust the music.
Weird.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you!
Oh, they're real.
Sharing my birthday cash.
Please don't sing for me, though.
It'll embarrass me.
I wouldn't embarrass you, Slice Saber.
Don't worry.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, dear Slice Saber.
That's you!
Slice Saber!
One
more time!
How old are you now?
Slice Saber, how old are you now?
Woo!
You're not embarrassed, right?
Oh, yeah!
One more time!
You're almost a ghost.
You're almost like Minto.
Yeah!
Um, die without regrets, or you'll be a ghost.
Die without regrets, or you'll be a ghost.
Asking for the three digits.
Oh, what's your credit card number?
the three digits on the back what's your credit card number
plus the three digits on the back and don't forget the zip
code where
did you go to school and your first pet's name and what was
your childhood childhood sweetheart and your mother's maiden
name okay
I think we're good I think we've thoroughly clearly
embarrassed Slice Saber for their birthday.
Don't ever say, don't sing to me, it's embarrassing.
The AI told me it was your birthday that you turned 37.
Wait, the AI is just like, it's Slice Saber's birthday and
everyone's singing to it.
turning 37.
No way.
Oh my gosh.
Paying you to stop.
Happy birthday.
Don't get me anymore.
Damn, I'm only 34.
Well, soon you can come back and watch this in three years
and it'll be accurate.
Not my Yoshi trying to commit.
credit card fraud and going on a main cafe spree i would
never i would never i would never anyways you guys welcome
back to ghost trick this is our third time playing baby and
um last time we ended it was so crazy someone stole my
credit card info so i had to cancel the card i used to pay
for membership in youtube trying to charge me for eight
times in one day was it did youtube steal Oh my gosh
That's crazy I'm so sorry I've had my card stolen Only once
And I I know that it was stolen Because I went to I went to
Get some breakfast before work And my card declined And I
checked my bank account and I was negative and I was like
that shouldn't have happened and they they had the person
had ordered like a bajillion pizzas so yeah it was not great
but you know luckily it only happened once was it a was it
Matara I or get away with it.
You know?
Man, the best party ever.
Yeah, on my dime.
But honestly, I say a bajillion.
But like, he couldn't even order that many pizzas because I
did not have that much in my bank account.
Why are you stealing from some poor ghost like me?
Huh?
Thank you.
Choo!
Stolen money is the best money.
I don't know about that.
Pizza party fun.
Yippee!
Spent all my money on seven pizzas.
Mine got stolen once and they spent 700 bucks on an office
depot.
Why?
What are they buying?
maybe maybe they thought that you were like loaning them
money for the start their business you know what i mean it
was a small loan right okay okay okay okay no more talking
about stolen credit cards no more credit card business talk
okay we're gonna talk about ghost and tricks that's had my
card denied while shopping out of town because of suspicious
purchases in California to buy guns.
It's about that was approved.
Oh my gosh, wait!
That was, that has happened to me because when my card was
stolen, it was a different state.
But I have gone to other places before and had my card
declined because I thought it was suspicious.
So weird.
But meant the story time.
Um, um, we left off on a clip hanger last time we played
where, um, we the guy that Lynn was been trying to get in
contact at the police station and it's a special police
station of people with special crimes and that's the guy
that Lynn is wanting to help is getting executed tonight in
like an hour or something so we have to like whoops we have
to kind of skedaddle hopefully the Audio will be okay.
If not, if it's too quiet, during, I can adjust it as well.
So just let me know.
And I will.
Oh, five minutes.
Wasn't it five?
It was, actually, I think you guys are right.
It was, I'm being kind of gracious.
It was five minutes.
Cost Co.
Pizza slice, supply drop.
Yummy.
Five minutes until he fries.
he's turning getting being turned into fries I'm a soup
casual breed thanks for one man thank you thank you guys for
returning all the members returning thank you so much really
really appreciate it can't believe it's been a month oh my
gosh well not a month since I've been back I guess a little
over a month that I've since I've been back yeah I kind of
wanted to do something a little bit decided to do the
english karaoke on wednesday so um it's not it's not much
but um i have been cooking i have been cooking a lot of
stuff oh my gosh like um well actually most of everything
that i've been cooking has been for um my anniversary which
will be in july which i'm like oh my god can i is it okay if
i say that it's my four year anniversary Because technically
I didn't even get to celebrate my first year anniversary.
But it would be kind of cool to say that it's a four year
anniversary because four is a spooky number.
Technically we never even got to celebrate one anniversary.
So we will celebrate.
And I have some fun things that I'm planning for...
Anniversary.
I was like, oh my gosh, I gotta start working on stuff now,
honestly.
I was like, change.
One in four.
I was kind of like thinking of doing like that.
But I was like, if I do like one zero, or not zero, one like
one slash four or one in four, people might get confused.
I don't know.
Hey, I'm Minto.
Hope your day is good.
Work was pretty crazy, but I'm getting hyped for this gym
session with my Kamiyoshi.
It's the perfect voice for it.
Yeah, it's cool!
Gym time.
Then four in one.
Oh, yeah!
V has come too.
But wouldn't it be one V?
One V has come one.
Hmm.
timer pause when you went to heaven them's the rules you're
basically a newer streamer no let's do all four
anniversaries yeah well uh four is one V is two okay so next
year I can say V has come too yeah
but anyway I'm still figuring it out we'll figure it out
that joke is gonna be so funny next year back to being
okay let's not waste any more time sorry I was like so busy
though because I was like okay I'm wasting more time because
like oh my gosh I woke up this morning and I was I was
emailing so many people and I was I was I was doing phone
calls During the phone calls, I was, I mean, this is like,
not stuff that you'll ever see.
It was stuff that I needed to get done.
But during phone calls and meetings, I was also messaging
people about other stuff.
Oh, I was so busy this morning.
We will always be here for you, you nerd.
Fun for days, Miss Min.
Thank you, Josh.
I love for the pink.
Thank you.
Yeah, but I was like, I was really, I've been really like
kind of, kicking butt to get stuff done and like um one
thing that like i was i've been in charge of is getting all
the artwork for the patreon for the postcards and so um it's
been a lot of like back and forth between so many different
artists and like they'll send something and i'll be like and
then i'll like respond and we're sent to matara and be like
do you want any changes and this and that and like i'm
talking to like six different artists at once so i'm like
wow and then i'm also ordering the postcards and i'm also
like oh and i'm also uh i'm having a busy weekend this
weekend which is why i'm having to take off a couple days
and so i'm just like i gotta get ready for that i gotta get
to do this and i gotta record the podcast and i gotta email
this person back and like people are emailing me for like
events and conventions and stuff.
So I'm just like, okay.
Or like other things that seem kind of cool.
So I'm just like, I gotta email this person back.
So there's like been so much going on behind the scenes that
I like wish I could share more of, but I have been trying to
work hard to do lots of stuff.
It's a lot to deal with.
Yeah, but it's so much fun.
It's actually so much fun.
Um...
I think if I...
Well actually not that I think.
The day, whenever I decide to not be a streamer anymore, one
thing that I really love is just like general planning.
And like, I would love to like...
Um...
I don't know.
Like maybe one day be like a manager to like a VTuber or
something.
Project manager mint.
Yeah!
It's fun.
I used to plan a bunch of stuff.
Even before V-Tubing.
And even as a V-Tuber, I love planning stuff.
So, but trying to plan things.
Yeah.
Starting your own V-Tuber company with Kacha and Idols.
How many directions did you plan things in?
What do you mean?
hey, I helped with planning some stuff at, like,
conventions.
It's probably the easiest way to say it.
So.
I got that reference.
Happy one month, Miss Fartome.
Thank you.
Poppy!
Thanks for the pink!
I couldn't make it for the last two streams, but I'm so glad
I can finally watch my favorite streamer my favorite VTuber
stream my favorite game live!
Hope you enjoy the ride, man!
Thank you!
Thanks for the pink!
There's a much cooler ambition than working in a grocery
store.
Look, I didn't know.
I didn't know!
Bye.
Um.
What was I gonna say?
Oh!
Oh my gosh, you guys.
Yesterday, I saw my grandma and my mom for Mother's Day.
And, um, I'm sorry, we'll get to the game eventually.
Holy cow.
But, uh, I gifted my mom, um, uh, this thing.
Let me see if I can get it.
Let me see if I can get a picture.
Or, uh, say what it is.
Hold on.
Uh, uh.
okay oh i have to do this too oh my gosh okay um so my mom
is really into like meditating and relaxing and stuff like
that and i found this thing and i got it on sale thank god
because it was really expensive but it's called this it's
called the drift and it's like it's like it's like a you
know those those zen gardens where you the sand.
It's like one of those, but it's, but it's, it's a, it, you
put a metal ball on it and it, Kansai Dorifto.
Yeah.
And like, and then you, you, you put, you get an app and you
beep, beep, beep.
And then it draws a design on the sand for you.
And it's like, oh my gosh, at one point we were all just
standing there in silence like staring at it and just like
inside we were all like watching it draw in the sand and i
had to leave before my um before my grandma because my
grandma went to sleep i had to leave before she got to see
it but then my mom texted me a picture of my grandma and she
was just let me see what she said She sent me a picture of
my grandma just staring at it.
She said, thank you so much for the gift you bought me.
Grandma and I are sitting here in the quiet, just mesmerized
by it.
I was like, it's a picture of my grandma just staring at
this thing.
Like, so, like, locked on.
It's so funny, too, because my grandma likes to wear
headbands.
She always has as, even when I was like a young ghost.
And, and, and the headband she was wearing this time was,
was, was black headband.
And I was like, like around her head.
And I was like, Grandma, you got infinite ammo.
And she, oh, but she wouldn't stop talking about, she
wouldn't stop talking.
She would be like, she would be like, my grandma's at an old
person home, right?
But she loves, usually I feel like old people don't like the
old people's home.
But my grandma is obsessed with this old person's home.
She loves the old people home.
She's like, she's like, don't ever take me out.
And we're like, we're not.
My mom's just like, yep.
Because my grandma will be like, she's like, I go up and
down those halls.
And I keep everybody in check.
I, you know, recently fights have been getting, have been
breaking out with the, with the, with the old people and
with the doctors.
And she, she just like always calls it one flu's, flu over
the cuckoo's nest every time I see her.
She's like, have you seen one flu over the cuckoo's nest?
That's this place.
And I'm in charge.
And I'm like, yeah, I know, grandma.
Elderly uprising.
Well, she was just like, there was a fight that broke out.
there was a fight that broke out and I went in there I went
in there and I said hey you fuckers cut it out because I
need that doctor because I have to shit my grandma
what do you mean why do you mean by that grandma mint is
living the dream it's true my grandma man
my grandma she said she
oh my grandma I'm trying to think of what else she's she
kept talking she like the whole time I was taking I was
driving with her she wouldn't stop talking about her
explosive diarrhea I don't think I should share that with
you guys so much
Is your grandma a big boss or something?
My grandma doesn't hold back about anything.
Yeah, let's not share it.
Is your grandma Johnny?
Oh, grandma.
Ugh.
Okay.
That's how we play the game.
Sorry.
I just thought of that because I was just like...
I kind of want to get the thing now for me too.
So I can sit in the dark or sit in silence just mesmerized
by this little ball drawing in the sand.
It's really mesmerizing though.
But they're really expensive.
I bought it because it was a combined like Mother's Gate,
Mother's Day, birthday, did I say Mother's Gate?
Your mom's what?
That was a mother's day birthday gift.
Okay, I'm going to continue the game.
We're playing the game now.
Oh my goodness.
Okay, we have five minutes until a person is dead, you guys.
We can't be laughing.
We can't be...
Search game.
What is wrong with me?
First search gay and now mother's gay.
You really can't talk your way.
Okay, no, I can talk my way out of it because I combine day
with gift, okay?
This is actually how my brain works.
Everything just is like, you take all the words of a
sentence and you go, you go, you take all the words and then
you go, and you smash it all together, okay?
Mother's gay?
Yeah, they are, both of them, how do you know?
I don't, I, the other day, the other day I was, this is,
what did I type, hold on, I was messaging someone, and, and
I was messaging someone, and they were like, Do you have a
deadline when you went to this finish?
And I was like, no, whenever you have fun.
Because in my brain, I typed have.
And so my brain just said, have fun.
But I meant have time.
And I was like, no, not fun time.
Don't have fun.
My brain is so weird.
Enjoy your meal, you too.
It's just because, like, I'll finish something.
I'm so afraid to type on stream because of it.
Because I know, like, ouch.
Sorry, my eye is bothering me.
I know that if I type, if there's a certain phrase that I'm
typing, my brain will, it, like, auto-finishes.
And it's just, it's just, it's so stupid.
because I type things and I'm like, why did I type that?
I don't mean have fun at all.
Don't have fun.
Not very nice there, Min.
30 minutes and we've made it to the file select.
We're cruising tonight, guys.
No, we're starting.
We're starting right now.
Okay, everybody comfy.
Let's start the game.
But please, I can't breathe.
Stop being hilarious for like one second.
her brain is too far in the future I swear I'm I'm always
clowning I'm always clowning alright alright someone's dying
you guys 1055 p.m.
I went to try and rescue prisoner D-99 even under ordinary
circumstances that prison has a strange atmosphere but this
time there's something even stranger about it hey I happened
to enjoy the ghost yapping thank you I'm calm I'm normal I'm
normal an execution with my memory gone I don't have a clear
image of what that is in my head but even I can sense the
strong feeling of foreboding that hangs in the air you don't
know what an execution is maybe I'm too late no
oh no he's he's grooving is it really quiet i'm really hold
on i even turned up the sound okay well i'll turn it to nine
the sound is fine it's pretty quiet on my it sounds quiet
even to me hmm i'll turn it up just a little bit okay so
how's it going with the generator in the basement why is oh
they're trying to fix it now it's gonna take a while they
said they haven't even gotten the internal phone there back
up yet waiting for the inevitable mint apologizes after
being three hours late to her stream to explain that she was
watching circles in sand stream hey now i just hope the
Routies, don't rush the guard room.
Oh, we don't have any Routies here.
And what's more, the one who committed the most atrocious
crime isn't even here anymore at all.
Wait, what?
You promised not to talk about that.
Look, would you not get off with that weird flipping and
flopping around?
I can't stand looking at it.
If you don't stop, I just might have to pound you.
Where's the fanfic of these two?
This is a glorious dance That's been passed down in my
family for generations When you don't know what else to do
Dance, dance, dance We call it the panic dance
This is special detention calling from the death chamber the
internal phone is finally back up oh it's pitch black down
here though until they get the generator going again how's
it going up there the phone's been ringing off the hook from
headquarters the death chamber oh boy we can't let the
existence of this prison become known to the outside world
we'll have to round up the prisoners somehow Is Bailey
dancing?
Yep, you should see him.
Whoa, thank you for the 20 gifts!
Wait, who's gifted?
Kido!
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
Take a video of it.
We can all watch it together when we're done.
Once the generator is back up, I'll record it with the
security camera.
This is so messed up.
Someone is about to die and you're like, dancing and then
we'll watch it after the guy is dead.
Oh my god.
I'm going.
Generators still not up?
I can't keep this up much longer.
Believe me.
Nobody is asking you to.
Why don't you just stop?
Oh wait, this is the guy that has the accent, right?
He has a southern accent.
Will you dance instead then?
Me?
You kidding me?
Somebody has to do it!
Oh, he's going faster.
Oh my god.
If that somebody is me, I'll keep dancing until I drop!
Oh my god, he's going even faster!
Despite how it looks, the situation seems pretty serious.
Bailey's dance is certainly intriguing.
Thank you for being awesome and as cool as heck.
Thank you, Kiori!
Thank you for one month.
But that telephone call that came in is even more
interesting.
The man said he was calling from the death chamber, eh?
Now that I have the extension number, I should go check it
out.
Oh, it's a trick.
Internal.
Special detention.
Was it that one?
I assume the death chamber is...
Oh.
Whoa!
It's so dark.
This is not good.
Not good at all.
Fortnite emote the panic away.
Yeah, I feel like a ghost is going to show up any minute
now.
Now, wouldn't that be silly?
Ghost?
Hey, come on.
Show some respect.
There's a dead man here.
Wait, what?
That's right.
Me.
Wait, hold on.
That's right.
Me.
Me too.
Hey, Sissel, I was dead before you, okay?
This is my sh-dick.
But, woo, I never saw that one coming, did you?
Wait, so did they, like, electrocute him and it was so
powerful?
It took out the power.
Who could have?
Anyway, the generator is going to be fixed soon, so I guess
we hang tight.
Okay.
There's a dead man.
Who?
I guess darkness doesn't really exist in the ghost world.
Even without light, I can still see what's going on.
I can use the ghost world to help me find that generator.
A whole month already.
Thank you!
Love you.
Power supply?
Emergency light?
Water drop?
Oh, that will probably help me get down.
Wait, is that the dead man up there?
Uh oh.
Oh no, it's a spoon.
Wait!
Wait, this is the guy he's been crawling out this whole
time!
Oh my god.
Wait, where'd the water drop Tropical.
This must be it, right?
Oh, geez.
Where'd that wrench go?
Without it, I can't tighten the last bolt on the generator.
I sure wish I could see in the dark like a cat.
Or like a ghost.
This appears to be some kind of control panel.
I might be able to operate it.
But it doesn't seem to be responding.
It's too dark to really tell, though.
I guess the first thing I need to do is to restore that
generator.
So the wrench.
Hello.
I can't hold on much longer.
Lion from the game just dug up a child memory of the
cliffhanger guy from between the lines.
Okay.
Huh?
Okay!
Cliffhanger.
Cliffhanger guy.
I don't know.
I don't know that one.
Actually, I don't think so.
It says between the lions.
That's between the lions.
That's why he's called cliffhanger.
The real ones in chat give me...
I've seen these things before.
Some kind of tool for turning things.
It's leaning up against the wall.
If I knock it over, I wonder if he'll notice.
Darn, it's too heavy.
It won't budge.
Oh, man.
Let's see.
Was this...
It's a lie.
Maybe, um...
Oh, I can barely!
Dang.
Okay.
Let's wait for the droplet to form again.
Oh, okay.
Now if I go and drop.
Now I'm in the bucket.
Oh, I can't do anything in the bucket.
Toolbox.
Let's open it up.
Oh!
Oh, he saw it.
Oh, hey, there it is.
These guys remind me so much of like the...
The, what's it called?
The Genome Soldiers.
There, done.
Did it?
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Yippee!
Wait, is this a good thing that we...
Oh.
Is it a...
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh!
What?
Wait, so if the generator is off and all the cells just
open?
I don't think that seems very...
Um...
Now the lights are back on.
But what happened here?
The answer is still shrouded in darkness.
I better see if I can pick up on some more information.
Can't seem to shake this bad feeling I've got.
Me too, though.
And then we'll go to here.
This one.
Wait.
Oh my gosh, the timing has to be...
Pitch perfect!
Okay.
There we go.
What if I lower this?
lover didn't do anything did someone say the door to
darkness hey do you think this execution was really the
right thing to do what the heck are you saying I mean I know
this country has the death penalty but how many years has it
been since we used this chair what do you mean was oh yeah I
don't know it had quite a dirt on it i bet that's what
happened all that debris damaged the wiring well i think it
was divine retribution don't be stupid the prisoner wanted
to be executed you know
he's dead inspector jowl i guess i was too late so when are
they gonna pick up his body They'll be sending over a car
from the public cemetery pretty soon.
After we hand over the body and clean up the mortuary, we're
done!
Yeah, okay.
Are we the bodies?
No!
No, no.
What else are they saying?
This chair scares me.
I don't want to repair it or get anywhere near it.
Why is there so much water?
Who knows when it's gonna blow up?
I knew it blew up.
Or let loose with the juice.
Just mint is the baddie, I think.
No, no, no.
Weirdest mortuary assistant DLC.
I'm not gonna lie, when they said mortuary, I also thought
of mortuary assistant.
And then I remembered that is the scariest game I've ever
played in my entire afterlife.
It's so scary!
Oh my gosh.
Loose with the juice.
Yikes.
Shut up, man.
Accidents can happen with anything after all.
But let's just get this thing fixed.
Come on.
If I'm executed by an accident, I'm gonna come back and
haunt you.
I can make that happen.
Haunt me?
Why me?
Sounds like a pretty dangerous chair.
Hmm, the chair that gives shocks.
Can I use that somehow?
Oh, are you gonna kill them?
Oh my gosh, this little...
Kind of insane.
Wait, how do I get over there?
Uh.
Oh, the drips.
Oh.
Wait, I can't reach.
Let's see what he says.
So Detective Jowd has already been executed.
Looks like there was a reason for that bad feeling I was
getting.
But that's okay.
This isn't a big problem for me.
But if the body is taken from the mortuary, that'll be bad.
I have to use my ghost tricks to save him before that
happens.
Yeah, but how do I get over there?
My arm's too short.
Um, lever.
Um, does it do anything?
Uh.
Oh, there's a phone in there.
Nobody probably called from in there, though.
I don't think I have the extension.
Is it?
napping?
What's he doing up here?
Let's see.
Where does the water?
The water from there.
Hmm.
He's taking a little nap, you guys.
I guess we'll go back to him.
Oh, wait.
Power just...
Oh.
what do i say here this guy seems to be taking oh he's
actually taking a nap i doubt my paltry powers are enough to
wake him rest in peace curry lover one month already i love
you and your grandma ah thanks it's kind of spooky when a
ghost says it
can i can i make it over no there's no way ah ring the bell
we have to go back and ring the bell so he goes home
uh lower row
time here still appears to be like a caged animal the only
difference is i don't see any of the inmates oh wait it was
the wait and of course our death row inmate isn't here
either yeah because he's dead what are you talking about did
the curry lover ever find his curry
My time will soon be locked away from me as well.
I can't waste what I have left.
I better get going.
Trick time!
Yeah, so stop talking, buddy.
Oh.
Wait.
Emergency button.
I better not set off the emergency alarm right now.
The inside of my head is already in a state of emergency as
it is.
Okay, never mind.
Uh, we'll go upstairs.
Oh my gosh.
Ugh, all the, all the phew, phew, phew, phew.
Sometimes messes with my head.
No.
Meow.
My arm is too short.
Wait, can we go through the...
the toilet or flash no let's
try going back to the guard room maybe and seeing what's
going on there oh this panic dance that has been passed down
in our family for generations there's just one problem with
it hey quit acting so bored and ask me ask me what's the
problem Bailey yeah yeah what's the problem Bailey panic
dance the problem is it's hard to know when to stop
hey quit acting so bored and pay attention I like this guard
I don't remember his name but I like his perpetual smirk.
Ghost!
Thanks for one month.
Guess it's hard for you to know when to stop talking to.
Ooh!
Wait, the CV is now.
Was it always facing?
Wasn't it facing us before?
Or maybe not.
Nothing going on here.
Hunk!
Did they change seats?
Yeah, they did.
It's the panic dance.
Jump out of your pants.
We're panicking.
We're panicking over something.
Something has gone wrong.
What could it be?
Something has gone wrong and it deals with me.
The panic dance is the panic dance.
Take off your pants!
It's the panic dance!
When you panic, you get hot.
And that's why you don't need pants.
It's the panic dance!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's the panic dance The panic dance!
What could be wrong?
I don't know!
But I feel...
Really concerned!
The panic dance!
It's the panic dance The panic dance It's the panic dance
Anyway How do
I get to the spoon guy?
Where are my pants?
They're gone!
Were you panicking?
I'm in severe stress.
I'm overthinking it.
Oh, am I?
Does it not have to do with him?
Oh, I didn't mean to go that far out.
Uh, back.
Thanks for the pants.
Oh, the jeans.
Do I go to the bucket and do something?
No.
Doodle bob.
What do you mean doodle bob?
No,
wait, how am I supposed to get out?
There we go.
Manipulate.
This appears to be some kind of control panel.
I might be able to operate it.
I'll give it a try.
Peep-boop.
Oh!
Oh my god, I'm going to kill them.
Some lamps came on.
Not sure what that means.
Maybe that changed the situation, though.
Oh, I think they're about to die.
Uh.
Oh, wait.
Let's turn on the lever.
Let's kill these guys.
Execution!
Xagga!
Okay.
I just got a shock.
You are a shock.
Here we go.
Bucket.
Oh, dang it.
Fast!
Oh, I have to...
Okay, okay.
Fast!
Oh, I have to...
Chop, chop, chop, chop.
And I'm gonna rock that piece!
Woo!
Oh!
Spooky!
Son of a!
Oh!
And then I'm gonna rock the cart.
And then I'm gonna go back and here.
Oh, we're inside.
Same thing here.
Looks like this is just an internal phone, too.
It doesn't call outside.
So the only places I can go with this telephone are other
phones within the building that I've already possessed.
Okay.
Spooky card.
Flower vase.
Person's body.
Hey, can you hear me?
Where am I?
Oh, he's not alive.
He's awake!
This is the ghost world.
The land of the dead.
Detective Jowd.
Who is that?
Is that me?
Oh boy, not you two.
This is getting old.
Thanks for the Superchild!
I guess I'll just give the usual explanation.
The dead lose their memories.
Oh, so I'm dead, am I?
I didn't realize that.
It's you guys, right there.
It's you, it's you.
You're looking a little thin.
You need to eat more.
That's why you can't remember anything right now.
That's fine with me.
Huh?
I don't like a messy room.
But I hate cleaning up even more.
Not having my memories is a welcome thing.
Now I don't have to have as much trash to take out.
Memories are like trash?
Now that I'm dead, what do I need with memories?
And things I don't need are just trash.
Not to me.
I need your memories.
Besides, I promise Lin, I try to stop your execution.
Lin?
Hmm.
It looks like I still have a few bits and pieces of garbage
left lying around.
Why is he calling them garbage?
Wow!
I remember now!
About Lin, Jowd, and the execution?
What?
And what about you?
Who are you?
Yeah, you only remember those things because I told you!
Sir Chaddington, right there.
I'm Sissel.
I'm looking for my memory.
Or trash, as you call it.
Sissel.
Does my name ring a bell?
I think you know me.
Sorry.
It must not have been a very big piece of trash to me.
I want to let you guys know that you're all big pieces of
trash to me, okay?
You're all big pieces of trash.
Thanks, man.
I'm honored.
That's all right.
I guess you'll find out when you get your memory back.
But for now, I'd like you to come back with me.
Back to four minutes before your execution.
This is going to be so traumatic.
Oh my god.
It's not just a regular death.
It's an execution.
It's the nicest thing anyone's ever said.
about me yeah this is the past four minutes before my death
that's right oh sorry you'll get to see your own execution
well don't smile and say that and then we're gonna change
your fate well first can I ask you a question wait four
minutes before this guy is dead he's not even in the chair
yet they got it done so quickly.
Lynn told you, didn't she, about what I did?
Yeah, she did.
Well, actually, we found out from a newspaper.
Then is it really the right thing to do, to save a guy like
me?
I don't know.
But Lynn believes it is.
Okay, let's get started.
Oh.
Jinkies!
Okay.
Oh no, it gets stuck.
It's clogged.
Uh-oh.
This is what happens when...
This is what happens when you flush stuff other than...
other than poop down the toilet.
Wait, what did he say?
Uh-oh.
I was too busy thinking about poop.
It's time.
Gochiso-sama-deshta.
of ketchup no
don't you do it too what was in the trash can that you
couldn't flush it or that you couldn't throw away your
napkin oh my god they're all the
same ten huh oh my god sorry I keep yodding so the time's
finally here huh too busy thinking about poop eating choices
Yeah, I wonder how many years it's been the last time you
weren't even here yet I never thought I'd have to attend an
execution, but you know, I wonder why the justice minister
suddenly signed the order There's definitely something up
with that Hey, come on.
Let's just focus on our work.
This guy is such a doubter.
I love him Vivi core.
Thanks for the five gifted.
Thank you Yeah, all right 10
Right, left, oh, up, up, down, down, up, up, down, up, down,
up, down, down, down, up, prisoner D99, it's time, let's go,
all right, men, I'm ready, sorry to have to go through this
unpleasant, oh, sorry, you have to go through this
unpleasant experience, what, no, we, uh, oh, well, I guess
it's all about collecting experiences for you and for me oh
my god Troy thanks for the 20 gifted thank you so much thank
you can't get over his Chad face this guy is such a Chad
face I think the Chad meme was based off of him
oh my god prepare to test throw the switch wait it explodes
and then he dies
So this is an execution, huh?
Seems to me there's got to be a safer way to do it.
It must be nice to have no memory like that.
It makes things more interesting.
I envy you.
I really do.
It's no laughing matter to me.
This guy's so awesome.
That was an example of a failed execution.
Although the outcome was the same.
Fail?
Ugh.
They haven't carried out an execution in a long time.
Wait, what if it was one of the guards?
We're going to switch the guard position and the chad
position.
They dragged out...
They dragged that old chair out from under some mothballs.
And I guess it had a short.
So I guess that means that if I can stop the explosion...
I don't know about that.
Then I'd be executed as planned.
And I'd still wind up just as dead.
So what should I do?
Beats me.
You're the one who came to save me.
You figure it out.
He's not making this easy.
I mean, can you even blame him?
I actually agree with him.
Rewind time.
Trick time.
Uh, who you call it?
How's it going down there?
We just finished setting up the chair.
we're all prepared I see it's time please bring in the
prisoner but but but but boot that chair it hasn't been used
in a long time but what if Bailey there's nothing we can do
now it's time all right I'll send the guards to a cell I'll
have them call when they get into position okay we go there
did he just say Do it.
Do it yourself.
Basically.
Oh my god, this guy is drunk.
I have this strange feeling of uneasiness.
I must dance it out.
How about you?
How do you feel?
I feel chubby and jittery and I can't stand still.
I feel like I might start dancing at any minute.
If you're gonna dance, let me know.
I'll get the video camera.
already nobody will listen to my concerns concerns huh so
he's worried that man is always worried about something
whatever he's worried about it's always it always comes true
without fail mm-hmm
listen to me that chair is dangerous I know Bailey that's
why I don't advise you sit on you to sit on it no no no
that's not what I mean machines like that are very sensitive
to dust if the guys throw the switch in the chair shorts out
there might be a huge explosion down there in that death
chamber oh my god he called the whole thing oh come on
nothing's gonna happen besides even if the on the off chance
it does blow up we're way up here we'll be fine i know why
don't we go and test it out first no way i don't want to get
blown up you'll go by yourself so this spot would be safe
even if it does blow up, eh?
What is it?
You have a new look in your eye.
Why can't I stop yawning?
If the switch in the death chamber is thrown, the chair will
blow up.
That's right.
And if the chair blows up, the execution can't be carried
out.
True.
It only stands to reason.
And if there's nobody in the death chamber when the chair
explodes?
Nobody will die.
Precisely.
Very nice, Sissel.
You've hit upon some excellent points there.
Okay, I'm starting to see a plan now.
Sophie!
How do we have nobody in there?
Time is passing.
Oh my gosh, oh my gosh, oh my gosh.
Let's dial...
Wait, there's no...
Oh yes, that's right.
We can't use the phone lines.
I can only move over phone lines in the past when it's in
use.
Sadly, this applies to the internal extensions as well.
Ow, ow, ow.
Get everyone up there.
Exactly.
Everybody has to come up here.
Or.
Or, or, or, or, or, or.
We somehow pull the switch early.
I think.
Getting the chair to shore out.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Why can't I stop a yawning?
Hold on.
I'm gonna eat a cookie.
Cookie time.
It's cookie time.
Maybe some sugar will help me.
Eepi ghost.
Ah!
I dropped my controller.
In the past world, I can't just use the phone lines whenever
I want.
These guards seem to be in a fog.
I doubt they'll be using the phone much.
Maybe I need to start over?
Wait, no!
What?
What do you mean?
Maybe I do need to start over.
I'm stuck here.
I thought he said he would call.
He said he would call when it's time for the guy to go
there.
I'm just sorry I didn't get to see Bailey's famous dancing.
Getting the chair to short out when nobody's around it.
The plan is starting to solidify in my mind.
But I'd better find a different path next time.
From the beginning.
Did he say he would call?
I thought he did say he would call.
Oh, bad.
I think we need to attach ourselves.
to...
Uh...
This guy, maybe.
Got it!
Oh.
Um...
Alright then, four minutes from now.
This chair will short out and explode and you'll die!
It's very sad.
If I stop the explosion, you'll be executed and you'll still
die.
Sorry I was ever born.
I have to protect you from the explosion and stop the
execution.
The key to this whole thing must be this chair.
I apologize for all your trouble.
Could you stop with the insincere comments?
Ha ha ha.
Wait, am I stuck here?
Oh, oh.
Oh, here we go, here we go.
Now it's time to go get the prisoner.
I'm in position.
The other two are coming to bring the prisoner to you now.
Got it.
I feel like we have to try every spot.
Unless they call one more time, but maybe they don't.
They might not call one more time.
I don't know.
I have no idea.
We can't get...
We can go to the paper.
Okay.
Paper.
Open up the note.
Let it free.
Oh!
Alright, my jam grooved off the clock.
Now get down there to Sausage Head.
Go, go, go!
Okay.
Oh, wait.
Wait, that's about to- Ew, that was terrifying.
Oh, God, he's so gross.
Okay.
What is this for?
in the present world four minutes into the future sausage
head was lying passed out in the tunnel oh I wonder if like
the shock got him not knowing about the execution he must
have kept digging and digging and the guards didn't notice
he was gone so I guess Curry's man Curry man's future has
now changed a bit fate changed okay oh
can't reach it but we need to get to oh
yes we ring this because he needs to go back downstairs
right he needs to go back why is he so freaky he needs to we
need to go with him back in there because that's how we get
into the other room ew and he licks it okay attach to the
spoon yeah we're gonna use him we're gonna use him
come on hurry it up
oh never mind I thought he would go back inside just kidding
but that's okay we can now go to his place to you and um the
napkin what did he do with the napkin again oh he also
flushed the napkin he also flushed the napkin I think we
have to be the napkin And then when we get flushed, we can
then go downstairs, probably.
After looking in the trash can.
Yeah, what's in there?
Open?
Oh!
Wait a second!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Wait, how do we get the circle?
I might have to restart.
Oh, we notice it's full.
This thing is as full as I am.
Oh, no.
It needed to be.
Okay.
We know, though.
We know, no.
We know now.
If he gets it...
I'm actually curious.
If he grabs this, will we be able to do it again, I wonder?
We know, no.
It's too late.
Is it because he's not eating anymore?
Oh, oh, shoot.
Oh, shoot.
There we go.
I almost missed my chance.
Oh, okay.
Never mind.
It's too late.
We gotta restart.
He's not eating anymore.
He's just sitting there.
It's so sad.
Okay, let's restart.
After fate change.
Okay.
That's okay.
Now...
Uh...
Your soup!
Do you have a favorite instant curry brand?
I've only ever bought Vermont curry, but I feel like maybe I
should look at others.
PS prisons open all doors that the power goes out, so that
if there's a fire, it won't burn all the inmates.
Oh!
Which has happened before?
There has been fires in...
Was it?
What was it?
Was it Alcatraz?
Oh my gosh.
I want to go to Alcatraz so badly.
I want to go.
But the one day that Mia Matara can maybe go, they
weren't...
They were all full.
I just dropped my drink.
Hold on.
I don't know.
Oh, man.
man i think it's fine i just dropped the straw side right
onto the floor though so i can't drink any more of it that's
fine but yeah i really want to go i've never been i've never
been to san francisco before but because of off kai i can go
i will be able to visit so i was like i want to visit can't
go because I don't well I don't I don't know we might maybe
try a different time if there's any openings or if they're
if the place is open too but
yeah I want to I want to go I want to go
it closes really early like 3 p.m.
no no no we looked at the website um they have we were gonna
try for it they have nighttime tours as well and we were
gonna try even though she was scared i was like come on it's
probably fine it's probably fine i'm a ghost like what i'm
gonna run into another ghost oh ringa ringa ringa ringa oh
my god did anyone else play drigalia ringa
The way he like slorps his spoon is so weird.
Oh my gosh, I have to be pretty...
I have to go pretty quickly with this, I think.
Huh?
Oh, Will.
I missed Regalia.
Me too.
I missed Regalia so much.
All right.
What is the order here?
maybe
i might have to restart one more time but he like he has to
be holding his i think one okay i think it's the timing of
when he's holding the napkin over the trash can but before
he opens it right yeah it needs the oh it needs oh now now
now yeah yeah
Wow.
Oh, let me possess the napkin.
Perfect timing.
Ringling!
Time is passing.
Okay, and now we're gonna possess the spoon.
Once he brings us up.
Can I reach it now?
No, not yet.
Time is passing.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Spoon!
Ta-da!
Okay, very nice.
This is the most lax prison I've ever seen ever.
Okay.
Alright.
Alright, hurry up, please!
Hurry up!
Oh!
Oh,
God.
Okay, come on, crawl!
Crawl, man!
Crawl!
Ah!
Okay, okay.
Sorry, that guy was still in the hole, but...
Oh, what just happened?
We just stopped to death.
The power's down throughout the whole facility.
No way.
If the power's down, that means...
All the cell bars open automatically!
Damn it, the internal phones aren't working either!
State of emergency!
Now the execution can't be carried out and your life is
saved.
Crisis Averted You're a pretty daring guy!
I really enjoyed myself, and I think I learned a thing or
two as well.
About what?
By the way, is it true what the guard says?
The cell bars open automatically?
Jail break!
Yep, it's true.
It's a little drawback to the system.
If the entire facility blacks out, the locks are released
for the prisoners' safety.
But nobody thought it would actually ever happen.
So in other words, now is the time to escape if you're
gonna.
Anyway, we managed to stop the execution.
Let's get back to the present.
You're still not out of the woods yet.
And Now that guy's gonna get his memories back.
He can tell us who we are.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, let me give you one piece of advice.
What's that?
When we get back to the present, head for the spoon.
Okay.
Spoon?
Huh?
You'll see when we get back, Sissel.
Okay, time to go to the spoon.
Spoon, spoon, spoon.
Oh my gosh, he wants to spoon me.
Now the execution can't be carried out.
Jowd is safe for the moment.
A new present has been born.
Jowd still isn't safe from execution, of course.
I guess I still have a job to do.
Help a death row inmate escape from prison.
Oh, yeah.
Yippee!
We cleared the 1055 to 1109 challenge.
Jowd taking by fate.
Nice.
That one wasn't so bad.
Oh, this level coming up is the worst level in the game.
Uh-oh.
Okay.
I'm mentally preparing myself.
Yeah, that chapter was pretty short.
Now I'm back in the present, and it's completely shrouded in
darkness.
I can't see it, but I can feel the tension in the air.
It's a state of emergency.
Yeah, it's not good.
You'll see why very quickly.
It's really rough.
Okay, thanks guys for the warning.
And that's only natural.
With the power failure, all of the cell bars opened
automatically.
Plus now a death row inmate is loose in the darkness.
I did what I promised Lynn.
I stopped the execution.
But that condemned criminal is now in just as much danger as
before.
Okay, to the spoon.
What are these guys?
Oh, these guys are working on it.
Let's go to the spoon.
Okay, I'm here.
The detective told me to head for the spoon when I got back
to the present.
So here I am.
And he is asleep, like before.
Oh, he's awake!
Oh god.
He's gonna like...
The bell!
Better get back!
Oh god, he's so scary!
This guy!
Woo, I'm back!
Thank goodness someone flushed his toilet.
That was good timing.
Now to use the cover of darkness to help the detective
escape.
But first I have to find him.
Oh gosh.
Is this like a sneaking mission?
But in this game...
Huh?
Oh!
Oh my god.
It's prisoner C74!
Secure the prisoner!
Oh no.
I see.
Oh, no, it looks like there are hunters in this darkness.
I hope they haven't found Detective Jowd.
Oh, no.
Where is he?
He's not here.
Oh, oh, what's that red light?
Hmm, looks like the hunter's eyes glow red.
Oh, no.
It doesn't look like escape is going to be easy.
Round.
Look at him.
Oh my god.
Wow.
He's just a ball.
Let's talk to him.
Ah, there you are.
I was wondering what I was going to do.
Are you the one who made that toilet bell ring?
That's right.
I still had another napkin lying around.
Thanks to that, I managed to make it here.
How did you know how to do that?
I learned a few things about your ghost tricks during our
time together.
Peak form.
I love him.
They certainly can be very useful powers, but at times, not
so much.
I knew that if the internal phones weren't working, you'd be
trapped in the death chamber area.
So I quickly came up with an alternative route.
How did he know about the guy digging underneath this prison
though?
Does everyone just know that?
A route that made use of sausage head spoon in my napkin.
Wow, this detective is good.
He's pretty good.
Next time you praise me, go ahead and say it out loud.
He can read my thoughts.
I forgot.
Oh yeah, he did see me in there, right?
That's true.
Anyway, it looks like it's time for a strategy meeting.
An escape strategy, huh?
This could be interesting.
Let's do it.
Escape strategy.
Let's make sure we're both clear.
The key to my escape is this darkness.
Once the basement power supply is restored, escape will be
impossible.
Okay, okay.
Thanks for the Superchild Empire.
Thank you.
So we move under cover of darkness, huh?
I know I won't have much trouble with that.
But I'm afraid I won't be able to see.
So you'll have to lead the way.
Lead the way?
Cicil sometimes like...
Cicil sometimes kind of like snake.
Lead the way.
Once you find a safe spot for me to move to, I want you to
give me a signal.
Anchor, thanks for this over time.
Okay, fine, but how?
Second floor basement.
way the dead don't have voices even if they did we have to
be quiet don't you worry about that I have an idea let's
just try it and you'll see how it works this detective likes
to just dive right into things even more than Lynn does I
wonder if they're related if they find me I imagine they'll
shoot first and ask questions later Did they shoot sausage
head?
But if I die again, we can just start over, right?
He says cheerfully.
Prison security.
I don't know if you know it or not, but this is a special
prison.
There aren't many, there aren't any dangerous criminals
here.
Except for me, that is.
Yes, I did hear something about it being a special place.
Sausage man is fine.
He was in his cell.
Oh, so if you leave the cell, they'll shoot.
and because
of the special status they're not prepared at all for
emergencies they have four timid security guards at most you
would think that would make them the fact that it's a
special prison would make them more like prepared it's mint
real it's me I think I saw some hunters lurking in the
darkness though those are the guards they're wearing night
vision goggles Ah, uh, I wonder, I wonder, night vision
goggles.
Who, who needs night vision goggles?
You don't even need those.
What stupid, what a stupid invest, what a stupid thing to
try.
Night vision goggles?
Like who even, okay.
Okay, I'll, I'll, I'll.
Night vision goggles.
night vision goggles there's special glasses that lets you
see in the dark very handy things if I enter their field of
vision it's all over so it's all about staying out of the
guards is line of sight day make sure you guide me to safe
spots like under the table okay now about that signal I want
you to give me yeah how am I supposed to do it I've already
been dead once I don't know if it's because of that or what,
but I can sense your powers now.
Ooh.
You what?
For example, you're in the bunk right now, aren't you?
Yeah.
I guess you have a sixth sense.
I think it's more like a detective sense.
That doesn't sound right somehow.
Anyway, the details don't matter.
Do you see this R here?
Yes.
Where did that come from?
Do you see this R button here?
Snake, turn off the console.
I mean, ride and turn off.
R button?
Let's use it as our signal.
How will that work?
If you press R, I'll sense it.
Then I'll move to wherever you are.
So for example...
A spoon?
If you move to that spoon and press R, I'll run to the
spoon.
Simple, right?
Alright.
Fine.
Let's start our escape plan.
Just make sure you guide me to safe spots, sisal.
Oh.
So...
Oh, okay.
What is this part?
Oh, bulletproof vest.
Okay.
Alright, so if I move...
here and if I press R after after this after he turns around
oh wait go under the table what are you doing he's gonna see
you I was like he's gonna check out what the enemy is doing.
For now, how about just aiming for the neighboring cell?
We can't hurry too much in this darkness.
Let's take it slow.
I tried!
Joud?
Joud!
Oh, okay.
Okay.
What is this?
Hatch mechanism.
Open.
Interesting.
very interesting there's another guy here interesting okay
wait so if I like go here I'm like hey come up here wait
where's the end goal is my other thing are we trying to it's
in the neighboring cell so
I feel like if I try to get him over to the toilet it's too
far but unless I tell him to go all the way over here.
Go.
Run, run, run, run.
Oh, nice, nice, nice, nice.
Okay.
Okay, oh, okay, so...
Oh, oh, there's another guy.
Where'd you come from?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I have to wait for him to come back.
He's going up the stairs?
Oh, I can't see.
And he's going all the way up.
Look at him go.
Wee!
He's going down the stairs.
He's back to where we are.
Okay.
Let's follow him.
What do we have?
What is that?
Oh, that's the cover of the toilet.
Okay.
Uh...
Let's see where he goes, actually.
Is there anything over here?
There's...
What the?
Is that a guy lying down?
Oh my god.
Wait, he scared me.
What is that?
Oh, there's a guy in between!
What's this?
Oh, empty can.
Hmm, this area under the stairs is a blind spot for the
guards.
find him here this spot is safe okay we have to wait for him
to we have to wait for him to will he oh gosh we'll have to
start from the very beginning though if we okay will he like
walk behind the guards you know so if I'm like go go now
Wait, how do you see him?
Okay.
What just happened?
Apparently there was a hunter lurking in the ceiling.
Could you do something about him?
It's so dark, I can't even see the bullet coming.
He dodged the bullet if it wasn't dark?
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Wait, is this the very beginning?
Oh, man.
Okay, okay.
I think...
Oh, wait.
Open.
I'm gonna...
I'm going to...
I'm going to open this up.
I'm gonna open up this little mechanism in the meantime
because I feel like we're gonna need it later.
Unless...
Did me opening that open all the other ones?
I don't think so.
Mint is so cute.
What do you mean?
guy
go run run run run run run run run run okay very good all
right now this guy is walking back oh my gosh what if i had
gone and uh oh no wait come back up i
forgot i need to do attach myself to him whoopsie it's okay
i can drink my water
whenever i make oatmeal i make it at a mug and then
afterwards i make tea in the same mug and so it's like kind
of an oatmeal like because I like oat milk so it's like an
oatmeal drink it's so good mug meal it's actually so yummy I
see the vision yeah so it's like an oat it becomes like an
oat flavored tea what a weirdo you're the weirdo how do I oh
how do I attack how do I get to the
Maybe now!
A valve.
Open?
Wait.
Oh!
Oh, y'all!
Oh, now they're both walking.
Hello?
Okay, wait.
Wait, this doesn't...
Oh, I wish I could, like, drop this on his head, but it's a
valve.
Okay.
Wait, this doesn't seem very good.
Oh wait, wait.
Does he just walk back up and close it again?
Or...
Hold on, let's see what happens here.
What's he doing?
He's going all the way up.
I'm stuck here, actually.
If I close this, does he lay back down?
Whoopsie.
Oh, this one's tough, though.
The timing on this is really rough.
I think.
Oh, he fell again.
He fell again.
Okay.
Maybe.
Now.
Oh my god, that was so close.
Holy cow, that was so close.
Oh gosh.
Okay, okay, okay.
Um...
Oh, man!
We're gonna close that up so he stops dropping.
Come on, I can't reach you!
Come a little closer.
Get close to Minto.
Wait, though.
Oh, I was like, hello?
Oh, wait.
Oh, I followed the wrong guy!
Don't stop!
Close.
Oh, so I can't close this right now.
Somebody is falling through it.
Okay, now we can close it.
Where should we go next, though?
Where can he hide next?
Waste basket, toilet.
There's like nothing here.
Hmm.
Okay, he should come over here.
Not yet.
Here?
Okay, okay, okay, there we go.
Wait, where do I go?
This part is tricky.
The valve seems important.
But the valve...
I can't do any ghost trick to it.
She just stops right there?
Oh, no, he keeps going.
He keeps going.
Okay.
Where are we going?
Are you kidding me?
Oh, boy.
No way.
You have to go all the way.
Over there?
No.
Is that real?
Yes way?
Chat, is this real?
There's nothing...
Unless, um...
Unless the valve.
Unless...
Maybe if I... if he hides in the ceiling, will they still
see him?
Maybe they won't see him if he hides in the ceiling.
Okay, I'm gonna have to wait for somebody to come rescue me
from the bunk.
Come rescue me from the bunk, please.
Keep going.
Walk.
Come here, boy.
Yeah.
That's right.
You know what, it's better to try that than trying nothing
at all.
Let's go to the valve.
And just sitting here wondering, you know?
If we die, we just get here again.
If we die, we just...
Trick our way back.
Oh wait.
Uh...
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You invited me to come get you.
I pressed the...
I pressed sorry.
Sorry.
My bad.
Don't do that.
Okay.
Okay, here!
Okay, he's gonna go down.
And while he's walking away, he's walking that way.
He's gonna go.
Okay, go, go, go!
What do you want me to climb up into the ceiling?
I think I can manage that.
But as things stand, I don't have access.
Oh, no!
Could you open that hatch and create...
an entry point for me.
Oh, you lost your chance!
Wait, maybe actually this guy will be stuck on this side.
What?
Okay.
Okay, now.
Wait, he's turning around!
Oh no, he's gonna get seen.
Is this guy gonna fall through the floor?
Ah, I should have.
Yeah, no time.
This guy's gonna fall through the floor.
There we go.
Okay.
Let's close the hatch.
Wait, they're both going up now.
Oh, but one will continue going up and one will turn around.
All right, as soon as he's passed.
Thank you!
As soon as he's passed.
Oh, gosh.
The timing on this is like Why do you have to stop right
there, man?
There's no time!
Made some delicious al dente parmesan.
And cheddar cheese pasta with broccoli and chicken.
Please stop.
I'm so hungry.
I even perfected my rule.
Added some fred pepper flakes.
It was really good.
Mint streams give me energy.
That sounds amazing.
Oh, also, Yanwei, I forgot to answer.
My favorite instant curry, I actually really like the...
Um, I really like, I don't remember the brand actually.
Hold on, let me look it up.
I've actually never tried the Vermont curry before, but I
like, I like, uh, apple curry.
Curry.
It's, it's a golden curry.
The golden curry one.
Hmm.
I like it.
But I've never had the Vermont.
But I just add my own apples to it.
Golden.
I'll try it out next time.
Whenever I make curry, I use the golden curry.
Oh, geez.
Oh, cheese.
Hey, we're not gonna...
Maybe I have to...
Maybe I have to close this.
Again.
Because he's gonna come back.
I don't want him to fall down the stairs.
There he is.
Then he goes down.
What?
The timing on this is whack!
The timing on this is so whack!
Because he immediately turns around, but this guy stops
here.
Yeah.
The timing was okay before you dropped him.
Maybe, yeah.
Okay.
Okay, maybe...
Nope, nope, nope, nope.
Ah, maybe I do need to drop him again to reset the timing.
Maybe this will help reset the timing, actually.
Okay.
This is a bit better.
Okay, okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Walk.
Walk, walk, walk.
Trick.
And then here, here.
And then, just go.
Just go.
Go, go.
Oh my god, that scared me.
I just can't seem to find the brick I need.
And you'll just have to make one.
Make one.
Try calling me to all kinds of different places.
I'm agreeable.
go pretty much anywhere.
Okay, I can see why you guys said this is not a good level.
No, we have to...
Wait!
Oh, thank goodness we don't have to start at the very
beginning.
Oh, yeah!
The game is kind to us.
Oops.
Okay, good, good.
Come over here.
Oh, and it's closed.
Okay.
Wait, this might actually be it.
Wait, this might be it.
Now close the hatch.
They won't see him now, right?
I love making super spicy curry with pineapple in it because
the sweet mix with the heat is great.
it feels wrong.
I can't have spicy, so I like sweet curry.
But pineapple curry sounds pretty good, too.
That's the most precise part?
So now...
Oh, it's so scary.
Oh, wait.
No, no, no.
Stop!
Cancel, cancel, cancel.
Oh, wait.
No, I need to get to the I need to get to the...
Okay.
Wait.
Oh, you have to open this, though, don't I?
I have to open this.
Yeah, now we make him fall.
Wait, no, no, no.
Wait.
Okay.
I have to be, like, super good timing because I have to open
this.
Wait, I don't have to open it?
Oh, I don't.
Oh, okay.
Let's just go to the bunk then.
Just roll?
Oh.
Okay.
Wait a second.
Oh, well, if I get him over here, there's nowhere else to go
from here.
So...
Oh, wait!
Ah, come back!
Come back!
Sir!
Maybe, actually, he can go over here.
Um...
There's nowhere, like, down here to lead him to, though.
This guy turns around eventually, right?
A good officer would turn around and check his back.
A good officer would turn around and make sure no one's
sneaking up on him in the dark!
Check the wall.
No!
Oh!
Okay, okay, okay.
Can I like tell him to come over here?
How do I tell him to come over here?
now
turn around oh my god yeah oh oh my god please sir please if
I move now I'm going to fall could you close the hatch for
me yes yes yes can't you just jump okay now go go please go
so what do you think I'd say if we've come this far we did
it great job sis so
The basement generator has been repaired.
Restoring power to all areas.
Oh.
Uh-oh.
Run!
Don't just stand there.
But the question is, what now?
I don't have anywhere else to go.
Do I?
Maybe I'll go back to my cell.
You better be kidding!
But I'm still a condemned...
criminal you know I doubt anybody'd welcome me with open
arms why don't you try contacting Lynn she went to see some
justice minister guy so an escaped death row convict is
supposed to just report into the justice minister is that it
mmm I kind of like that hello Minto good luck with game love
your stream thank you thanks cold breed thanks for whole
money you have yet to be kidding me wow that would be nice
yes all right sisal until we meet again wait how does he
escape from the prison though there's still other doors with
other people oh well let's just not think about that part
yes so I've now I've saved a condemned his life and helped
him escape.
Is that really the right thing to do?
I guess all I can do is believe in Lin at this point.
Yeah, I don't...
Why is there big boss?
That's why you're the best boss.
Great job, sneaking.
Thank you.
Oh, all four guards were at the cells.
No one was upstairs.
Oh, that makes sense.
Detective Jowd was painting my picture in his cell.
He knows me.
I'm sure I'll be talking to him again.
Well then why doesn't Ian say something?
Thank you, thank you!
Real military grade NVG doesn't emit anything because it'd
be easy to detect.
It's all passive light amplification with tech.
I don't understand it, so it might as well be magic.
Yeah, right?
If you think about it, it's kind of like...
It's like, yeah, it would be pointless to use it if you
could see it through like a whole trail of light, right?
That'd be so silly.
Uh, let's go to...
Let's go to the guard room.
The mortuary.
Anybody here?
Did you hear?
He escaped.
Yeah, we're supposed to repair this thing by the time they
catch him again.
But I wonder why he escaped.
But it's so cool.
What, the light in the dark?
I agree.
The trail of light is so awesome.
Splinter Cell misled a lot of people on artistic decision.
Aesthetic wise, it looks great.
Practicality?
Not so much.
Reminds me of Godot.
I mean...
But that's like, that's like not night vision.
And his mask emitting light is like, kind of a big thing.
I wonder why he escaped.
I heard Detective Jowd wanted the death penalty.
Right.
It's not like him to change his mind.
Maybe on this final night of his, he just got a voice in his
head or something.
It was me!
Yeah, me.
Maybe it told him to run.
Are they talking about me?
What kind of a voice do you think it was?
You know, something evil.
If you ever have a Minto voice in your head, something evil.
Like a devil or a demon or something.
Maybe a ghost.
I picture something with a pointy head wearing sunglasses.
Something like that.
They are talking about me.
Can they see me?
Trick time.
That's so silly.
All right.
Guard room.
Hey, how they know about your pointy ghost head thing?
My stai kakushi!
I don't know.
Sixth sense, I guess.
But Detective Jowd's until we meet again came around quicker
than I expected.
When I got back to the guard room, fateful call came in.
It's the panic dance.
Hello, this is...
Oh!
Cicil, are you there?
Hello?
Oh, I'm not talking to you, officer.
Anyway, if you're there, Cicil, come here immediately.
I'll be waiting for you.
If you make it in time, that is.
Wait a minute!
Oh my god.
Go, go!
Oh, oh, it's just so...
Oh, wait, uh...
Dial, dial!
Oh, wait!
I kinda wanna see what Officer Bailey has to say.
That call!
Who is it from?
I don't know.
Some weird call.
Ah, but who will call an end to my dancing?
You're supposed to record it.
Yeah, well, once you get going like that, I'm not gonna stop
you.
It's a contest then!
Which will stop first?
My dancing or the turning of the planet?
Yeah, good luck with that.
Alrighty, external line.
Go to...
Oh.
Go to here.
Wherever this mysterious place is.
Meow!
Whoa.
On the other end of the telephone line, the scene that
greets me tells me one simple fact.
Is Lynn dead?
Holy cow, that was the soundtrack.
Oh!
That our great escape plan has ended in failure.
Never expected to see you here, Inspector Cabanella.
I believe that's my line, old friend.
What were you doing here?
Believe that's my line too, clear.
I came to attend your execution.
They told me what time it was.
Couldn't get into the chamber, so I was observing a moment
of silence here.
And when I looked up my eyes full of tears, there you were,
baby.
You're so adorable.
What am I doing?
Why am I adorable, though?
It's just the way things turned out.
I took part in what seemed like a fun game, and here I am.
Here's what I wish, my old friend.
Wish it was anybody but me who found you here.
What does he mean by that?
He is gonna shoot him?
Because now that I've found you, man, I have to turn you in.
You have to stay spotlessly clean after all.
Thanks for coming.
I wanted to say goodbye to you because you are adorable.
What did I do?
As you can see, I guess I'm not going to be much help to
you.
What's going to happen to you?
Being executed tonight is just about the only thing on my
schedule, it seems.
No, no, there must be something we can trick to.
Executed, huh?
Death is pretty much meaningless to me.
Anyway, I guess we'll be seeing each other again.
By the way, there's something I'm looking for.
Well, that's right.
Your lost memory.
You know things I'd like to know.
Would you mind if I asked you a few questions?
In return for tonight's fun little game, is that it?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, let's ask about the execution.
Let's go down and up, down to up.
Thank you.
Two.
Plus one.
Mint is indeed cute.
I'm...
Stop!
Someone's about to die!
We're talking about me!
This is...
This is not how it should be.
Someone's about to die.
And all you think about is anime.
What's wrong with you?
Someone's about to die and you think about anime.
Anime girl!
How could you think about anime at a time like this?
Is your execution really the right thing to do?
I had a fair trial, and that's what was decided.
No problem there.
But still, this is the punishment that I should receive.
What if Anime Girl is cute made?
It doesn't matter!
If I was about to die and want to think about how cute Mint
is too, odd but cute.
I am continuing this game.
I'm continuing Forward
In order to bring a final close to that case And put it to
rest forever
Kawaii, where?
Lin believes you're innocent She's running around right now
trying to prove it
Ah, you too
You're all gross You're all gross
For disregarding this man's death.
Q is justice.
Moe is justice.
Moe.
Moe is everything.
But it's not me.
Okay.
We're trash, remember?
I need to go get more tea soon.
Oh my gosh, this soundtrack is so awesome.
Okay, can I please continue the game?
Is that all you have to leave her with?
No problem there?
I was sentenced to the death penalty for killing my wife,
Alma.
But to me, that's not all it was for.
We mourn in our own ways.
My cats are cute.
You're okay, I guess.
Cats are always the cutest.
Oh my gosh, no, I'm gonna save it for the podcast.
Oh my god, I'm gonna save it for the podcast.
Kawaii Coco.
What do you mean?
That's not all it was for.
Stop interrupting me!
Okay, I'm gonna go get some water.
Since you guys need to get this out of your system, get it
out of your system.
I'm gonna get some water.
You guys, I wanna read the important things going on.
What's wrong with you?
Why would you interrupt right now?
water i'll be right back i'll be right back a cliffhanger
for like two minutes actually i'm gonna go to i'm gonna go
to the little ghosties room too so like five minutes not
even less than even less than okay be right back i'm
back i'm back i'm back thank you for all the super dance
thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you that was quick i said it would
be quick I said so.
I said so.
I found a cute ghost, her name is Mint Phantom.
Scatter!
Did you wash your hands, of course?
Why would you ask me that, Dustcall?
I always wash my hands!
Cute ghost needs back, everyone scatter!
Okay.
Are we ready to continue the game now?
Are we ready to continue the game?
Continue the story?
Are you ready?
Yes.
Okay.
Thank you for all the super chats, you guys.
What do you mean that's not all it was for?
I'm talking about something that happened even before this
case.
I stole somebody else's life.
The Master Davina.
Thanks for the gifted.
What?
Um...
The other murder.
Uh-oh.
It was 10 years ago.
I'll never forget it.
That day I saved the life of a little girl.
And I stole away the life of a man.
Oh, yeah.
A quite positive genius ghost myth.
Da-yo!
10 years ago.
The life of a little girl.
little girl could that little girl be Lynn she told you
about that yeah she said you were her hero now just calm
down and drop that weapon stay back if you come any closer
I'll shoot her it's I mean you you I mean you you you thanks
for holding her up I need to feed my cats
10 years ago in a certain park.
A little girl was taken hostage.
Okay, this is a good summary or a good reminder of what
happened before.
I was still young then.
Stop, Spanjima!
No, Garlovo!
Sekai no Ichi, Kawaii, Minto!
Thank you for the akato no, thank you.
Thank you so much.
But you couldn't tell me that yesterday, huh?
When we were playing...
when we were playing Lethal Company, huh?
Yesterday I did a Patreon stream.
And we played Lethal Company.
Do you want me to?
I will next time.
No!
Not at all.
I was still young then.
I didn't have any self-control.
Sounds like you guys.
I remember asking myself at the time.
Jowd, are you going to shoot this guy?
And this is what I answered.
Yeah, I'm gonna shoot that guy.
I was too starstruck.
It's okay, if you're part of the Patreon, the two tiers,
we'll do another one.
Another one, so if you missed out, don't worry.
My hand was shaking a little, if my hand slipped, the man
might die.
even the little hostage girl was in danger
nevertheless that was my answer yeah I'm going to shoot and
the
man died I took his life yeah it's pretty messed up Lynn was
never told the outcome she was so young at the time I don't
deserve to be called a hero deserve is execution.
Aw, he has all that guilt.
But he was holding a little girl hostage.
I'm sorry, what?
So anyway, I started blasting.
That man pointing the gun at you right now.
They say he's your good friend.
Why is good friend?
In quotes.
And he's your good friend.
Yeah.
Is your...
Is your... good friend!
History would say they were roommates.
We were.
We were in the detective division together.
That was a long time ago.
I think we're gonna have to kill this guy.
Platypus, thanks for the month, thank you!
Now he's the head of the special investigation unit.
The top of the elite.
Getting ahead is the only thing he thinks about now.
And that white coat of his is the symbol of his
determination.
His white coat?
For somebody looking to get promoted to the top, what's the
one thing they're afraid of most?
Getting dirty.
Ghosts?
A blot on their record, of course.
Like a stain on a pure white coat.
Who would promote a man with a coat covered in sand?
stains.
If it was me, I'd go with a black coat that didn't show the
Oh, then why don't you change your red coat, huh?
The world is full of excellent candidates.
Even one mistake could be the end of a career.
But everyone makes mistakes, right?
Nevertheless, Cabanela has chosen the path of the white
coat.
And he'd do anything, anything at all to hide his shadows oh
so it's not so clean after all oh my gosh take the coat take
a UV light to that coat take a UV light to that coat and see
what it shows huh like send his good friend to the gallows
that's because oh because that's the right thing to do I'm a
condemned criminal after all covered in ectoplasm no I was
thinking the blood What were you guys thinking?
I was thinking of blood.
That you, like, use the solution.
And then it shows in the UV light.
Ectoplasm.
I don't think ectoplasm would show in a UV light.
Oh, wait.
Wait, yes, it does.
Uh-oh.
I think I'm in trouble.
Uh-oh!
I think...
And that's why he has that gun pointed at me right now.
Alright, let's ask about ourselves.
The one that I've been the most curious about.
I saw it, you know.
That picture you were painting in your cell tonight.
That was me.
Which means you must know me.
I'm very sorry, but...
I can't talk to you about that now.
What?
Why not?
Maybe I really am, Sissel.
Because I loved you.
I don't know your true face.
Oh my gosh, my glasses.
Oh, I'm one of those.
I don't take off my glasses.
My true face.
I'm a detective.
I can only talk about what I'm sure of.
However, I can give you one lead at least.
One month.
Yeah, roaring, John.
Thank you.
A lead.
What is it?
A long time ago, I gave Lin something to hold on to me.
On to for me!
The music box!
It was a music box!
Yes, yes, yes.
If you ever come across it, I advise you to open it.
It might jog your memory.
That wooden box I found in Lin's apartment!
And that's the only help I can give you right now.
Oh my god, we were right next to it.
The whole time.
Are we about to watch him get dead?
go my arms are getting tired you got it baby time for the
big show of hauling you in oh he's not gonna shoot don't
shoot oh that's right just let me make one last phone call
that's a big favor to ask so casually my old friend tell you
what I'll do I'll pretend I'm not watching I'll be
listening, though.
On that, you can rely.
Okay, why does the paints change on his jacket like that?
Cicel, you've got your own path to follow.
You'd better hurry.
My own path.
Flynn is at the Justice Minister's office right now, right?
It might not be a bad idea to say my final farewell to him,
too.
Hey, Poop-Popee.
Moshe, Moshe.
Hello?
Everything's fine here!
Uh-oh.
Lynn?
Uh.
Is this the chicken kitchen?
I'd like to request a delivery.
Um, the chicken kitchen is next door.
Aye, good day to you, sir.
Good day to you.
Oh.
Psh.
All right.
Sounds like she's in some kind of trouble.
It does, doesn't it?
Go help her out, would you, Sissel?
Sorry to keep Sorry to keep you waiting, inspector Ready to
go I bet inspector Cabanella is probably like Oh my gosh He
really lost his mind in the jail cell Now he's talking to
ghosts
Oh Oh before I forget Don't shoot Don't shoot Don't shoot Oh
I have a little something for you Oh
What?
Are you...
Are you gonna hypnotize me?
What's going on?
Just like my Dogen's.
A present, if you will.
There's nothing else like it, baby.
If there's nothing else like it, don't throw it.
Oh.
What's this?
A pocket watch?
Considering my situation, it's the last thing in the world I
need right now.
He needs more time.
He gave you more time.
Forgive me, man.
Let's just say I'm no good at choosing presents.
This is it, Sissel.
Let me just leave you with one thing.
Don't trust other people's memories.
Look for what you seek with your own eyes.
I'll remember that.
Hmm.
Actually, people's memories are very...
Are very unreliable.
Witness testimony is not great all the time.
They're gone.
There's nothing left here.
No hope.
No cores either.
Okay.
Without any cores, I can't follow after them.
This is the end of my adventure.
I feel pretty dejected, but I guess I'd better go find Lynn.
Fake memories are a thing, a scary thing.
Yeah, I can imagine.
parents memories however are rock solid holy hell is this
ace attorney yes thanks for the super chat evan i'll follow
the path detective jowd pointed out to me the path to the
justice minister's office where lynn went to try and stop
the execution i don't remember saying this before but Stop.
Trava!
Is that what the song is called?
Oh my god.
Let's save and keep going.
1141pm.
It's so late.
Why would the Justice Minister still be there?
Now that my assignment to stop the execution has ended in
such an unsatisfactory way, I decided to go see Lin at the
Justice Minister's office.
Oh yeah, it's here.
I forgot.
Detective Jiao's story about this other murder weighs on me
heavily.
Should I tell Lynn about it?
I just don't know.
He's the attorney of the Phantom Bay.
Why are there pills on the ground?
What is she doing?
Oh, she is...
This time, Lynn isn't dead.
Wow!
But the atmosphere makes me think it might be too soon to
count my blessings just yet.
I'm glad Lynn isn't dead.
Oh man, Lynn dead counter, zero.
What in the world is she doing?
Help step ghost, I'm stuck.
Then again, do I really want to know?
What is she doing?
Sorry, I was drinking.
I almost spit at my tea!
Oh my god, I almost spit out my tea!
Uh...
Lids?
What kind of greeting is that?
I mean, I know I'm a ghost and everything, but...
Well, and how did it go?
Was Detective Jowd still alive?
Um...
He'd already been executed by the time I got there.
I did manage to save him, but...
You did?
Oh, I'm so glad.
Wait, wait a minute.
Did you say but?
It's 3.30 a.m.
Do I grab an ice cream?
Thanks.
Yeah, I think so.
I love late night ice cream.
What kind of ice cream are you gonna get though?
Rip tea.
No, I drank it.
Luckily.
I told Lynn about my adventure at the prison.
About that other murder though.
I couldn't bring myself to tell her.
At least, you know, as much as I wasn't a huge fan of the
last thing where we had to do the sneaking mission, I
appreciate the game trying out other methods of, you know,
having us use the ghost trick.
So I think that's kind of fun.
Spectre Cabanela arrested Detective Jowd?
I can't believe it!
Cinder K!
Thank you for the time you did!
Yeah, a little breakup in design is cool once in a while.
Yeah, and it wasn't so long.
She seems to have some y'all by reading preferences.
My favorite ice cream is mint cookie crumble.
Ooh!
Ah, you're making me hungry.
I feel the same way.
I can't believe that, whatever, wherever I go, somebody is
always dead.
Either you or someone else.
Sorry about that.
So who is that lying on the floor there?
Oh, you noticed him, did you?
That's just the, that's the justice minister.
The man who signed the order to carry out Detective Zhao's
execution?
Uh, he was already dead when I got here.
shouldn't you have called for help in that case I guess so
Lynn Lynn but I I'm wanted remember for murder I was hoping
we could save him without me getting caught we eh oh boy the
guy with the marriage troubles I think so oops my bad let's
talk to him let's see what he's got to say Hey, can he hear
me?
Are you awake?
He's dead, but he still seems to be unconscious.
Could you rescue him now?
While he's still unconscious?
Instead of talking to him, I bet it'll be faster to see,
just to see for yourself what really happened.
Yeah, I bet you're right.
Back we go then, to four minutes before his death.
Wet.
Rewind time.
Well done.
I have some, uh...
Uh, some dried mango.
I'm gonna eat it.
Dried mango, 1131.
Yeah, this is the guy with the marriage problems.
What's he doing, right?
Oh, he's a jumpy bunch.
Emma!
Not Emma.
Oh, excuse me.
What?
All right.
Don't do as you say.
Look, it's terrible.
Mint mango.
What's going on?
Why doesn't she answer?
Um...
Is he gonna die from heartbreak?
Oh?
Oh
my god, medicine!
That explains the pills over there.
Pills here.
Oh, water!
Oh my god, this poor guy!
This is so sad!
Fucks!
Die!
Something about a serious flashback with a somber music?
and then SpongeBob saying, Arigato, Arigato, Chew is sending
me.
Such a foolish man.
Oh, you woke up.
He's a contradiction.
Contradiction.
The more we search for the truth, the further into a dilemma
we fall.
The world of men is steeped in contradictions.
If we choose this, we can't have that.
If a man tries to have his medicine bottle and water
pitcher, too, he loses both.
Thank you.
What will we find if we put your maid cafe under UV lights
mint?
Care to explain?
I don't know.
I mean...
I'm a ghost.
If I walk around, ectoplasm kind of gets places.
It's not my fault.
It's just how it is.
It's like I'm like a snail.
I don't know.
To me, it looks like you could have had both of those things
just now.
He didn't know the...
He didn't know the truth about the world.
That's why he died.
Such a foolish man.
Or maybe I should say a pathetic man.
That's more...
That's the more fitting word.
I don't think this guy gets it yet.
That the foolish and pathetic man is him.
Is that why they call...
Is that what they call a contradiction?
By the way, what's your name?
Uh, just call me a sicker of truth.
Side-step that one, didn't he?
Uh, riparone.
This one should be kind of quick, though, right?
Like, we...
Uh...
No need to think this one too hard about this one.
All I have to do is get him and his medicine to him.
Pretty simple.
But there's one more thing that concerns me.
What was that telephone call the Justice Minister got all
about?
Oh, yes, true, true.
It was right after that, his health took an instant
downturn.
I've never seen such a foolish, pathetic, and strange man.
I think you'd better stop there.
Okay, well, uh...
His body below is so creepy.
Emma!
Could it be?
Excuse me.
Wait, who's on the other line?
Oh.
Oh!
Oh, my.
forgive me for calling so late mr.
minister oh girl you can call me as late as you want who is
this how did you get this number we have your daughter oh
what we have your daughter who is this Emily's tutor would a
tutor call you at this hour no oh say it one more time we
have your daughter.
Nani!
My daughter, is she alright?
Tell me she's alright.
Here for yourself.
Papa, help!
I'm gonna be killed!
Oh my god, they turned her into a candle!
What do you want?
What are your demands?
I believe we already made our demand known the other day.
Oh, so it was you.
And have you complied?
Has the execution...
Why do they want him dead?
Has the execution been carried out?
I didn't do it because of your demand.
I did it because that's my job.
Yes, yes, of course.
They should be contacting me any minute now with the
confirmation.
There's no need for this kidnapping.
We're very thorough.
You'd do well to remember that.
A female ghost never talk about having a snail trail.
Because it's embarrassing, okay?
I keep it real.
And of course it goes without saying, we're watching you.
If this information leaves that room, you'll never see your
daughter again.
I trust you understand that.
She can keep my daughter.
Don't tell the police.
Is that it?
All you have to do is your job.
All right.
I'll do as you say.
I'll make sure the execution is carried out tonight.
You have my word.
Uh-oh.
Wait, but if we go there...
If we go there, he's gonna die.
Oh well.
Let's go see the sexy lady.
Mama Smurf, I'm coming for you!
So it was a recording of the little girl?
We're here.
Apparently the police in this country aren't so easily
fooled.
I had no idea a word of tonight's deal had leaked.
Papahou!
I'm gonna be killed!
Luckily, I managed to arrange it so that the Justice
Minister could hear her voice.
But what's taking the good so long to arrive?
I'm starting to get concerned.
Oh my gosh.
You're so sexy when you're concerned.
Wait, time is passing.
Oh, yeah, because he's dead.
Wait, I don't think I can go back.
I can't I can't go back I can't use the phone right now Like
I said All women are like traps That and this Are hardly
related But in the past Yep, yep, yep, I could all Oops
This looks so similar To the room that was In that guy's
basement In the junkyard Uh I think we're just gonna die
here.
Uh-oh.
This woman doesn't show any signs of moving from a spot.
And I can't use the telephone line either.
Looks like I fell into a trap.
No, I knew what I was doing.
Oh, all women are like traps.
Some are sweet traps.
Others are bitter.
Don't you understand that?
Okay.
I think I'd better rethink things here.
She's like really just...
She's like a statue.
She's just really thinking right there.
She's just really...
She's just... She's just... She's just standing there.
She's really like meditating so deeply.
Oh, three.
You can hit R to reset.
Yeah, but don't you want to spend more time with her?
I
think he's dead.
It's so anticlimactic just sitting here.
You don't see anything.
Okay, a mysterious kidnapping, eh?
I'd like to find out more about it.
But right now I have another problem to solve first.
Cause as little trouble for others as possible.
Now that's a rule to live by.
Never mind that.
Let's start over.
Okay, from the beginning.
All righty.
Trick time.
Oh,
excuse me.
And then we can skip through all of this.
Baa, baa, baa, baa, baa, baa, baa, baa.
Baa, baa, baa, baa, baa.
And papa, I mean papa, help.
I'm gonna be killed.
Baa, baa, baa, baa, baa.
Baa, baa, baa, baa.
Bala la la la la la.
Okay, good.
Stay here.
No.
This is terrible.
The kidnapping, eh?
Once again, I'm not sure I know what the word means.
It's apparently the cause of the minister's attack.
I mean, it's in the name, Sissel.
They napped a kid.
I think it's in the name.
Oh, he's slow.
Such a useless man.
Huh?
A useless man caught up in a useless case.
Why doesn't he understand that?
Anyway, we only have four minutes.
I'd better do something about that medicine.
Let's see.
Wait, what is he doing now?
Who is he talking to?
I have to call my wife.
I have to see if it's true.
Maybe they called the wrong person.
This minister doesn't accept the truth easily.
Oh, that's right she didn't pick up.
He's morally bankrupt.
Is putting a kid down for a nap a crime?
It's a crime against their free will.
What if they don't want to nap?
Actually, that's kind of crazy.
Who wouldn't want to nap?
His wife won't answer for some reason.
A wife who doesn't answer her phone.
I think I know who that.
is.
A morally bankrupt man deserves a morally bankrupt wife.
Kids, apparently.
Why doesn't that man understand that?
Oh, I'm sorry I ever brought this guy along.
Me too, a little bit.
Let's examine the pills first.
So this medicine stops the minister's attacks, eh?
If I could, I'd spill them onto his desk right now, but
unfortunately I don't know.
I can't even open the cap.
What a shabby excuse for a man.
Thank you, thank you.
Agidor, a simp.
Sorry, you lost the gotcha.
But thank you!
He wears his important-looking uniform and sits working at
his stately desk.
But what does he have inside?
Nothing!
A miserable shabby excuse for a man.
you have already said quite enough oh wait
if only he could at least drink some of this water it's
about he knocks this pitcher out to the floor at the end of
this four minutes such a stupid man once water is spilled
there's no getting it back and knowing this full well why do
people still spill water pitchers so true It's so true.
I don't know.
Those who do not learn from history are doomed to repeat it?
Let's flap the flag.
He doesn't notice.
He's so sad.
Oh, why doesn't she answer?
I guess let's be the medicine bottle for now and see what we
can do when he grabs us.
Arrgh!
Um...
No...
No!
Oh!
Uh...
Wait,
I think I messed up.
Oh!
The sword!
Swing the sword!
Oh, raise the arm!
Oh my god.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, rock the basket.
Swing the sword.
No, no, no, swing it.
I think he's dead.
Swing the sword?
Okay.
Melons.
Oh, man.
melons undo the hangar he's dead he's so dead okay well now
we know that some of these things don't work okay let's see
i thought that maybe swinging it would like okay hold on do
i have to do i really have just that like that that short of
a time frame to get this it's kind of crazy Oh,
it's already happening?
Uh, okay.
Okay.
Let's see what we got here.
Raise the arm.
Thank you.
Turn the basket.
Rock the basket.
oh I did something I'm not sure what that did actually yeah
I don't think that did anything it was an honor being able
to play and verbally exchange words with you yesterday
ghosty sorry I couldn't save you from the face hugger my
cookie tray wasn't strong enough it's okay you tried undo
this oh yeah it does anything what am I supposed to do here
okay next time let's just uh next time let's stick around
with him maybe what
the curtain do I don't know I can't even reach it hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm maybe let's see what if there's anything we can
do with the water okay
it starts to die starts to This one was tough for me, but I
really liked it.
Okay, hold on.
Is there anything?
There's a flag.
We can also flab.
Does it do anything?
Oh!
Wait.
Did that spook him?
Actually, I'm not sure.
Oh, yeah.
There's like...
Oh.
Can't use the phones.
I...
Okay, okay.
Even though we knocked it off the thing.
Let's find another path.
Sorry.
There we go.
I thought we could stabilize it or something.
No.
Okay.
Okay, I think we have to...
Oh, the flag now!
You guys are so smart.
The flag to stabilize it.
to be like and make it make it go okay so i was i was on the
right path with the flag i think okay okay okay i have
another mango yeah hello but
now you not even work reach for it there it is
Everything else was a red herring.
Well, I was thinking initially, I was like...
Somehow getting the mango...
On the sword and then...
Is golfing it over?
Putting it over?
But...
When I couldn't do that...
And there wasn't anything else over there that would really
let me do...
I was confused.
There, that should help.
At least he's now had some water.
Okay, all good.
He's still breathing, apparently.
But he looks far from recovered, unfortunately.
Such a wishy-washy man.
He can't make up his mind whether to live or die.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Hmm.
At least now I bought some time to get his medicine to him.
How do we get over there, actually?
Wait, now how do I get over there?
Oh.
Flap.
No.
Wait, how do I get over there?
The minister's fate has changed, but the situation still
seems the same.
I can't move anywhere now.
Did I miss something?
I think I saw a path.
Just for a second while the minister was drinking the water.
A path while he was drinking the water.
from the beginning.
Oh, come on, Sis-O!
Wait, while he was drinking the water?
Wait, no, but I have to do from the beginning, right?
I can't do it.
Wait.
Hold on.
What's the fate change?
Is it while he... When he grabs the water, or...
No.
Okay.
From the beginning!
I...
Maybe it has something to do with the papers.
Maybe like a paper flew and I didn't realize it.
Yeah, because that's the only other thing we can highlight.
Or the documents.
Okay, let's hang out in the flag for now.
It's a split second, but it's there.
I missed it.
Okay, I'm ready.
I'm ready to flap.
Reach for it!
Oh, that was too early.
Oh, come on!
No!
This guy is too clumsy.
It's stinking butterfingers over here.
What is wrong with you?
You don't want...
Maybe he's right.
Maybe his ghost self is right.
Wishing-washy man.
Do you want to live or do you want to die?
Oh.
along.
Okay, I'm ready to flap.
Okay.
Once it's spinning around.
Flap!
There we go.
Oh!
Okay, now let's go to the papers.
Ah.
Uh...
It was the pitcher.
Oh, I thought when he went crazy, I thought maybe a piece of
paper flew off.
I gotta go to the pitcher.
I thought I missed a piece of paper flying in the wind.
Why people are being like, why papers?
I said this from the very beginning, I was like, okay, once
he lifts once he lifts the the water i'm gonna go to the
papers and see if i if i you're just like why did you do
that you stupid ghost when i said it from the beginning that
that's what i was going to do
i why did you do the thing that you said that you were going
to try okay reach for the water
flop okay picture time
Okay, spin harder.
And then it will probably blow the paper.
There, that should help.
Blah, blah, blah.
Okay.
Wait, if I spin harder, how am I going to...
We read all of this.
How am I going to...
There we go.
Oh, how nice.
All right, now we're here.
Grab the medicine.
Time for the next step.
How about this medicine bottle?
The minister is going to make a full recovery.
have to deliver this thing to him how is a ghost with no
hands or feet hey my hands are like this because I'm a ghost
supposed to do that I guess I'll just have to use my head
instead let's see let's raise this raise the roof whoop
whoop lower oh okay I was gonna say okay I was going to oh
wait I can reach this now.
Never mind.
Close the curtain.
Time is passing.
Okay.
Raise the roof.
Spin.
I'm not quite sure what to do.
Oh.
Wrong way.
Maybe.
Roll.
Oh.
good undo okay i'm just i'm just i'm just fumbling around
right now you guys hold on i'm fumbling around a little bit
let me see what i can do let me see what's possible um rock
the boat melon
uh-huh okay okay okay okay so i I roll the globe.
No.
Yes?
Wait.
Uh.
Yeah, I roll the globe.
And then I hit it with the melon.
Would it be the globe or would it be the...
Well, actually, it could be either the vase or the globe.
Not quite sure.
I think I need to restart, though.
because I don't have a thing to roll.
I don't have...
But I need the globe to drop to knock down the vase.
I don't think it's supposed to be a catapult.
I think it's supposed to be...
Like, hold on.
The globe drops from here and rolls onto here down and then
when it gets to this side we use the melon to to wait I'm
not so sure actually swing take
all the time you need I don't I don't have time let's see
what they say that was so close if the swing just had a
little more reach to it I think it'd be I think I'd better
look for something else Oh,
uh-oh.
Okay, I'm going to try spinning the globe next time and
seeing if that works.
Goodbye, mister.
From the fate change.
Okay, okay, okay.
Spin harder.
All right, here we go.
Alrighty, I'm going ghost.
No.
I think this is the order, the order that I did before, I
think is correct?
Because otherwise, the painting will be facing slanted this
way.
And that won't help me with...
That won't help, it'll just Let's fly over the medicine.
It'll fly over the medicine, right?
So let's close this.
Raise the roof.
Salute.
Turn around.
No, wait.
I didn't turn before.
Boss.
Spin?
Let's see what happens here.
Ah!
Oh!
But this can knock this over.
This one can get knocked over.
This one right here.
Wait.
Was it this way?
Hold on.
Oh.
Wait.
That's exactly what I said I didn't want to happen.
Read the thought bubbles for hints.
I don't, I'm purposefully not reading it because I do not
want to hint.
I want to figure it out.
I don't want to hint.
I'm trying to figure it out myself.
Though I already feel that I messed up.
Though I feel that I have all...
I already made a grave mistake.
Ah.
Globe.
Woo!
Okay, okay, wait, wait, wait, wait.
So, I maybe...
Wait.
Well, like I said, if I do this...
If I... if I...
Wait, if I do this...
But then I...
Stop posting!
the answers.
Stop posting the answers I'm not reading.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
I said no hints, I said no hints.
Oh my god, time limit.
Okay.
Shut up, Cecil.
I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know.
Let's see.
so
many moving parts honestly a great puzzle to think through
yeah it is fun it's interesting for sure okay i feel like
i'm just gonna have to try it and if it's not the correct
way i do it the opposite way i guess i suppose
Wait, wait, wait.
No, we want the...
Yeah, no.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Trial and error.
Exactly, exactly.
Because sometimes something might not go as you predict it
will.
And I'm just kind of confused over on this end.
If I do this, what do I knock over?
You know what I mean?
Like, if I knock this down...
Okay, if I knock this down...
and create the if I create the the little angle like this
like before I feel like the and then if I drop this if I
drop the top thing and put the globe here and drop this down
and catapult it but it'll just fly into the air I feel I
feel like the vase will just fly into the air.
Just try it.
Okay.
You're right.
Might as well just try something.
Phew!
Oh, wait.
If I...
Oh, no.
I need to... I need to turn it.
And then I need to rock it.
Rock it.
baby oh okay and then if i go here and do these it's called
thinking out loud i'm an out loud thinker why did the
thought bubble come up it's scaring me make me feel like i
did it wrong okay and now we go to here here and uh to there
and we knock you down phew time is passing And then we...
When I turned it around, it still knocked over the base,
isn't it?
I think so.
Spin!
Oh!
What?
Roll?
Oh!
Wait, can I roll that?
No, I can't roll that.
Oh, wait, am I catapulting?
Am I catapulting?
Wait, hold on.
I need more time!
Don't rush me game!
Wait, so if I put this in the middle, this vase, and roll
this here, and then that knocks down.
This catapults the globe.
Okay, let's try that.
After this, After the fate change!
After the fate change!
Oh, spin harder.
Spin harder.
Okay.
Beep, peep, boep, boep, boep, boep, boep, boop.
So we go.
And then that also makes it so that falls on, the melon
falls...
Oh wait, no.
We have to have this fall down instead of the melon oh wait
I want to go up I want to go up real quick we undo this guy
a little undo a little screws loose wait yeah no okay okay
this
way spin it went the wrong way I
remember getting tricked by that too yeah it's a little it
feels like a little like not misleading I think is the wrong
word but you kind of like your brain thinks like oh if it's
facing the direction of the base then it will go to the
direction of the base you know what i mean
okay if it didn't take so much to get there it wouldn't have
been an issue i wish i could turn off the intensity of the
ghost trick effect you know that's the only thing that makes
me you know what i will turn this while we're here
I will turn that.
Oh, I unlocked a bunch of stuff.
I don't know why.
I just unlocked it now.
But okay.
Time is passing.
I'm working on it.
Gosh, don't rush me.
Okay.
Now we turn it.
And then we spin it.
Pshah.
Okay.
Then we drop it.
like it's hot.
No time is passing.
Wait.
Then we drop the globe.
Okay, sorry.
Wait, we drop the globe and then we drop the other vase,
right?
Spin it, tap it, bonk it, twirl it.
Think so, yeah?
Right.
And then we, yeah.
And then we will go back and we would launch the globe.
I sure hope this works.
Oh wait, not turn.
Rock.
Yippee!
Mumbai medicine!
Oh my god.
Whoa, I don't think that's gonna help you, mister.
I don't think that's gonna help you.
Help you!
The minister finally took his medicine.
Okay, it took me a minute to get that, but we finally got
there.
Yippee.
I think maybe he took too much medicine.
Such a greedy man.
He's supposed to take two capsules with water.
Why doesn't he know that?
Aw, cut the guy some slack.
There?
Oh, there.
See?
He took his meds.
Everyone be like him.
Two.
Too much medicine challenge.
We saw all of them go into his mouth.
Well, we don't know if he'd swallowed all of them.
That was a lot of work.
Yeah, it was.
You're telling me.
Well, hopefully this taught him a lesson.
Huh?
He greatly underestimated his dependence on his medicine.
I hope he learned something from this experience.
First, know yourself.
That is the key to everything.
I think you need to listen to your own advice, buddy.
Anyway, let's go back to the world of the present.
Take your meds.
And so the justice minister is now back to life.
But the furrows on his brow are even deeper now.
Oh, Lynn!
And apparently our lady detective is the present cause of
those furrows.
Look, detective, he was sentenced after a fair trial, and
the man himself wants to be executed.
But there was no evidence!
All they had was his own confession!
But it was no ordinary confession.
It was the confession of an esteemed detective.
Oh, stay back!
I told you I don't want anybody coming near me.
Okay, you're sensitive.
Mr. Minister, please listen to me!
I might be able to gather new evidence in that case tonight!
What?
So please, please just give me a little more time!
I just got a call from the prison.
Your death row convict apparently just escaped.
Unfortunately, after all this time, it seems he now wants to
dodge his punishment.
but when he is apprehended his sentence will be carried well
he got apprehended like really fast so tonight no but when
the sentence was handed down you were against enforcing the
death penalty so why did you sign the order all of the
sudden hmm well I I was simply performing my duty as justice
minister.
That's all there is to it.
Doubling back about the faulty memories, does anybody else
remember a British Lin or am I getting Mandela effect?
Hmm, that's so mysterious.
I think you're getting Mandela effect.
Right, everybody?
You're crazy.
She was never British.
Okay.
let's hit her in the head.
Wham!
Oh, oh wait, that actually worked.
Sissel, there you are.
Sounds like the minister is being very stubborn.
That's right.
Hey, yes.
Oh, sorry.
Maybe we shouldn't have saved him after all.
Damn.
Let him... The minister has to be, or has to have the
execution it out tonight and he has a very good reason for
it a good reason i told lynn about what i learned about the
kidnapping kidnapping oh sorry they kidnapped the justice
minister's daughter apparently oh my goodness Hmm.
Mint napping.
No, no, no.
But still.
That's still no reason to hurry forward with the execution.
Why don't you go ahead and say that to the justice minister
then?
Oh.
Your daughter's life is not worth more than this man.
The poor man.
I hate to do that to him.
Oh, by the way.
Do you think you could carry me?
Sure.
Not very handy, is it not?
Having no legs.
Oh my gosh.
She's got the whole world.
In her hand.
She's got the whole...
Wait, what was...
What is that black dot on the...
On the globe?
Oh, you can't get any closer?
This sword and globe is heavy and I'm it oh it's the North
Pole oh I thought it was a bug and I'm in here too don't
forget I guess that means a single soul is heavier than the
whole world maybe I'll use this thing to persuade the
minister to change his mind good luck with that dang all
right let's see what he's saying what are you going to do
with that globe crack me in the head with it Oh, this?
Pay no attention to this.
Kind of hard not to pay attention to it.
I know she looks like she's actually going to attack him.
By the way, and please pardon me if this is a silly
question.
Were you talking to someone just now?
But of course not, right?
I mean, there's no such thing as ghosts, right?
Are you talking about me?
phantom.
No, there's no such thing.
This is a dream.
It's nothing but a dream.
Don't you remember me?
My dream is talking to me!
So now I'm a dream, right?
Oh gosh, I'm starting to want to play Minecraft.
Mr. Minister?
We know.
We know about your daughter.
She was kidnapped, wasn't she?
And if the execution doesn't take place tonight, you won't
see her again.
Yes!
Oh, oh, oh, God!
Oh, your medicine!
He took the whole bottle, though.
Uh-oh.
I think we just committed a murder.
What am I going to do?
The death row prisoner.
has escaped.
If he hasn't executed tonight, my daughter, my Ameli!
But what if that execution isn't the right thing to do?
Come on, Lin.
If you keep pressing him like that, he's gonna die again.
What can I do then?
Oh, everybody's at a loss.
Time for me to trick time.
We have to do something about that kidnapping.
Until we do that, it'll be impossible to get the minister on
our That's the way I see it.
Gather info.
Sorry.
Let's see what he has to say.
We meet again, Mr. Minster.
What?
I've never seen you before.
In any case, I'm a very busy man.
If you're a dream, please don't bother me when I'm awake.
Uh, I'm not a dream.
She's making me yawn.
I'm sorry.
I'm starting to get so sleepy.
Looks like it's just a waste of time trying to talk to this
guy.
I think you're right.
Stubborn Justice Minister.
Please stop speaking ill of me inside my own head.
The voices.
The voices hate me.
Alright.
Should we go to Sexy Lady's house?
Here we go.
I really should pay the kidnappers hide out a visit.
After all, if we want the Justice Minister to come around...
We have to solve this problem first.
I feel like I'm slowly moving away from my own mystery.
But I'm not the kind of guy who can abandon a little lady
and a little lady in trouble.
So I guess I'm in this for a little while longer.
Oh, that was it.
1141 to 1210 AM Challenge.
Should I call it here?
Hmm.
I'm wondering if I should call it here.
How many?
We got through what?
Three chapters?
Hold on.
Let me see where we're at.
A little lighty.
10.
Oh, we're on chapter 11.
What?
11 out of 18?
Your call, boss.
I think maybe the next time we play, I'll endurance it into
the end.
So.
doing next chapter would make for a spice at your end oh is
it is it long though is it super long
it will be long yeah stopping here is okay
yeah I think maybe I'll just it's a little long it's not
really as long as as long as your puzzle solving skills
thanks I think sheesh Why am I getting insulted?
Like this.
One of the puzzles coming up stumps a lot of people more
than the stealth one.
Oh, really?
Okay.
Hmm.
Okay, maybe I'll just, uh...
Oh, since I can't stop the eye.
I can endurance it next time we play and we can go to the
end.
So...
Oh gosh, that's a lot of chapters though.
That's probably going to be like a 10 hour stream.
I guess that's an endurance, I believe.
I'm going to have to endure too.
I really thought we would get through more today.
It is only 1030.
Hmm, best mom ever.
Great job cooking on those puzzles.
Looking forward to seeing how this ends.
say tomorrow thank you thank you thank you i would book two
more streams yeah maybe we'll do two streams then okay
so one next week and then one more the week after and then
it will be good i'll finish it up before i go to japan
actually that works because i wasn't planning on starting a
new longer series until i get back from japan so once i'm
back from japan we can start something new Cool.
Two streams with about four chapters each seems chill.
I agree, I agree.
Cool, cool, cool.
Thanks, guys, for joining again today.
Thank you.
It's a little bit less of a cliffhanger, but there's still
so much mystery going on.
Why couldn't he just say who we were, man?
Why is he keeping us in such a mystery?
Also, I want to make sure I'm well rested for Ayami Sensei
tomorrow.
um there's a little bit i don't want to say an announcement
but something kind of cool um in tomorrow's stream so um i
think uh i think it would be fun and if you don't know ayami
sensei she's so silly and fun i think um i think uh i think
you it will be a fun stream yes yes yes so Ayami is so cute.
I know.
I love Ayami Sensei so much.
So, yeah.
The push push mama.
Push, push, push.
And Ayami is... Ayami, does she speak English?
She does, actually.
Ayami speaks such good English.
I'm gonna try and see how much English she'll speak
tomorrow.
But she is coming to the United States for a convention.
weekend and um so she's gonna ask me some questions about
the us and she also wanted to kind of get to know me a
little bit more um since this is our first ever collab
together um and but she was like so nervous she was so
worried about how she was like i wonder if anybody is going
to come see me at that convention she's gonna be at anime
central this weekend um she was like i wonder if anybody's
going to come see me and then i checked yesterday for her
autographs i was like i wonder how like, you know, how our
autographs are doing.
And they were all sold out!
And I was like, or booked up, I guess.
I don't think they were, I think they were free.
But they were all like gone.
And I was like, oh, I sent it to her.
And I was like, Ayami Sensei!
You were so worried for nothing.
So, hmm.
Everybody be extra nice to Ayami Sensei.
Yeah.
They were out within the hour?
Oh my gosh, really?
Whoa.
Reminds me of a certain someone who always underestimates
herself.
I wonder who that could be.
You know a lot of people.
But yeah, so we're going to talk about her coming to the U
.S.
and what she'll be doing at the convention and some other
stuff.
Talking about me a little bit.
Well, maybe more than a little bit.
She was like so interested.
She was like, I want to know everything about Mint.
And so I was like, Okay.
So yeah.
Hmm.
She's the only B2 Brite Ace in this year.
Yeah, actually you're right.
Oh my gosh.
But, um, exciting.
She wants your three sizes.
That's not even a joke.
But yeah, I'm really, really excited.
I hope then, um, next time we collab, maybe it could be like
a game or something.
so I'll see you guys tomorrow then for Ayami and that's
Wednesday for English karaoke I have no planned set list so
if you have any songs that you maybe are like hey Mito I
recommend this song you can always leave it in the comments
or you can leave it in the live tag on Twitter.
So I will look through it.
I will read it.
And a rock!
Welcome to membership!
Thank you!
Anything weird, Al.
Okay.
Goodbye, virtual YouTuber made mint.
Thank you.
Goodbye, Jordan.
Halo theme.
Limp biscuit.
Tenacious D.
Oh, I know one tenacious D.
song um i don't remember what it's called i think it's the
one that like everybody knows don't but stop stop
recommending stuff now stop it's not yet not yet yeah
tribute tribute was gifted a membership but now i'm
recurring oh my gosh thank you i really appreciate it i
appreciate it so much oh yeah stop don't recommend songs now
recommend them later So I recommend them when I have them on
paper or on pixels so that I can remember.
Write them down at least.
Enjoy your trip to Alcatraz.
If I can go, but beware, the island is the most haunted
location in California and possibly the country.
Cell Block D in particular is the most haunted place on the
island.
The island has eons of bad mojo.
It's okay, I'm a ghost too.
And if any ghost tries to mess with me, I'll just punch
them.
Which one is cuter for you, Minty?
Imperial Storm Troopers, original trilogy.
Or first order Storm Troopers, sequel trilogy.
Also, whose armor is cooling your opinion?
Captain Rex or Commander Wolf?
Okay, hold on.
I'm going to have to look up all of these real quick.
This isn't the best super chat in the world.
This is just a tribute.
Okay, original...
Wait.
First Order Storm Trooper.
What's the difference between them and the original?
Oh, wait, I see.
Oh, I see it.
Wait, they look the same to me.
Am I dumb?
Um, cooler.
Captain Rex.
Star Wars.
Oh, I like his.
Or Commander Wolf.
Oh.
I think Captain Rex's is cooler.
Commander Wolf for sure.
Wait, Wolf is epic.
Wait, am I looking at the wrong pictures?
Commander Wolf.
Hold on.
Oh, oh, wait.
Wait, yes, Commander Wolf, you're right.
I was looking at the wrong thing.
Yeah, Commander Wolf looks cooler, I think.
Oh, sorry, everyone said base.
I don't know.
Rex is the best.
And they both look really nice.
I like the blue.
How could my Oshi betray me?
Okay, guys, I'm going to go sleep now.
thank you guys again for watching and hanging out with me
today and we'll do finish this up in two more streams oh my
gosh do you guys want to see the coolest thing that I've
seen today though I'm still trying to decide if I want to if
I should pre-order this it's so awesome thanks for the fun
stream can't wait for the next part thank you wait oh I
can't show you wait oh no it's on the other screen and it's
hidden I have I'm currently on my I'm on my other my other I
can't get to it.
Okay, never mind.
Okay, I'm gonna go now.
Otsuminto!
It wasn't a Metal Gear thing.
Just tell us what it is?
Okay, I saw it on Ami Ami earlier.
It's a...
It's a Rubik's Cube, but it transforms into a mech.
But it's a real Rubik's...
Well, I don't know if it's a real Rubik's Cube.
Rubik's Cube.
But it can turn into a Rubik's Cube.
Like, like, uh, like the Cube version.
And then you can also turn it into a mech.
It's so awesome.
I want it.
What's the name?
Chogokin Rubik's Cube.
Chogokin.
Rubik's Cube.
It's so cool.
I was looking at it.
All right.
I think I was, yeah.
Anyway.
Ignoring what I just saw.
What was I saying?
I'd be a hypocrite if I didn't support you buying a
transforming toy.
Nah, I was considering it.
I was just, but I thought it was so cool, but I don't know
if I'll get it.
it it's kind of expensive so i was like um and i already
have some other figures i have to wait for so um you know
anyway okay awesome everybody thank you for hanging out see
you guys tomorrow bye bye have a good night have a good
night get lots of rest get lots of rest drink some water
stay Bye bye!
Bye bye!
It's so cool!
Look at him!
He's just a guy!
He's just so...
When he transforms into a Rubik's Cube!
I think if I knew how to solve a Rubik's Cube, I would
definitely get rid of him.
If I was like a huge Rubik's Cube fan.
But just the whole thing is such a fun concept.
right hmm mecha rubix ultimate form that's just a guy yeah
it's so cool right got tea pose it looks kind of when he
when he's not rubix he looks kind of like a tetris man this
looks like the tea like a tea block okay bye bye